Chapter 1 - Lin Ming

Within the Sky Fortune City, the capital of Sky Fortune Kingdom, the Seven Profound Martial House stands before the Great Mountain Zhou. Seven Profound Martial House, it is the martial house set up by the Seven Profound Valley, a martial arts clan with over six hundred years of heritage. It is also the only martial house set up by them in the Sky Fortune Kingdom.

As one of the biggest martial house, Seven Profound Martial House possesses a great number of legacy martial skills and martial masters as its tutors. It was only natural that it would become the holy land of the many young aspiring martial artists. Correspondingly, the entrance qualifications for new recruits in Seven Profound Martial House were set at a high threshold. It would not be an exaggeration to say that only one in a million would be able to qualify.

Under the scorching heat of summer, a young boy stood within a forest of the Great Mountain Zhou. Both his fists were wrapped up with strips of cloth as he stood bare chested before a rough looking big tree. He threw punch after punch, striking heavily against the tree trunk.

“Peng!”

“Peng!”

Heavy sounds echoed out around the forest. The layer of bark on the big tree that were struck had sunk downwards noticeably, exposing its greyish wooden texture. On its surface, traces of blood could be seen.

This young boy’s name is Lin Ming. He possesses a Grade Three Martial Talent.

In Sky Fortune Kingdom, half of its citizens have no martial talent to speak of and are unsuitable towards the path of martial arts. As for the other half, at least eighty per cent of them have a Grade One Martial Talent. Even if these people were to practice martial arts, they would not be able to reach anywhere. One in ten of the remaining people have a ninety per cent chance of having Grade Two Martial Talent. If these people were to be diligent in their practice of martial arts, they have a chance to accomplish something in life. However, becoming a master of the martial arts would be near hopeless for them.

Lin Ming’s Grade Three Martial Talent could be considered as a high-class existence. If one were to be boastful, one could claim that he is the cream of the crop. However, even with his martial talent, it would still be difficult for him to enter the Seven Profound Martial House!

Lin Ming was well aware of this. Together with his female childhood friend, the beautiful Lan Yunyue who also has a Grade Three Martial Talent, they had agreed to take the entrance assessment for the Sky Fortune Martial House even though it is nowhere near as good as the Seven Profound Martial House.

The Sky Fortune Martial House is part of Sky Fortune Kingdom. Since the day of its inception, it has only eighty years’ worth of martial skills, legacy and foundation, a limited number indeed. Legacy martial skills are something of great importance to martial artists. Without a good set of martial skills, the goal of completing the final Physical Training Stage, the Pulse Condensing Stage or higher would be near impossible.

The Pulse Condensing Stage is a realm that most martial artists vied for. It is also the first turning point for cultivators of the martial way. Once the Pulse Condensing Stage is successfully attained, a martial artist’s lifespan would be greatly increased. Additionally, they would also be granted the title of nobility, allowing them to live a life of prosperity, bringing a blessing to their descendants.

It is in this Pulse Condensing Stage training that the Sky Fortune Martial House falls greatly behind the Seven Profound Martial House.

Lin Ming’s heart pulsed for the sake of the martial way. It was only natural that he too, desired to enter the Seven Profound Martial House. If his talent was insufficient, then he could only rely on his own diligence and perseverance to impress the examiners. However, the prospect of him entering was very low. Moreover, once he failed, he would have to waste half a year’s time to wait for another opportunity. For martial artists, this amount of time is highly precious.

Placing all this into consideration, in addition to the fact that he had promised Lan Yunyue, Lin Ming decided instead to enter the Sky Fortune Martial House.

Lin Ming and Lan Yunyue had trained and played together for many years. Even though the both of them were still young and the topic of marriage never came up, those emotions have already begun budding. Lin Ming’s parents on the other hand, had shown their approval and love towards Lan Yunyue. They would always invite Lan Yunyue to their house for dinner.

A mutual feeling of goodwill existed between Lin Ming and Lan Yunyue, leaving only a thin piece of paper between the two. Once they grow slightly older, this piece of paper would certainly be torn apart.

Lin Ming viewed the agreement between them both seriously. He had determined to charge towards the Pulse Condensing Stage even if he could only train within the Sky Fortune Martial House!

However, on the day that Sky Fortune Martial House held its entrance assessment, Lan Yunyue failed to show up.

At first, Lin Ming had assumed that Lan Yunyue was unable to arrive due to some matters. It was only later that he learnt of Lan Yunyue entering the Seven Profound Martial House. Additionally, the one who had ensured her success in becoming a disciple of Seven Profound Martial House was Zhu Yan, the genius Young Master of Green Mulberry City’s number one family.

Although Lin Ming was only fifteen years old, he had accompanied his parents to do battle on the outside before. Thus, he has a greater level of maturity compared to others. He understood the meaning behind Zhu Yan’s act of ensuring that the Seven Profound Martial House accepted Lan Yunyue.

For a great family such as the Zhu Family, their prerequisite in selecting future wives lied not in terms of appearances, but rather their martial talent. A highly talented wife would have a higher chance of giving birth to a martial genius. Although Lan Yunyue’s family is only average, her Grade Three Martial Talent is very good considering her gender. In addition, Lan Yunyue herself is a beauty with an outstanding temperament. It was only natural that Zhu Yan would fall for her.

For Lan Yunyue, the difference between the Sky Fortune Martial House and Seven Profound Martial House is simply too great. The opportunities, honour, glory, and potential accomplishments that both could able to provide are simply incomparable. This is especially true regarding the extension of life that could be gained after one successfully reaches the Pulse Condensing Stage. Such a kind of temptation is simply irresistible for girls.

Faced with such appealing prospects, most females would have chosen to go with Zhu Yan as well. After all, Zhu Yan himself possesses handsome features; his family background and future are both far better compared to Lin Ming’s.

Although he was able to understand, to say that this matter did not greatly affect Lin Ming would be a lie. He shut himself within his room for three days. After that, he walked out and proceeded to eat, sleep and train. Moreover, the intensity of his training had become much higher than before.

Before Lan Yunyue had left him, Lin Ming had already made the decision to break through into the Pulse Condensing Stage and pursue an even higher realm of martial cultivation. The current Lin Ming was no different. If he still had any doubts before, then Lan Yunyue’s act of leaving him had hardened his resolve towards the Martial Way.

He made the decision to enter the entrance assessment for the Seven Profound Martial House, no matter how difficult the process may be.

“Peng!” “Peng!” The heavy sounds of fists striking against the tree trunk echoed continuously throughout the forest. The name of this tree is Iron Tree. Not only does it possess an extremely tough layer of bark, it also has strong regenerative properties. Many beginners of the martial way would choose this Iron Tree to train themselves.

After throwing out who knew how many punches, Lin Ming finally exhausted himself. Leaning upon a tree trunk, he sat down on a piece of rock and removed some herbs from a backpack placed on the ground. He smeared them onto the surface of his fists and kneaded. For those who pursue martial arts, frequent usage of body treatment herbs is necessary. Not doing so would cause internal injuries to build up. Once these internal injuries accumulate, there is a possibility of becoming a cripple or even death.

This herb is called Iron Thread Grass. It was given this name because the green juice produced from squeezing Iron Thread Grass could help heal wounds but would cause a terribly painful sensation akin to having iron threads brushing upon the wounds.

Lin Ming gritted his teeth as he endured the pain. He retrieved a white cloth from within the backpack and rolled it around his fists, bandaging it.

Truth be told, there were many other herbs that are more effective compared to the Iron Thread Grass. These herbs also has a milder side effect, but comes at a much higher price. Lin Ming’s circumstances made it impossible for him to afford such herbs.

Lin Ming’s parents run a restaurant within Green Mulberry City. However, this restaurant does not belong to them. It actually belonged to the Lin Family^1 of Green Mulberry City.

Although Lin Ming’s surname is also Lin, his family line had been separated from the Lin Family by several generations. The Lin Family placed some off their less important assets into the hands of their distant relatives for management. Lin Ming’s parents livelihood were dependent on their management of this restaurant. Every year they would be given a fixed amount of income and some commission. This money was naturally enough for them to subsist on, however, it would be a stretch to use it to fund Lin Ming’s pursuit of martial arts.

Lin Ming’s parents had originally wanted Lin Ming to continue the family business and become a treasurer for the restaurant. However, seeing Lin Ming’s ardent devotion towards the martial way, they instead chose to take out all their savings for Lin Ming to purchase healing herbs.

Since then, Lin Ming’s family savings had decreased bit by bit. But Lin Ming on the other hand had remained at the first stage of Physical Training.

The Physical Training Stage is the first realm for those who pursue the martial way. It involves the primal tempering of their bodies and is separated into six stages. The first stage is Strength Training, second is Flesh Training, third is Viscera Training, fourth is Altering Muscle, fifth is Bone Forging and sixth is Pulse Condensing. After that, one would be able to step into the Primal Assemblage Stage.

After applying the Iron Thread Grass juice onto his wounds, Lin Ming rested for half a long hour (1 hour) to allow his wounds to absorb the medicinal properties of the herb. He then straightened himself and was about to continue training his fists when a fat youngster walked into view. This fat youngster was carrying a long sword with him. Seeing Lin Ming, he grinned and spoke. “Brother Lin, today is the registration day for the entrance assessment of the Seven Profound Martial House. Could it be that you have forgotten about it? Why are you still practicing your fists here?”

This youngster’s name is Lin Xiaodong, he is slightly younger than Lin Ming. Growing up together, the two of them have a very strong bond of brotherhood.

Lin Xiaodong is a direct descendant of the Lin Family. However, even for direct descendants, there exists a form of ranking. As it happens, Lin Xiaodong is part of the lowest ranked ones. As for Lin Xiaodong’s parents, they too were engaged in business and have a close relationship with Lin Ming’s parents.

After seeing Lin Xiaodong, Lin Ming turned his attention back to the tree trunk and said. “The beginning part of the registration will have too many people. The queue would take up to one or two long hours. Going there now would be a waste of time.”

“Damn it, you won’t even let go of this small amount of time. Do you really have to go that far?” Lin Xiaodong spoke out in exaggeration and walked up to the tree trunk. Observing the indentations caused by the fists and the traces of blood, he turned to see Lin Ming’s bandaged fists. He then let out a sigh of disappointment. “You really are crazy, to be able to damage Iron Wood to such an extent. However, with your current training methods, Iron Thread Grass alone won’t be enough. If you keep this up, your hands would become crippled!”

Lin Ming did not say anything. The martial way is a constant struggle against Heaven. Considering his Grade Three Martial Talent, attaining the Sixth Stage of Pulse Condensation was incredibly hard. If he does not give it his all while he was still young, then he would have no hope at achieving his goal. Once he had given his all, there would certainly be the possibility of him becoming a cripple due to the accumulation of internal injuries. However, there was also the possibility of him attaining success before that happens. And once he could successfully enter the Pulse Condensation Stage, he could attain true primal tempering of the body and the internal injuries would vanish.

For Lin Ming, this was a battle with his back against the raging river

This was also a gamble with his life on the line.

Lin Xiaodong gave a sigh and pulled out a bundle from his bosom. He unfurled the bundle layer by layer and said. “Brother Ming, take this.”

Lin Ming turned around and was shocked to find a bloody crimson coloured ginseng lying upon the cloth bundle. Judging from its appearance, this strain of blood ginseng is at least a hundred years old. It is a high-grade medicine used for mending wounds and nourishing blood. A thin slice is enough for each use. In addition, the powerful healing properties of this blood ginseng are very gentle. This blood ginseng should be worth at least a hundred and fifty gold liangs, the equivalent of Lin Ming’s family’s annual income.

Lin Ming’s body paused, and he shook his head. “I cannot accept this Blood Ginseng.”

Even though they are close brothers, this Blood Ginseng is simply too expensive. Lin Xiaodong’s position within the Lin Family is very low. Even though his family situation is much better when compared to Lin Ming’s it would still be far from comfortable if their income were used to supplement Lin Xiaodong’s martial training.

Lin Xiaodong forcibly pushed the Blood Ginseng onto Lin Ming and said. “I bought this Blood Ginseng for you. You know how I train, I fish every three days and dry the fishing nets every two days

My body’s injuries are no more than a fart’s worth. Using this would be a waste. If you refuse then I would have bought this for nothing. I do not have much ambitions in life. I just want to continue holding on to my position as a direct descendant of the Lin Family. As long as I do not end up losing this position and my next generation could also successfully maintain their place in the Lin Family, that is enough for me.”

Lin Ming stayed silent for a moment before keeping the Blood Ginseng. He then spoke out. “Very well, I will accept this Blood Ginseng. For the sake of this ginseng, I must break through to the Pulse Condensation Stage.”

“Haha, now that is more like it. Not only should you break through into the Pulse Condensation Stage, you must also turn that son of a bitch, Zhu Yan upside down. That bastard has been an eyesore for a long time!”

Zhu Yan huh… Lin Ming sighed lightly. Zhu Yan had already been admitted into the Seven Profound Martial House. In addition, Zhu Yan is currently one of the high ranked disciples within the inner Heavenly Abode, his strength having reached the pinnacle of the Third Stage of Physical Training. Even so, Lin Ming had set defeating Zhu Yan as his objective. This decision was not due to Lan Yunyue but rather due to his pursuit of the martial way. This path required him breaking through one threshold after another; conquering one mountain after another. As for Zhu Yan, he has the honourable spot of being the number one to be conquered.

At the foot of the Great Mountain Zhou lied a stretch of buildings extending up to twenty li (10km) in length. This is the area of operations for the Seven Profound Martial House and the Sky Fortune Martial House and today is the day of registration for those who wishes to take the Seven Profound Martial House’s entrance assessment. A crowd was gathered on the field before the Seven Profound Martial House.

Even though Lin Ming and Lin Xiaodong had deliberately chosen to arrive late, they came to realize that they had underestimated the number of applicants. The applicants were all lined up in three lines, with each line extending up to several meters in length. Judging by the current queue, half a long hour (1 hour) would be needed before registration could be completed.

“We will have to wait,” Lin Xiaodong gave a sigh and stood helplessly in line.

“En,” Lin Ming nodded his head.

“Hey, there are very few people there,” Lin Xiaodong pointed towards a small gate nearby. There were only a few people there. Furthermore, the ground was also paved with red carpet.

“That place is reserved for nobles…” Lin Ming noticed the writings on the sign.

Since the Seven Profound Martial House was built upon the grounds, buildings and resources of Sky Fortune Kingdom, it was only natural for them to give some face to the elite classes of the kingdom. In fact, many of the martial house’s affairs would be handed over to the elites to manage. One such example would be today’s registration for entrance assessment.

“Damn it,” Lin Xiaodong muttered in discontent. Nobility was something that only the Imperial Family could grant and could be inherited. Even though the Lin Family is a wealthy family, it is not a noble family.

Lin Xiaodong was cursing off at the nobles while consoling himself when the doors of the gate opened. Two young males strode out from the gate; one of them was wearing blue clothes with a long sword attached to his waist. His hair was tied up into a gold coloured headgear and had a handsome appearance.

Seeing the appearance of this man caused Lin Ming to frown. This was none other than Zhu Yan.

The Zhu Family’s daughter had married into the Imperial Family and had become the Eldest Prince’s favoured concubine. With the Eldest Prince’s position in the royal family, the Zhu Family soared to become the number one family within Green Mulberry City. Moreover, they were also granted the rank of nobility, thus allowing Zhu Yan to ensure Lan Yunyue’s admittance into the Seven Profound Martial House.

“Damn, we end up meeting a detestable person,” Lin Xiaodong muttered unhappily.

Zhu Yan was walking side by side with the other young man. A few other nobles waiting outside then chose to follow the two of them. It would appear that Zhu Yan was bringing the other young man to register. The two of them continued walking forward. At this rate, it was inevitable that Lin Ming and Zhu Yan bump into one another.

With his current position and strength, it was possible that he would end up suffering badly if they were to bump into one another. But, Lin Ming chose not to run and instead looked forward in a calm manner as Zhu Yan approached.

Zhu Yan’s pace was disrupted after catching sight of Lin Ming and Lin Xiaodong. His first reaction was that of shock. After that, he frowned. Seeing Lin Ming made him feel uncomfortable. Although he had snatched away Lan Yunyue, she had refused to engage in any acts of intimacy before their wedding. Clearly, Lin Ming still exists within Lan Yunyue’s heart, not to mention her feelings of guilt. The only reason she had chosen Zhu Yan was due to the Seven Profound Martial House. As a man, Zhu Yan was unable to tolerate the fact that his future wife’s heart remained within the palms of another man.

“You are called Lin Ming, am I right? How unexpected, you would actually follow us all the way here. You, with a mere cultivation level of First Stage in Physical Training want to take the test to enter the Seven Profound Martial House?”

The meaning behind Zhu Yan’s words was obvious. He would never allow Lin Ming to enter the Seven Profound Martial House. Even though Lin Ming’s strength was of no threat to him, Lin Ming’s existence within the Seven Profound Martial House would make it impossible for Lan Yunyue to forget Lin Ming.

“Whether or not I manage to pass the assessment is my own problem. I am not here as a result of following anyone. I am here due to my pursuit of the Martial Way.”

“The Martial Way? A mere above average talent like you dared to utter the words of pursuing the Martial Way? Insolence!” Having said that, Zhu Yan’s finger released a light sound; after that, his long sword shot out from its sheath! Zhu Yan grasped onto the sword and slashed the air, releasing an intense sword qi, which created an air splitting sound. A barely visible wave flew outwards, directly cutting down half the canopy of a nearby tree.

The sounds of “pususu” could be heard as a large number of branches and leaves fell to the ground. The people around all stared with bulging eyes. Most of them were of roughly the same age as Zhu Yan and were not that much younger. However, Zhu Yan’s accomplishment in the Martial Way had already left them far behind.

The reason Zhu Yan unleashed this sword slash was to give Lin Ming a mental blow, and show him the gap between the two of them. “I am a Grade Four Martial Talent. I began training in martial arts since I was twelve, consuming countless medicinal pills in the process and have now entered the Heavenly Abode’s Sword Sect within the Seven Profound Martial House. I am currently at the pinnacle of the Third Stage of Physical Training. Even so, I am barely at the beginning stage of the Martial Way. And yet, someone like you with a mere First Stage in Physical Training dared to talk about the Martial Way?”

Zhu Yan’s manner of speech was so arrogant, it caused Lin Xiaodong to become enraged. “Surnamed Zhu! You are simply someone born two years earlier than us! What are you boasting about? If our age were reversed, this senior would use just one hand to toss you away!”

Zhu Yan frowned and turned to look at Lin Xiaodong. He took a step forward, the primal energies within his body exploded outwards as he asked. “Who are you?”

“I…” Due to the oppressive pressure sent out by Zhu Yan, Lin Xiaodong’s words were stuck in his throat. He took a step backwards, swallowed his own saliva and patted his chest before speaking. “This Young Master is called Lin Xiaodong, you better remember it!”

“Lin Xiaodong? Heng, those from the Lin Family that has the qualifications to talk with me can be counted with one hand. What makes you think that a clown like you have the qualifications to speak to me? That includes even you, Lin Ming! If not for Lan Yunyue, you have no qualifications to talk to me at all! I will give you this advice, a man must know his own limits. Someone like Lan Yunyue is not someone that you could match up to.”

A female with Grade Three Martial Talent with good looks and bearing is rare within Green Mulberry City. Most of them would only appear in great families. However, considering the conflicts of interest between the great families, they would never allow their talented females to be married off into other families, leading to the strengthening of their rivals’ bloodline. Thus, most great families would request that the male side marry into their family. This is the reason why Zhu Yan had said that.

“A thousand gold liangs! From today onwards, I do not want to see you face again!” Zhu Yan said as he pulled out a stack of gold bills from his sleeves.

The people around were rendered speechless. A thousand gold liangs is a very high sum of money, enough for a martial artist in the Physical Training Stage to buy up necessary high-grade herbs for training usage for up to three years.

“A thousand gold liangs? Do you take us for beggars?” Lin Xiaodong pushed back the stack of gold bills. Truth be told, he was simply putting on a brave façade. Even for him, a thousand gold liangs is a huge sum of wealth.

Zhu Yan flicked his hands and a powerful repelling force knocked Lin Xiaodong away. Zhu Yan coldly stared at Lin Ming, awaiting his answer.

Lin Ming took a deep breath before speaking out in a slow yet powerful tone. “Zhu Yan, I am not your match in terms of talent, I am even less so in terms of family support. However, the cultivation of martial arts does not depend only on talent and financial support; there is an even more important factor… the heart of a martial artist!”

“Your cultivation of martial arts is done for the sake of wealth, status and vanity. However, my cultivation of martial arts is done for the sake of pursuing the Martial Way. The Martial Way does not exist for those with talent, it does not exist for those with authority and it does not exist for those with money. It exists for those whose heart beats for the sake of martial arts! There will come a day when I will surpass you!” As he reached the end of his sentence, Lin Ming spoke out each word with emphasis and in a clear voice. Everyone who were standing nearby could clearly make out what he had said.

A Grade Three Talent wanted to chase after a Grade Four Talent. In addition, there was an enormous gap in terms of background between them both. This brat has gone mad!

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, Zhu Yan became momentarily stunned before laughing out. “Good! Very good indeed! I will be waiting for you!” After saying that, Zhu Yan kept the stack of gold bills. With a “weng” sound, the long sword returned to its sheath. Zhu Yan then gave Lin Ming a long look before turning away.

Chapter 4 - Legacy Skill

Sky Fortune Martial House has only eighty years of history. The Seven Profound Martial House on the other hand was founded by the third-grade sect, the Seven Profound Valleys. They possessed six hundred years’ worth of heritage and numerous Legacy skills!

Those who practice the Legacy skills from Sky Fortune Martial House have little hope of achieving Pulse Condensation Stage. However, the same cannot be said about the Seven Profound Martial House’s Legacy skills. As long as one has a Grade Four Martial Talent, breaking through into the Pulse Condensation Stage using Seven Profound Martial House’s manuals is not difficult at all!

As for Lin Ming, he has not even a decent training manual. All he had was a ‘Beginners’ Martial Arts’ manual. Every day, he would train by punching tree trunks and debone animals. This was Lin Ming’s martial way!

For the past few years, the only thing he could depend on was himself. He explored the aspects of martial arts himself through hard work and carved his way, step by step, until he reached the First Stage of Physical Training!

For him, legacies were an important existence!

Lin Ming was incomparably excited and he voraciously sorted out the knowledge regarding this Legacy skill. Not long after, this ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ surprised him yet again!

‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ is a pinnacle level Physical Training Manual from the Divine Domain. However, even though it is of the pinnacle level, it is only about Physical Training and thus was not that valuable within the Divine Domain. The reason Lin Ming became surprised was because he had finally understood what the Divine Domain is.

The Divine Domain is a higher realm that possesses hundreds of millions of years’ worth of Legacies. Physical training, martial arts, swordsmanship techniques, technical skills, arrays, all of it have been developed and honed to the extreme. It is a world reserved for the strongest of the Martial Way! Their abilities and might are not something that the current Lin Ming could hope to imagine!

Thus, this ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ is simply invaluable! Additionally, there are even more soul fragments stored within the Magic Cube. Once his strength had reached the sufficient level, he would be able to incorporate even more of them!

Considering all of this, Lin Ming’s heart was incredibly excited.

Presently, what Lin Ming fear most would be for the skill manual to be incomplete. After all the soul fragment that he had absorbed was only a small speck. It would be an absolute pity if that was the case. Thankfully, as he continued incorporating the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, he saw that it was intact. Everything from Strength Training, Flesh Training, Viscera Training, Altering Muscle, Bone Forging and Pulse Condensation were there.

This fact was surprising enough for Lin Ming. In Sky Spill Continent, Physical Training Manuals were generally for one stage only. For example, the ‘Genuine Altering Muscle Channels’ manual is specifically meant for the Altering Muscle Stage, the ‘Golden Bone Forging Divine Formula’ manual for Bone Forging Stage, the ‘Divine Nine Pulse Skill’ manual for the Pulse Condensation Stage and so on. However, this ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ is capable of propelling one from the Strength Training Stage to the Pulse Condensation Stage. But what Lin Ming found after this shocked him even more.

Within Sky Spill Continent, Pulse Condensation marks the end of the Physical Training Stage. After which, one will step upon the Primal Assemblage Stage. The Primal Assemblage Stage is divided into Post-Celestial Stage and Pre-Celestial Stage. For most people, Pulse Condensation is a bottleneck, which they could not break through. These people would be forever stuck in the Bone Forging Stage.

Pulse Condensation is the limit for the veins within the human body. That is a commonly accepted knowledge. However, according to the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, there exists another stage beyond Pulse Condensation - Tempering Marrow!

Above the Tempering Marrow Stage, there are actually others! Eight Hidden Inner Gates! Using the Eight Trigrams to correspond with the movement of the Nine Celestial Bodies, one could open up eight gates within their bodies. Then, Nine Stars of the Dao Palace! With it, one could break through the limits of the body and reach an even higher level of strength!

Regardless of Tempering Marrow or the Eight Gates, neither one of them would affect a martial artist when entering the Post-Celestial or Pre-Celestial Stage. This gives one a far higher degree of martial achievement compared to others. The benefits are self-evident!

Realizing this, Lin Ming was rendered speechless from shock. This ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ is a timeless treasure!

Lin Ming was fervently excited to start practicing. However, before he began, he checked his pocket within his bosom for the Magic Cube. To his surprise, the cube had disappeared!

Lin Ming became fearful and cold sweat started coming out of him. His hand probed around and felt something strange on his chest. He took off his clothes and found a strange symbol on the skin of his left chest. The symbol is exactly the same as the mysterious symbol of the surface of the Magic Cube.

The Magic Cube entered my body? Lin Ming recalled that the holy woman had summoned out the Magic Cube from her palm. It was no wonder that she could do that. However, Lin Ming had no clue as to how to summon it.

Lin Ming tried to summon the Magic Cube, but to no avail. Lin Ming felt somewhat disappointed. After all, there were so many soul fragments within the Magic Cube. Back then, he had only touched the smallest and dimmest of fragment and had such a great harvest. If he could incorporate more of those soul fragments, then the amount of treasure that he could unlock would be simply unimaginable.

Thinking about that, Lin Ming suddenly gave a self-deprecating smile. He was being ignorant. If the smallest ownerless soul fragment had nearly swallowed his consciousness, then the bigger ones would likely be able to instantly exterminate him!

Stop dreaming, Lin Ming!

It appeared that the secrets of the Magic Cube and the knowledge within the soul fragments would have to be left for when his cultivation had reached an even higher level. What he needed to do right now was to practice the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ as soon as possible.

Lin Ming stopped trying to summon the Magic Cube and began to explore the Legacy skill from the Divine Domain.

The essence of ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ is to transform the body into a divine weapon with amazing strength.

Additionally, the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ also emphasizes on techniques that utilizes strength. Its first layer of Strength Training is already far different from the norm.

Normally, once a person is capable of a force of a thousand jin (604 kg), that person would have achieved minor comprehension and could smash an Iron Tree with a punch. The Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians however, requires not only the training of strength, but also the training of precision, the control over the amount of strength used. Once major comprehension is achieved, one would be able to use their palm to turn a tree trunk into fine fibres!

Reading this part gave birth to a great sense of longing within Lin Ming. There was no doubt that training this ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ would make him far stronger than the average master!

…

Three days later

At the foot of Great Mountain Zhou, with the full moon suspended in the skies, Lin Ming stood upon a plain of grass with his eyes closed. He breathed following a specific rhythm, standing there for who knew how long. His entire being was still like a sculpture, illuminated by the moonlight.

He was practising the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, a special method of circulating true primal energies derived from the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ manual. This formula is much better at utilizing the true primal energies to temper the body and forge the bones. Once major comprehension of this formula is attained, the resulting strength and durability would be greatly improved to a level surpassing those of the same realm!

Under the night’s blowing winds, numerous fine grasses came together to form undulating waves which danced about. Lin Ming’s breathing seemed to be in accordance with these undulating waves, as though he had become one with the surrounding environment.

A drop of dew rolled upon a leaf just above Lin Ming’s head. Condensing quietly, it eventually dropped down.

Lin Ming who was originally motionless suddenly opened his eyes. He stretched out his right hand, allowing the drop of dew to fall upon his fingertip. The drop of dew rolled down the finger onto his palms. Grasping the drop of dew, Lin Ming’s right hand suddenly formed a fist, his shoulder and thigh moved to position, and he threw out a punch.

“Boom!”

With a muffled bang, the thick tree trunk before Lin Ming was shaken, traces of a fist appearing amidst the swirling tree dust!

Lin Ming exhaled and let go of his fist, allowing the drop of dew to drop down. With a “pa da” sound, it fell upon the grass and was scattered.

A smile emerged on Lin Ming’s face.

When ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ reaches a state of perfection, then the drop of dew would have shot out together without being splintered [2]. Although his current state of comprehension has yet to reach that far, he had still made some success.

In addition, the earlier punch had left a fist mark of roughly half a foot in depth upon the Iron Tree. Three days ago, his punch could at best only leave half an inch. His current achievement was all due to the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’.

In these three days, Lin Ming had been practicing this ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ non-stop and had finally succeeded in reaching the beginning stage. Truthfully, Lin Ming was only able to train so well thanks to the memories of the senior.

The senior’s experience and comprehension had greatly benefited Lin Ming’s training. Even the circulating method of the skill had been deeply ingrained into the senior’s soul. All Lin Ming needed to do was use his body to recollect them.

Due to how crazy his training schedule was, Lin Ming’s consumption rate of medicinal herbs was also much faster. He had used up three slices of the Blood Ginseng. At this rate, the Blood Ginseng would be used up within less than half a month’s time.

He now has the solution to training manuals, but still faced the problem of insufficient medicinal herbs…

Thus, two days went by and Lin Ming’s strength kept growing. The current Lin Ming was able to debone Level One Ferocious Beasts effortlessly. For him, even dismembering five Level Two Ferocious Beasts was considered easy.

…

One morning, Lin Xiaodong came to the Grand Clarity Pavilion to find Lin Ming. Lin Ming had earlier informed Lin Xiaodong that he was working in the Grand Clarity Pavilion, although he omitted telling him the reason behind it.

“The Annual Martial Arts Fair?” Lin Ming felt shocked, hearing Lin Xiaodong’s proposal to go there.

“That is right, many martial arts masters and nobles will be there. As for the items that will appear there, there are no rare items, only extremely rare items!”

Lin Ming shrugged and replied. “How could we afford those items? As of now, I only have less than twenty gold liangs on me.”

“So what if we cannot buy it? We can just go look around. Just take this as an act of gaining experience. Besides, we will be entering the martial house soon. We must at least buy a good weapon before that. Even if I cannot afford the high grade weapons, I should be able to get our hands on some middle grade weapons.”

Not wanting to disappoint Lin Xiaodong, Lin Ming chose to go out with him. After all, it would be a beneficial experience.

As they were headed there, Lin Xiaodong kept talking non-stop about the fair. He was very familiar with the details of the fair, its distance from the Seven Profound Martial House, the areas that are considered sub urban and so on. As they were walking down an alley way, Lin Ming suddenly stopped and placed his hand on Lin Xiaodong’s shoulders.

“What is wrong, Brother Ming?” Lin Xiaodong asked.

“Someone is blocking the way,” Lin Ming touched his waist where his boning knife was strapped onto. Thanks to his training of the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, Lin Ming’s perception abilities have greatly increased.

He could guess who it was.  A few days ago, he had beaten the man with monkey like ears. Now, the man’s master has decided to show himself. This moment was something that Lin Ming had been preparing for.

Chapter 6 - Fighting Barehanded

Wang Yigao felt that this person before him must have some mental issues. While it is not impossible for one to defeat an opponent who is at a higher level of cultivation, that requires genius talent and pinnacle martial arts taught by masters. Lin Ming is a poor young man, for him to attain his current state of strength was already a great accomplishment. But considering his mediocre talent, he actually thought he could win? Could it be that he did not get enough sleep yesterday? Is he sleepwalking right now?

Wang Yigao asked with a smirk. “What do you want?”

“If I win, I want two hundred-year-old Blood Ginseng, and five hundred gold liangs.”

Two hundred-year-old Blood Ginseng, and five hundred gold liangs! The people around were all rendered speechless: This child is quite the high maintenance type! Two hundred-year-old Blood Ginseng would require up to three hundred gold liangs. All of it would sum up to a whopping eight hundred gold liangs! This is no small number; however, one needs to be alive in order to take it.

“Eight hundred gold liangs?” Wang Yigao coldly snorted. “You think you qualify? You think your arms and legs are worth that much?”

Within Sky Fortune Kingdom, the lives of nobles and commoners are not equal. Even if Wang Yigao were to kill someone, he would only end up being confined as punishment. After that, all he had to do was pay a compensation of two hundred gold liangs.

Lin Ming slowly replied. “For martial artists, their arms and legs are priceless. If you are unwilling, then I understand. All you need to do is break off your own tendons.”

“Screw you! You are asking for death!” Wang Yigao furiously roared out, pulling the long sword on his waist.

Lin Ming’s face remained expressionless as he spoke. “You have yet to answer my question.”

“Heng! A mere eight hundred gold liangs? I can give you a thousand gold liangs! However, do you think you can live to take it? This senior will cripple you. If you can still preserve your life after three moves, this senior will have my name read upside down!

Wang Yigao had become agitated, to Lin Ming’s delight: More money for the taking. “Very well, a thousand gold liangs it is!”

He had only finished speaking those words when Wang Yigao’s sword slash descended upon him.

A faint trace of golden light radiated from the sword, and a piercing sound resounded for dozens of metres.

A martial technique!

Martial techniques involve the use of primal energies to kill the enemy. When Wang Yigao claimed that he would kill off Lin Ming within three moves, he was not just being carried away by his emotions. Rather, he had confidence in his abilities, in his martial technique! The opportunity to learn these techniques is something that only the young masters of great families or disciples of martial houses could have.

Once the martial technique is employed, those who do not possess martial techniques would find it difficult to endure. This was especially true considering the difference in martial cultivation between Wang Yigao and Lin Ming. Wang Yigao had absolute confidence in winning with just one move. The reason he had said he would kill Lin Ming within three moves was simply him preparing a backup in cases of ‘what if’s.

Wang Yigao was correct in his assumption that Lin Ming had not learnt any martial techniques. Lin Ming could only resort to common moves to deal with Wang Yigao’s attack.

When the surrounding people saw this scene, they all felt that the outcome had been determined. As for Lin Xiaodong, his heart became nervous. How could Lin Ming block off this sword attack?

Lin Ming’s attention was focused upon Wang Yigao’s incoming sword slash. Since practicing the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ from the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, his perception had increased by several folds. In Lin Ming’s eyes, Wang Yigao was a wild beast lunging towards him! For the past few days, Lin Ming had been dismembering countless number of wild beasts. Even though the beasts were already dead, dismembering them still required him identifying the gap between the bones. Whenever his knife descended, it would be quick, accurate and vicious!

At the moment when Wang Yigao’s sword descended, Lin Ming’s knife shot out. There were no calculations or considerations within his move; it was based purely on instinct. The knife went through the loophole within Wang Yigao’s move, slashing upwards with a slight tilt.

Equipped with a dazzling sword, going against an extraordinarily common knife, yet the results was something that no one could have expected. Lin Ming leaned to the side and dodged Wang Yigao’s sword slash. The knife in his hands however, had incredibly stabbed into Wang Yigao’s ribs!

“Ping!” After suffering from a stab of the knife, Wang Yigao exclaimed, his body collapsing and tumbling down onto the ground.

What is going on? The surrounding onlookers were unable to understand what had just happened and were stunned.

Presently, a one-foot long hole had appeared on Wang Yigao’s clothing, from his chest to his ribs. However, no blood was issued out. Instead, something silver shined through the hole.

“Flexible armour?”

Lin Ming secretly lamented. It turned out that Wang Yigao was wearing a flexible armour under his clothing. If not for the armour, that blow earlier would have dealt a heavy blow towards Wang Yigao’s fighting potential.

“You!” Wang Yigao was both shocked and furious, his eyes turning blood shot. He had actually been hit! He was hit by someone whose martial cultivation level was one stage lower than him! In front of countless onlookers! For the prideful Wang Yigao, this was an unacceptable matter.

“I want you to die!”

Logically speaking, that strike earlier signified that Wang Yigao had lost. But, how could the enraged Wang Yigao admit his defeat? Wielding his sword, he once again aimed a slash at Lin Ming!

Another martial technique was launched!

As for Lin Ming, he was just like an experienced hunter, catching onto every weakness shown by a wild beast!

“Ping!” The scene from earlier replayed itself. This time, a slash tore open a hole on the right side of Wang Yigao’s clothing, turning it into a waistcoat.

The surrounding onlookers were all stunned. They stared in disbelief at the outcome of the battle. How could this have happened? As the saying goes, ‘one inch longer is one inch stronger’. Wang Yigao’s sword has a far longer reach than Lin Ming’s boning knife. In addition, Wang Yigao possesses martial arts techniques and has a higher level of martial cultivation. But, in this fight, he ended up being stabbed twice with a seemingly ordinary move.

“That child, both his body speed and his knife speed is faster than Wang Yigao!” A martial artist who was observing the duel commented. A Physical Training First Stager beating a Second Stager in terms of speed was an unusual occurrence!

Lin Ming’s speed was indeed faster than Wang Yigao. In fact, the disparity in speed was quite considerable. This was the results of practicing ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’! Before practicing it, Lin Ming’s knife wielding skill was already extremely accurate and insightful. However, his speed and strength was unable to complement it. It would only be natural for him to be unable to defeat Wang Yigao who was at the Second Stage of Physical Training.

But, with the existence of ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, the situation was now completely different!

“Aah!” Mad with fury, Wang Yigao tore off his outer clothing, revealing a silver looking flexible armour. He had lost to a Physical Training First Stager brat. If he were unable to exact vengeance, then he would have no face to remain in Sky Fortune City.

“I will slaughter you!” Wang Yigao desperately poured out the primal energies within his body, causing his sword to emit an even brighter radiance than before. He slashed down onto Lin Ming’s head. If this strike were to connect, Lin Ming would certainly end up dying.

At this moment, Lin Ming made a move that surprised everyone. He threw away his knife and faced his opponent bare handed!

All the onlookers were unable to comprehend this move from Lin Ming. This slash from Wang Yigao was obviously the final blow, backed with every last drop of energy. So, why is this teenager throwing away his weapon at the most critical moment? Surely, the knife is stronger than a fist? In times of crisis, he could even use it to parry the opponents sword.

Chapter 7 - Innate Divine Strength?

The strongest attacking method within the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ that Lin Ming practiced was not a sword attack, but a fist attack!

At present, the force behind Lin Ming’s strongest punch could leave a half-foot-deep indentation on an Iron Tree trunk. The durability of the Iron Tree was in no way inferior to steel. If the object being punched were stone, it would have been easily smashed to pieces!

Lin Ming kept his gaze onto Wang Yigao, his eyes locking onto Wang Yigao’s chest. Moving to the side, he threw out a punch!

“Peng!”

With a muffled sound, Wang Yigao spat blood out of his mouth and flew out. Even with the protection of the flexible armour, even with a martial cultivation of Second Stage of Physical Training, even with the training to toughen his flesh to an incredible degree, he was still unable to endure this superb punch from Lin Ming.

Observing Wang Yigao falling onto the ground like a dead pig, the surrounding onlookers were left speechless. Wang Yigao had threatened to defeat Lin Ming in three moves, but the result was the complete opposite. Lin Ming instead defeated Wang Yigao in three moves!

Within the exchange of three moves, each one had ended with Lin Ming being victorious. If not for the flexible armour, Wang Yigao would have lost early on. How was this a fight between a Physical Training First Stager and a Second Stager? This seemed to be the complete opposite!

“Senior Liu, what is your opinion regarding this incident?” In the midst of the duel, an elderly man appeared amongst the onlookers. In his younger days, this elder had once attained the Fifth Stage of Physical Training, Bone Forging Stage. He was only one-step away from reaching the Pulse Condensation Stage; however, he had ultimately failed to break through. A Bone Forging Stage martial artist has the same amount of lifespan as the common people. Naturally, their bodies could not withstand the ravages of time.  Now that this Senior Liu’s age had exceeded seventy, he no longer has any fighting strength. But, his perceptive eyes remained.

The elderly man pondered for a moment before replying. “That child is gifted with innate divine strength!”

The grade of a martial artist, be it Grade One Martial Talent or Grade Two is simply the measure of the speed and ease with which their body could absorb primal energies. The faster they could absorb primal energies, the higher their martial talent would be.

However, the martial artist’s body strength is not included in the measurement for martial talent. That is because most people have the equivalent amount of strength.

Occasionally though, some people would be born with innate divine strength. Some are born with ten times the strength of the normal people, and others more!

With great strength comes great speed. Naturally, they would have an advantage in battles.

Yet, the number of these martial artists is small. In addition, not many of them are successful. After all, as martial cultivation progresses, the primal energies become more important and the effect that one’s innate strength has becomes correspondingly smaller.

“So that is how it is…” The surrounding observers nodded their heads. This explanation was very reasonable.

Lin Ming picked up his knife and walked step by step towards Wang Yigao. The current Wang Yigao was in a miserable state. His clothes had turned into strips of fabrics, blood spilled from his mouth and his face was covered with dirt. Wang Yigao wanted nothing more than to kill himself. He had completely lost his face in today’s incident. He would likely become the laughing stock amongst his peers within Sky Fortune City.

Lin Ming spoke up. “You are the one who said it earlier, one thousand gold liangs, cough it out.”

Shit!

Hearing those words, Wang Yigao nearly spat out another mouthful of blood.

Oh, what a son of a bitch I am! Did I really have nothing better to do? Why did I have to turn eight hundred to one thousand? Even though Wang Yigao is a child of a great family, taking out one thousand gold liangs is no small matter!

Today’s incident was certainly the most miserable and unforgettable one in his entire life. With so many people bearing witness, Wang Yigao was unable to go back on his words.

Additionally, since it was the terms of a duel, he could not even think about exacting vengeance or risk being ridiculed by all. Unless, unless it was done in utmost secrecy.

“Money, bring out the money!” Wang Yiago shouted at his men! Today, he would have to admit his loss. But, this was not the end, he swore that he would hack Lin Ming to pieces!

The group of men were all shocked senseless by Lin Ming’s performance. Even if all of them were to gang up on Lin Ming, there was no guarantee that they could win! Is he really just a Physical Training First Stager?

“Xiaodong, collect the money,” Lin Ming said. One thousand gold liangs was no small sum. Even though Wang Yigao is rich, he would not have brought so much money with him. Thus, he could only pool them up through his men.

From the moment Wang Yigao vomited blood, Lin Xiaodong had been stunned. It was only after Lin Ming had called him that he finally reacted: Oh, heavens! Is this for real? He actually won?

Furthermore, they had won a thousand gold liangs. A thousand gold liangs! All of Lin Xiaodong’s wealth combined amount to no more than only two hundred gold liangs. Buying up a single Blood Ginseng took up more than half of it!

Looking at the gold bills within his hands, Lin Xiaodong’s expression was one of shock. Then it turned into ecstasy before turning into one of laughter.

His eyes were never big to begin with. Now that he was smiling to such an extent, his eyes were almost unnoticeable.

“Haha, we are rich, we are rich! You are too kind, what could I say? Thank you so much for your generosity. Knowing that we were in a tight spot, you seniors have chosen to gift us with some spending money, thank you!”

“Especially brother Gao Yiwang who felt that eight hundred liangs was not enough and had insisted on giving out one thousand liangs. On behalf of the common people, I give you my thanks.”

Hearing Lin Xiaodong’s sarcastic words, ‘Gao Yiwang’ who was already seriously injured felt his mouth overflowing and spat out another mouthful of blood. Back then, he had said that if he could not kill off Lin Ming within three moves, his name would be read upside down.

Screw your granddaddy!

Wang Yigao furiously gritted his teeth. As for the others, their faces were contorted to the extreme. As it so happened, Lin Xiaodong’s face was not the attractive kind. To them, Lin Xiaodong’s current face was so disgusting, it could kill. After collecting the gold bills, Lin Xiaodong spit out some saliva onto his palms in an exaggerated manner and started counting the bills one by one.

“Twenty, thirty, fifty, hundred, hundred five, hundred seven…”

Lin Xiaodong counted the thick stack of gold bills three times, then said with a grin and squinted eyes. “Eight hundred and fifty gold liangs, one hundred and fifty short. I say, aren’t you all men of wealth? How is it that you cannot even cough out such a small sum of money?”

Hearing Lin Xiaodong’s words, Wang Yigao nearly vomited blood yet again. His face sank deep, he shook his right hand and a “ding” could be heard. His long sword was embedded in the middle of the square. “Verdant Sharp Sword, it can be sold for two hundred gold liangs in any weapons shop. We are leaving!”

Six of them came to exact vengeance on others. However, the end result was them having to hand over all their possessions, including their swords. This pathetic state was a first for Wang Yigao!

Seeing the Verdant Sharp Sword, Lin Xiaodong grinned. He has some knowledge regarding weapons and the Verdant Sharp Sword is truly an extraordinary weapon. At the very least, it is far better than the one he was using.

Lin Ming said. “If you like it, you can have it.”

Lin Xiaodong replied. “I cannot do that. Brother Ming, you do not even have a weapon yet.”

Lin Ming replied. “My fists are my weapons. For now, I have no need for a weapon. Later on, I will get myself a weapon that fits me. Even though this Verdant Sharp Sword is sharp, it is too light for my fighting style.”

Lin Xiaodong recalled the fearsome fist that Lin Ming had thrown back then and had to agree that this sword was simply insufficient to complement with Lin Ming.

“Very well, I will take this sword then. However, you sure are fearsome, Brother Ming. I never saw you as such a character before,” Ever since Lin Ming started practicing martial arts, Lin Xiaodong had never witnessed Lin Ming in action. How could he have known that Lin Ming’s strength had soared to such a degree. He believed this to be the results of Lin Ming’s hard work.

Lin Ming explained. “Wang Yigao does not have a detailed grasp on his own strength, and is only a beginner Physical Training Second Stager. In addition, his foundation is also unstable. His level of cultivation is probably a result of stuffing himself with medications. Even his martial techniques were nothing of note. Beating him is nothing to be proud of, my first goal is Zhu Yan.”

Zhu Yan is different from Wang Yigao. Zhu Yan possesses a high amount of strength and a solid foundation. His Grade Four Martial Talent is not simply for show. In addition, he is also quite the hard worker. Thus, the current Lin Ming had no chance of beating Zhu Yan.

Lin Ming accepted the gold bills, then split them apart and handed one stack to Lin Xiaodong without counting. “Use this.”

“What are you doing? This gold were all earned by you. I have already taken the sword. As for gold, I have no need for it. With my way of practicing, ten gold liangs per month is the most I will need.”

Lin Ming remained silent for a while, then without objecting, he kept the gold bills into his own bosom. Between him and Lin Xiaodong, such details were unnecessary.

“All right, let us go to the fair.”

“You are right! Haha, I nearly forgot about it, the fair! Now we have the capital for it, one thousand liangs! Son of a bitch! This senior had never even laid eyes on such a huge sum of money before! This time, I will be making a splash!”

Chapter 15 - Overwhelming Symbol

Today, Lin Ming had prepared as well as he possibly could; solely in the tracing of the lines and symbols, he was no less than those lofty masters!

Manipulating the Sky Wind Grass juice, Lin Ming opened both his hands and a single drop of emerald liquid flew into the air where it steadily remained.

Looking at this liquid green pearl, Lin Ming closed his eyes as his hands flashed and formed a series of seals. These movements had long ago been printed in his mind, and along with memories of the soul fragment, these complex signs were as instinctual as breathing.

With a deep breath, Lin Ming began. His ten fingers flowed like a branches in a storm, and they even collided with each other as his speed of seal formation was too fast. His fingers blurred as another drop of liquid from a different material flew into the air. With his soul force at full strength, Lin Ming rapidly formed the beautiful and mysterious inscription symbols. In order to preserve his soul force, Lin Ming had started working on another material before the first had finished!

In this high-intensity and highly complicated plan, Lin Ming’s error rate was low extremely low.

When the inscription was half finished, Ming began to feel the strain.

When the inscription was two-thirds complete, Lin Ming felt that his soul force was reaching its end, and he began to revolve the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula.’

With that on his mind, the chance that a problem would arise also increased. Lin Ming clenched his teeth and pressed on. He still had to divide the several materials to use them to draw the final rune.

“Sky Worm Silk…has completed!” The tense Lin Ming finally let loose a breath of relief. Sky Worm Silk was what he lacked the most, he could now allow for failure here.

“There are five runes…” Lin Ming counted the number in his heart as his soul force reached the limit.

‘Four…Three…Two….”

“Success!”

Lin Ming finished the inscription at this moment. The sparkling runes shined and flashed for a brief moment as they coalesced into an inscription the size of a square inch. It hung there suspended in air.

Lin Ming had almost collapsed, but as he looked at this completed inscription floating in air, he felt nothing but absolute joy! This small inscription was like his precious child; he had spent a month of inhuman suffering and massive amounts of money to raise it up!

The elder had named this inscription the ‘Overwhelming Symbol.’ This title was a tad too vulgar and childish, but stemming from the respect that Lin Ming held for this elder in his heart, he did not change its name. It was the ‘Overwhelming Symbol!’

Lin Ming had bought fifteen of the cheapest symbol papers at one to two taels of gold per dozen. With just a slight bit of soul force, the ‘Overwhelming Symbol’ fell onto the symbol paper. Gold lines converged to form ancient runes on the symbol paper. The symbol paper truly was plain, and the overall effect made it look bland and unremarkable.

At the last minute of forming the symbol paper, Lin Ming changed the outwards design appearance with his soul force. It resembled a flame pattern.

This kind of design left on the inscription treasures would become a sign. His sign! Many inscription masters had their own personalized designs as a mark of their work.

Lin Ming decided on flames, as flames represented rebirth into nirvana.

Cultivating a martial path was a trial by fire. Pain was constant, and danger was ever present. Travelling down this path would burn one into ashes! Only those that have firm hearts and immeasurable wills would be able to be rebirthed through the flames, and become a dragon or phoenix that ascends like a god into the skies!

Lin Ming carefully received this precious symbol paper. He opened the window and the fresh air and bright sunlight sprinkled down on him and reflected on his bloodshot eyes. He was bone tired with exhaustion and wanted to go to sleep right away, but Lin Ming had an unprecedented sense of satisfaction.

Time left before the Seven Profound Martial House’s exam - two months and ten days!

In the past five days Lin Ming had branded his last inscription onto the symbol paper. Thus, all his materials had been thoroughly exhausted. He had managed to altogether create four copies of the ‘Overwhelming Symbol.’

Looking at these symbol papers, Lin Ming has an unforgettable sense of achievement. Now he wanted to sell these four symbol papers!

At the last trade fair, Master Baihong’s engraved inscription had sold for 1500 taels of gold. Clearly this was affected by the renown of the inscription master. Lin Ming had not sold any inscriptions before so he was not famous or well known, but he was confident in his work. This inscription came from the Realm of the Gods! Its effect compared to that of Master Baihong’s work was like the Heavens and Earth; there was simply no comparison.

In that elder’s memory, the ‘Overwhelming Symbol’ was merely the most basic inscription, but it was enough to use on a superior piece of equipment, a third grade piece of equipment. If used on lower grade equipment, then the effect would increase by at least sixty percent!

Not only that, but the ‘Overwhelming Symbol’ also granted equipment an additional skill!

Some top tier inscription techniques can add additional skills to equipment. By concentrating soul force, it was possible to use these skills. They ranged from energy attacks, armor increasing shields, illusionary techniques, to demonic techniques and more!

Lin Ming’s inscription, if engraved on a weapon, would give that weapon a skill called the ‘instant violent strike.’

The small inscription rune was in fact a complex array. When the user concentrated a massive amount of soul force into the weapon, the inscription would absorb this energy, compress it to the limit, and then instantly erupt! In a close combat battle, this move was truly formidable in its lethality.

Lin Ming didn’t actually believe his inscription was as amazing as the ones he recounted in the elder’s memories. There was also definitely no way for a piece of equipment to achieve a 60% increase in power at his current level. As for that ‘instant violent strike,’ Lin Mind did not know if it actually would work because the inscription technique was too complex. After making the end product, all those runes and symbols were concentrated in that tiny inscription so it was difficult for even the creator to judge the ability of the end product. There were just too many possible structures, and a corresponding number of possible mistakes. In the worst case scenario the weapon might even blow up! As long as there was the tiniest of problems, the entire inscription would have to be sold at great discount.

Lin Ming finally had a night of full rest, and slept blissfully until the early morning. His soul force and energy were in peak condition. He asked Lin Xiaodong for some trade fairs and auction house addresses, and then departed with his symbol papers.

He had bought some new clothes included a hooded cape that covered his face. Although the trade fairs and auction houses always had a good reputation for safety, and wouldn’t leak the identity of patrons, it was best to be careful. After all, if the four symbol papers were sold for any high price, then if that person were known, they might rob and kill them for their possessions.

Lin Ming first went to the official Sky Fortune City Auction Hall. There were many auction halls in Sky Fortune City, and there wasn’t one that stood out among the rest, so he chose one with a slightly better reputation.

As long as these four symbol papers sold, he would be able to purchase the materials for medicine!

However as Lin Ming approached the auction house, he thought that it was just too simple.

Chapter 16 - Frustration

The auction house had an extremely strict review process, in particular concerning the goods they sold; otherwise fakes and replicas would be manage to get through and the reputation of the auction house would suffer a loss. To an auction house, reputation was everything.

A middle-aged man greeted Lin Min; to be more exact, blocked him, and asked .”Sir, is there anything I can help you with?”

Lin Ming was wearing a clean and crisp robe and he looked like any other well-to-do citizen. However his height was shorter than an adult male by several inches. In addition, his voice had not yet fully matured, so it wasn’t possible to cover up the fact that he was a young boy of only 15 or 16 years.

Therefore Lin Ming simply said with his own voice, “I’m here for an appraisal of inscription runes.”

‘Oh?” The middle aged man looked at Lin Ming somewhat suspiciously. “Can I see your inscription?” In fact, this man’s manners were already very polite. A 15-16 year old coming into the auction house to appraise some inscriptions was already strange. The price frequently rose to over a thousand taels of gold. Most people would have well founded suspicions that this was a practical joke.

After Lin Ming pulled out the symbol paper, the middle aged man frowned as he noticed the shoddy quality of it. This was the most basic and cheap symbol paper that was available on the market at one or two taels of gold for a dozen. Although the cost of the symbol paper did not affect the quality of the inscription, it was still a sign of the inscription master’s status. Naturally they would never use this kind of symbol paper! They would normally use high quality symbol paper that cost several taels of gold each, to show off the results of their inscription.

However there was a faint energy which emitted from the symbol paper and the middle aged man was able to determine that this was a complete and real product, not a practical joke. He looked at Lin Ming and asked, “Do you have some sort of certificate stating which inscription master created this?”

Lin Ming shook his head.

“Well alright, come with me.”

The middle aged man led Lin Ming through the hallway to an appraisal room at the back of the auction house.  The man in the appraisal chamber wore an unlined black garment, and looked to be a harsh grandfather in his 50’s or 60’s. Lin Ming also noted the sign in front of the man that wrote “Advanced Appraiser.”

The black robed man took this symbol paper in hand and noted that the inscription was placed on inferior paper, but he didn’t reveal any expression that indicated he was disgusted or skeptical. Instead, he maintained a tranquil and calm demeanor, and quietly slipped on a pair of white gloves and invested his full attention towards an earnest and practical appraisal of the work. This demonstrated that he was a true professional!

However the appraiser only just began when he raised his head, his face slightly more serious, and looked at Lin Ming. “If I’m not wrong, the one who created this inscription symbol, his strength should not exceed the third level of the body transformation stage?”

The inscription symbol would always carry a slight hint of the makers soul force. It was possible for an appraiser to judge the creators martial arts cultivation level through these traces. Since Lin Ming created the inscription paper, the soul force trace would naturally be weak, but since he practiced the overwhelming ‘True Primal Chaos Formula,’ the soul force was much thicker than the average martial artists. If the appraiser knew that the inscription was created by a mere boy at the first level of the body transformation stage, his chin would surely drop to the ground.

Lin Ming knew that there was no way to deny this, so he nodded.

The only man sharply inhaled, and then sighed, “To think there was such a talent within the young generation. A trivial little third level body transformation cultivation can draw an inscription symbol. It is shocking!”

Usually, the inscription masters tended to be of the older generation, and most were above the bone forging boundary. Many even broke through the pulse condensing boundary and some even at the pre-celestial boundary.

Perhaps this third level body transformation was just an inscription masters apprentice, and happened to get lucky and create a successful inscription. However this boy brought in four of the same inscription, which was truly amazing.

Lin Ming heard the old man’s praise and thought things were going well, but he didn’t expect the old man to change his mind. “It is a complete and real inscription symbol, but the creator is only an apprentice, therefore we are unable to identify the increase in strength it would provide or the integrity of the inscription. You must know that an apprentice’s soul force is generally limited in quantity and quality, and it is very difficult to complete the myriad and complicated inscription designs. Even If the symbol increased the strength by ten percent, if it cannot be placed onto superior equipment, then we cannot auction this as failed product would harm the auction houses reputation.”

Inscriptions were used only on superior equipment, because only superior equipment was sturdy and strong enough concentrate the soul force and energy of martial artists in battle. Since the inscriptions modified soul force, it needed to be at least that level.

Therefore the lowest quality goods that someone would place an inscription on were at least several thousand gold taels!

This equipment was not something the average person was able to obtain. Even the juniors of aristocratic families had to cultivate to at least the altering muscle or bone forging level to even be considered for having such a high quality weapon.

For instance, Wang Yigao had an excellent family background, but because his cultivation was low, even though he had used a fine blue sword, it did not necessarily mean it was a treasure. That blue sword was only two hundred taels of gold.

The number of times that you can engrave on a weapon was limited, essentially, it was only one time. After an inscription, another cannot be placed on. Thinking about it, who would spend several thousand taels of gold on a weapon, only to place on it an inscription of dubious origin?

Therefore the inscription market for apprentices was nonexistent.

Lin Ming had expected this result and said, “I only need to auction three, the last you can use for experiments.”

After the inscription is made, it is too difficult to test the result. Even the creator can only guesstimate its effectiveness.

When a martial artist purchased an inscription, he was basically gambling on his luck, so high level inscription masters were well received because they had the reputation to guarantee the effectiveness of their products. Very few people would purchase an unknown master’s inscriptions, much less an apprentice’s. It was just gambling with their own precious money!

The appraiser said, “Of course. However, the experiment needs to be done with your own equipment.”

Lin Ming suddenly turned silent. A weapon worth several thousand gold taels? He supposed it was impossible for the auction house to casually put up a weapon worth several thousand gold taels to test as an experiment.

If Lin Ming were an inscription master then things might have been different, because the masters have reputations and wouldn’t need have their inscriptions tested. Moreover, the auction house would be happy to be on good terms with such a figure and even provide their own weapons.

At Lin Mings moment of highest worth, he only had 800 taels of gold. Where would he get a weapon that was worth several thousand taels of gold to engrave an inscription on?

He did not bother arguing or saying anything else. He could have said that there was no way their equipment would have suffered a loss, but there was no reason to believe him, because the soul force on the inscription really was too weak.

So Lin Ming took his four symbol papers and turned around to leave the Sky Fortune official auction house.

“Sorry, but we need proof that the inscription association provides, or a signed notary provided to the inscription master…”

At the Sky Fortune City trade fair, the merchant had directly rejected Lin Ming after seeing his age.

This was a polite rejection. Afterwards Lin Ming went to several private shops and the attitudes of these people were even worse.

He tried the inscription transaction trading pavilion that was under the jurisdiction of the Trade Association. The store was opulent and luxurious with six floors, each filled with high class establishments and boasted an air of refinement. Everything was expensive nothing was cheap; the goods ranged from a few hundred to several thousand gold taels. Even the shopkeepers were needlessly arrogant. If a rich young master came, then they would be polite and offer tea, kind words, and never-ending bootlicking. But for the poor salesmen, they received nothing but a straight boot to the rear.

Some did not even bother saying anything, and just waved him away impatiently.

“Look kid, don’t make trouble here, you’re blocking my good business.”

“Hey you, this isn’t a place where a little boy should come to….oh, hey customer, what do you need! Come see…”

“Haha, child, don’t try to tease me here, I’ve already laughed today. This is just toilet paper! And you drew some small flames on this toilet paper. Did you think it was an inscription? Haha…”

Chapter 19 - Muyi’s Doubts

The Sky Fortune Kingdom held martial arts in high esteem, especially in the military. A tournament would be held every three years, for the selection of talents into higher positions, and to raise the fighting spirit of the martial warrior.

The requirements for this tournament were that one had to be less than thirty years old and had achieved at least the third level of body transformation. Thousands of competitors would enter in, and after several tests and three rounds, only fifty would remain.

Now the third and final round of the competition was beginning. The competitors had gone through their rounds, and soon there would be only fifty remaining.

This was the last battle. The contestants would put forth all their hidden abilities and fight with all their might! The stage would fill with the aura of a raging fire as each man made their last stand!

However the start of the competition had not caused the higher ups to pay much attention. The competitors on the field so far either had low strength, or too much of a disparity between them. It had reached the twentieth round so far and there hadn’t been any rousing fights. All Qin Xiao cared about so far were the results.

The competition now had two sides. One was the son of a general, a handsome 29 year old man at the peak of bone forging. The past few years this man has gone on numerous missions and earned many medals and awards for his service. His strength had been strengthened by these events, and in his possession were even two treasures; a saber and a suit of armor. The saber also had an engraving on it from an inscription master; its strength was no small matter!

But on the other side was a birth soldier of humble origins. His name was Tie Feng. His talent wasn’t outstanding, but he practiced diligently to the point it left one breathless. He was fearless in battle; not even the threat of death could cause him to waver. He had killed many enemies and earned himself many merits, even more so than the general’s child! Now, Tie Feng was also at the peak of bone forging.

It was rare for two soldiers to have such a similar and high cultivation at their age. After slaughtering their enemies in the battlefield, in the future it was possible that they would enter the pulse condensation period and become pillars of the country!

As the referee announced the two competitors, a silver emblazoned general smiled with happiness and gratification. The one going on stage was his son!

“Haha, old man Li, your son really did you proud this time.” Qin Xiao smiled as he said this. This silver emblazoned general had once been under his command and they were old friends.

“Commander is too polite. This poor son of mine has grown up with many rare medicines and still hasn’t shown much promise; he really isn’t making an effort to succeed.” Although the silver emblazoned general said this with deprecation, he couldn’t conceal his smile. He was very satisfied and proud of his son.

“Mm, this Tie Feng has had very good results, but he will find it difficult to win today.”

Qin Xiao said so because of the difference in martial skills and the disparity in rare equipment.

The silver emblazoned general’s son had two rare treasures, and they also had the engraving of an inscription master to bolster their strength. This Tie Feng came from a humble background; naturally he wouldn’t have such things.

This battle didn’t seem fair, but Sky Fortune Kingdom’s tournaments have always been so. Treasures and equipment were considered part of a soldier’s inherent strength! In the midst of the battlefield, because of the disparity in equipment, if you were cut down by the enemy, could you then complain that it was unfair?

It was impossible for the army to supply each soldier with rare equipment, thus is if a soldier wanted to prepare, then their family background also became a part of their strength, and even an important part.

When Tie Feng came on stage, he drew out his four foot sword. Qin Xiao turned to Muyi who was sitting beside him, “Mister Muyi, is that Tie Feng’s sword also a treasure?”

Muyi stroked his beard and nodded, “Treasure indeed, but it is damaged.”

“Oh, damaged?” After Muyi said that, Qin Xiao also saw that the sword missed the tip. It really was a damaged sword.

Muyi said, “Damaged equipment is of course worse than a whole one. Not only that but it is Tie Feng’s only treasure, whereas Li Qi has two. Their two levels of cultivation may be similar, but Tie Feng’s martial skill manual is inferior to Li Qi’s’. This battle, Tie Feng will lose.

Qin Xiao said, “Although he will lose, that this Tie Feng managed to get this far with a damaged sword is also amazing. If in this next battle he can manage to take twenty moves, I might promote into the armies martial hall. Xingxuan, take a good look at this battle; you too will enter the fifth layer of body transformation. Although you practice a specialized martial skill for women, all creatures are the same, so if you watch carefully it will help you.”

Qin Xiao’s last few words were to Qin Xingxuan. She politely nodded and said, “Yes, grandfather.”

As soon as the referee commenced the start of the fight, that man named Li Qi rushed forwards with several fierce strikes. He hoped to end the battle as soon as possible. He had the advantage in every aspect! The quicker he finished this, the better!

He began to utilize the secret skill passed down through the Li family, the ‘Five Sacred Mountains Saber Art’! This kind of swordsmanship was overwhelming as if a mountain were falling down upon you. Each slash and thrust was accompanied by an incomparably imposing sense of power. It was able to instantly overwhelm anyone of a lesser cultivation level. Even with an equal cultivation, it was difficult to defend against this strike that crushed down on you like innumerable mountains. Most would just succumb to the demolishing heavy attack.

As soon as Li Qi wielded his saber, the air filled with the whistling of the wind, as if an entire orchestra were playing a battle song. The saber in his hand was 500 jins; it was the perfect combination to display the overwhelming power of the ‘Five Sacred Mountains Saber Art!’ If the enemy’s weapon quality was less, then the weapon would simply break apart!

Tie Feng saw Li Qi’s come chopping down and his eyes hardened, his complexion changing. He knew of Li Qi’s secret move. He sunk his waist and steadied his legs. With both hands gripping the broken sword, his body erupted with a flood of turbulent true essence that poured into the blade!

Facing Li Qi’s overwhelming strike, he could only meet him head on with all of his strength!

But as Tie Feng poured his true essence into the sword, his heart gave a slight skip. The true essence was flowing as if…as if it were much smoother than before!

Tie Feng had already had this sword for several months. Before now, when he poured his true essence into the blade, it was like pouring water into a drainage ditch. The sword couldn’t absorb much true essence, and in fact wasted a lot. But this time the blade was sucking up his true essence like an eddying current. The smoothness of absorption was incomparable, and there wasn’t a single feeling of waste!

How can it be like this?

Tie Feng didn’t have any time to think with Li Qi’s saber coming down on him, so he simply cried out and cut his blade upwards!

With his common low-grade army martial skill ‘Total Annihilation Strike’, he met Li Qi’s secret high-tier martial skill passed down through his family, the ‘Five Sacred Mountains Saber Art!’ Their blades collided any a loud explosion filled the air. The collision of true essence erupted into the air, and the floor of the area was smashed apart. Li Qi was forced backwards three or four feet, but Tie Feng was also forced back a few steps!

Evenly matched!

Tie Feng gasped and looked at the blade in his hand, his face filling with color of disbelief. He had never fought before with Li Qi before, and had only heard of him. After that strike now, he finally realized how fearful this man truly was! Before, he would have suffered some light wounds, not how he had managed to keep that saber of his in check!

He knew with absolute certainty that it was not his own strength that increased, but this sword of his had changed…was it because of the inscription symbol from yesterday?

Tie Feng did not understand exactly how inscriptions worked, but knew that they could strengthen weapons. Tie Feng thought they might increase the sharpness of the blade, but after testing it out yesterday on several trees he did not feel anything different, so he had been disappointed. He had never realized that the inscription technique used true essence to enhance the strength of the weapon!

Was this really the inscription symbol of an apprentice? How could it be so fierce? Although he did not understand the pricing of most inscriptions, in his heart he absolutely knew that with such strength and such a powerful effect, there was no way that this inscription could be bought with only 100 gold taels!

With just a collision, Li Qi had been struck back down to reality. This man had taken his saber strike with that broken blade and had come out even…perhaps even higher! This man…was terrifying!

“Good!” Qin Xiao praised, “The ordinary army martial skill was able to keep off Li Qi’s ‘Five Sacred Mountain Saber Skill’ with a broken blade. This Tie Feng is good! Very good! Mister Muyi, what do you think?”

Muyi wrinkled his brow and was at a loss for words. Although he and Qin Xiao had about the same level of cultivation, he was also an inscription master, so his understanding of treasures naturally exceeded Qin Xiao. In that brief strike a moment ago, he clearly saw that Tie Feng’s broken blade was not any less amazing than Li Qi’s saber! And that was because the true essence that poured from that blade had even shocked him!

How could it be like this? Looking at the damaged blade, he could see that it wasn’t a high grade treasure.

Could it be because of an inscription symbol?

Chapter 32 - Oppress With Others’ Power

Zhao Mingshan gaped at Lin Ming. He recalled that Lin Ming had once said the words ‘You want to tie me up, but once you do, there won’t be a good outcome for you.’

Faced with such a superior backing, Zhao Mingshan had no choice but to lower his head and play as a dog for this boy. Even though this was a heavy loss of face for him, it was nothing in comparison to keeping his own little life.

Zhao Mingshan immediately changed his countenance. His whole face locked up with a forced smile as he said, “It appears that we accidently fished out two dragon kings. These two fellow brothers, today was truly just a silly misunderstanding. I hope you can show some mercy and overlook my transgressions. You people, quickly untie these two fellows!”

Although he hadn’t been untied yet, Lin Xiaodong’s gag cloth was taken out, and he was a bit perplexed. But Lin Ming had given him all sorts of surprises these days, so he adapted quickly.

Was it that elusive and mysterious master that Lin Ming had spoken of?

To Lin Xiaodong, such a powerful and mighty being was only a foreign concept to him. But in any case, with someone like that backing them up, he had no need to fear these idiots!

“F*ck your whole family, f*ck your mom and your family you little mother fuckers!” Lin Xiaodong let out a string of epithets as the officers struggled to unwind the ropes that bound his large body. They were pushed aside by Lin Xiaodong as he rolled around.

“You think that you tie me up and let me go whenever you want?” Lin Xiaodong had originally suffered a loss of face, but now that he had the upper hand, he naturally would return the favor.

Zhao Mingshan had nothing he could do but to take the words and suffer silently. He smiled and painstakingly said, “Little brothers, I was blind and foolish, would you be merciful and overlook these matters today? I would truly be grateful if you somehow allow us to compensate you…”

Lin Xiaodong crooked his neck. These officers of the Police Department only had a tiny salary with a bit of gold that they scraped up off the books. Lin Xiaodong did not have a liking for any of this money, so what was the point of offering it to him?

At this time, Lin Xiaodong happened to see Wang Yigao off to the side. He was taking advantage of the distraction to make his escape. Lin Xiaodong angrily said, “Stop! Whose mother said to let that kid go! Return here right now!”

Wang Yigao nearly fell off of his horse as he heard these words. The turn of events and frightened him silly. His father was waiting for him to return home for punishment, this was an absolute nightmare.

Now even seeing Lin Ming made his heart shudder with dread. Forget retaliating, if he ever saw Lin Ming again he would make a full effort to scamper away. Not only did Wang Yigao fear Lin Ming, but he also didn’t know what kind of backing Lin Ming had. Whatever it was, it was greater than anything he could compare with!

Losing the only advantage he had, Wang Yigao finally realized he was completely inferior to Lin Ming.

“You…what do you want?”

“You want to get away? You think there is anything in this whole world that is that easy?” Lin Xiaodong had a sudden inspiration. He turned to several officers. “You there, beat this guy up.”

Wang Yigao trembled as he heard this. Zhao Mingshan grimaced; now he really didn’t know if he could preserve his own head. If they hit Wang Yigao any more, he really might die.

Zhao Mingshan looked to Lin Ming with a pleading look.

Lin Ming finally said, “Consider this finished. There’s no point dealing with this kind of person.”

He looked to Wang Yigao and asked, “I ask you, when you came up to stir trouble, I saw that there were also people spying on me from the blue carriage. Was that Zhu Yan?”

Wang Yigao felt his stomach fall. Did this man have eyes on the back of his head?

He had already thoroughly feared Lin Ming, but now that fear was deepening as terror filled his eyes.

He still didn’t speak, so Lin Ming took a single step towards him, and coldly said, “Yes, or no?”

Wang Yigao’s heart stopped and he clenched his teeth. He nodded.

“Today’s matter was also thought up by Zhu Yan?”

Wang Yigao nodded again.

“Good. You may go.”

Lin Ming was already thinking that this was the case. Zhu Yan did not want him to enter the Seven Profound Martial House. Wang Yigao was just a pawn that had been used to prevent him from taking part in the entrance exam; Lin Ming did not want to bother with such a small bit player again. The reason was because Wang Yigao’s father was the general. Lin Ming also knew discretion, and he had already left behind some hidden true essence in him that would leave him confined to his bed for a period.

Zhao Mingshao breathed a sigh of relief as he heard Lin Ming. He hurried forward to personally untie them.

Lin Xiaodong flexed his chubby wrists and look at Zhao Mingshan who had jumped off a black maned horse. Lin Xiaodong had a sharp eye for money, and he understood at a glance that this horse was a superior breed. Although they couldn’t compare with the snow white horses of the Martial Quarters, their value was no less than 500 gold taels.

“We’re fine, you don’t need to send us off. Leave behind two horses. That black maned horse is also nice. I’ll take it.”

Zhao Mingshao’s mouth twitched as he heard this. This horse was his beloved and treasured beauty. But he clenched his teeth and said, “If these fellow brothers like my horse, feel free to ride her.”

“Haha. Then don’t mind me being impolite.” Lin Xiaodong said. He leapt up and his pudgy body seated on the black maned horse. “Heh heh, let’s go!”

As they left the group, Lin Xiaodong was in an excellent mood. “Sh*t, that was better than getting money! I’ve never felt so great in my life. Not only did that idiot ‘Gao Yiwang’ earn his lesson, but even the captain gave me his own horse. Haha, this is what they call the great life!”

Lin Ming smiled and said, “We borrowed others’ power and influence today, but anyone can rely on connections to do that. If we really want to feel great, then we must get strong ourselves and depend on our own strength to intimidate the world. Then no one would dare to bother us. That feeling would really be great.”

“Intimidate the world? Haha, Brother Lin, I don’t have such grand dreams as you; I’m fine with relying on others’ power and influence. How about this Brother Lin, when one day your name is known across the world, you cover for me. I’ll tell them your name, and frighten them off.”

“Okay!” Lin Ming laughed out loud.

The two were originally only brought three or four miles down the road. They galloped on their horses and in a short while arrived back at the square. In the square were still a sea of people; it seemed that the Strength Trial had just begun.

Lin Ming had forgotten about the blue carriage until now; he noticed that it was still sitting there. But now Zhu Yan had disembarked from it. He was holding onto a long sword while staring an ice cold gaze.

“It seems I gave you less credit than was due. You are quite talented.” In a moment, Zhu Yan had transmitted his voice to Lin Ming. They were 200 meters away, but it was as if Zhu Yan was speaking right beside him.

This was a message sent with true essence. It required an extremely high degree of control of true essence to achieve. Zhu Yan must have reached the peak of the Third Stage in the last six months.

“Don’t think that just because you reached the Second Stage of Body Transformation that you are anything special. Beating up some useless potatoes that are on the same level as you is no accomplishment at all. You said that one day you would surpass me? Good. I will wait for you. I will let you know the true difference between you and I, and you will learn that you are not destined to be an elite of this world.

“An elite of this world?” Lin Ming looked at Zhu Yan and smiled. “Certainly not of this world…”

Chapter 37 - Invulnerable To Ten Thousand Evils

As this beautiful and impossibly exquisite example of womanhood stood before him, this image was unforgettably carved into his mind and he felt the tower of his will tremble in its firmament. His breath became shallow and blood rushed to his head. After all, when it comes to matters between men and women, Lin Ming was still only a young boy.

Qin Xingxuan reached her arms around Lin Ming. She was like a warm and fragrant jade that surrounded him and the delicate fragrance of her virgin body wafted into his nostrils and left a strong impact in Lin Ming’s heart.

Fabrication!

Illusion!

Lin Ming squeezed his eyes shut and in his heart he began to revolve the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, He managed to hold down his quickly fleeing sanity.

“Lin Ming, do you not like me?”

This voice was gentle and soft like a spring rain. Lin Ming’s eyelids jumped, but he remained unmoved as before.

“Ah….” With a gentle sigh, she let Lin Ming go. Qin Xingxuan stood up, her expression revealing some hidden bitterness, and she slowly departed.

The scene before him began to slowly fade away, and the world returned to tranquility.

The third hurdle had finally been passed.

Lin Ming breathed deeply, his heart still beating rapidly and his palms still wet with sweat.

This third trial was truly fierce! It had managed to find and unearth the moral flaw in his own heart of martial arts. It seems that he had been too naïve. There was no human between heaven and earth that was not without a single weakness.

“Mm. This boy has passed the hurdle. It wasn’t a short time; it took around half an incense stick of time.” An old man looked to his side where an incense burner stood. A single stick of incense in it had been burnt over halfway.

“This boy is different from Ling Sen. In Ling Sen’s trial, he only used several breaths of time, but this boy used half an incense stick. His heart was probably filled with a girl that he liked. However as it stands now, he probably won’t be able to break Ling Sen’s record.” The old man meaningfully smiled with a ‘ha-ha’ as he said this.

“Heh heh. Valiant heroes have loved beautiful woman since ancient times. This is normal. I like this normal part of a hot-blooded boy full of vigor. That young fellow Ling Sen made me feel overwhelmed; watching him only let me feel cold and uncomfortable.”

Several elder teased between themselves, because of the generational difference. Qin Xingxuan had digressed from conversation, and was peacefully sitting there while she looked at Lin Ming. In her heart a strange thought suddenly appeared; who exactly was the girl that had appeared in the dreams of Lin Ming?

The fourth trial. Lin Ming had fallen into the depths of hell. The surroundings were dark and dim. Lin Ming was immersed waist deep in a thick, crimson pool of blood. White skulls were piled high like mountains that emerged from a sea of blood. The overwhelming shrill cries of ghosts and endless devils that blotted out the sky rushed towards Lin Ming.

“Ten thousand ghosts want to stop me?” Lin Ming sneered and revolved the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’. His whole body began to shine with a brilliant golden light, and an overwhelmingly pure true essence emitted outwards.

‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ originated from the Body Transformation manuals found within the Realm of the Gods. It was said to have been created by a war-god Buddha and represented the purest light and Yang; it could pierce all evils, shatter all illusions, and cut away all demons within the heart.

Lin Ming disregarded these ghosts and demons and continued to revolve the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ to its limit.

‘My heart is at peace; not even ten-thousand evils can break me!’

Luminous golden light radiated out and all of the malicious ghosts and devils it touched disintegrated into ash!

“Damn! It’s over?”

In the five trials of the dreamland, the first tested courage, the second tested morale, the third tested temptation, the fourth tested one’s inner demons, and the fifth tested the will.

The first two trials were rather simple. The latter three were on a different level; how they appeared differed from person to person. Ling Sen had been stuck on the fourth trial that tested the demons in his heart. Perhaps it was because of Ling Sen’s bloodthirst, but the demons in his heart had been a terrifyingly difficult trial for him. Therefore he had slaughtered in that blood sea for half an incense stick of time, and only then did he barely cut away his inner demons.

“This Lin Ming; does he not have a single inner demon within his heart?”

“His heart and mind are pure. It is truly rare. Including the first four trials, only half an incense stick of time has passed. This is a good seedling,“ an old man exclaimed honestly.

…

As time went on, more and more candidates failed and appeared back on the shores of the lake. The first and second trials were easy, but from the third trial and on, the number of people being kicked out sharply rose, and the jade platform flashed with brilliant lights.

Lan Yunyue had been paying attention to Lin Ming from a distance. Lin Ming had not always been calm, but his expression was firm and did not resemble the other candidates who had fierce fighting expressions, horribly distorted faces, or were bone white.

At this moment, Lan Yunyue had a feeling that she couldn’t identify. She somehow knew that Lin Ming had passed, had crossed the trials of the dream realm, and was on the last step before the end.

The last trial of the dream. Lin Ming had still not left hell. He was still soaked in the oozing thick blood, but suddenly the blood sea became scalding hot as it bubbled.

The temperature had suddenly risen! The sanguine sea seethed with a dark fury, each bubbling pocket that burst open showered the air with a crescendo of blood. It was as if the blood sea had turned into a lake of flowing lava.

Lin Ming could distinctly feel the pain that gushed into his body; it was if he was being boiled alive in this sea of blood. Although he knew that it was merely an illusion, this kind of pain was incomparable, it was a throbbing misery that made him almost wish for death so that his suffering would end.

The first four trials were illusions, but he hadn’t anticipated that the fifth trial would be true pain. Lin Ming clenched his teeth and desperately clung to his consciousness. When he had practiced with only a tiny amount of iron thread grass to ease his pain, or when he had suffered the agonizing soul tearing pain of fusing with the soul fragment, he had shouldered the pain. This scalding sea of blood was nothing but a light summer day to him!

As Lin Ming thought this, the blood sea suddenly ignited. A combustion of black flames shot to the sky in a hellish inferno!

The flames surged towards Lin Ming. Lin Ming could clearly feel the waves of hot pressure pressing down on him. Seeing this flood of flames, an average person’s impulse would have been to feel utter and complete horror.

Lin Ming suddenly gave a ferocious shout!

“My martial arts path is like a moth to the flame, you wish for me to turn to ashes in an ocean of ten thousand flames? I couldn’t wish for anything more!”

Flames swallowed Lin Ming. In the next moment, everything turned to nothing, the world became void. Lin Ming stood up and looked around. He had returned to the jade platform. All around him were boys and girls that were grimacing in pain, or had lost all their color.

Seeing Lin Ming suddenly open his eyes and stand up, Muyi was startled. He looked at the incense burner, that incense stick still had a tiny bit left!

Frosty Ling’s record had been broken!

Qin Xingxuan was also incomparably surprised. She had experienced the five trials of this dream realm before and knew exactly how fierce and powerful they were. Although her sixth grade talent was unprecedented in Sky Fortune Kingdom, talent was not much help in passing the trials of the dream realm. Qin Xingxuan had used less than half an hour, but Lin Ming had used less than an incense stick of time before he had awoken. Anyone would think this was absolutely impossible to believe.

“Extraordinary! Extraordinary! This is the first time I have seen someone with such a heart of martial arts! Yes, what was his score in the Strength Trial?” An old man asked the beautiful lady supervisor who had been in charge for then.

“2700 jins.” Lin Ming had taken the first place in the Strength Trial, the beautiful lady supervisor remembered with certainty.

“Oh?” The old man’s moved and he eagerly asked, “What is his talent?”

Listening to the old man, before the lady supervisor had even replied,  Muyi had already said, “Grade three medium.”

“Only grade three?” The only man was surprised, and he began to shake in disappointment and sighed, “What a pity, what a pity!” A grade three talent wasn’t too bad, but it was inferior to the prodigies of the Seven Profound Martial House.

However Muyi said. “Sometimes talent isn’t everything. Just you wait and see, that Lin Ming is a dragon among humans.”

Muyi said this with confidence. When he had first seen Lin Ming’s talent grade, he had been greatly surprised and had thought that there had been some sort of mistake. But he knew that Lin Ming already had a great achievement that many people in their entire lives could not hope to reach. Since that mysterious elder had chosen Lin Ming, then Lin Ming must have extraordinary talents that he could not see!

Though Muyi spoke with confidence, the other man only shook his head. The role that talent played in a martial artist’s future was too vital and important. It was pivotal for their future achievements. With a medium grade-three talent, even if this boy had massive financial support backing him, he would only end up stuck at the Pulse Condensation Stage.

As Lin Ming left the stage, Lan Yunyue who had been distantly looking at Lin Ming, had eyes full of complex emotions. She had long known that Lin Ming’s will was firm and steady, but did not expect that he would have passed the dream trials so quickly.

She also now knew that for Lin Ming to give up the martial arts path was impossible. His own determination had reached the highest limit.

After Lin Ming left the jade platform, he was led to the resting lounge where he would later be escorted to the final trial - the Exquisite Pagoda.

Chapter 39 - Unstoppable Force

There were many floors to pass; Lin Ming could not afford to waste his energy and stamina. He had to rush to the top in a single leap and take the first place reward - the Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill!

Seeing Lin Ming flying at him, the shadow warrior raised his staff to block him. But Lin Ming was too fast and before the staff had been raised to his chest, a hard fist had already imprinted itself onto its chest.

“Peng!”

The shadow warrior’s chest collapsed and it spat blood, before it fell over dead.

Lin Ming easily passed the first floor. This was natural, as Lin Ming’s strength had greatly surpassed those of the same cultivation.

Onto the second floor!

This was still a black space like before, but this time a vicious beast stood in front of Lin Ming.

“A first-level vicious beast!”

A first-level vicious beast was equivalent to a martial artist at the Third Stage of Body Transformation. This beast was a single-horned rhinoceros. Its strength as a first-level vicious beast was relatively poor; it was about as strong as a peak Second Stage martial artist.

Although its strength was rather ordinary, it had superior defensive abilities due to its tough hide. Even if a martial artist greatly exceeded it in strength and cultivation, they must still expend some effort to defeat it.

Lin Ming had to overcome several obstacles and did not want to waste his stamina. His hand turned, and a chilly deboning knife appeared in his palm. In Lin Ming’s mind appeared the single-horned rhinoceros’ blood vessels and body structure, with each of its weaknesses clear as day.

Lin Ming’s advantage was his familiarity with the weaknesses of vicious beasts.

The single-horned rhinoceros suddenly roared, and trampled towards Lin Ming. Although this was an illusionary realm, Lin Ming felt a rumbling vibration in the ground.

An illusion array was not the same as a killing array. In an illusion array, the illusions didn’t have the power to kill you, they could also cause you to feel fear. As long as you kept your heart and mind and stood your ground, then the illusion would shatter. But a killing array was different; standing still would only be suicide.

As he watched the single-horned rhinoceros barrel towards him, Lin Ming suddenly leapt to one side. His jumping posture was odd. His body was parallel with the ground and one of his shoulders nearly touched the dirt. In the next moment, the huge body of the single-horned rhinoceros passed by him. Lin Ming slammed his hand against the ground and the force propelled him underneath the beast’s abdomen.

He raised his hand and slashed with the knife!

“Puff!”

The boning knife struck just half a foot up from the center of the single-horned rhinoceros’ front thigh. This exact spot was the softest patch on the beast’s abdomen, and was also where its abdominal aorta was located.

The knife slid in like butter and gouged out the beast. A stream of blood jetted out like a broken pipe and the single-horned rhino let loose a keening anguished howl. The vicious beast trembled fiercely and then fell to the ground.

Seeing the success of his knife strike, Lin Ming was unable to restrain a sigh as he thought of how lifelike and realistic this magic array was. The single-horned rhinoceros phantom had a body structure and weaknesses just like a real single-horned rhinoceros. He thought that perhaps the magic array had a beast spirit of the single-horned rhinoceros sealed inside, thus its potent realism.

After the successful knife strike, Lin Ming pulled back instead of taking another cut. Although killing the single-horned rhinoceros at this point was not difficult anymore, he wanted to save his stamina. There was no resting between the floors of the Exquisite Pagoda.

The aorta had been cut open, and the single-horned rhinoceros was losing more and more blood. Its movements began to slow, but this time Lin Ming waited for another opportunity and slashed his knife down again. There was a ‘puff!’ sound and the abdominal aorta on the other side of the single-horned rhinoceros was also cut!

The fight has lost its suspense, it was only a matter of waiting now. The single-horned rhinoceros thrashed about as it teetered back and forth on the edge of death, until it unwillingly went still.

Lin Ming had entered the third floor!

“Oh? Someone has entered the third floor!” Outside the Exquisite Pagoda, several elders had seen that the runes and symbols on the third floor began to move and light up. The third floor was activating, but they did not know who it was that had entered.

“It should be Wang Yanfeng. He is strongest in consideration of his age. Lin Ming’s strength lies in his martial heart and in his inborn divine strength. In terms of combat prowess, strength is only a small part. Speed, skill, and fighting techniques are not any less important than strength alone.”

“Most of the candidates are still stuck on the first floor. That Wang Yanfeng has already rushed up to the third floor is impressive.”

As these elders discussed, another person had reached the third floor. This person was only thirty breaths slower than Lin Ming. This person was Wang Yanfeng.

Wang Yanfeng and Lin Ming were similar in age, and the opponents they fought on the second floor were the same; both were first-level vicious beasts that were equal to the peak of the Second Stage of Body Transformation.

Wang Yanfeng was at the early Third Stage of Body Transformation. Not only that, but his combat strength exceeded that of those his age. The vicious beast was not his match, but its skin was coarse and its meat thick and tough. Wang Yanfeng had spent much of his true essence to defeat it.

There was no rest in the Exquisite Pagoda. On the third floor, Wang Yanfeng now came head to head with two dark and shadowy humanoid figures holding two long swords. These shadow warriors were at the early Third Stage of Body Transformation.

Wang Yanfeng gritted his teeth and maintained his dignified demeanor. He could deal with these two warriors, but he also had to think carefully about how to use his true essence, otherwise breaking through to the fourth floor would become increasingly difficult.

He had to make this as quick a victory as possible. He began to revolve the true essence within his entire body, and prepared the display martial skill handed down in his family, the ‘Nine Paths of Truth’.

…

At this time, Lin Ming also confronted two early Third Stage shadow warriors on the third floor.

The Third Stage of Body Transformation was Viscera Training. He hadn’t anticipated that he would face something of this level at only the third floor. And there were also two! The difficulty of the fourth and fifth floors could only be imagined and there was no rest allowed between them. No wonder the middle-aged man had so confidently said that the fifth floor was impossible to pass.

While Lin Ming revolved the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, he also cautiously kept the two shadow warriors in his line of sight. For now, the two were motionless. He would be glad to this moment to recover just a bit, although he had not spent that much true essence.

But the two warriors did not give Lin Ming the chance. In a single leap they both reached him, one attacked from the left and one attacked from the right, both with vicious killing intent.

The two warriors were amazingly swift and had teamwork. Their movements seemed to be in harmony with each other like two halves of a whole. One warrior swept the ground with his long sword. Lin Ming jumped to dodge the strike, but the other warrior took advantage of Lin Ming as he was twisting in the air and stabbed his sword towards Lin Ming’s chest.

“Ha!”

Lin Ming cried out and suddenly shot his foot out towards the warrior’s wrist. “Kacha!” The warrior’s wrist broke with a single kick!

However the shadow warriors did not feel any pain. The shadow warrior only shook his wrist and sent an open palm flying towards Lin Ming. Every movement he made left him wide open! These shadow warriors could only aggress; they could not defend or retreat. This was a suicidal form of fighting which wished for both sides to perish!

This moment was where Lin Ming’s old strength would have perished, but he had a new strength now. Seeing his opponent fight with such a self-destructive style, he forcefully revolved the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ and forced his true essence to the forefront. A punch went flying out that intersected with the shadow warrior’s palm.

“Peng!” The shadow warrior was forced back a few steps and spat out a mouthful of blood.

But Lin Ming’s vitality only swelled up. It was easy to force them down and he didn’t even have a single injury. Even so, he was secretly surprised. These two shadow warriors may not have been top tier martial artists but they were not weak either. Their close cooperation and kamikaze fighting style were really tricky and difficult to deal with. And this was only the third floor; there was still the fourth and fifth.

Although he was surprised, Lin Ming had not stopped moving for a single half second. He had landed back from the recoil, and while the injured shadow warrior was catching his breath, he slammed his fist straight into the shadow warrior’s face.

Now the other shadow warrior rushed to intercept him. He wielded his long sword in his hands and cleaved downwards. This strike was to cut Lin Ming in half.

“Ha! Now it’s you! Die!”

Lin Ming’s fist was only a feint. He suddenly turned around with the deboning knife in hand and made a horizontal cut on the shadow warrior’s blade.

“Boom!” Sparks scattered everywhere as the blades met.

As the knife met the sword, Lin Ming had not been forced back. This was a reflection of his astonishing physical strength!

“Be defeated by me!”

After Lin Ming fended off the long sword, he punched out at the center of the shadow warrior’s chest!

“Peng!” There was a dull thud as the opponent’s ribs collapsed, took a fatal blow to the heart, and died on the spot.

After defeating one, the other was already injured and no longer a threat. Lin Ming set out several kicks at the last shadow warrior’s legs, and then stabbed him with the knife.

The third floor, passed!

Outside the Exquisite Pagoda the elders saw the magic array of the fourth floor light up and they were startled. “My goodness, the fourth floor, and it only took half an incense stick of time!”

Chapter 40 - Break Through The Fourth Floor

Outside of the Exquisite Pagoda, the elders saw the magic array of the fourth floor light up and they were startled. “My goodness, the fourth floor, and it only took half an incense stick of time!”

“This Wang Yanfeng, he’s not simple.” These elders had already expected Wang Yanfeng to reach the fourth floor, but hadn’t anticipated that he would do it so quickly. “At such speed, perhaps Wang Yanfeng can break through the fourth floor and step into the fifth. Certainly I had thought that the fifth floor was impossible, but he should be proud even with this result.”

“I just don’t know how Lin Ming and Liang Tieshan will perform. Those two’s results weren’t too bad. Liang Tieshen was the tall and burly youth who had inborn divine strength. He was also fifteen years old.

Lin Ming and Liang Tieshan were fifteen years old, had cultivation at the Second Stage of Body Transformation, and also had inborn divine strength. This kind of power at their age was definitely impressive.

However in the eyes of the numerous elders, if these two were compared to Wang Yanfeng, there was still a gap.

That Lin Ming had inborn divine strength was not wrong, but he was only at the Second Stage of Body Transformation. Wang Yanfeng was at the Third Stage of Body Transformation. The main characteristic of the Third Stage was infusing true essence into the visceral organs. Viscera Training martial artists’ heart and lungs would be empowered. Their breaths would be long and their endurance double that of a Second Stage martial artist.

Without a doubt, Wang Yanfeng also had superior technique and speed. Even looking at strength, Wang Yanfeng’s record was only 300 less than Lin Ming; the disparity was not too great.

For this third trial, if there was no accident, then Wang Yanfeng would take first place.

The third trial also accounted for the largest proportion when it came to the final evaluation. If Wang Yanfeng came out first in the third trial, that in addition to his talent would surpass Lin Ming, and the entrance exam’s first place would belong to him.

However at this moment, the truth was that Wang Yanfeng was struggling at the third floor. These two martial artists were difficult to deal with, for every few moves they traded, he would encounter one that threatened his life. Wang Yanfeng used a tremendous amount of strength and true essence to defeat one, but had also suffered a minor injury.

“Damnit, how is this so freakish. Even with the ‘Nine Paths of Truth’ that is passed down in my family I only managed to kill one. It seems that chances of reaching the fourth floor are getting less and less certain.” Wang Yanfeng worried; he had already consumed 20% of his inner true essence. In this dreamland he was unable to supplement it with pills or drugs. He could only depend on his Third Stage viscera training to supplement his energy bit by bit.

…

Wang Yanfeng was anxious over his true essence consumption rate, but Lin Ming was also worrying over the same reason. He was not at Viscera Training, but was only at the Second Stage of Body Transformation, Flesh Training. He did not have excessive vitality and his every move consumed more true essence.

Luckily, Lin Ming had the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ and had achieved the small success of the first stage. This ancient skill revolved within him, it allowed him to supplement his true essence with an unceasing supply. Although he could not use it endlessly, it was still able to alleviate the intense pressure he felt.

This time in front of Lin Ming, the opponents were two first-level vicious beasts - Iron Armor Bears.

There were strong and weak first-level vicious beasts. The Single Horned Rhinoceros was weak; it was only equal to a peak Second Stage martial artist. But this Iron Armor Bear was actually equal to a peak Third Stage martial artist. Not only that, but there were two.

Lin Ming was solemn. Before this he had never fought against an opponent at the peak of the Third Stage. He did not have complete confidence in victory in defeating one, and not to mention this was a pair.

But most importantly was that this battle had two strict conditions. First, he could not use up his limited true essence. Second, he could not receive a single injury.

Lin Ming took a steadying breath as he recalled every detail he knew about the Iron Armor Bear.

The Iron Armor Bear’s strength was 5000 jins. Its speed was a bit slow, but the entire body was covered in thick plates of bone armor. A sword or spear would find it hard to penetrate this carapace, and it did not have any specific weakness.

Although he knew that the armor did not have any weaknesses, Lin Ming knew that the Iron Armor Bear itself had a weakness, and that was that between the numerous intersections and crosses of the bone armor were a few small slits.

The slits were located at the joints. They were thin and hard to target; if he wanted to strike at these places in the heat of battle, he must open his eyes to his insight and utilize instantaneous judgement and peerless accuracy to have a chance.

But after practicing the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, Lin Ming’s perception had risen to a new level and his judgement and accuracy had been fostered steadily by his years of deboning.

“Zhu Yan should have easily been able to deal with these two Iron Armor Bears half a year ago, not to mention now Zhu Yan must have progressed. I can’t lose to him like this.”

Lin Ming stared at the two Iron Armor Bears and his fighting spirit began to rise in his heart.

“Hu!”

An Iron Armor Bear suddenly leapt upwards and smashed its thick, heavy paws at Lin Ming.

The Iron Armor Bear weighed over a thousand jins. Coupled with its awesome strength, this strike would have even felled an elephant!

Lin Ming’s eyes widened and he did not retreat. Instead, like a graceful bird that flew with grace and poise, he passed by the Iron Armor Bear. His eye’s focused onto a point of the bear’s abdomen where two bone armor plates joined with each other and struck out with his knife!

“!”

It was only a simple deboning knife, but Lin Ming had practiced its strokes tens of thousands of times. The knife accurately slid between the two bone armor plates. The knife was quick, and with only a slight hitch in the thick flesh, it slid through with extreme speed.

As soon as the blow struck, before the time it takes to snap a finger, blood shot into the air.

“Rahh!” The Iron Armor Bear became mad. The knife wound had not been fatal and it rushed crazily at Lin Ming!

…

“Less than forty people have been eliminated and more than fifty have passed. This is a decent result.” A Seven Profound Martial House elder slowly said as he watched the candidates who had been kicked from the Exquisite Pagoda.

The Exquisite Pagoda was completely sealed from the outside. The elders were not Xiantian experts and had no way to see what was happening inside the Exquisite Pagoda. They could only judge how far the candidates had gone by which layer they had been ejected from.

If they were ejected from the first floor then they were eliminated, and if they were ejected from the second then they passed.

A quarter of an hour had passed since the candidates had entered the Exquisite Pagoda, and all of them had long since passed the first floor. Some had arrived on the third floor and some were even challenging the fourth.

“Now only five people have not yet come out.” As an elder said this, the symbols began to flash on the Exquisite Pagoda and another two candidates were kicked out. They had been ejected from the third floor, so they had failed at the third floor.

Several martial artists had already ran up and were caring for the unconscious candidates.

These two candidates were at the peak of the Third Stage of Body Transformation and their strength results had been 2300 jins. Unfortunately they were also seventeen and eighteen. They had not been able to break through the third floor of the Exquisite Pagoda, but they were also proud of their results.

When these two people were ejected, Lan Yunyue immediately turned to them and instantly distinguished that they were not Lin Ming.

Out of the 92 candidates that had entered so far, 39 had already been ejected from the Exquisite Pagoda. Lan Yanyue could clearly see that these people did not include Lin Ming. That could only mean that Lin Ming was still within the Exquisite Pagoda!

Lin Ming… Lan Yunyue lightly nipped her lips as he eyes glazed over with memories.

She knew that this meant that Lin Ming had passed, and was at least at the third floor.

The third floor was in truth an enormous glory. In the school records of the Seven Profound Martial House, those that passed the third floor would one day achieve the peak of Body Transformation, the Sixth Stage of Pulse Condensation.

The Royal Government would bestow upon all those martial artists of the Pulse Condensation Period a rank and title within the kingdom. Although it was only a third-class viscount, it was not that different from an official position and was even hereditary.

This was a noble title! In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, this was a symbol of glory and of the aristocracy. Because of a single person’s personal glory, their family would enter the lineage of the aristocracy and bring honor to their ancestors.

Just then, another candidate was expelled from the fourth floor.

This meant that Lin Ming had passed the third floor!

This tall and sturdy boy with thick features was the boy with inborn divine strength, Liang Tieshan. He had put forth his utmost effort and after taking a severe wound had broke to the third floor and was defeated nearly upon arrival.

“This Liang Tieshen is a good seedling. He’s worth cultivating with resources.”

“Mm., he’s quite good. Now there are two left, Lin Ming and Wang Yanfeng.”

“That Lin Ming can persist even with his present strength is not easy. His strength is greater compared to Liang Tieshan’s and he also has a strong heart of martial arts that helps him. But to break through the fourth floor is uncertain…”

“Mmm, let alone Lin Ming, even Wang Yanfeng will not find it easy.”

…

“Poh!” With a single stroke from his knife, blood shot out from the leg of the Iron Armor Bear. Lin Ming tumbled away as the angry Iron Armor Bear pounced on him.

By now, the two Iron Armor Bears had become Blood Bears. They each had several more knife cuts across the weak points between their armor plates. While the wounds were not fatal, loss of blood could quickly become deadly!

The motion of these two Iron Armor Bears had obviously slowed down from excessive blood loss.

Chance!

Lin Ming dodged around the two bears who tried to catch him. Their blood loss and exhaustion exposed openings in their defense, and Lin Ming sprung upwards like a cheetah.

“Roar!” The Iron Armored Bear stood up on its hind legs and threw a strike with its paws. But Lin Ming had already escaped, and while evading at the same time, Lin Ming directly stabbed his deboning knife into the Iron Armor Bear’s eye!

Blood splashed from the grisly wound and the Iron Armor Bear let out an angry and painful roar. Lin Ming closed his hand into a fist and punched down on the handle like a jackhammer, and the deboning knife sunk directly into the brains of the beast.

The Iron Armor Bear died!

Chapter 54 - Unfair Gambling Bets

Although the words were pleasant, the provocative meaning behind them was too obvious. Lin Ming frowned. He turned his head to see that the man who spoke was the other youth who had stood beside Liu Mingxiang and Wang Yanfeng, the young man with immeasurably deep strength.

This youth wore an entirely blue outfit, and in his hand he carried a long and narrow saber as wide as three fingers. It had a very short handle and did not have a hand guard, the blade was directly attached to the hilt.

Among martial artists, the number that used sabers was very few compared to the number who used swords. Lin Ming paid attention to this; with such a short hilt it would not be easy to wield. The saber didn’t have a handle guard so their hand would be easily injured by the opponent. But, there was a benefit to this. The saber could display the fastest speed possible; it paid the price of sacrificing defense to pursue the limit of rapid attacks. To even dare to do such a rash thing, it proved that this youth’s saber was extremely strong.

Perhaps this youth might even be fiercer than Liu Mingxiang. Lin Ming stayed on alert, because even if someone was arrogant, he would never look down on them. He hesitated for a second and then asked, “What do you want?”

“Nothing. I just wanted to experience the majesty and grandeur of the first place candidate. Have I misread, is your cultivation only at the Second Stage of Body Transformation?”

“Gee, this year’s candidates are just so bad. A Second Stage Body Transformation boy could actually achieve first place. What rank of talent are you?” Liu Mingxiang echoed. The truth was that he had already inquired earlier and knew everything there was to know. Lin Ming was only a medium third-grade talent. This talent may have been decent outside of the Seven Profound Martial House, but in the Seven Profound Martial House, it was the lowest of the low. He had intentionally asked this to provoke Lin Ming.

“What does my rank of talent have to do with you?” Lin Ming coolly replied.  He knew that these two boys were just coveting his true essence stones and wanted to provoke his anger into making a gambling match with him as they had with Wang Yanfeng.

In Sky Fortune Kingdom, the authorities would not involve themselves in the scuffles between martial artists, because even if they had the mind to, there was no way they were capable of doing so. Therefore, the solution was a gambling on the martial arts duels. As long as both parties mutually consented, and agreed upon the conditions and prizes of victory, then the loser could not pursue afterwards.

This sort of proposition was very popular; even the Seven Profound Martial House was no exception.

“Hehe, of course it has nothing to do with me, I had only heard some rumors that brother Lin is a medium third-grade. I just felt this to be a bit strange. Although all the candidates of the recent entrance examination are trash, how could a useless, good-for-nothing piece of sh*t like you achieve first place?”

It may have been some hypocritical double talk at first, but these words directly had no consideration for face. In the view of these two youths, Lin Ming was just a small boy, to step on him, they did not even need to bother faking anything.

Lin Ming gave a frosty look and quipped, “You do this sort of thing in the Seven Profound Martial House? You depend on conniving and stealing a new disciple’s true essence stones to barely maintain your own pathetic and feeble existence? To do such shameful things, it’s best that you leave this place early, you are only losing face for your family.”

“Little boy! You’re courting death!” The youth’s complexion sank, “You are just some third-grade talent trash! Dog sh*t like you only managed to luck your way into the Seven Profound Martial House by eating some rare material! In my eyes, you are even less than dog shit!”

Listening to such vicious words, Lin Ming knit his brows, and felt his heart move to anger, “I originally didn’t want to meddle too much, but this is fine. Yes, this is fine. Since you really want to stir things up and make a gambling match with me, then if that’s the case…”

“Lin Ming!” At that moment a voice sounded from behind Lin Ming’s back. “Don’t fall into their trap!”

Lin Ming turned his head around to look and saw Lin Wu and Lin Fengyuan jogging towards him. The man who had spoken up and interrupted him was Lin Wu; his complexion wasn’t too good. These two were tricky. Concerning their family, Liu Mingxiang’s Liu Family was not inferior to their Lin Family. But when discussing strength, he was simply not a match for these two.

“Lin Wu, if you’re smart then you’ll immediately get the hell out of the way.” The youth with a saber coldly snorted and his entire body exuded a faint murderous intent. The boy’s saber was affected by this murderous aura and began to faintly ring.

This young man had already become one with his saber!

Lin Ming remembered, if a martial artist was able to become one with their weapon and communicate with it, that weapon would be able to sense its master’s intentions and true essence, and thus have such a response. This kind of boundary needed an extremely high level of talent and perception, as well as carefully cultivating a treasure. This was not something Wang Yanfeng could compare with. Although Wang Yanfeng also had a rare treasure, but when had usually used it, Lin Ming was able to see that it was full of flaws, and thus had been able to break through his martial skill with only a first.

Moreover this person had such a thick murderous intent; he had probably killed many people before. Such a person would not be easy to handle.

Lin Ming frowned. Whether this guy or Lin Mingxiang, they both appeared to be arrogant idiots with no brains, but they were actually hidden masters. He was definitely not their match.

Lin Wu was forced back by this strong murdering intent, and his complexion became increasingly ugly. Although he was also in the Earth Hall, his ranking was far behind these two, and was simply not their opponent. To make conflict with these two youths was absolutely unwise. He pulled Lin Ming sleeve and whispered to him, “Lin Ming, let’s go.”

“You want to leave? Haha! Lin Wu, you truly are worthy of the title cowardly turtle! I thought it was strange, how could a weak little coward like you infiltrate the Seven Profound Martial Hall’s Earth Hall! Is Green Mulberry City’s Lin Family a family that specially cultivates turtles? Especially cowardly turtles?”

Lin Wu lost his temper facing this unscrupulous ridicule, especially since it involved his family. He just couldn’t bear this! He grasped his sword and stepped forward, but was stopped by Lin Ming. Lin Ming could see that Lin Wu was not this person’s match.

“Don’t be so impulsive. They came for me. A gambling fight isn’t too bad.”

“Haha! How straightforward and refreshing! This elder brother may as well be the little brother, heh heh. List the time and place you want.” The youth said as he laughed with an arrogant smile.

Lin Wu urgently said, “Lin Ming, don’t be tricked by him. The guy came for your true essence stones. His name Zhang Cang, he is at the peak of Viscera Training! And he is also half a step into the Altering Muscle stage. This person’s blade work is astonishing. His Ranking Stone place is 109, do you even know what sort of existence the 109th place is? A new disciple at Seven Profound Martial House who can enter above 180 is already rare. Even Ling Sen, Ta Ku, Zhang Guanyu and other characters like them that used to be first place candidates could not go above 130!”

Ling Sen? Ling Ming naturally knew this person. He was the elder senior apprentice of the Heavenly Abode. If he didn’t factor in the several core disciples, then Ling Sen would be first place among everyone in the Seven Profound Martial Hall! His battle prowess might even surpass Qin Xingxuan!

Although he hadn’t heard of Ta Ku and Zhang Guanyu, he guessed they were the same ruthlessly strong type like Ling Sen, and probably weren’t too far off from him.

Lin Wu continued, “This Zhang Cang is the top character among those in the Earth Hall. After some time he will probably enter the Heavenly Abode too, there is just no hope of winning for you.”

Lin Ming replied, “Elder brother, I know.”

Lin Wu anxiously said, “Why are you so obstinate! You don’t know where things stand! I know that you are strong and can fight someone at the peak of the Third Stage of Body Transformation, but which one of the disciples of the Seven Profound Martial House’s Earth Hall is not a genius? You can fight others above your rank, and others cannot? With Zhang Cang’s strength, outside of the Seven Profound Martial House not even martial artists at the peak of the Fourth Stage of Body Transformation are necessarily his match!”

What Lin Wu said was not wrong. The Seven Profound Martial House was where all the talented geniuses converged and gathered together. Daily battles among them were not uncommon. Although Lin Ming’s current physical strength was comparable to someone at the Fourth Stage of Body Transformation and the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ was potent, it still was too difficult for Lin Ming to fight a fellow genius who was two stages above him.

As Lin Wu spoke, Zhang Cang crossed his arms over his chest as he watched with a grinning smile.

“Are you done discussing? Are you going to be a little turtle or are you going to bet with me?”

Lin Ming opened his mouth and said, “You don’t need provoke me, there is no significance in stirring things up. I only want to know, what sort of gambling stakes will be involved?”

Chapter 62 - The Final Grade

“This wound isn’t light!” Lin Ming revolved the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ to suppress the injury, but it still bled.

“The wound’s bleeding. My strength will slowly fall… it’s impossible to wage a battle of attrition. If that is the case…” Lin Ming’s eyes were cold as he locked onto an early Altering Muscle martial artist and the Crystal Backed Spider. “You two, I’m going to put my life on the line to kill you both. I will make the most of my remaining strength in the time I have left to obtain the biggest victory I can and try for my highest possible final score.”

“Spear, to me!”

As Lin Ming thought this, the rows of weapons that had disappeared before reappeared in front of him. An overlord spear appeared in Lin Ming’s hand.

“It turned out to be the overlord spear!”

This overlord spear was crafted with potent darksteel. Such a spear sacrificed its elasticity in exchange for devastatingly destructive power!

The overlord spear’s shaft was eight feet in length and the spear head was eight inches long. The barrel was thick as an arm, and because it was made with heavy darksteel, the spear’s total weight was 580 jins. With a sweep of the spear, even trees would be smashed apart.

Lin Ming’s arm strength was 3200 jins; wielding this heavy spear was just right.

“Good spear!” Lin Ming laughed out loud as soon as he saw it. He tightly gripped the overlord spear and swept outwards in a great arc. A martial artist at the early Third Stage, not realizing the change in circumstances, raised a sword to block the strike, but was only sent flying backwards!

“Hah!” Lin Ming shouted out and his entire body erupted in an imposing aura. A surge of overwhelming Yang aura covered the entire area as it blotted out the sky with killing intent. The group of over ten strong enemies were stunned by this cry, and were unexpectedly so shaken that they dared not step forward.

The floor beneath Lin Ming shattered as he slammed his feet against the ground and shot forward like a beam of light. With an unbelievably imposing aura and a 580 jin overlord spear in hand, he thrust out at the Crystal Backed Spider.”

“Hiss!” The Crystal Backed Spider reacted and spat out spider silk straight at Lin Ming’s chest. This spider silk could bind a human and it was also keenly sharp! It may not seem like an arrow, but it could pierce through a person’s body!

Even a master at the Altering Muscle stage could only evade when facing this spider’s silk. But once dodged, the Crystal Backed Spider could also retreat and continue its long-range attack.

Lin Ming did not dodge or evade; he ran at the spider silk and cut towards it with the overlord spear! How slender and thin was the spider’s silk? The spearpoint was only a point, hitting it at high speed was easier said than done!

Although Lin Ming didn’t know marksmanship, he had spent years delicately working with a deboning knife; with his keen eyes he had accumulated experience and precision. With just this, he had defeated Wang Yanfeng’s ‘Nine Paths of Truth’ with just his fist!

But regardless of whether it was a fist or deboning knife, with this 580 jin overlord spear in hand, it was essentially no different than wielding anything else!

“Break for me!” Lin Ming angrily shouted. The overlord spear hit the spider’s silk. The spider silk was quick like an arrow, but its weight was actually like fluttering cotton. The 580 jin overlord spear meeting the spider’s silk was like a galloping horse running into a fly.

Its momentum not reducing at all, the overlord spear thrust straight into the Crystal Backed Spider’s eight eyes!

The Crystal Backed Spider hadn’t expected that its silk would be blocked by a spear. At this moment it was vulnerable to the cold, killing point of the spear!

Speed was not a Crystal Backed Spider’s strength. Its true power lay in its armored body, and its defensive abilities were comparable to stone pillars. It usually depended on this amazing defensive power to keep off its enemies.

But even so, how could it block the 580 jins overlord spear that was combined with Lin Ming’s 3200 jin strength?

“Pah!” The Crystal Backed Spider had no idea at all as its brain was pierced by Lin Ming’s spear!

“Tsee Tsee Tsee!” The spider that was as big as a small cow was nailed to the ground with its eight legs still twitching. A single spear had killed the enemy!

Green mucus liquid shot out as Lin Ming pulled out his spear and rushed towards the other Altering Muscle martial artists to kill them. However at this moment, there was faint sensation at the back of Lin Ming’s mind, as if a poisonous viper was preparing to strike at him from behind.

He dodge to the side, and a shining electric light ripped through the ground where he had been.

Martial Skill?!

Lin Ming immediately turned his head. Behind him was a phantom man holding a longsword and wearing a bamboo hat.

“Peak of Altering Muscle!”

This enemy was the one that appeared after he killed the Crystal Backed Spider! Not only did its cultivation reach the peak of Altering Muscle, but it could also use martial skills.

Seeing that his enemy was someone at the peak of Altering Muscle, Lin Ming’s heart was filled with a surge of heroic pride. This was the first time he had fought an enemy at the peak of Altering Muscle!

…

“Wasn’t Lin Ming injured? Why hasn’t he finished by now?

“This guy is too tough, the third incense stick is already half burned! After he was injured he still managed to last another half stick of incense!”

“There are only six people left on stage. The last person’s result was 139.  It’s incredible that he is continuing to persist in there!” Most of the present audience didn’t want others to succeed.

“This Lin Ming is already injured. It’s inevitable that his battle prowess will drop. Even if he’s managing to stay in there because of his own stubborness, it’s not known how many points he could have gotten.”

As these people talked, two people on the altar gave a cough, apparently seriously injured. They were unable to last any longer and were shot out by the altar. One of them was shockingly Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was pale, and his every breath was heavy. Overall his performance this time was not perfect, or he would have been able to advance a few more ranks. But he didn’t care. At his final moments he was able to wield a spear to slaughter his enemies, including two enemies at the early Altering Muscle stage. He had immensely benefitted from such a fierce battle.

“Lin Ming finally came out. It took two and a half incense sticks of time; it’s not too unreasonable.”

“Mmm. Looks like he will be able to enter the top 150 ranks. The Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill and Golden Scarlet Snake Pill are truly incomparably wonderful medicines. This boy was similar to Wang Yanfeng just a few days ago, but now after taking these two wonderful medicines he’s at this level, yah, it would be great if I could eat it too.” The crowd said. Many were envious and could not mentally accept Lin Ming’s results.

At this moment the Ranking Stone magic array flashed. The first light was a person who had come out at the same time as Lin Ming. After the flash, his name appeared in the 136th ranking. After the youth saw this result he was utterly ecstatic. He was only 17 years old and had practiced martial arts for two and a half years at the Seven Profound Martial House. To have this result was quite good.

Then, Lin Ming’s name flashed, and it suddenly vanished from the original place at the 210 ranking. More than 100 pairs of eyes were staring at the stone tablet as it updated the results.

The Ranking Stone had altogether 23 rows. Each row had ten names. Most people’s eyes were looking at the 15th row, as this was the ranking of 140 to 150 and it was where Lin Ming’s name would most likely appear.

However this section of the magic array’s image was tranquil like water and did not have the slightest change.

“Mmm?”

It was too late for anyone to feel surprise. The Ranking Stone’s 13th row actually fluctuated. The 125th rank and 126th rank were pulled apart by an invisible force, and then the two characters ‘Lin Ming’ impressively appeared among them.

Lin Ming. Rank 126!!

Chapter 65 - The Heavy Spear, Penetrating Rainbow

When they entered the second floor, there was suddenly far less people. There was a huge space with only a few customers milling around. A pessimistic middle-aged man wearing a long, grey robe was sitting behind the counter drinking a cup of tea.

The sales clerk gave a respectful salute to the middle-aged man, then walked over and said a few words in his ear.

“Oh? This young hero must choose such a heavy spear shaft?” The middle-aged asked with interest as he looked at Lin Ming, “How heavy a spear shaft were you looking for?”

“800 jins.”

“800 jins?” The middle-aged man’s eyes flashed a glint of light. “An 800 jin spear would take at least 4000 jins of strength to use. Can you?”

Lin Ming said, “Even if I can’t freely wield it now, I will be able to later.”

“How bold! I will look for a spear shaft for you.”

The middle-aged man stood up and moved to the side. A moment later, he returned, carrying a long wooden chest. Although he appeared as if he was taking light steps, Lin Ming discovered that every step the middle-aged man took on the wood paneled floor would cause a creaking sound. The wood panels were unable withstand the weight of the load that the man was carrying.

The wooden chest in his hands was clearly very heavy!

The middle-aged man placed the wooden case on the counter and flipped open the lid. Inside was an eight foot shaft wrapped in a thick cloth strip.

The middle-aged man unraveled the cloth strip, suddenly revealing a dark purple shaft and a deep red spear head. On the dark purple shaft’s body was engraved two characters that were written in inscription symbols - “Penetrating Rainbow.”

The two plain words combined with the massive spear shaft made it feel as if there was a boundless gas rushing out.

Good spear!

The middle-aged man said, “This spear is named the Penetrating Rainbow. Its shaft is eight feet long and the head is eight inches long. It is a half-treasure.”

“Mmm? Half-treasure?”

The middle-aged man said, “Only the spearhead is a treasure, the spear shaft is not, thus it is a half treasure.”

Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened. The crafting process that went into the spear shaft was complex; therefore it was too difficult to place an array on it. But the spearhead was the same as a sword or a knife, so it was easy to set an array on it and make it into a treasure.

But alas, it was impossible to connect his true essence through the spear shaft due to it lacking an array, so its power was greatly reduced.

The middle-aged man said, “Although the spear shaft is not a treasure, but if comparing the toughness, it could be equal to an ordinary human-step low-grade treasure.”

The difference between a treasure and an ordinary weapon was that that a treasure was inscribed with an array, and thus one could channel their true essence into it. It was not a fact that a treasure would be more durable or solid than an ordinary weapon.

This weapon could not concentrate true essence. During an actual fight, as soon as martial skills were displayed, the disparity between the two would be evident. The treasure would be a step more powerful than an ordinary weapon.

The middle-aged man continued, “This spear shaft was forged with dark purple elastic iron, and the spearhead was made from cloud vein wrought iron. Both sides of the spear’s edge have been mixed with profound gold and are incomparably sharp. The spearhead and spear shaft originally came as a pair, they cannot be separated. The total weight is 820 jins.”

Dark purple elastic iron?

When Lin Ming had attended the lecture, he had heard the elder talk about this strange metal. This wonderful metal was unmatched in weight and also had a high degree of elasticity to it. It was even used to make strong bows. With a bow made from it, combined with the sinews from a high-level vicious beast to make the bowstring, it could easily project an arrow 2000 steps away and pierce fine steel plates!

If this dark purple elastic iron was used to make a spear shaft, even the thick spear shaft would be able to bend into a half-moon and snap back with enough force to crack open a tree. If a martial artist with 5000 jins of strength shook it, even the light vibration from the oscillations alone could kill a person.

However, for all its thousands or tens of thousands of good points, dark purple elastic iron had to be hammered innumerable times during its molding in order to forge it. It was impossible to inscribe an array upon it, as an array could not be hammered. Therefore this metal could not be used to make treasure weapons.

Even so, dark purple elastic iron was cherished and loved by many refiner masters, because it was just too great and fitting a material to make a spear or strong bow with.

Lin Ming took this spear shaft made from dark purple elastic iron into his hand. He  shook it a bit, and all along the spear shaft it began to quiver. But the quivering was not too intense, because Lin Ming’s strength was insufficient and could not shake the dark purple elastic iron.

Even so, the middle-aged man was suddenly startled. This young boy! What an abnormal strength! If he could still shake the spear like that, his strength must not be less than 3000 jins! And he was only at the peak of the Second Stage of Body Transformation, what a good physique he had!

Lin Ming made a few spear movements with his hand. Even if he was able to raise a 820 jin spear easily into his hand, he could not wave it around with a high degree of fluidity. If he fought with such a weapon, even if Lin Ming had the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ supporting him, it would quickly exhaust his strength.

But Lin Ming did not worry. Soon he would break through his bottleneck, and this weight would be just right in his hands.

“How much is this spear?”

“9000 gold taels!”

9000… Lin Ming wasn’t too surprised. This spear was worth the price. The cloud vein wrought iron treasure spear head’s price was 3000 gold taels and the dark purple elastic iron spear shaft’s price was 6000 gold taels. Both of these prices were absolute bargains.

Lin Ming pulled out all the gold banknotes he had on him, and even the gold purple VIP card, and placed them on the counter. The Divine Weapon Hall was part of the chamber of commerce, thus the VIP card could give him a 10% preferential discount benefit and cause the price to become 8100 gold taels. Even so, with all the gold Lin Ming had on his body, he was still missing 50 gold taels.

The middle-aged man saw this VIP card and his eyes brightened. “Young hero, are you someone from the Martial Quarters?”

Lin Ming thought about it, hesitated, and said, “No, it’s just from my friend at the Martial Quarters.”

Although Lin Ming lightly said this, the middle-aged man knew that this young boy was definitely some important personage of the Martial Quarters; otherwise it would be impossible for him to have a VIP card, much less have one given to him. He said with a smile, “So that’s how it is. Since this young hero is an honored guest of the Martial Quarters, for this spear, 8000 gold taels is good enough.”

“Many thanks.” Lin Ming was not too sentimental. 100 gold taels, was not much of anything, to either him or the Divine Weapon Hall.

The sales clerk bound the weapon in the cloth strip and placed it back inside the box. Lin Ming carried the box on his back, and after saying goodbye, returned to the back mountains.

The shaft was made from dark purple elastic iron, and the treasure-rank spear head was made from cloud vein wrought iron. Such a wonderfully superb spear, it simply made Lin Ming too excited!

After he arrived at the back mountains, he went to an open space. Because he was carrying a 820 jin spear, as soon as Lin Ming stepped on the grass with his feet, each step made a dent in ground.

Feeling a heavy pressure on his back, Lin Ming’s heart filled with a surge of heroic pride. He aimed at a big stone, and suddenly the spear cleaved downwards. There was only a ‘bang’ sound as that giant stone was immediately pulverized by the heavy spear. Because of the spear shaft’s elasticity, Lin Ming didn’t feel any intense shaking in his hand. This was an advantage of the dark purple elastic iron. If this was a pure darksteel spear shaft, then this vibration would cause his thumb and forefinger to be numb. If the rebound force were any larger, then maybe his entire hand would be numbed.

“Ha! What a good spear!”

Ling Ming recklessly waved the spear around. He didn’t know any spear techniques, and simply followed the same routine as his fist techniques. With an 820 jin spear in hand, his spear dance was a little haphazard. Lin Ming practiced for a quarter of an hour, and gradually felt his arm begin to swell, and his strength was somewhat weakening.

“This spear is heavy!”

At this time, in front of Lin Ming, a bright flame burst into life. Mmm? Sound transmitting talisman?

Chapter 66 - Martial House’s Resources

At this time, in front of Lin Ming, a bright flame burst into life. Mmm? Sound transmitting talisman?

“In a quarter hour, arrive at the Seven Profound Martial House’s martial stage! The Martial House shall be allocating resources to disciples based upon their ranking in the ranking war!”

The Martial House’s resources!

With his heart full of delight, Lin Ming strapped the long spear to his back and flew down the mountain as quickly as he could. Although he was moving at his fastest speed, he was still 30% slower than before because he was carrying such a heavy spear on his back. Before, he might have jumped his way through the tree branches with impressive force and agility, but at the present he could only run through the thick, knee-high grass, each step flattening the foliage underneath him, while he carried the spear on his back.

But this failed to cause distress to Lin Ming. In fact, he was even more excited! Carrying such a heavy spear was also a form of practice!

…

After a quarter of an hour, Lin Ming arrived at the martial stage at the Seven Profound Martial House. Instructor Hong Xi had already arrived there long before, and most of the 20 new students of the Earth Hall had also arrived. Seeing Lin Ming come, Hong Xi lifted a hand and tossed a jade slip to Lin Ming.

“Resource details are inside. Look yourself.”

“Yes, Instructor.” Lin Ming poured his soul force into the jade slip. Inside was a detailed map of the Seven Profound Martial House, and the sections of resource locations at the Martial House were outlined in detail.

Inside the illumination of the jade slip were killing arrays used by martial artists to cultivate. They were the Golden Soldier Hall, Wood Puppet Lane, Lava Cave, Boulder Slope, Violent Wind Tunnel, and Thunder Valley. These seven were known as the seven major element killing arrays of gold, wood, water, fire, earth, lightning, and wind.

These seven major killing arrays were constantly in operation all year round, and they consumed a massive amount of true essence stones.

Although the killing arrays were constantly in activation, they could only allow 12 people to cultivate at a time together. The Seven Profound Martial House had too many disciples; it was impossible to allow all of them to come as they pleased, so the only method to allocate time was for disciples to gain it for themselves by struggling their way up the Ranking Stone. Disciples that weren’t on the Ranking Stone were not eligible to enter, and disciples followed the rankings to be allotted time

According to Lin Ming’s ranking, every month he could practice at any killing array for three days.

In addition to this cultivation practice, Lin Ming was also qualified to enter the Seven Profound Martial House’s depository and select a low-grade human-step cultivation method and two low-grade human-step martial skill manuals. Lin Ming could not bring the cultivation method and martial skill jade slips outside of them Seven Profound Martial House, but he could bring them out of the depository and back to his own residence to study them in his own time.

“Martial skill and cultivation methods, and also arrays to cultivate at, these are the most valuable resources that the Seven Profound Martial House can provide. Martial skills can increase a martial artist’s combat prowess and versatility, the cultivation method is the fundamental of martial art, and being able to practice in a killing array can speed up a martial artist’s cultivation and enable them to achieve twice the results with half the effort. Many disciples come to the Seven Profound Martial House for these three resources. ”

“Out of these three resources, the most important is the cultivation method manual. But, I have the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, so the cultivation methods they have here are of no significance for me. What I need most right now is a martial skill and a cultivation room. It’s a pity that I can only practice three days per months, it just isn’t enough time. I have to rise as fast as I can on the Ranking Stone.”

Lin Ming outlined everything he needed in his mind, then withdrew his soul force from the jade slip.

Hong Xi said, “Everyone has finally arrived. Now all of you follow me, we are going to the depository.”

…

The Seven Profound Martial House’s depository was a pavilion that was divided into the inner and outer rooms. Only core disciples could access the inner pavilion; the outer pavilion was for the rest of the disciples.

The inner pavilion contained top-secret cultivation methods and skill manuals that were left behind by masters and sages of the Seven Profound Valley. These manuals and jade slips were not permitted to be handed to outsiders, under great penalty. Lin Ming was only able to enter the outer pavilion at the moment.

Although the outer pavilion’s cultivation method manuals were a grade lower than the inner pavilion, they had a much larger collection and higher level of variety then the inner pavilion did. Inside were several thousand jade slips that had been collected and accumulated by the Seven Profound Valleys over 600 years. Occasionally, a Seven Profound Valley disciple would undergo a mission, and on the way, they would come into disputes with other martial artists and kill them. These martial artists often had cultivation method jade slips on them. Although these jade slips were useless to the disciples of the Seven Profound Valley, they were able to sell them to the sect and this would increase the number of cultivation method jade slips that the Seven Profound Valley had. However these cultivation methods were not the legitimate original methods of the Seven Profound Valley, therefore they would distribute these to the regional Martial Houses so that the disciples there could study them.

Even so, all these cultivation methods were extremely precious within the Sky Fortune Kingdom. Out of the 20 new Earth Hall disciples, many of them had never practiced a cultivation method, so once they came into this outer pavilion and saw such a vast collection of options to choose from, many people grew breathless and colored with excitement.

After Lin Ming arrived at the depository, he handed his jade slip in his hands to the warden elder who guarded the outer pavilion. Not only did this jade slip contain the distribution information on resources, but it also served as a record of Lin Ming’s data and results.

The warden elder examined the jade slip with his soul force, and then said to Lin Ming, “You may proceed. You may choose a cultivation method and two martial skills. You may bring the three jade slips out of the depository but they cannot leave the Seven Profound Martial House. Also… if there are too many people wanting a jade slip, you will need to reserve an appointment, and the length of time you can study it is based upon your rank on the Ranking Stone.”

It was too difficult and troublesome to duplicate a cultivation method’s jade slip; therefore each copy was rare and unique. Some cultivation methods were much more popular and coveted than others, and if many other disciples chose to study that specific one, then there would be a conflict in time and resources. To arrange the reservation time, that would depend on one’s own ranking. Therefore the low ranking disciples often didn’t choose a well-known or prominent cultivation method; otherwise they would not have many opportunities to study it.

“The Seven Profound Martial House really is where strength reigns supreme. Here, ranking is all that matters.” Lin Ming sighed with feeling, and then walked into the depository.

At this time, there were many disciples gathered in the depository, but none of them were making even the slightest sound. If one carefully listened, they could hear that these disciples were even holding their breath for the space of half an incense stick of time, as they were single mindedly studying the cultivation methods in the jade slips.

“So many masters…” Lin Ming lightly breathed. The Seven Profound Martial House was really a den of crouching tigers and hidden dragons. Zhu Yan was a top-tier talent who ranked among the best in Green Mulberry City, but here at the Seven Profound Martial House he was only able to be in the top 30.

Hong Xi said, “Start to choose. Don’t be anxious, there is plenty of time. Make your choice wisely. Jade slips that don’t have a mark are the most basic of skills and cultivation methods. Those with marks on them have a grade. Red marks are low-grade of the human-step, and purple marks are medium grade of the human-step. Near each jade slip is a record that shows how many people have chosen that one. If your ranking is too low, I suggest you to not choose one that is too favored, otherwise, since time is assigned according to your ranking, you may not have much of an opportunity to study it.”

According to the regulations of the Martial House, between ranks 100 to 200, they could only chose a low-grade human-step cultivation method manual. Lin Ming’s ranking was relatively high, so he could chose a popular cultivation method.

However not even mentioning low-grade human-step cultivation methods, even if it was a high-grade human-step cultivation method, Lin Ming would be completely uninterested in it. But, he still had to appear as if he wanted one.

So he began to browse around all the shelves. Near each cultivation method was a label that was made of symbol paper which had the names of the disciples who had chosen that cultivation method. The popular cultivation methods often had 4 or 5 names, but the less popular ones often didn’t have any names at all.

The gap between various low-grade human-step cultivation methods was just too great, thus the disciples who were over rank 100 learned cultivation methods far superior to those below them.

Lin Ming looked for a while, and suddenly moved as he saw Zhang Cang’s name.

“Shadowless Art! I guess this is the cultivation method that Zhang Cang cultivates.”

As soon as Lin Ming looked at the label, he was stunned to see seven names written on it. This cultivation method was truly welcomed by all!

Lin Ming sank his soul force into the jade slip and saw the overview of these cultivation method pop into his mind.

‘The ‘Shadowless Art’. Heavy offense, light defense. The cultivator’s true essence density and purity would be extremely high; they could even compare with a martial artist a whole stage above. This is truly one of the best and most outstanding low-grade human-step cultivation methods among its peers; it is not too far from being a middle-grade human-step cultivation method. However this cultivation method is not easy to practice, and those that reach the Large Success stage are too few, thus please be prudent in your choice.’

Seeing this overview, and reading that it was too difficult so one had to practice it with caution, Lin Ming only smiled and laughed. All of those in Earth Hall over rank 100 were talents, the more difficult it said it was to cultivate, the more those brave and arrogant geniuses would desire it. This cultivation method was also one of the best ones within its rank, how could they not want it?

But certainly, in this cultivation method, Lin Ming had no interest.

He continued to look around, and was preparing to casually choose one, but then his footsteps paused as he wandered near a bookshelf in a corner.

“Spear arts?”

Chapter 86 - The Limit Of Killing Speed

The several detectives sent by the princes immediately burnt their sound transmitting talisman. The Crown Prince was informed of Zhu Yan’s status; after all, Zhu Yan was one of the important figures who served under the banner of the Tenth Prince.

Murong Zi saw Zhu Yan’s ranking and curled her lips in disgust. She wasn’t too satisfied or happy with this Zhu Yan sticking to her footsteps like melted candy.

“Humph, next time I will leave him in my dust.” Murong Zi said with some satisfaction.

“Haha, then you must work diligently. Your talent is better than Zhu Yan; it’s almost fifth-grade.” Bai Jingyun said with a smile.

“That doesn’t mean anything. In the entire Seven Profound Martial House, not counting the core disciples, only Zhang Guanyu is a fifth-grade talent. But that fellow Zhang Guanyu is just an oily playboy with nothing in his head. I don’t like him very much. Well… Sister Jing, are you concerned about Lin Ming?” Murong Zi discovered that Bai Jingyun had been watching Lin Ming.

“Mm. He is going to go on stage now.”

“There is nothing about him that’s worth paying attention to. His talent is limited, he just happened to have a spot of good luck and ate some valuable material, and that’s why he has his current strength.”

Bai Jingyun shook her head and said, “Luck is also a kind of strength. Isn’t being born with a good cultivating martial talent also a kind of luck? Being born in an aristocratic family is similarly also a kind of luck. Like that, you and I can be considered very lucky people also. Nobody can say that Lin Ming won’t be able to continue this streak of good luck. Also, he wasn’t so strong when he had entered the Seven Profound Martial House. It must be the Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill and the Golden Snake Scarlet Pill that allowed his cultivation to progress so quickly. Perhaps his physique is particularly suitable for absorbing the efficacy of precious medicines…”

As Bai Jingyun was speaking, Lin Ming had already stepped onto the altar.

The eyes of everyone present turned to Lin Ming. They wanted to see whether or not this Lin Ming would be able to create a new record today, and have his name written down as the miracle among the new disciples of the Seven Profound Martial House.

The operatives sent by the major powers also rallied their spirits. In these groups of people were intelligence veterans as well as seasoned lobbyists. They were waiting for Lin Ming to leave the Seven Profound Martial House, and then persuade him with their eloquence to support their master.

The cover of light from the Ten Thousand Killing Array came down, and Lin Ming’s entire body was bathed in a glow. In the next moment, he was transported to a vast, white world.

Like last time, there were a variety of weapons that were presented all around him. The sabre, the sword, the spear, it had it all.

“Spear. Spear shaft, 8 feet. Spearhead, 8 inches. Dark purple elastic iron spear shaft, cloud vein wrought iron spear point, total weight 820 jins!”

Lin Ming devised the weapon in his mind, and in the next second, a dark purple colored long spear almost the same as the Penetrating Rainbow appeared in Lin Ming’s hand.

Lin Ming’s casually shook the spear in his hands, and the dark purple long spear began to hum. The strength of the vibration that flowed down the spear shaft could easily crush rocks!

At this time, in front of Lin Ming, a dozen phantom shades appeared in front of him. These phantoms included martial artists and vicious beasts. The majority of their strength was at the early Second Stage of Body Transformation to the early Third Stage of Body Transformation. There was even one who was at the peak Third Stage of Body Transformation.

To the present Lin Ming, these opponents were nothing at all!

Lin Ming steadied his feet and took his stance. His right hand held the spear horizontally, and his elbow was pressed up tight against the spear’s end. This stance he exhibited now was the ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’.

“Roar!” The dozen phantom shades rushed forwards together. These were just phantom illusions, but they had the ability to coordinate, and they dispersed into a semi-circle around Lin Ming, and then lunged at him at the same time!

Generally a martial artist, even if they were a master, being encircled by so many bloodthirsty enemies, could only evade first, and then dodge left and right in the crowd and defeat them one at a time. Because unless there was a great disparity in strength, nobody was able to simultaneously deal with the attacks of a dozen enemies that came from all directions!

However, to Lin Ming, he was able to completely disregard all these attacks!

With a cry, his left hand slapped the spear’s end, and his right hand gripped the spear shaft and suddenly sent it flying out horizontally. The long spear lashed out like a dragon’s tail; it could sweep away an army of a thousand!

As the spear swept out, the dark purple long spear hit the first enemy’s body. This was a first-level vicious beast. Because of Lin Ming’s formidable strength, as the spear head smashed into the vicious beast, the spear bent like a bow. Then, with a popping sound, the spear shaft straightened, and the vicious beast’s spine was directly crushed!

The momentum of the dark purple long spear did not lessen, and it swept on and hit the second vicious beast’s body!

“Cha!” The vicious beast was torn in half!

Followed by the third!

Lin Ming’s strength was more than 4000 jins. Combined with an 820 jin dark purple long spear, a single sweep contained an invincible surging might. In that moment, of the dozen enemies, more than half were all swept away by Lin Ming’s spear!

“Roar!” Of the dozen phantoms, only the vicious beast with strength equal to the peak Third Stage of Body Transformation was able to dodge Lin Ming’s long spear. In that moment, it suddenly accelerated forward like a meteor and charged at Lin Ming’s chest.

Lin Ming’s long spear was out, and his defenses were open. He had no weapon to defend against the sharp fangs of this second-level vicious beast!

As Lin Ming saw these sword-like fangs come forward to stab into his neck, Lin Ming cried out. His right hand held onto the spear, and his left hand was suddenly formed into a fist.

“Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!”

“Peng!”

Lin Ming’s fist pounded into that vicious beat’s chest, and with a loud crack, the body of that giant vicious beast which weighed several hundred jins was instantly split apart!

Lin Ming’s whole body was bathed in blood. His right hand drew back his long spear. He turned his body and gripped the spear in both hands. A red full moon suddenly appeared at the end of the cloud vein wrought iron spear point.

“Killing circle!”

“Pah pah pah pah!” Suddenly what seemed to be like several leather blood bags exploded in the air, showering the entire area with rich red blood. All of the remaining enemies had blown up!

From when these vicious beasts and martial artists had thrown themselves forward, to when Lin Ming had made his strike and completely destroyed all of them, the time had been no more than two breathes!

Lin Ming had used two spear moves and one fist. The Ten Thousand Killing Array did not even have the time to create new phantoms!

The entire illusory magic array had been completely cleared by Lin Ming!

This killing speed was completely abnormal!

After two blinks, there was a distortion in the space, and new phantom shades appeared. This time, whether it was a vicious beast or a martial artist, their strength was a level higher than before!

“He who strikes first has the advantage!”

Lin Ming did not even wait for these phantoms to stabilize their form and had already shot towards the nearest one. “Flood Dragon Goes to Sea!”

The dark purple long spear thrust out with indomitable momentum.

“Pah!” The peak Third Stage Body Transformation martial artist was pierced by Lin Ming’s spear!

With a wave, Lin Ming threw the corpse off of his spear. His spear seemed filled with an epic spirit, the eight feet eight inch dark purple long spear was just like a dark purple flood dragon that swam in a sea of bloodshed. Everywhere the spear went, blood would flow!

To sweep away an army of a thousand, there was only the spear!

In the chaos and midst of battle, the spear was the absolute best weapon!

Of course, the prerequisites were that one must have thick and vast true essence, as well as the physical strength to support such a terrifying rate of strength consumption.

“Killing circle!”

Lin Ming wielded his spear, and three vicious beasts were blown flying backwards, their hands cracked open. At this point, Lin Ming’s muscles corded and his veins bulged like twisting worms. Lin Ming was rapidly revolving the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ in his body, and with every breathe, the air current condensed into a large snake that floated in the air.

Only with the Perfect first layer of the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ together with the true essence provided from the Third Stage of Body Transformation, was Lin Ming able to kill the enemies with such demonic speed!

Chapter 89 - The Result That Defies Heaven’s Will

“62!?”

“My heavens!”

Under everyone’s burning hot gazes, these two simple characters of Lin Ming, inserted in the middle of a row of names, was utterly dazzling!

62!

In his second assessment, he had soared into the top 72 rankings! The Heavenly Abode had 72 people altogether. This meant that Lin Ming’s strength already sufficed to enter the Heavenly Abode!

15 years old, entering the Seven Profound Martial House for one month, cultivation of the early Third Stage of Body Transformation, and he had the qualifications to enter the Heavenly Abode!

For the last 100 years, three martial artists had appeared who had entered into the top 100 during their second round of assessment. But if talking about someone who could enter the Heavenly Abode during their second assessment, there had never existed anyone like that!

All of the disciples present, and the scouts sent by the princes, stared wide-eyed at the Ranking Stone. Murong Zi incredulously covered her mouth in disbelief. The scouts were so shocked, they had forgotten to immediately report the results via their sound transmitting talismans.

This defied the heavens’ will!

This was an absolutely monstrous genius who surpassed Ling Sen, Ta Ku, and Zhang Guanyu!

“No… it’s impossible! He only managed to pass through four incense sticks of time, he should only be past the first 100 rankings, how could his ranking possibly be so high!?” The Heavenly Abode martial artists said. Their rankings were in the 70’s and above. With Lin Ming rising into the middle of them, that meant there was the possibility that one of them would be squeezed out of the Heavenly Abode.

“Was there a mistaking in the Ten Thousand Killing Array’s Ranking Stone?”

“How could that be possible? It was an illusory magic array engraved by a Xiantian master.”

“Even a Xiantian master could make a mistake…” Some people were unconvinced. No one wanted to be kicked out of the Heavenly Abode.

“Shut up, it’s impossible for there to be an error in the Ranking Stone. That Lin Ming could kill his way into the top 72 with only four incense sticks of time is because the speed at which he killed his enemies in the Ten Thousand Killing Array is much quicker than martial artists at his level!”

The deacon who was responsible for the Ten Thousand Killing Array spoke up. This person was a graduate of the Seven Profound Martial House and had already broken through to the Pulse Condensation Period. In the Seven Profound Martial House, he was not only a deacon but also an instructor.

Much quicker than martial artists at his level?

Hearing the deacon’s judgement, it was as if all the air in the surroundings had been sucked out. In the Ten Thousand Killing Array, the enemies overwhelmed to the point of blotting out the sky. Wave after wave of enemies would come, each wave more formidable than the last. The assessment would cause one to not be able to catch their breath; everyone would try to slow down in order to find an opportunity to restore their true essence. Therefore everyone who entered the Ten Thousand Killing Array would kill enemies at the same time and so their ranking could be judged by how long they took.

If Lin Ming slaughtered at such a speed, then without a doubt he would consume his strength faster, and die faster!

It was just too abnormal!

Murong Zi was still covering her mouth, finding herself at a loss for words. It was only after a moment that she turned to Bai Jingyun and said, “Big Sister Jingyun, you were right… this Lin Ming is simply a farm animal, I don’t know what kind of food he was fed growing up…”

She was very clear on the significance of this ranking. Beyond the top 62 rankings, there were about a dozen students who were set to graduate at the end of the year. Even if Lin Ming stayed at the same ranking, he could enter the top 50 at the end of the year. He could even leap past the top 50 rankings!

But how could Lin Ming stay at the same rankings? He might even enter the top 30 by the end of the year and become her own competition!

Bai Jingyun snorted and then smiled, “Little girl, mind your manners. You are just envious of others.”

“Humph, why would I envy him? I just have to take things a little more seriously, and then we will see if I am surpassed by him!” Murong Zi raised her small fists. Before now, she had just wanted to play around all the time. Before, at the Dream Trial during the entrance exam, Murong Zi’s result was an absolute mess. It was only by taking risk after risk did she cross each hurdle.

…

…

“Damnit! Hurry up and report this to his highness the Crown Prince faster! Damn me, this result has really turned me into a blind dog!” The lead detective under the command of the Crown Prince burst out at his group like an exploding chestnut!

“Yes, yes, we will immediately send the report. A little guy whose head had been knocked around hurriedly whispered the information, and then lit the sound transmitting talisman in his hands…

Meanwhile, the followers of the Tenth Prince also burnt their sound transmitting talisman. The man who led them looked at the four Crown Prince’s men in the bamboo grove, an evil smile curving on his face.

“What a bunch of idiots. They are still making a futile effort to struggle. Time is on our side, his Highness will inevitably win. What kind of trash can the Crown Prince put out? For this Lin Ming, his Highness has already especially prepared a set of human-step scriptures and a top-quality treasure!”

…

At this time, the Crown Prince Yang Lin was in the Eastern Palace. He was playing chess with his mentor, Mister Muyi.

“Haha, what was your highness thinking? That chess move was wrong.”  Muyi smiled as he moved a piece and took another one. Yang Lin’s bottom left side of the board had already become a lost cause.

Yang Lin smiled as he shook his head. “Teacher, I have never won playing against you. Whether I lose early or I lose late, the difference is not big.”

“Haha, even if you say that your strength is inferior, you cannot lose your backbone or fighting spirit. Chess is like a battlefield, even if your technique is inferior; someone who dies on the battlefield remains a hero as he was before. But if he surrenders and is captured and then killed, it is only a shame.”

“Teacher’s lesson is wise.”

To Muyi, Yang Lin had no superiority as Crown Prince. In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, a middle Houtian stage master was someone that even the emperor had to give three points of respect to. More so because the current government and court were turbulent, Muyi was the most important person that Yang Lin relied on.

“Tell me, what’s on your mind?” Muyi asked as he put a pawn down on the board.

Yang Lin said, “I visited my father, the emperor today. His body seems to be worse than before…”

“Mmm…” Muyi thought silently. He knew that if Yang Lin was worried about anything, it was the throne change due to the old emperor’s deteriorating condition. He did not have too many forces on his side, and now he had to consider the power and strength of the other princes. The Tenth Prince, the Cloud Prince, was ambitious; he probably would not be willing to stay just a prince. But if comparing the influence in the court, their supporters, and even individual strength, Yang Lin was far from the Cloud Prince. Once a struggle began, he might not come out as the victor.

In the struggles of the throne, once one was defeated, their fate could be imagined. Yang Lin was already the Crown Prince; even if he didn’t want to struggle, he had no choice but to do so. Otherwise, he would lose his life! So these days, Yang Lin has been heavy-hearted, and had not dared to show his hand.

Muyi said, “Your highness. I had just said that chess is like a battlefield. You cannot lose your backbone or your fighting spirit. Your highness, if you lack confidence, then the subordinates under your control will also be anxious. These subordinates of yours have already resolved to follow your highness, and have handed over their lives and their families’ lives. If your highness loses, then the Cloud Prince will surely show no mercy, and will thoroughly cleanse the government. When that time comes…”

Muyi did not say it, but in all the ancient changes of the throne, they were often accompanied by massacres and the thick smells of blood and death. At those times, things like affection and friendship would all be nothing but a joke.

Chapter 94 - Martial Intent Reappears

Of course this was great. Their Lin Family had always been pressured by the Zhu Family, and even the younger generation was being pressured by Zhu Yan. Now Lin Ming was able to mercilessly get justice for them, and even challenge Zhu Yan at spear point. To overturn this mountain that had always been suppressing the younger generation of the Lin Family, how could he not be feeling great?

There that night, 12 more long range sound transmitting talismans were used in succession to return news to the Sky Fortune City Lin Family branch. The instructions the Lin Family Head gave were, “Do not hesitate to use all supplies available to support Lin Ming. We must create the best and most ideal conditions for Lin Ming, so that he can defeat Zhu Yan one month from now.”

So today, because of the instructions from the Head of the Lin Family, the Lin Family branch sent Lin Wu to bring Lin Ming resources to support him.

“This is…” Lin Ming looked at a small porcelain bottle and a small jade box in Lin Wu’s hand.

“The Head of the Lin Family sent an urgent message through 12 long-range sound transmitting talismans to the family branch. He wants you to train well, and try your hardest to defeat Zhu Yan a month from now.”

Lin Ming took the porcelain bottle and the jade box. He opened the porcelain bottle. Inside were ten pills. They were lustrous and round, with a delicate and gentle fragrance. As soon as one saw these, it was easy to tell they were superior medicines.

“High-level Soul Gathering Pellet?”

The main ingredient of an ordinary Soul Gathering Pellet was a 100 year old Yuan fruit. Its value was no less than a 100 year old Blood Lingzhi.

But a high-level Soul Gathering Pellet was made from a 300 year old Yuan fruit. Its value was at least 7 times more than an ordinary Soul Gathering Pellet. Moreover, it was not easy to buy!

A Soul Gathering Pellet could not directly increase a martial artist’s strength, but it could enhance a martial artist’s ability to condense true essence and thus increase their cultivation speed. Although these types of pills’ effects of increasing strength were slow, they did not have any side effects, and one could take them constantly.

Because of this, of all the pills that martial artists had, the consumption of Soul Gathering Pellet was the highest. This bottle that the Lin Family gave of high-level Soul Gathering Pellets was worth nearly 20,000 gold taels.

The family had really used all their resources.

Lin Ming looked at Lin Wu and then opened the jade box. After opening it, he saw neatly placed inside were two layers of crystal clear stones that looked as if they were carved from ice. True essence stones!

Lin Ming could see with one sweep of his eyes that this box held 30 true essence stones!

30 true essence stones was not a small number! And these true essence stones were glittering as if they were carved from translucent glass. If compared to those given by the Seven Profound Martial House, they were somewhat purer.

These true essence stones; their value was also not low!

Seeing this bottle of Soul Gathering Pellets and this box of true essence stones, Lin Ming understood that if he received this great gift, it was equivalent to his tacit approval, and that he was willing to become a direct descendant of the Lin Family.

Lin Wu realized that Lin Ming’s look had changed, and he faintly guessed in his mind what he was deliberating. He said with some embarrassment and a hint of apology, “Young Cousin, I know that this icing on the cake is not of a timely nature to truly help. I know that when you first came down to Sky Fortune City, not even a shadow of the family was here to help or assist you. Now that Young cousin has become a dragon among men, the family only then delivers medicine and true essence stones. It really does not honor you or do you justice, but there is also a reason we do the things we do. The family’s resources are limited… there are just too many children of the Lin Family. If each generation equally divided the family property, then the Lin Family would have already disappeared.”

Lin Ming understood what Lin Wu meant. Lin Ming’s own great grandmother was the matriarch of the family office, Madam Fang. This relation was passed down to Lin Ming. The children of a large family tended to have many wives, and thus they flourished. The number of heirs and descendants exponentially increased with each new generation. The property had to be concentrated together in order to ensure that the family traditions could continue.

The family gave some businesses to the branch family juniors to manage, and to let these distant families earn a salary. This was already a kindness to the branch families. In fact, this was very generous. If it wasn’t for Lin Ming practicing martial arts, his family’s life could also be very wealthy.

To the Lin Family with which he shared the last name, Lin Ming felt a little thanks, but he did not have any real sense of belonging to them. But Lin Ming knew that his parents had very traditional and serious mindsets, and they had always dreamed that one day they could return to the main family. In his parents’ eyes, recognizing their ancestors and returning to the main family was the orthodox.

This was because his parents’ status in the family would rise, and they would even receive the respect and veneration of the family head!

To the parents, this was a glory, and this glory would be brought because of him. Which parents did not hope for their children to have great accomplishments in the future, and return home with riches and honor? Lin Ming was a rare talent that had never been seen in the last hundred years of the Seven Profound Martial House. His rising star was enough to bring honor to his ancestors, and to give shade to his descendants.

Thinking this, Lin Ming accepted the pills and true essences stones, and said to Lin Wu, “Thank  the family head for me.”

“Young Cousin is too humble. The Lin Family thanks young cousin, and we hope you win for us.” Seeing Lin Ming accept these gifts, Lin Wu relaxed and let loose a deep breath. He also had feared that Lin Ming had a cold and lonely heart towards the Lin Family.

It was only a few more months until the end of the year. Lin Ming was already calculating in his mind. There was a vacation period at the end of the Seven Profound Martial House school year. The Martial House disciples usually went home to celebrate the new year. He himself had to take advantage of this opportunity to visit his parents. His father and mother had worked hard enough for a lifetime; they deserved an easy and comfortable retirement in old age.

Bidding Lin Wu farewell, Lin Ming took the pills and the true essence stones with him, and carried Penetrating Rainbow to the Icy Pond Waterfall once more.

“Junior Apprentice Lin.” As soon as the deacon senior apprentice responsible for the Icy Pond Waterfall saw Lin Ming, his whole face had lit up with a welcoming smile. “Junior Apprentice Lin is truly basking in the limelight. But, ah, it is just too wonderful; Ranking Stone rank 62, terrific, terrific, and certainly unprecedented!”

Lin Ming smiled and didn’t respond. These last two days he had heard far too much similar flattery.

“What difficulty does Junior Apprentice Lin want?”

“Nine levels!”

The highest difficulty in the Icy Pond Waterfall array was the twelfth level. The deeper one went, the higher the level one went, the more difficult the array would be. The only person capable of just barely withstanding the twelfth level of difficulty was Ling Sen. Even he could only last for an incense stick of time, and then he too had to surface and meditate. Therefore Ling Sen only practiced at the eleventh level of difficulty.

In one month, Lin Ming had jumped two levels of difficulty, and gone from the seventh level to the ninth level. This was a truly unbelievable matter, but Lin Ming’s ranking spoke louder than words.

“Okay.” The deacon senior apprentice said without hesitation, and immediately opened the ninth level of difficulty.

Lin Ming swallowed a high-level Soul Gathering Pellet to help him increase his cultivation speed, and then he carried the Penetrating Rainbow with him as he dove into the icy pond.

As soon as he entered the icy pond, Lin Ming felt once more a bone chilling cold that was like tiny ice needles piercing him from all directions. The difficulty had kicked up a notch!

Of the Seven Profound Martial House’s resources, the Soul Gathering Pellets and true essences stones couldn’t be considered true treasures. Only these seven major killing arrays could be considered such. Each second and each minute was incomparably precious; he could not even waste a smidgen of time!

He only had two hours of time. Lin Ming stood on the big rock underneath the waterfall. He kept Penetrating Rainbow even and steady. In the ninth level of difficulty, the waterfall’s pulsing impact had increased tremendously. When Lin Ming had gripped his eight foot eight inch spear underneath the waterfall, he immediately felt the huge impact force of the waterfall, as if at any moment his arm would break under the weight.

Underneath the effects of the waterfall array, it was not easy to stand, and the water was also freezing cold. The unending flowing water constantly slicked off of the body’s heat. Adding an 820 jin spear that he kept horizontally underneath the waterfall, even with his own thick true essence and amazing strength, he could only support this consumption for a blink of an eye!

Even if it was Lin Ming, he had to absorb the true essence in a true essence stone to support himself.

“Mm? The absorption speed of true essence went up by 50%!” Lin Ming was startled, but he immediately understood. This was the effect of the high-level Soul Gathering Pellet.

An 1800 gold tael high-level Soul Gathering Pellet, eating one was a true treasure. The effects of this kind of luxurious and amazing pill were especially good!

By relying on the true essence stone and the high-level Soul Gathering Pill that was difficult to buy no matter how wealthy one was, Lin Ming was unexpectedly able to persist in this extremely violent situation!

Originally, Lin Ming had thought he could hold his breath for two quarters of an hour at most, but now, even though his true essence was depleted, he could still rely on the high-level Soul Gathering Pellet and true essence stone to supplement his body and barely continue.

Although Lin Ming felt that the pain was difficult to endure, he was still standing.

The advantages were immense in maintaining this condition. Not only did it rapidly enhance his spear skills, but it also tempered his body with true essence, and increased the synchronization of the tiny units in his body!

Each point of his muscles and organs independently absorbed true essence. His body continually resisted against the severe cold. When a common martial artist practiced martial arts, it was inevitable that their body would have a spot that they did not cultivate. But when every inch of the body was independently absorbing true essence, then this situation would not occur.

Lin Ming’s one breath had already lasted for half an hour!

Because of the biting ice-cold chill, Lin Ming’s body temperature had already dropped to an acutely low degree. An average man would have already died, but a martial artist relied on the protection of their true essence to maintain their blood flow.

Because of the long time he had been under this condition, Lin Ming’s consciousness began to fade away from his body. Slowly, the thunderous sounds of the waterfall began to fade away and vanish into nothing. Lin Ming’s mind entered a completely quiet and tranquil time and space. Here, it was as if he could clearly feel the flow and sound of each impact, and he could hear his own slow heartbeat as if it were frozen. This heartbeat beat with a rhythm of a booming drum.

At that moment, Lin Ming felt his soul leave his body once more. In his body, he once more felt that elusive state that he had been in before. Because he was unable to consciously control his body, the true essence in his body moved in accordance of its instincts. This sort of circulation route, compared to when Lin Ming was controlling his true essence himself, was far more perfect!

Lin Ming didn’t know, but this state was the rudimentary form of ‘Martial Intent’.

Chapter 99 - Fast Spear

This thought caused Hong Xi to suddenly freeze. He remembered glancing at the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’, and recalled that the essence of this ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ was… vibration!

Vibration!

Heavens! This boy!

Hong Xi’s Adam’s apple spasmed. This kid should not have learned the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’!

It… It was impossible. Although true essence vibration was mentioned in the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ jade slip, it had not said how to train this true essence vibration; it had lacked the most essential basic part! The ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ was 70% incomplete, and it was also an Earth-step martial skill. Even an immortal would be helpless to do anything!

If Lin Ming was really able to cultivate this ability, then even those evil monstrous geniuses would be nothing but weak and pale in front of him; he would simply be the reincarnation of immortal gods and infernal demons!

“Boy, that vibration technique you had used a moment ago; where did you learn that from? Hong Xi’s voice held a hint of trembling; obviously he was very disturbed and restless. He could not calm down after experiencing something like this. This meant that not only did Lin Ming have a superior heart of martial arts, but he was also able to comprehend his own martial intent. Not only that, but he was a beyond brilliant monstrous genius prodigy with perception that defied the will of the heavens!

To this kind of evil-doer genius, any talent was simply floating clouds!

That these monstrous geniuses could accomplish the impossible with their own hands, what sort of concept was that? Hong Xi did not even dare to imagine.

Lin Ming truthfully said, “They were some hints that I picked up from the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ jade slip.” He had not planned to conceal anything to begin with. In fact, he could not even try to hide it. Sooner or later it would be exposed, unless he never used this skill.

But the truth was that even if he was exposed, it was impossible to teach or explain things like martial skills or cultivation methods without the jade slip. Only someone who has reached the Large Success stage of that martial skill or cultivation method would be able to copy it down, so Lin Ming simply did not worry that anyone would covet it.

Mentioning the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ would only increase the number of chips in his hand, and cause the Seven Profound Martial House and the Crown Prince to be even more protective of him. This way, he would be even safer.

After hearing Lin Ming’s affirmation, Hong Xi could not speak for a long time. He merely stared at Lin Ming as if he was looking at a monster.

Whose mother would dare mention or look down upon Lin Ming’s martial talent again?

This Lin Ming was the most abnormal talent in the last 100 years of the Seven Profound Martial House!

There was only Qin Xingxuan who could compare with Lin Ming; moreover, she wouldn’t necessarily be better!

“Peerless monstrous genius…” Hong Xi finally gave his evaluation after he was speechless for a long time.

“Lin Ming, in my Hong Xi’s entire life, you are the best and most outstanding and talented martial artist that I have ever witnessed! Although your talent is only a medium third-grade, you can make up this deficiency with your ethereal martial intent! With just that, you can be considered a fourth or fifth grade talent. Still, that would not be anything special enough to attract the Seven Profound Valleys’ attention. But, your perception is just too terrifying; you can practice any skill with twice the result and half the effort. In addition, with your pure and strong heart of martial arts, you may even be able to comprehend a second martial intent. In that case, even the Seven Profound Valleys will not be able to hold you! You will at the apex of the entire Sky Spill Continent’s younger generation!”

“Your future is limitless. What I can teach you is limited. All I am capable of at present is being your teacher. I was prepared to teach you the spear skills that I had learned, but it seems that it is not necessary anymore. You have your own understanding of spear-play, and I am afraid that my own comprehension will negatively affect you. All I can teach you now is the basis of spear skills, as well as the spear cultivation method!”

“A moment ago when I fought you, I discovered that your spear is already very steady. You could say that you’ve reached the boundary where your spear is still like a cast metal statue. But, your spear is not quick! In my two spear moves, you were only able to return one! With this kind of speed, you will be unable to catch up to Zhu Yan!”

“The steady spear that cannot catch up to an enemy’s shadow is useless! Lin Ming, just watch! Hong Xi turned and punched a tree trunk. The autumn leaves that had already begun to turn yellow and wither immediately began to rustle and fall down.

Hong Xi’s eyes flashed with a glint of light. The spear in his hand shot out just like a deadly snake!

Cha cha cha!

Spear shadows covered the sky!

Even with Lin Ming’s excellent eyesight, he could not clearly see Hong Xi’s spear point!

He could only use his soul force to catch up to Hong Xi’s movements. With each stab of Hong Xi’s spear, the spear point pierced a fallen leaf, rapidly turned back, and then pierced another leaf. Like this, there was a string of fallen leaves on the spear point!

As the spear shadows flashed everywhere, the fallen leaves began to rapidly disappear with a speed obvious to the naked eye. In the span of a few breaths, Hong Xi had strung together a thick stack of fallen leaves on his spear point!

Finally, there was not a single fallen leaf that touched the ground.

Lin Ming could not help but exclaim at such wonderful spear skills!

It had to be known that Hong Xi’s spear point was very wide; the widest part was four finger widths wide.

But these fallen leaves were elliptical in shape. Only the long axis was over four finger widths in length; the short axis was only two finger widths.

Thus, all the fallen leaves have been pierced by spear point through their long side; otherwise, the leaf would be cut in half!

Lin Ming looked at Hong Xi’s spear point, and really did see that the several dozens of leaves that were strung together were in consistent order, it was as if they were especially organized to be that way!

The leaves were small, and their longest side was only a bit over 4 finger widths, but Hong Xi had managed to accurately pierce through all of the fallen leaves in this area, and did not cut any of the leaves apart. This control of strength caused Lin Ming to feel amazed!

Hong Xi’s spear was not only quick, but he had great control of his strength!

As the saying went, a month to use a stick, a year to train a fist, and longer to practice a spear!

The difficulty in wielding a spear was high. It was meant to thrust, the shaft was long, it was hard to grasp and hard to control. If Hong Xi had been doing this with a sword, it would have been much easier!

The sword was faster than a spear, and it was also more accurate.

But a sword could not compare with the might of a spear.

For Lin Ming, this was an eye-opener.

Hong Xi said, “Cultivate your spear like this. Practice your spear skills so that you may use several dozen spear thrusts in the time of a few breaths. These several dozen spear thrusts must not be blind; but each and every spear move must be accurate! Control your strength until you can attack and withdraw freely! This fallen leaves are the appropriate practice method!”

“These falling leaves are very fragile, they will be cut apart if you use too much strength or if your aim is poor. If you can have these several dozen leaves completely strung together on your spear point, then your spear skills will have arrived at the Small Success stage. But you only have one month of intensive practice; it will take a much longer time to practice the spear. Do not irresponsibly talk nonsense and bite off more than you can chew. At this moment, do not seek to control the force, but instead you must do everything you can to maximize your spear speed to the limit, so you can chase down Zhu Yan’s sword!

“I understand.”

With this brief meeting with Hong Xi, Lin Ming had benefitted greatly.

“Good. Practice by yourself. This will be enough to have you occupied for some time. Later I will come back to teach you the next move.”

“Thank you, Instructor Hong.”

“Heh, no need to thank me. Right now I’m teaching you, but later I won’t even be able to stand in line to teach you.” Hong Xi laughed, launched a movement technique, and vanished into the forest.

After Hong Xi had vanished, Lin Ming watched the yellow leaves on the tree. He shook Penetrating Rainbow in his hand. His spear speed truly wasn’t good. Even if his spear skills were swift and fierce, they would have no meaning if they weren’t able to reach Zhu Yan.

Bang! Lin Ming punched the big tree, and thick leaves began to fall. Lin Ming looked at these leaves and the spear in his hand began to stab out rapidly.

“…”

The leaves were shredded apart by Lin Ming’s spear!

Though he wanted to string these leaves on his spear, it was not a simple task to constantly do this. During the time when the leaves were gently falling, they were often tumbled around in circles. During that brief period of time, he had to thrust out his long spear in the center of a leaf, and have the spear edge pierce through the long axis of the leaf. Only then could he string them on the spear. But as of now, Lin Ming was far from reaching this stage.

After several dozen leaves had fallen, Lin Ming had split some in half, and some had fallen to the ground. There was only a few that hung on Lin Ming’s spear point.

“Maybe I should start small. I should not use such a tiny elliptical leaf to practice…” Lin Ming thought. The small elliptical leaves were just too difficult right now.

He chose another, different tree. This tree’s leaves were heart shaped, and were the size of a palm, Regardless of any angle, as long as the spear pierced through the center, he could string the leaves on the spear tip.

“This tree is good. I’ll practice with the one.”

…

Day after day, Lin Ming went to spend his mornings tempering his body at the Icy Pond Waterfall. He set the difficulty to the ninth level to push his body to the limit, so that he could experience his ethereal martial intent. During the afternoon he would spend his time training his spear, and in the evening he would train the ‘Flow like Silk’ boundary, and cultivate his ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’.

Ten days had passed in the blink of an eye. Lin Ming’s ethereal martial intent was becoming increasingly stable. To enter it at first, he would push his body to the limit, and then by supporting himself with the high-level Soul Gathering Pellet and true essence stones, he could slowly enter the ethereal martial intent under these harsh conditions.

Afterwards, as long as Lin Ming meditated under the Icy Pond Waterfall, he could spontaneously enter the ethereal martial intent state.

After cultivating in the ethereal martial intent state for a long time, Lin Ming’s ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ had finally entered the second-level. His true essence became even thicker, and his strength and speed also increased.

During that evening, Lin Ming sat alone in his room and meditated for a long time, He adjusted his mind to the most peaceful and tranquil condition he could achieve. Then, slowly, he pulled out the reward he won from taking first place in the entrance exam - the Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill!

The Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill was created by mixing the bone marrow of a Crimson Gold Dragon with many precious medicinal herbs, and then refining them all together.

The Crimson Gold Dragon’s dragon marrow was inestimably precious and difficult to find. The other rare and precious medicinal herbs were also high-quality and rare. Not only had that, but to refine this pill required a top-tier alchemist. An alchemist of this level usually came from a large sect, it was impossible for a common person to even catch a glimpse of them, let alone ask them to come out create such a pill. Even if they did come out, the fees alone would be overwhelmingly expensive.

Therefore the Sky Fortune Kingdom had never produced a Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill. Not even the Royal Family could buy it, as its value could simply not be measured with gold.

Then, Lin Ming took out a ‘Lower Spirit Cure Symbol’ symbol paper that he had prepared in advance. He had trained hard for a half month to create these two ‘Lower Spirit Cure Symbols’. The first had already been used on the Golden Snake Scarlet Pill, and the second was to prepare this Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill.

Normally a martial artist could only absorb a small part of a pill’s efficacy, and the rest would dissipate. But the symbols that Lin Ming had drawn up could control and stimulate this pill. With it, the effects of the pill would not dissipate in a martial artist’s body, and instead infiltrate and be absorbed. This way, the pill’s efficacy would increase by several times!

Lin Ming crushed the ‘Lower Spirit Cure Symbol’ in his hand. The symbol paper turned into a bright red flame that immediately flew to the Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill and began to integrate with it. In a few breaths of time, a flame-shaped inscription symbol had appeared in the center of the pill.

Chapter 101 – Arrival Of The Decisive Battle

However, Hong Xi was even more startled. Even though he had not used true essence, he had still used his full and complete strength in this strike; but Lin Ming was able to block it head-on!

Hong Xi had already known that Lin Ming’s strength was otherworldly, but he did not think that after achieving Large Success in the Third Stage of Body Transformation, that his strength would undergo such a dramatic rise. This strength must be no less than 5000 jins! His body was simply like a vicious beast!

Although he was surprised, Hong Xi’s movement hadn’t slowed in the slightest. He took advantage of Lin Ming’s blowback from his spear strike and aggressed on him. He thrusted his spear out three times, and each strike cut off all of Lin Ming’s dodging paths. Lin Ming could only raise his spear to defend!

Dong!

As they collided, Hong Xi’s spear fell upon the spear shaft of Penetrating Rainbow. The dark purple elastic iron spear shaft was hammered by Hong Xi and forcefully bent like a bow!

Lin Ming’s feet sank into the ground, and his right foot was trapped in the thick soil. He pushed back with all his strength on Penetrating Rainbow, and just managed to force back Hong Xi’s spear. But Hong Xi had backflipped into the air, and as he was airborne, his long spear drew a perfect arc, and he did a straight thrust from under his belly towards Lin Ming’s throat.

The spear came flying at him too fast and too suddenly. With him having recklessly forced back two of Hong Xi’s blows, he had exhausted his true essence, and the blood in his chest was roiling. He was not able to block this strike, and Hong Xi’s one spear thrust came perilously close to Lin Ming’s throat.

At that moment, Lin Ming could clearly feel the bone-chilling wind from the spear, painfully flowing against his skin. But in a flash, Hong Xi had withdrawn his spear, and the spear point stopped a half inch away from Lin Ming’s throat, not injuring him in the least.

What accurate control of force!

Even knowing that Hong Xi’s spear would not pierce him, Lin Ming’s breath had stopped in that instant as the spear wind blew against his skin. This spear thrust that was like a bolt of lightning was just too scary.

Three moves. In just three moves, Lin Ming was defeated!

As Hong Xi received his long spear, he said, “Lin Ming, although I suppressed my true essence, I did not suppress my strength. Still, you were able to last until the third spear move, which is already far beyond what someone of your level can accomplish! Your strength really goes against heaven’s will; I guess it must be more than 5000 jins!

“5300 jins.” Lin Ming replied truthfully.

“5300 jins!” Hong Xi clicked his tongue, “ A martial artist at your cultivation would have been thrown 18 streets away by you. Your strength is truly appropriate to wield the spear; using a sword would have been a waste! When you had received my three strikes, you were actually not at your best level. When you were defending, you had one very weak point. That is your momentum!

Momentum!

Lin Ming was slightly stunned. Early on, his momentum had really been overwhelmed and crushed by Hong Xi’s swift and fierce spear moves!

“When you had fought against Zhang Cang, you had used the most basic foundation moves ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’ and ‘Flood Dragon Goes to Sea’ to break apart Zhang Cang’s ‘Sunset Cut’. This was because your spear carried with it a tide of surging momentum! But a moment ago, because my spear moves were too quick, you did not have enough time to gather your potential! Yes, although the momentum of your spear is strong, but it actually has a fatal weakness, and that is that its start is too slow!”

“Zhu Yan uses a sword, and he has great attainments in swordsmanship. His attacks are extremely swift and aggressive. If you are suppressed by him, then his moves will be faster than yours, and you will not be able to gather your momentum. When that happens, you will be led into his rhythm, and finally be defeated!”

Hong Xi was indeed an instructor of the Seven Profound Martial House; he had quickly discerned and pointed out another weakness of Lin Ming’s.

Indeed, no matter how good a skill was, if one did not have time to begin unleash it, then it would be useless!

“Now you must learn how to gather your momentum while you are attacking! Have you ever heard of some martial skills that are in a set, for instance, something something 18 palms, or whatever whatever 9 swords, or something silly like that?”

Lin Ming nodded.

Hong Xi said, “This set style often starts from the first, weakest move. A move will follow the previous move, and each move will be stronger than the last! You might ask; why would someone waste their energy doing this and not use their strongest final attack on the first move? The truth is, it is not that they don’t want to, but that they cannot. This is a question of gathering their momentum. They need to begin at the start, and save up their potential, and finally explode with power in that last move! This is what it means to gather your momentum!”

Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened, “I understand.”

“If you want to learn how to gather your potential, then it is very simple. All you have to do is fight! Starting from today, except eating and sleeping, the rest of the time we shall fight! I want to see how long you will be able to stand it!”

For the next ten days, Lin Ming started a hellish combat training routine.

Although Hong Xi had said that they would fight each other whenever they weren’t eating or sleeping, but he hadn’t thought that Lin Ming would be able to persist through it.

Although a Viscera Training martial artist had vitality and endurance, and their hearts and lungs were powerful, it was impossible for them to maintain such intense fighting for a long period of time. However, Hong Xi quickly discovered that he had once again underestimated Lin Ming.

This Lin Ming was simply a perpetual motion machine in human form. His endurance was abnormal and outrageous!

His true essence was thicker than other martial artists of his cultivation by several times, and it was also purer; it could almost be said to be growing without end!

Even Qin Xingxuan who cultivated the rare and forbidden cultivation manuals of the Seven Profound Valley was not as exaggerated as this. Hong Xi didn’t have any words to comment, he only chalked up this sort of bizarre situation to Lin Ming’s ethereal martial intent and inborn divine strength.

They could fight for an entire eight hours with only a single breath!

Even Hong Xi was sweating profusely. His armor had already been tossed off to the side, and he was shirtless. But Lin Ming’s entire body was wet and sticky with perspiration, and he took great panting gulps of breath. Every time he exhaled, the hot air would form steam, and every time he inhaled, the air would form a mini whirlpool. Even flying leaves near Lin Ming were blown away.

Hong Xi noted this phenomenon of nature. This boy, his breath was so long, no wonder his endurance was so good. Were his lungs a pair of bellows?

“Instructor Hong, let’s go again!” Although Lin Ming was dead tired, his eyes still shined brightly with fighting spirit. In merely one day, his progress had been beyond astonishing. At the start, he had only been able to meet three spears from Hong Xi, but now he could take 7 or 8 moves from Hong Xi and still not be defeated. One time, he even met 10 moves!

These were attacks from a martial artist at the Pulse Condensation Period!

By fighting in such a manner, Lin Ming began to gradually discover what it meant to gather his potential and momentum during a fight. If in the past Lin Ming had depended on his strength and superior thick true essence to defeat his opponents, then now Lin Ming’s combat skills were gradually catching up.

“Good! Come again!” Hong Xi’s spirit was also aroused by Lin Ming’s hot-bloodedness. In this day of fighting, even though Lin Ming’s strength was far weaker than his own, he was still fighting with his full strength!

…

For ten days, whenever Lin Ming wasn’t eating or sleeping, he was fighting with Hong Xi. By relying on his second-layer of ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, and the resiliency given by his long, bellow-like breaths, Lin Ming was able to adhere to this practice regimen every day.

From the beginning, he had only been able to persist up to three moves, but afterwards he was able to last for more than 20. Lin Ming’s flow of momentum and potential was becoming more and more skillful; he could send his momentum out with every strike of his spear. Even the momentum of his old self was less imposing! Each move he made with his spear was able to constantly accumulate momentum, getting stronger and stronger!

At the same time, Lin Ming’s movement also made considerable progress. The ‘Foundation Movement Technique’ was not some sort of profound movement technique. Its movement was very simple and basic. However, Lin Ming was able to forcefully rely on this technique to slowly catch up to Hong Xi’s movements.

Bang!

After the continuous momentum of 20 moves had gathered, Lin Ming’s spear cleaved downwards. It brought with it a surge of torrential rivers and streams, and hacked towards Hong Xi. Everywhere the spear wind touched was blown away like sand!

“Good spear!” Hong Xi lifted his spear to meet the oncoming blow. Although he was able to block this spear, he was forced back a step by the backlash from the formidable momentum and intense vibrations that ran up Lin Ming’s spear.

This was the first time that Lin Ming had forced back Hong Xi!

A Viscera Training stage martial artist that could force back one at the Pulse Condensation Period? Even though Hong Xi had suppressed his true essence, this result was enough to frighten anyone!

And Hong Xi was not an ordinary Pulse Condensation Period martial artist!

“Lin Ming, no matter what happens to your body, I don’t think I can ever be surprised again.”  Hong Xi smiled, and received his long spear. “This was only ten days. If there was perhaps a month, then I don’t think I would be able to defeat you without using more of my true essence.”

Although Hong Xi was praising him so, Lin Ming had no room for complacency. He knew that for a martial artist, the higher one’s cultivation was, the more important true essence would be. Someone using true essence versus someone not using true essence; the gulf between them was too fast. Especially in the body of a martial artist, once they had connected their meridians and opened them, then their true essence would be incomparably smooth and unimpeded. Attacks with true essence were the strongest methods of attack. If Hong Xi had used his full strength, then there was no doubt Lin Ming would die in less than three moves.

Lin Ming said, “I fall far short from Instructor. If Instructor Hong was serious, then being able to withstand one move would already be the edge of my limits.”

“Hey! You boy, you want to rely on your Viscera Training stage strength to whole-heartedly compare with someone at the peak Pulse Condensation Period? That you can force a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist to take a step back is already very good. Are you dissatisfied with that or something?”

Listening to Hong Xi say it like that, Lin Ming also smiled. His cultivation was simply too low; he was three stages worse compared to the Pulse Condensation Period! Moreover, for the boundaries of a martial artist’s cultivation, the higher one went, the harder it became, and the bigger the gulf between each realm!

Hong Xi said, “Tomorrow will be the day of your match against Zhu Yan. Today we will stop here. You go and take a good rest, and adjust to your peak condition. If you lose, I won’t forgive you.”

Lin Ming grinned and laughed as he said, “At first when I challenged Zhu Yan, I really wasn’t sure of my chances. But after practicing with Instructor Hong for so many days, I think my odds are pretty high now.”

“Ha! I’ll take this as you having learnt something!”

Lin Ming’s Large Success of Viscera Training stage against Zhu Yan’s early Altering Muscle stage.

Although there was only a difference of half a stage, this was a fight between the apex of talents. A half-stage difference was already amazing, and that wasn’t even counting Zhu Yan having spent more time at the Seven Profound Martial House for two and a half years more than Lin Ming. In this time, he had been able to use the seven major killing arrays for much longer!

Zhu Yan was truly a formidable and daunting opponent. In the entirety of the Seven Profound Martial House, one could say his talent was only inferior to the three people; Ling Sen, Ta Ku, and Zhang Guanyu!

Time passed quickly, and it was soon to approach one month. This was the 64th day since Lin Ming had arrived at the Seven Profound Martial House. Today was also the day of Lin Ming’s and Zhu Yan’s duel. The location of this duel was the Seven Profound Martial House’s Martial Stage.

In the Seven Profound Martial House, there were placed that were off limits to outsiders. For instance, those that involved secrets, heritages, and legacies; these were places such as the depository, the seven major killing arrays, the Ten Thousand Killing Array, the Exquisite Pagoda, and so on. All of those areas were restricted, and outsiders were not allowed to enter. When the servants of the Tenth Prince and the Crown Prince had entered the mountain valley to observe the ranking war at the Ten Thousand Killing Array, it was only because the stage was distant and it was hard to see clearly.

Outside of these places, the other areas of the Seven Profound Martial House were not so strict. For instance, the lecture hall, Martial House square, and so forth. When Lin Ming had borrowed a Pass Card to enter the Zither Department to look up information on materials, this was also a place that was generally open to outsiders.

As long as one had a pass or were of aristocratic status, they could enter these places.

The Martial Stage was also one of these places.

The disciples of the Martial House occasionally held martial arts contest, and there were a few people that often came to the Martial Stage to observe from the sidelines.

But today, the Martial Stage was packed to the brim with people. These people were all extraordinary characters; there were the talents and geniuses of the Seven Profound Martial House, the heroes of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s martial artists, the nobility and aristocrats of Sky Fortune City, various famous and respected families, and important political figures.

Chapter 102 – The Focus Of All Eyes

But today, the Martial Stage was packed to the brim with people. These people were all extraordinary characters; there were the talents and geniuses of the Seven Profound Martial House, the heroes of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s martial artists, the nobility and aristocrats of Sky Fortune City, various famous and respected families, and important political figures.

Lin Ming was an inestimably rare talent that would appear only every 100 years at the Seven Profound Martial House. His rising star and bright halo was enough to attract the attention of most martial artists. Zhu Yan was also a first-class master of the Seven Profound Martial House; he had the possibility to be one of the top ten future talents of the Seven Profound Martial House. These two people’s match symbolized a duel between the top geniuses of Sky Fortune City’s younger generation.

If it was just this alone, it would not have attracted the nobility of Sky Fortune City and the political figures to gather here.

They did not belong in the circles of martial artists. No matter how strong Lin Ming or Zhu Yan were, this would be of no relation to any of them.

The reason this match would cause them to pay special attention was because there was political significance behind it!

The news of Lin Ming and Zhu Yan’s match had spread out far and wide long ago.

Everyone was aware that the Tenth Prince’s mother, the imperial concubine, came from Green Mulberry City’s Zhu Family. This Zhu Yan also had a very high possibility of being the next head of the Zhu Family. Zhu Yan was without a doubt a person of the Tenth Prince.

But Lin Ming had rejected the Tenth Prince’s advances when the Tenth Prince had tried to win him over a month ago, and instead was in favor of the Crown Prince. Moreover, according to reliable sources, Lin Ming and Zhu Yan had some sort of enmity between them, and Lin Ming and Mister Muyi were friends between generations. By virtue of these points alone, Lin Ming had an almost absolute possibility of being a person of the Crown Prince!

This match, while being a duel between Lin Ming and Zhu Yan, also symbolized the struggle between the Crown Prince and the Tenth Prince. These past few years, the hidden conflicts between the Crown Prince and the Tenth Prince had occurred often, but the Crown Prince had lost nearly every time! Although most of these battles had not genuinely wounded the Crown Prince’s strength, they had without a doubt weakened the Crown Prince’s momentum!

It was not a secret that the Tenth Prince wished to snatch the throne away. In this case, the Crown Prince had repeatedly suffered setbacks, and all of this perpetuated the notion that the Crown Prince was inferior to the Tenth Prince. Therefore, the people who supported the Crown Prince unavoidably panicked and were flustered, and less and less people supported the Crown Prince. Instead, the Tenth Prince’s influence only grew by the day!

Many of the nobility and aristocracy came today not to see the contest between Lin Ming and Zhu Yan, but the contest between the Tenth Prince and the Crown Prince! The sooner these people supported the man they thought would be the dragon who would ascend the throne, the larger the advantage they could obtain in the upcoming throne battle!

Because of the appearance of these nobles, there were special protections at the Martial Stage, and bodyguards to protect these important guests.

Due to too many important people attending, the disciples of the Seven Profound Martial House were pushed far away. This made them angry, and criticize these nobles in their hearts.

Lin Ming had already arrived. He stood quietly on the empty Martial Stage, his body as straight as Penetrating Rainbow.

Faced with the eyes of everyone looking at him, and so many of them being important people, Lin Ming closed his eyes and meditated, his mind calm and tranquil like a still lake.

In a battle between two of similar strength, one’s state of mind became very important. Even a slight change would affect the outcome of the battle.

The best condition for a martial artist’s mind before a battle was to be tranquil and still like water, not having even a single distracting thought. Though saying this was easy, a battle usually involved great significance; how could a martial artist settle down and keep their heart still under this condition? In addition to the disturbance from so many other possible factors, there were very few martial artists who were able to achieve this calm and tranquil mental state.

However, Lin Ming had comprehended martial intent and had achieved this state. To him, this was as easy as turning his hand over.

It was half an hour from the agreed match time. At this moment, a sharp, high-pitched voice suddenly called out; this was the unique sound of the palace court eunuch. “The Crown Prince arrives!”

Everyone was shocked; even Lin Ming who had been standing on the Martial Stage opened his eyes. His Highness the Crown Prince had unexpectedly come!

Accompanied by the clear clip clip clip sounds of hoofbeats, several Snow Dragon Horses appeared and started to come into view. They were led by a young man wearing a purple gold crown and a silk imperial robe. He wore a pair of Kirin styled boots, and delicate eyebrows framed his fair face. He had a broad forehead, and a very handsome face. His movements were filled with an innate, distinguished atmosphere.

This man was His Highness, the Crown Prince.

At the Crown Prince’s side was an old man wearing green clothes. His face had a warm and friendly smile, yet it gave off an immeasurably deep and unfathomable aura. This person was the Crown Prince’s teacher, the outsider from the Marshal’s Quarters, Mister Muyi!

“His Highness, the Crown Prince!”

“Mister Muyi!”

Seeing these two famous figures come together in unison caused everyone present to feel awe. They cleared a path for these to come forward.

Muyi looked at Lin Ming with a smile and a nod, and Lin Ming smiled in return. There was much goodwill and friendship between Muyi and Lin Ming.

But good things came in pairs. Similarly, after a half quarter hour, the Tenth Prince, the Cloud Prince, also arrived!

The Cloud Prince’s appearance and the Crown Prince’s appearance were somewhat similar. His appearance was only more resolute, his eyebrows were like swords that angled towards his temples, and above the center of his forehead was a vague purple cloud hidden under his skin. This was the legendary Purple Air Comes From the East, the King of Air!

At the Cloud Prince’s side was also a slender young man in silk clothes. This young man was Zhu Yan.

As soon as the Tenth Prince saw Lin Ming, he smiled with a ‘haha’. “Little Brother Lin, you’ve come very early. This is our first time meeting; it’s nice to meet you!”

Though his voice was loud, there was no arrogance in it. Instead, it was very comfortable and pleasant to listen to.

Lin Ming silently thought, “This Tenth Prince is also a character. I refused him at first, but he doesn’t seem to bear a grudge. On the surface he talks and laughs joyfully with me, as if nothing had ever happened before.”

“There seems to be some sort of silly misunderstanding between Little Brother Lin and Zhu Yan. The warriors of my Sky Fortune Kingdom have always resolved their hatred in a martial way. I happen to think that both of you are fine heroes among men. No matter what sort of misunderstanding or unhappiness occurred between you two, as soon as this fight is over, how about we sit down for a chat and see if we can put an end to these hostilities, and turn swords into plowshares?”

‘Turn swords into plowshares? I’m afraid Zhu Yan wants to eat my meat and flay me alive.’

Lin Ming understood that the Tenth Prince had said these words because he didn’t want to be his enemy. He politely responded, “I did not expect Your Highness the Cloud Prince to watch this match. It is my utmost honor and greatest pleasure to see you here.”

Lin Ming’s words were neither arrogant nor servile. He directly responded to the Tenth Prince. The Tenth Prince only smiled, and no longer said anything.

At this moment, Zhu Yan dismounted and slowly stepped up onto the Martial Stage. As soon he saw Lin Ming, he confirmed that this boy had made a breakthrough in this month!

Large Success of the Third Stage of Body Transformation!

Zhu Yan felt the enormous pressure, but did not feel that anything was wrong. When Lin Ming had challenged him with a deadline of one month, Zhu Yan had expected Lin Ming to make astonishing progress during this time. He had probably comprehended some kind of martial intent.

Zhu Yan arrived on the other side of the Martial Stage, and stood distantly opposite of Lin Ming.

There was a quarter hour until the decisive battle!

Lan Yunyue was among those in the crowd. She was distantly looking at Lin Ming and Zhu Yan on stage. He heart had overturned, and it was like all the good and bad emotions and feelings in her life had mixed together.

She was the one who was most unwilling to see this fight happen. Regardless of who was victorious or who was the defeated, each option would be a knife to her heart! Her eyes still reverberated with a phantom echo of those words Zhu Yan had said to her one month ago, “He wants me to… divorce you!”

She did not even dare to think what would happen if Zhu Yan were to lose, and how she would face life afterwards. She did not even have a chance to regret…

Although Lin Ming and Zhu Yan had already arrived, the battle had not started. Zhu Yan closed his eyes and meditated, adjusting to his own peak condition.

To him, Lin Ming was a formidable and daunting opponent. He had to adjust his pre-battle condition to its maximum, and display 120% of his strength!

Only half a year ago, Lin Ming had been an irrelevant loser, unworthy of even mentioning. Even if Lin Ming had defeated that child of General Wang, Wang Yigao, it was nothing to Zhu Yan.

In Zhu Yan’s eyes, Wang Yigao was a good-for-nothing playboy that was not fit to be called a martial artist.

Zhu Yan had not thought that there would be a day where he and Lin Ming would be standing against each other, and fighting on the Martial Stage in front of so many important people. Even the Crown Prince and the Cloud Prince had come to watch this fateful battle.

And beyond that, Lin Ming’s strength had also grown to the point of threatening him!

To prepare for this battle today, he had tortured himself for a month, and had even caused the foundation of his cultivation to be a bit unstable by enhancing his strength as much as possible with precious pills!

In the face of this battle, he too wished for a calm heart to face critical situations, to adjust his condition in this quarter hour before facing this great enemy!

This was a battle he could not afford to lose!

The victory and defeat of this battle not only concerned Zhu Yan’s future, but it concerned his dignity as a martial artist, and more so, his dignity as a man!

As the sundial shadow began to gradually move, it finally became noon. Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly flashed open.

“It’s time!”

Zheng–!

With a loud ringing sound, Lin Ming flourished his spear, Penetrating Rainbow. It was just like a dark purple flood dragon that shivered as it fell into Lin Ming’s hand! At this moment, Lin Ming had not fought, but his indomitable aura had already been released and it billowed outwards. Everyone present, even if their cultivation was higher than Lin Ming’s, felt an invisible pressure pushing down on them!

“This aura… is this really something that a martial artist at the Third Stage of Body Transformation can release!?”

“This Lin Ming is too strong, his imposing manner and aura are enough to make one feel breathless!”

Even the disciples of the Seven Profound Martial House were fearfully startled. This Lin Ming’s power was rising too fast! They hadn’t seen him in a month, and his strength had already risen to another level!

Zhu Yan took a deep breath and slowly drew out his treasure sword. This sword in his hand was a low-grade human-step treasure, one of the best among its kind. Its name was Scarlet Flare, and it had already accompanied him for many years. He had long ago been able to communicate with his sword.

Facing Lin Ming, it was impossible to count on his opponent being weak. He could only ask that his own strength was stronger!

Fu–!

With a light sound, Zhu Yan’s sword lit with flames visible to the naked eye! Substantializing true essence and giving it tangible form! This was a stage that only those a step away from reaching the Pulse Condensation Period could achieve. Generally only those who were at the Large Success of Bone Forging were able to reach this realm, but Zhu Yan, who was only at the early Altering Muscle stage, had already achieved this!

Lin Ming and Zhu Yan had not fought, but with just a few random movements, they had already displayed their frightening strength as the pinnacles among talents. This was a fierce struggle between two evenly matched opponents!

The entire Martial Stage audience was silent; even the sound of a pin dropping could be heard. The audience was silent with bated breath, and they steadily looking, with unblinking eyes, at the stage that held two solitary figures, for fear of missing even a single thing.

Chapter 105 – Torrential River Rope!

“Even though I will be punished, it is far better than being surpassed by Lin Ming in the future!”

“Moreover, a dead genius is no longer a genius. The Seven Profound Martial House will not kill me over someone who is dead. With the Tenth Prince secretly helping me, the worst that will happen is I will be dismissed from the Martial House and banished or exiled to the frontier.”

But to Zhu Yan, being banished didn’t mean anything anymore. As for being dismissed from the Martial House, although it was a pity, it was absolutely worth it as long as he could kill Lin Ming!

This was the only chance he had to assassinate Lin Ming!

But, did he really have the ability to kill Lin Ming?

In his heart, Zhu Yan lacked confidence.

“I still have my strongest martial skill. But, this martial skill has an enormous toll on the body. I can usually only display 60% of its full might, but if I recklessly stimulate myself to force out 100% of its abilities, I might damage my meridians. If I damage these meridians, it will be difficult to connect and open them, and become a great barrier when I want to break through to the Pulse Condensation Period. But since it’s come to this point, I have no other choices left.

Zhu Yan’s face flashed with ferociousness as he triggered all of the true essence in his body to the limit. The Scarlet Flare sword in his hand began to issue out a shrill, keening sound.

“Zhu Yan’s going to go all out!”

“What a terrifying true essence force! I’m afraid even a martial artist at the Bone Forging stage does not have such terrifying true essence!”

After everyone realized that Lin Ming had perceived the secrets of the ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ through meditation, no one doubted Zhu Yan’s strength again. That Zhu Yan could exchange blows for such a long time with a monstrous genius like Lin Ming was testament to his extraordinary skill.

Lin Ming faintly smiled as he felt a heavy murderous intent emanating from Zhu Yan. ‘You want to go all out? Then I’ll follow you!’

From the very start of the fight until now, Lin Ming had been gathering his potential!

Even though he had been using his full strength with every strike, he had been saving his momentum!

To constantly use moves and save momentum; this was the key to gathering one’s potential in a fight!

Now all of Lin Ming’s potential was poured into the Penetrating Rainbow spear, waiting for this last, final strike!

“This fight today, is the most important fight in my life so far. And Zhu Yan, he is also the most important opponent in my life so far. In the Seven Profound Martial House’s entrance examination’s Dream Trial, he was the cause for the flaw in my heart. Today, I and Zhu Yan will put forth our strongest moves, and I will defeat him to complete my perfect heart of martial arts!”

As Lin Ming walked forward step by heavy step, the hard floor tiles underneath him cracked and exploded into flying shards. Lin Ming’s right arm was flat and smooth, and lay upon Penetrating Rainbow. This was the most basic spear stance, ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’.

Yet in Lin Ming’s hands, even such a simple stance gave off a boundless feeling of vigor. The dark purple Penetrating Rainbow was calm as if it were a cast iron statue. It was like a rope that stretched across a torrential river. No matter how the river flowed and surged, it was unable to shake that rope a single inch.

Unmovable no matter the force, ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’!

“It’s the ‘Foundation Spear Technique’ stance, ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’!

“Heavens! I finally get to see Senior Apprentice Brother Lin Ming’s ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’ in action again!” A little girl half a year younger than Lin Ming clenched her fists in excitement. Her face was ruddy with joy. She had just entered the Human Hall.

To many of the lower disciples in the Human Hall, Lin Ming and his ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’ stance were a legend!

Many of the lower disciples from the Human Hall came from a humble birth and background, and their worth was meager. In the Seven Profound Martial House, because they were the most basic and lowest of disciples, they did not have any nice cultivation methods to choose from. Although they had the glory and honor of being a disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House, they did not entertain high hopes for the future.

However, Lin Ming, who had also came from a humble birth, had used the ‘Foundation Spear Technique’ to defeat Zhang Cang, a master of the Earth Hall! And he had used the ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’ stance!

This was a miracle!

In Lin Ming’s hands, the simple, minimalist ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’ stance had become tranquil and immutable like a mountain! Any magnificent or exquisite martial skill was broken by a single spear!

A lone strength to shatter 10,000 styles!

The only person in all of the Seven Profound Martial House who could use the ‘Foundation Spear Technique’ to resist Zhu Yan’s finishing blow was Lin Ming!

Facing Lin Ming’s ‘Iron Bridge Blocks the River’, Zhu Yan’s complexion became filled with unprecedented dignity.

This was the most important match in his entire life. Even if Lin Ming used the ‘Foundation Spear Technique’, he would not look down on a single fine hair of his. Against such a monstrous genius of perception, any cultivation method in his hands could be turned into a divine miracle!

“Hah!” Zhu Yan shouted. The silk clothes that covered his upper body began to burn up in flames from the searing air waves that were condensed by his true essence. The charred fragments of his clothes fluttered down to the floor.

Zhu Yan ripped off his robe like a slip of paper and tore it to shreds. He revealed a toned, muscular upper body, but because of the high amount of true essence that converged on him, his skin was red like a fiery demon.

The Scarlet Flame sword in his hands combusted into a brilliant, shimmering flame. Zhu Yan could not yet feel the fiery true essence damaging his meridians, but the pain was like countless flame needles that gripped him. However, this pain had actually filled Zhu Yan with a bloodthirsty excitement.

“Die!”

Zhu Yan’s still body suddenly soared upwards into the sky. Whistling flames in the air formed together into phantasmal illusions. Zhu Yan gripped his sword with both hands and lifted it high above his head. His spine curved like a drawn bow. Fire true essence began to gather all around Zhu Yan. It condensed together and turned into a blood-red lotus that began to quietly bloom in the air…

“Red Lotus Purgatory!”

The entire space seemed to flash black for a moment. This strange red lotus swallowed that dark light, and it was as if it contained not just true essence, but had also gathered the blazing sun!

Facing Zhu Yan’s killing move, at that moment, Lin Ming’s mind was calm like water. His ears had lost all outside noise, whether it was the sound of burning flames, or the cheers and shouts of the audience.

In his vision, he only saw Zhu Yan. In his heart, there was only the Penetrating Rainbow!

All of his momentum had gathered into Penetrating Rainbow. The strong true essence violently vibrated. Lin Ming thrusted out his spear, and it was like throwing down a mountain!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s spear and Zhu Yan’s ‘Red Lotus Purgatory’ frantically collided. There was a loud, deafening detonation like a rumbling thunderbolt. That intense collision of true essence sparked a fierce shockwave, along with a ‘ka ka ka’ sound as the Martial Stage was destroyed. Large broken pieces of tiles flew off everywhere in the air.

Peng!

A silhouette wrapped in crimson flames flew outwards and loudly hit a column on the Martial Stage. Along with a breaking sound, the stone column was smashed apart from the center!

This silhouette was Zhu Yan. At this moment his entire body was bathed in blood. He was unconscious on the ground, life or death unknown.

And Lin Ming was not feeling good. He was injured in the impact of that terrifying strike, and he had flown backwards several dozen feet before using Penetrating Rainbow to steady himself in the air and fall on the ground with the support of the spear shaft.

His blood began to roil, and he almost spat out blood, but by revolving the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, he was just able to press it down.

“What a ferocious move. If I had not learned to gather my momentum and set all of it aside for a final blow, then just that move a moment ago would have defeated me, the best case was both of us being wounded! The aftermath of the impact broke through my protection of vibrating true essence and only almost made me cough blood. This was thanks to my true essence from the Large Success in Viscera Training, otherwise that strike would have injured my internal organs and caused me to be severely wounded.”

“Zhu Yan’s last move had gone all out and overdrawn his strength. His injuries this time will not be light.”

…

Zi zi zi…

As the fragments of flames still burned, the entire audience was dead silent.

This was the pinnacle of battle! Even two peak Bone Forging martial artists could not be so intense!

Zhu Yan was already a top-tier talent, but Lin Ming had actually jumped up half a realm to defeat him!

“Did Zhu Yan die?”

“That last move of of Zhu Yan’s was an absolutely desperate one with his life on the line. ‘Red Lotus Purgatory’ is not a martial skill Zhu Yan can use. He has overdrawn his true essence.”

“Overdrawing true essence will harm one’s cultivation. For Zhu Yan to do that in order to win this match, his obsession runs too deep. But even so, Zhu Yan was defeated. This Lin Ming is truly terrifying!”

There were many masters and experts present; they had naturally seen how the final fight had played out.

Even several elders of the Martial House were present. They had seen the murderous killing intent contained in Zhu Yan’s final move.

“I find it strange. Even though Lin Ming’s perception is good, his martial talent is bad. It should be impossible for him to progress so quickly, and yet in these last two months his cultivation has leapt up an entire realm. How was this possible?”

“This… seems to be because Lin Ming has comprehended some kind of martial intent.”

“Martial intent? What’s that?”

“Well… I have only heard about it. I don’t know the specifics, but it should be powerful.”

Two of the low-level Human Hall disciples were having a casual conversation; however their conversation had been overheard by one of the top 50 disciples of the Ranking Stone. His eyes immediately widened, “What did you just say? Martial… martial intent? Lin Ming had comprehended a martial intent?”

“Uh, yes.” That low-order disciple said with a look of bewilderment.

“Who told you that!?”

That Heavenly Abode disciple was suddenly all excited; this made the low-order disciple feel a bit of fear. Facing a top 50 ranking disciple of the Heavenly Abode, it was impossible for them not to feel pressured.

“This… this matter was said by the deacon of the Icy Pond Waterfall, Senior Apprentice Brother Xie Dong…”

“Xie Dong…” The Heavenly Abode disciple gulped. Although Xie Dong had not reached the Pulse Condensation Period, he was a deacon who had worked at the Seven Profound Martial House for many years. His experience was vast, and it was impossible for him to be so wrong.

This Lin Ming, had actually managed to comprehend a martial intent!

The perception of a monstrous genius, a pure and strong heart of martial arts that was a cut above everyone else, and he also had a martial intent!

It was just too terrifying!

At this time, the medical personnel of the Seven Profound Martial House hurried onstage to apply medicine to Zhu Yan. But Lin Ming had already stepped down from the Martial Stage. His true essence had already been depleted from the fight, and at present his combat strength had fallen by several levels. He might not even be able to hold off a normal Third Stage of Body Transformation martial artist.

But still, there was a hidden aura on Lin Ming’s body that emanated. Along with his formidable strength and monstrous perception he had just displayed, this made those people looking at him feel bursts of pressure.

This was the dread that came from seeing a powerhouse.

When Lin Ming stepped down, several of those nearby pulled back. Even the martial artists that had been famous for a long time stepped made way with respect. And those low-order disciples who had idolized him, only worshipped him Lin Ming with more fanaticism.

“Mister Lin Ming! Congratulations!” Crown Prince Yang Lin stood up from afar and warmly greeted him. Among his words was just the right amount of veneration. This was the respect he demonstrated to a powerhouse, and had disregarded his status.

Chapter 112 – Crazy Zhu Yan

In order to avoid the eyes and ears of the Crown Prince, Wang Gan circled around the Cloud Prince’s palace a few times. He had wrapped himself in a cloak and entered the palace through the back door. Like this, he had come to the Cloud Prince to especially explain why he had been at the Crown Prince’s banquet, and also to report on the evil doings of Zhu Yan. The Tenth Prince probably wouldn’t like to hear about Zhu Yan, but Wang Gan had his own spin to add to the story.

He did not directly explain why he went to the Crown Prince’s palace and attended his banquet. Instead, he began by borrowing the Tenth Prince’s status in the army, and reporting to him about military affairs. He recommended to the Tenth Prince a brave father and son pair that had performed many meritorious military services. From this, he went back and forth on the greatness of such a father and son pairing, and then woefully sighed to himself about how his own household had suffered such misfortune and raised such a useless child. He then slowly edged in the matter of several months ago, where his good-for-nothing evil child had provoked Lin Ming, and then accidently dropped Zhu Yan’s name…

How could the Cloud Prince not know the meaning behind Wang Gan’s story? When he heard Wang Gan mention Zhu Yan time and time again, the Tenth Prince’s expression fell. He hadn’t known that Lin Ming and Wang Gan’s son had such a conflict on the day of the entrance examination, and that the instigator of this accident was Zhu Yan.

“Major Wang, you’ve worked hard today. Please head back to rest as soon as possible.” The Cloud Prince said with a blank expression.

“Yes, then I will excuse myself.” Wang Gan’s goal had already been achieved. Although the position he had in Sky Fortune City’s government was not too big or too small, it was actually a very sensitive and important middle-level commanding role. Wang Gan had to be constantly cautious in order to preserve his own head, and he had done that very well.

…

Sky Fortune City, Zhu Family Branch –

Zhu Yan was wearing white pants. His hair was disheveled as he lay down on the bed. He had a dejected look as he peered outside the window. His eyes passed through the layered windows of the complex as he stared at the brilliantly illuminated palace of the Crown Prince. He knew that today the Crown Prince was holding a grand banquet at his palace, and the star of that party was Lin Ming.

Thinking of Lin Ming, Zhu Yan clenched the bed sheets. The fine and expensive bed sheets were torn apart in Zhu Yan’s grip.

In that fight several days ago, he had seriously injured himself! The ‘Red Lotus Purgatory’ was a martial skill that he hadn’t been able to fully utilize yet. In doing so, he had overdrawn the true essence in his body and damaged his meridians. Zhu Yan’s cultivation was insufficient, and he had barely used it. In addition to the enormous load on his body, he had been pushed back by Lin Ming’s spear. The result was an even more severe injury on Zhu Yan!

The wounds of the flesh were easy to cure with good medicines and pills, but damage to the meridians was very hard to recover from. This kind of wound would become a major hindrance when he was breaking through to the Pulse Condensation Period!

“Damnit!”

Peng! The velvet pillow under Zhu Yan suddenly exploded. The countless snow white feathers fluttered around the room like snowflakes in winter.

“Ah!” Lan Yunyue jumped in fear as she covered her mouth. Zhu Yan was moody, and this caused her to feel not even the least bit of security. One moment he was quiet, and the next moment he would be filled with anger like a raging beast.

Lan Yunyue’s scream caused Zhu Yan to suddenly look at Lan Yunyue.

As soon as Zhu Yan’s eyes fell on her, Lan Yunyue’s breath caught in her chest. The look Zhu Yan gave her made her feel as if she was being submerged in an icy bath. She thought that Zhu Yan might even kill her now.

There was a pause before Zhu Yan suddenly asked, “Do you regret?”

“What… what regrets?” Lan Yunyue panicked. She took a deep breath, and tried to sound as calm as possible.

“You know what I’m talking about.”

Lin Ming’s present achievements were already several times more dazzling than Zhu Yan. Without a doubt, his achievements in the future would far outstrip Zhu Yan. Zhu Yan believed that with Lan Yunyue’s pragmatic heart, she would inevitably regret to the extreme.

“The Crown Prince is hosting the grandest of banquets. He is there. If you regret then you may go there and look for him. That sort of banquet, there are all sorts of celebrities and famous, influential figures. The aristocratic young ladies there wear magnificent and expensive attire, and their manners and poise are elegant. Isn’t that what you’ve always wanted? You may go now.”

Zhu Yan’s calm voice brought an icy chill with it. It caused Lan Yunyue to feel fearful and apprehensive. She knew that today, Zhu Yan was walking on the edge of a cliff. If she really did say she ‘regretted’, she did not know what he would do in his rage.

Lan Yunyue was on pins and needles. She clenched her lips and said, “I no longer have any qualifications to regret anything anymore.”

Zhu Yan evilly smiled, and revealed the corners of his teeth. “You are very honest. At least you weren’t hypocritical and said you didn’t regret. Good. You truly do not have the qualifications to regret. Such being the case, take off your clothes!”

“What!?” Lan Yunyue subconsciously grabbed her own collar in surprised. “Zhu Yan, we are not married.”

“Marriage? Lan Yunyue, you do not understand your position and identity. Do you think that you are a princess? The reason I have not made an advance on you is because I respected you. But you, you must at least have the qualifications that are worth me respecting! Have you ever had me for even a moment in your heart? Now prove it to me, take off your clothes!”

“Zhu Yan, you…” Lan Yunyue felt an impending sense of alarm and subconsciously leaned towards the door. Before this, Zhu Yan’s disposition had already been dark, with a sense of high-risk danger. But the truth was that Zhu Yan had never made a move on Lan Yunyue. In fact, most of the time he had been the very image of a gentleman’s gentleman.

But today Lan Yunyue did not doubt that Zhu Yan would rape her. Because of his failures and frustration from his defeat in the match, as well as his future setbacks, he had already become similar to a wild, angry beast.

Zhu Yan saw Lan Yunyue’s petty actions and his voice lowered in anger, “Although I am injured, I am more than enough to deal with you. I advise you not to move towards the entrance. If you take another step towards the door, I don’t mind personally moving.”

“Zhu… Zhu Yan…” Lan Yunyue bit her lip. Tears had already begun to form at the corners of her eyes. She grabbed the collar of her clothes, and her knuckles and already turned white from the excessive gripping.

Her voice trembled as she said, “You lost to Lin Ming in the match, and you think that by abusing a woman that Lin Ming had liked, you will be able to retaliate and vent your anger against him! Is this your heart of martial arts!? Zhu Yan, why must you use this method to psychologically comfort yourself? Does this make you feel better?”

“What did you say?” Zhu Yan’s face had completely sunk. Every word Lan Yunyue said had punished his heart and poked his sore spot. The reason he wanted to move on Lan Yunyue today was exactly because of this repression that he could vent or retaliate against.

He hated. He hated everything about Lin Ming. He urgently needed to find somewhere, anywhere, where he could be just a tiny bit better than Lin Ming. He would take complete possession of the woman Lin Ming used to like, in order to rid his heart of its demons!

But, his thoughts had been bluntly revealed by Lan Yunyue. To look for a sense of superiority in a woman’s body; this made Zhu Yan feel extremely pitiful!

Therefore, he became angry out of his shame!

He revolved his true essence, and was about to pounce on her. But at this moment, a voice sounded behind the door. The old servant’s voice resounded from outside, “Young Master, the Tenth Prince has come.”

“Mm?” Zhu Yan frowned. The true essence that he had begun to circulate gradually calmed down.

Lan Yunyue was strained to her limit. Her body was up against the wall, and she slowly slid down against the floor. Her back was covered in nervous sweat. In this past month, the name of the Tenth Prince had been her nightmare. At that time, with just a few words, he had almost caused Zhu Yan to renounce their engagement and divorce her. But now, hearing the Tenth Prince’s arrival, it actually made her feel incomparably relieved.

Zhu Yan rose up and began to dress himself silently. To see the Tenth Prince, he would naturally neatly dress himself and greet him in the hall. Only someone whose wound was too heavy or was terminally ill would meet in their bedroom.

However, as Zhu Yan was putting on clothes, there was the sound of disorderly footsteps outside.

The door opened, and the Tenth Prince stood at the entrance. He had a few followers with him, and his face was calm, showing neither joy nor anger.

“Greetings, Your Highness.” Zhu Yan bowed. Lan Yunyue also stood and bowed, before she moved back to a corner of the room.

According to customs, when an official bowed to the prince, the prince would dispense with the ceremony with a show of words. However, the Tenth Prince had not said anything, and Zhu Yan had bowed.

“You know Wang Yigao?” The Tenth Prince suddenly asked. This question made Lan Yunyue feel completely senseless.

Zhu Yan immediately understood that the Tenth Prince was referring to the matter that happened at the beginning of fall. Otherwise, it would be impossible for the Tenth Prince to mention such an unimportant person like Wang Yigao so suddenly. Because Lin Ming had become famous, Wang Yigao had been held accountable and confessed to his father, which was then passed to the ears of the Tenth Prince.

“Yes.” Zhu Yan admitted. He knew that the reason Lin Ming favored the Crown Prince might be because of this matter. He had not mentioned it at his own initiative, but now it was known by the Tenth Prince.

“Very good. Now I know why it was so easy for my third elder brother to win over Lin Ming. You might not have known, but the one who had rescued Lin Ming from Wang Yigao was my third elder brother! This is simply icing on the cake, how much more timely could that help have been? You have been under my command for two years already, and you still have not even had half a minute of merit, and yet you already have given third elder brother such a great present. You may know that the Seven Profound Valleys has already started Lin Ming on the core disciple test tonight. As long as he passes, then he will be a core disciple!”

Zhu Yan’s heart maliciously twitched. Core disciple!

This was unthinkable. In the entire Sky Fortune Kingdom, only Qin Xingxuan was a locally born core disciple!

As for the others, they were children of the mystical martial arts families.

“Zhu Yan, do you know what the value of a Martial House core disciple is to me and my third elder brother?” The Tenth Prince expression was a bit grim. A core disciple of the Martial House would enter the Seven Profound Valleys in the future. Afterwards, they would either stay at the Seven Profound Valleys, or be sent back. In the second case, they would be appointed as either the Seven Profound Martial House’s Martial House Master, or as a Seven Profound Envoy.

If Lin Ming stayed at the Seven Profound Valleys, that would be alright. But if he was sent back to become the Martial House Master or a Seven Profound Envoy, then that was extraordinary!

The Sky Fortune Kingdom was a vassal state to the Seven Profound Valleys and under their jurisdiction. The Martial House Master and the Seven Profound Envoy had a status that surpassed even the emperor!

If Lin Ming was appointed as the Martial House Master or as a Seven Profound Envoy and publicly supported the Crown Prince, then there was no hope for him to ascend the throne!

And if he failed to ascend the throne, then the price would possibly be his life!

Zhu Yan clenched his fists so hard that his nails dug into the meat of his palm. Core disciple! How was this even possible!? If Lin Ming someday became the Martial House Master of the Seven Profound Martial House, or a Seven Profound Envoy, then to kill him would be as simple as crushing an ant. Thinking of this, he felt as if he were sinking in a bottomless well of despair.

This enmity, could it ever be fixed?

Lan Yunyue was slumped up against a wall, and her face had lost all of its color. Core disciple… Lin Ming, he wanted to become a core disciple?

In the future he would be the Seven Profound Martial House’s Martial House Master or he might be a Seven Profound Envoy…

To her, this kind of existence was nothing but simply fanciful legends; it was simply too remote an idea for her.

At this moment, the Tenth Prince also noticed Lan Yunyue. He had thought that Lan Yunyue was a maidservant, but after noticing the fine clothes Lan Yunyue was wearing, he realised he had been mistaken. “You are… Lan Yunyue?

Chapter 116 – Maddening Materials

Body inscription was a type of inscription drawn onto the body. It was able to increase a martial artist’s cultivation speed or enhance their battle prowess.

As with objection inscription symbols, there was a limit to how many could be placed. The amount differed depending on the grade of the body inscription symbol as well as the physical condition of the martial artist. For body inscription symbols, the most one could draw were about four or five.

With his match against Zhang Guanyu approaching in four months, he had to draw up a body inscription symbol within a month in order to display its greatest effects, otherwise the quality of the effect would be lessened, or it might even be a complete waste of time!

However, to draw up a body inscription symbol in a month was as difficult as ascending to heaven!

Although Lin Ming had the memories of the soul fragment, in order to successfully create one, it would still take a long time and also use up a massive amount of rare and precious materials in order to practice!

Practicing it was simple. What was difficult was finding a way to collect all of the incomparably rare and precious materials that were needed for the body inscription symbol. The degree to which these materials were rare and precious caused Lin Ming to shudder in fear!

In the elder’s memory, of the simplest body inscriptions, there were two. One was the Essence Gathering Symbol which could increase the speed of cultivation, and the other was the Strife Seal which could increase a martial artist’s combat prowess.

However, even if it were these two simplest body inscription symbols, the list of materials that needed to be used would make anyone go nuts!

Just the fifth level vicious beast blood, a single tael of this precious fluid would cost 30,000 gold taels. Lin Ming needed to buy 2 taels, which would mean 60,000 gold taels. And not only that, but it simply wasn’t something that could be bought by just anyone.

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, there was no one who was able to match up against a fifth level vicious beast. For a fifth level vicious beast, perhaps only a peak Houtian master would be barely able to deal with it!

These kinds of martial artists usually came from a large sect or an aristocratic martial cultivation family. The blood of a fifth level vicious beast would only flow out from a large sect and then into the smaller countries. To these small countries, its price would be frighteningly astronomical.

Then there was Star Obsidian. This material came from a meteorite that fell from the sky. The high temperature in the atmosphere would condense. This iron essence could only be naturally formed by the power of the heavens and earth, and beyond that, not every meteorite would have Star Obsidian. Only those meteorites that were above several thousand jins would possibly be able to produce 1 or 2 jins of Star Obsidian. The lowest market price of a single jin of obsidian was 150,000 gold taels!

And it was extremely difficult to find!

Fortunately, Lin Ming only needed two taels.

Lin Ming estimated that if everything was bought that the lowest market price, and he bought these materials whenever he could find them, then the total of these materials would need at least 300,000 taels. This was simply a dream within a dream!

Of the materials he needed, many were like the fifth level vicious beast blood and Star Obsidian. They just didn’t have a market price. So that meant that more gold would have to be spent. The amount he would need might even go up to 500,000, or even 700,000 wouldn’t be strange!

And even if he managed to somehow obtain 6 or 700,000 taels of gold, he would be incredibly lucky to obtain these materials in a couple of years. If his luck was garbage, then he might not be able to find these materials even if he looked for 10 years.

On the list of materials, the most basic ones would be considered precious valuables within Sky Fortune City’s Inscription Association!

And one also needed points from the Inscription Association in order to buy anything. The last time Lin Ming went there; he had already used up most of his points, and didn’t have many left. Without points, these so called ‘basic’ materials would not be sold at any price.

These would be the treasures of the Inscription Association.

Looking at the list gave Lin Ming a throbbing headache. It was simply impossible for him to find all of these; he could only rely on the Crown Prince.

This was one of the benefits of joining a major power. The Crown Prince’s subordinates were numerous, and they had wide channels and networks they could work through; they could do him a great favor in helping him.

Yet even if the Crown Prince made every effort, he would be limited in obtaining the materials.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming shook his head and ruefully smiled. “I joined the Crown Prince as one of his subordinates, and still haven’t done a single thing, yet I actually want to make a sudden demand to find such a large amount of materials. And these precious and rare materials can’t even be found in the city. Even if they were the relatively basic materials that I need, the Crown Prince would not be able to purchase them easily.”

Lin Ming knew that the Crown Prince was not wealthy. Even though the Crown Prince’s palace looked opulent and grand; the palace had to hire several hundred people and pay them for their work. There were also several other expenses. In addition to the banquet, the Crown Prince gave gifts, rewards, and other such expenditures in order to win over others and raise his own influence. The annual amount of money that he spent was probably around 2 to 300,000 gold taels.

For instance, when the Crown Prince had given Lin Ming a gift of more than 100 pure true essence stones, the cost of that had been several tens of thousands of gold tales. The manor that was situated near Sky Fortune City along with 100 acres of fertile farmland, servants, maids, and so forth would cost at least 100,000 gold taels. In addition, there was also the Purple Gold Flexible Armor; added up altogether, it must have been more than 300,000 gold taels!

Because the large expenditures, the economic situation of the Crown Prince might even be inferior to those famous inscription masters that had been working a long time. For example, Muyi, Wang Xuanji, and those kinds of people; they had a high income, and their spending was low. After amassing money for many years, they were overflowing with riches.

The Crown Prince used a very large amount of money. Depending on just his salary from the government, this would be utterly inadequate. The Crown Prince’s income mostly came from his estate, farms, and also stores.

The estate and paddies were things like the manor that had been bestowed upon Lin Ming. But as for shops, Lin Ming actually knew that the Crown Prince didn’t have many. This was because the biggest and busiest shops of Sky Fortune City were firmly grasped in the hands of the Allied Trade Association.

Compared to the Tenth Prince who constantly campaigned in all directions and plundered countless lands, the Crown Prince was very poor. Because he was poor, he could not win over others, and thus the Crown Prince’s influence was suppressed by the Tenth Prince.

“The cost of the all the gifts that the Crown Prince gifted me should total to around 300,000 gold taels. For the Crown Prince to suddenly hand so much over to me, he probably doesn’t have much money on hand at the moment. I just received so many gifts, yet now I also want materials; it just isn’t too appropriate. However, I have to ask for these materials; otherwise I will never be able to collect them on my own. Originally, finding the materials for the medicinal inscription symbol already took a very big effort on my part, and this body inscription symbol’s materials are much more precious. I just don’t have any way left but to ask the Crown Prince to help me find them. As for the money, I will find a solution… but first I should return the manor to the Crown Prince…”

“With the two body inscription symbols, the Essence Gathering Symbol and the Strife Seal, in addition to my ethereal martial intent, ‘Flow like Silk’ ability, and the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, I will have the confidence to face Zhang Guanyu four months from now. But I’m not sure if I can reach Ling Sen in 6 months. This Ling Sen, the stronger I am, the more I can sense just how terrifying he actually is…”

“But provided that the Crown Prince can help me find the materials I need for the inscription symbol, there are certain materials I listed that might only be found in a sect. With just the Crown Prince’s connections, how many would I be able to find?”

…

Inscription Association, Inscription Hall –

Lin Ming had just stepped into the Inscription Association and was immediately discovered by the young reception lady who had received him last time. The young lady’s eyes lit up, and she immediately put down the task she had been working on. She quickly walked over to Lin Ming, her breath somewhat rapid.

These days, there were many people in Sky Fortune City that knew the name Lin Ming. But although they were able to recognize Lin Ming’s name, and they didn’t know what he looked like. However, this young reception lady had once been responsible for Lin Ming’s inscription master examination and had his information. The Inscription Association of course knew that the dazzlingly bright star of Sky Fortune City and the number one genius of the Seven Profound Martial House was exactly the young man who had participated in the inscription master examination.

This was an amazing character!

“Mister Lin.” The young receptionist lady greeted with a sweet smile. She bent her small waist in a courtesy bow towards Lin Ming. Her beautiful figure combined with the secretary clothing had a flavorful appeal.

“Oh, it’s you. I’d like to speak to the association president.” Lin Ming said. He recognized this young reception lady.

“Very well. Please follow me.” The receptionist lady felt her palpitating heartbeat began to race. She was incomparably excited that Lin Ming had remembered her.

“Sorry for troubling you.”

“It is my honor to serve Mister Lin.” The young receptionist lady went straight to the inscription room. At this time every day, the association president would be at the inscription room. This was the time that he would teach his granddaughter. For Wang Xuanji, no matter how much time he spent on his martial arts cultivation or inscription technique, it would be difficult for him to have a breakthrough. Because of this, he had invested the majority of his efforts into his granddaughter.

The young receptionist lady opened the door to the inscription hall. This was the second time Lin Ming had been here. The first time was when he had taken his examination here.

At this moment, Wang Xuanji was sitting on a green jade platform. He was directing the fingers of a young girl at his side. This young girl was wearing the white robes of an inscription master. Her appearance was delicate, like fine, white dust. She was Wang Xuanji’s granddaughter, Wang Yuhan.

After Wang Xuanji noticed some people had arrived, he turned his head to look and was shocked.

“Mister Lin?”

“President Wang.” Lin Ming smiled and bowed in deference.

“Oh! Mister Lin is an infrequent visitor. It’s been a long time since you last came. I did not think that Mister Lin would not only be talented in inscription techniques, but also talented in martial arts! To be only 15 years old and be able to defeat the 32nd ranked disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House; your future is truly limitless!”

“President Wang praises me too much.” Lin Ming was not surprised that the Inscription Association was already aware of his situation.

Wang Yuhan also stopped her inscription technique that she was working on. She had a complicated look as she stared at Lin Ming. She was already extremely talented, with a fourth-grade martial talent and a fifth-grade soul talent. With this talent, her qualifications already surpassed that of Bai Jingyun and Murong Zi. In the aristocratic circles, those young juniors that wanted to marry Wang Yuhan were no less than those ardent fans of Bai Jingyun and Murong Zi.

But compared with this young man in her eyes, she simply felt too ashamed to even step out in public. The difference between her and Lin Ming’s inscription technique was already miles apart; it was simply comparing the Heavens to the Earth. She didn’t even want to think about the difference in their battle prowess. Wang Yuhan had devoted most of her energy into practicing inscription techniques, but in the martial arts aspect, she also only paid attention to cultivating. This was because inscription techniques required a deep amount of true essence, and therefore one had to have a high enough cultivation. As for fighting skills, Wang Yuhan knew nothing of those from the start. Let alone those monstrous geniuses of the Seven Profound Martial House, she would even lose to someone at the same cultivation level as her.

How the hell did this fellow practice? She had been practicing inscription techniques since she was 8 years old, and in her life she had always prioritized her cultivation and specialized in inscription techniques. Even if it was the monstrous talent Qin Xingxuan, she could compare with her in terms of inscription techniques.  And recently she had progressed very fast; perhaps she might have even surpassed Qin Xingxuan.

But in contrast to this Lin Ming, Wang Yuhan was completely at a loss for words. Even if he started practicing inscription techniques from his mother’s womb, why would his level of skill be so bizarrely abnormal? She was still working hard at training the basics of finger movements, but he had already been able to use the ‘Bright Buddha Plucks the Lotus’.

“Mister Lin comes today, is there matter you need to discuss?”

As Wang Xuanji asked this, Lin Ming did feel somewhat embarrassed. For better or worse he was a registered inscription master of the Inscription Association. However, after registering and obtaining some materials, he hadn’t returned. And now that he finally came back, it was also for materials to use for inscription symbols.

Chapter 125 – Masochistic Cultivation

The deacon senior apprentice brother was totally confused; were there monsters inside of the Violent Wind Tunnel?

No, that was impossible. The Violent Wind Tunnel was used daily; how would there be monsters inside? Or had he made a mistake with the difficulty level? He turned around and looked at the array formation’s panel board; it was indeed the seventh level of difficulty.

But, why would Junior Apprentice Brother Lin’s appearance be so shabby? What happened inside?

Could it be that Junior Apprentice Brother Lin’s footwork technique was not steady?

That was also impossible. He remembered on the martial stage that Junior Apprentice Brother Lin had been steady like a towering mountain. It was impossible for there to be anything wrong with his footwork technique.

In this case, Lin Ming simply couldn’t explain. He said, “Senior Apprentice Brother, could I trouble you to reduce the difficulty by a level, and open up the sixth level of difficulty.

At the seventh level of difficulty, the wind velocity was just too fast. The time Lin Ming was airborne for was too short. Just as he was about to feel the origin of the wind, he would immediately smash into the wall.

So he hoped to reduce the difficulty by a bit. To comprehend the concept of wind, he did not need to resist the strength of the wind. The force of the wind also did not matter.

“You want to reduce the difficulty?” The deacon senior apprentice brother was becoming a bit paranoid, but he hadn’t figured out how to open his mouth and ask Lin Ming.

Lin Ming once again entered the wind tunnel, and through numerous trials, he began to feel like he was starting to be able to sense the concept of wind. He wanted to use this opportunity to step into the threshold of the wind concept in one fell swoop.

After his 8 hours of practice time had ended, Lin Ming had already hit the wall at least ten thousand times. If it wasn’t for the top-quality injury medicine he had brought, the impact of so many hits would have already left him with several internal injuries.

At this point, there wasn’t a single spot on Lin Ming’s body that wasn’t bruised. When he swapped clothes and stepped out of the tunnel, the deacon senior apprentice brother was completely confused.

Standing by the deacon was a disciple of the Heavenly Abode. He didn’t recognize Lin Ming in his current ragged condition. He only thought, ‘Which wonderful low-order disciple is this? You couldn’t even think to open up a low level of difficulty? Was there a need to be so masochistic in your practice?’

“Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, what in the world were you doing in there?” The deacon senior apprentice brother asked.

“Practicing.” Lin Ming faintly smiled. Having given a perfunctory answer, he didn’t wait for the deacon to ask him another question, and left.

The disciple that was still waiting there asked, “Junior Apprentice Brother Lin? Which Lin? Lin Wu? That’s not right, although Lin Wu is a little weak, he’s not that bad.”

The deacon sent an ill-humored look at the disciple and snappily said, “Junior Apprentice Brother Lin Ming!”

“Lin Ming? Haha, Senior Apprentice Brother, your joke is too funny. If that Lin Ming can actually end up like that in that level of difficulty in the Violent Wind Tunnel, then I’ll walk in reverse from now on.”

“You can walk however you want to. Next time if you don’t believe then look yourself.” The deacon senior apprentice brother was disinclined to bother with the disciple. He began to close the formation array; it was about time for him to get off work.

…

After Lin Ming returned to his cabin that night, he prepared a boiled bathtub full of medicinal herbs. As soon as he stripped his clothes, he jumped in and soaked inside the bathtub for two hours. The wounds on his body began to slowly mend themselves. As he sat in the tub and mediated for the night, by the next day his flesh had absorbed the potency of the medicinal herbs and his bruises had disappeared.

The cost of that bathtub full of medicinal herbs was around 7000 taels of gold. Before, the amount of gold that he had spent on raw materials would have been enough for him to practice for 7 or 8 years. But presently, that bathtub of medicine had already been completely used up. This caused Lin Ming to sigh with emotion. If one wanted to cultivate martial arts but didn’t have money, then no matter what talent they had it would be useless.

Yesterday, he had gone through 8 hours of masochistic practice. Lin Ming had finally touched upon the concept of wind, but still hadn’t managed to cross the threshold. He was still far from being able to grasp that wind concept.

With such an esoteric and profound ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’, Lin Ming hadn’t expected to be able to cultivate it within a short time. Still, just practicing it a little was infinitely enjoyable.

Today, Lin Ming did not go to the Violent Wind Tunnel. He needed a period of time to let his body fully assimilate the experiences he had obtained yesterday.

Therefore he lit a sound transmitting talisman and passed a message to Wang Yuhan. Today, he would be going to the Inscription Association.

…

In the past few days, a modest affair had happened in Sky Fortune City. The Zhu Family had announced that because Zhu Yan had violated the family rules, his punishment was that he had been expelled from the family. Not only that, but the Tenth Prince, the Cloud Prince, had drawn a distinct line between him and Zhu Yan.

This matter had been dealt with in a very low-profile manner. However, all the major powers had taken note of this event. Everyone knew that Zhu Yan and Lin Ming had a grudge between them, and some of the even more informed ones knew that this was related to Lan Yunyue.

According to some reliable sources, Zhu Yan and Lin Ming were deep love rivals involved in a messy love triangle. They had many small battles, and their conflict became increasingly intense. At this point, the Zhu Family had expelled Zhu Yan from their ranks, and the Tenth Prince had drawn a line with Zhu Yan. Just what was the meaning of this?

Many people thought that the Zhu Family and the Tenth prince had done this in order to show a measure of good will towards Lin Ming. In order to woo Lin Ming to their side, they had directly expelled a talented person from their main family. But wasn’t this just too crude and reckless?

Although Lin Ming was amazingly strong, he was obviously close to the Crown Prince and on his side. If the Tenth Prince was unable to win over Lin Ming and had still expelled Zhu Yan, then wasn’t this double penalty simply giving an enemy one’s own wife as well as losing one’s own soldiers?

What was the reason behind the Tenth Prince’s actions?

After Lin Ming heard this news, he also felt it somewhat incomprehensible. Did the Tenth Prince make this decision in order to show good will? Was it necessary?

“Zhu Yan was expelled from the family and he also left the Seven Profound Martial House. I must be careful of him. He is living a gloomy life but he knows how to bear the suffering. This would greatly strengthen his toughness. Later, he will certainly try go against me somehow. My strength is growing and I am not afraid, but my parents are in Green Mulberry City. I must inform the Lin Family about this and have my parents protected.

“Unfortunately I did not kill him when I could on that stage, and now I’ve left a future trouble!”

A cold chill crept into Lin Ming’s eyes. Although he had not bothered pursuing when Wang Yigao and Wang Yanfeng had tried dealing with him using cruel methods, but that did not mean he was a soft-hearted person, especially when faced with the possibility that something could endanger the safety of his loved ones.

Thinking this, Lin Ming sent out a sound transmitting talisman to Sky Fortune City’s Lin Family branch, exhorting them about his parents’ situation.

…

That afternoon, Lin Ming had decided to go to the Inscription Association, which was why he had made an appointment with Wang Yuhan.

As he was walking down the road, Lin Ming suddenly stopped. He had run into a person. Lin Ming already had an impression of this person; he was a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist who worked under the Crown Prince – Liao Wenyuan.

The Crown Prince had helped Liao Wenyuan in his career and had shown him kindness. Before Liao Wenyuan had gained fame and fortune, a young Crown Prince had helped him. That stroke of graciousness and been unforgettably valuable.

That was why even though Liao Wenyuan now had a title and a rapidly advancing career, he had still decided to enter into the turbid waters of the struggle over the throne, and was willing to assist the Crown Prince in ascending the throne.

“Mister Lin.” Liao Wenyuan cupped his fist in a polite greeting towards Lin Ming.

“Senior Liao is too polite; this junior should be the one bowing to Mister Liao.” Lin Ming cupped his fist and returned a courtesy bow towards Liao Wenyuan.

Lin Ming didn’t find it surprising that he met Liao Wenyuan here. These days, he had felt eyes on him as he walked down the streets, as if people were intentionally or unintentionally following him. But, these people did not have any murderous or dangerous intent; they were obviously sent by the Crown Prince.

Lin Ming’s status was extremely sensitive. As soon as he took even one step out of the Seven Profound Martial House, there would be people immediately following him and protecting him in the shadows. It could be said that if the Tenth Prince wanted to kill him in Sky Fortune City, it wouldn’t be much easier than killing the Crown Prince himself.

The Crown Prince was apparently aware that he was often visiting the Inscription Association these days.

“Haha, I didn’t think that Mister Lin would know my name. To be truthful, I am a rather crude person and a I’m not too comfortable with these courtesies. If you don’t mind, I will be rude and call Mister Lin, Brother Lin instead.”

Lin Ming smiled, “Brother Liao’s words are frank and straightforward. Truth be told, I also do not like etiquette and honorifics.”

“Haha, that’s great! Brother Lin, today I came to especially look for you. You may or may not know, but Zhu Yan has been expelled from the Zhu Family.” Liao Wenyuan had sent these words via true essence sound transmission.

“Mm.” Lin Ming nodded, and also changed to speaking with true essence sound transmission.

“You must be careful of Zhu Yan.”

“I know, but I also find something strange. Why was the Zhu Family so ruthless?”

“This ruthlessness is because of Brother Lin. You have a possibility of becoming a Seven Profound Envoy or the Martial House Master. With that status, whether it is the Zhu Family or the Tenth Prince, they do not dare to annoy you. But to them, Zhu Yan will at most be a Pulse Condensation Martial artist in the future. A Pulse Condensation Period martial artist is an acceptable loss, so they drove him out. Later, Zhu Yan will hate you and try to assassinate you. If this happens, then Zhu Yan will take the blame and the Zhu family and the Tenth Prince will not be implicated.”

“So it’s like that… well, when it comes to the internal struggles of the large families and royal powers, not even family will be spared.” Lin Ming had no interest in things like the royal power struggle and large family interests.

“Yes, that’s why since ancient times a ruler must be crafty, otherwise it would be impossible for them to accomplish anything.” Liao Wenyuan paused and sighed. He was thinking of the humanity and righteousness of the Crown Prince, who unfortunately had insufficient determination.

“Ah, that’s right, Brother Lin, you had previously asked His Highness the Crown Prince to look for some materials, we have already begun to search for them. However, there are some things that the Sky Fortune Kingdom does not have. The Crown Prince has already sent people to the neighboring countries to look. The Huoluo Nation’s trade fair has things from all around, it should be possible to find some materials there. But to collect all the materials, it will take a long time. As for the matter of the manor that Brother Lin wishes to return, His Highness the Crown Prince has said that he has already gifted the land to Brother Lin, how could he take it back? Brother Lin, please feel relieved about that matter.”

Huoluo Nation was one of the larger countries under the governance of the Seven Profound Valleys. Regardless of military forces, or the number of masters they had, all of it surpassed the Sky Fortune Kingdom. Huoluo Nation’s trade fair was famous and very well-known within the surrounding area of 100,000 miles. It was only that it was too far from the Sky Fortune Kingdom. Even if one rode a Snow Dragon Horse that could cross 2000 miles in one day, it would still take a dozen or so days to arrive there.

With the time it took to get to Huoluo Nation, coupled with the time it took to find the materials, and the fact that some materials couldn’t necessarily be bought, it was wrong to depend solely on the Crown Prince to obtain the complete list of materials for the body inscription symbol.

Lin Ming said with heartfelt appreciation, “Please thank the Crown Prince for me. I, Lin Ming, will always remember this favor.”

“Haha, Brother Lin is far too polite. As soon as I ran into Brother Lin, I knew that Brother Lin was a man worth knowing. Rest assured, the Crown Prince has some savings that he’s accrued over the years. He can easily bear the burden of buying some materials. But the one who has a burden is really Brother Lin. Brother Lin not only has amazing martial arts skills, but also has a thorough understanding of inscription technique. This really makes anyone feel disbelief! Brother Lin, you really make me want to throw away what I thought the word genius meant.”

Chapter 127 – Despicable Means

After having cultivated the ‘Divine Acacia Power’, Zhang Guanyu’s heart had a strong wish. That wish was to cultivate the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ to the peak of the seventh layer, and achieve a long period of youth, the time where his Yang essence would never fade.

Once he achieved this boundary, he would have several hundred years of youth. He would be able to play with all the various beautiful and worldly women in society, take them, and plunder them. From the beauties of today to the beauties of several hundred years later, he would establish a massive harem that surpassed the Royal Family’s harem of 3000 beautiful woman. Every day he would go visit his personal harem and wantonly engage in reckless fun with them. Thinking of this, Zhang Guanyu would be filled with burning desire, and his blood would bubble to the brim with a maddeningly ecstatic excitement.

But with Zhang Guanyu’s talent, to cultivate the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ to the peak seventh layer was easier said than done.

He had just begun cultivating the ‘Divine Acacia Power’. If everything went smoothly, and he picked the best beautiful women to cultivate from, there was a small possibility that he would be able to reach the peak of the seventh layer. But if four months from now, he was defeated by Lin Ming in front of the eyes of everyone, then his spirit and heart would be suppressed and his Yang essence would not flow smoothly. In that case, it would be very difficult to reach the peak of the seventh layer!

So, Zhang Guanyu decided to completely and thoroughly defeat Lin Ming in the match four months from now. He would mercilessly trample over him so that he would never be able to stand up from his failure in his entire life! He would snatch everything from him; all the haloes that surrounded him and all the beautiful women that admired him!

His heart would be serene, his Yang essence would flow unimpeded, and his cultivation would increase by leaps and bounds.

That middle-aged man said, “Young Master, this subordinate is too dull-minded. But this subordinate only thinks that if you do such things, it will enrage Lin Ming. When the time comes, it will only deepen the animosity of an enemy.”

“Humph! So what if I enrage him!? You think I am going to admit defeat without a fight!?”

“But…”

“No buts! Lin Ming is scary, yes, and the Tenth Prince does not dare to move against him. I have to respect the Crown Prince, but this does not mean that I must be servile to him. If others rode on your head, would you also lie on the floor and act like a dog? Since this Lin Ming wants to defeat me, then I will eliminate him!

“Young Master is ready…” The middle-aged man did not understand what his upcoming plans and defeating Lin Ming had in common.

“I ask you, what is most fearful about Lin Ming?”

The middle-aged man thought for a moment and said, “His perception, martial intent, and heart of martial arts.”

“Yes, but the most fundamental of all these is his heart of martial arts. As long as I can break his heart of martial arts, then he will lose his martial intent. If he does not have his martial intent, then he will just be some garbage third-grade talent. Even if he has monstrous heaven-defying perception, his cultivation will be limited to below the Pulse Condensation Period. What sort of achievements could he possibly have? As long as he doesn’t become stronger, his halo will gradually disappear until everyone has forgotten about him. At that time, he will be nothing to but an ant. I’ll crush him to death with a single step.”

“He is under the protection of the Seven Profound Martial House now. It is impossible for me to publicly deal with him. I can only break his heart of martial arts!”

“To deal with Lin Ming, it must be before he grows!”

Zhang Guanyu devilishly grinned, revealing a trace of his teeth. But that middle-aged man only felt sorrow in his heart. If he could defeat Lin Ming’s heart, then that was of course good, but what if he failed? Then they would have seriously offended Lin Ming, and that might possibly affect the Young Master’s future status in the Allied Trade Association.

The Allied Trade Association would never appoint a successor that had offended a Seven Profound Envoy or the Martial House Master.

However, Zhang Guanyu was paranoid by nature, and he practiced the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ which strengthened his possessive instincts. How would he listen to his words?

Many cultivation methods could affect a person’s mind. For instance, cultivating the ‘Abiding Buddha Mantra’ could cause one’s thoughts to be stable, and pure in heart. The ‘Golden Bone Forging Divine Formula’ would cause a person’s Qi and blood to be filled with Yang energy and become indomitable. However, what the ‘Divine Acacia Formula’ did was cause a person’s possessive instincts to grow stronger and stronger, and their thoughts would be increasingly extreme and violent.

“Young Master, perhaps we should discuss this matter with the Master…”

“Mm?” Zhang Guanyu’s complexion immediately went cold, and he emitted a faint murderous intent.

The middle-aged man jumped in fear, hurriedly saying, “This subordinate should die, this subordinate should die!”

“Too much talk leads to error. All you have to do is your duty as a servant!” Zhang Guanyu withdrew his murderous aura. This so-called Master was naturally Zhang Guanyu’s father. Zhang Guanyu knew that if this matter was known by his father, he would absolutely not be allowed to do so. Because in the eyes of his father, the Allied Trade Association’s future was far more important than Zhang Guanyu’s future martial arts cultivation!

His father would never run the risk of offending Lin Ming and going up against him. In his opinion, in the worst case scenario, Zhang Guanyu would lose and that would be it.

But as for Zhang Guanyu, no matter how large the influence of the Allied Trade Association was, it was impossible for them to give him several hundred years of youth and never-ending Yang essence. Only strength would bring him this. As long as he had strength, all the worldly possessions of the Allied Trade Association were nothing but floating clouds!

Geniuses were confident. Lin Ming was confident and Zhang Guanyu was similarly confident. A truly proud talent would never recognize from the beginning that they were inferior to others. Otherwise, his heart would be blocked, and Zhang Guanyu would be more paranoid.

Geniuses always thought that they were the protagonists of the world’s future, and so they would fight. However, these fights must have casualties.

……………….

Sky Fortune City, Southwestern Suburb –

The Sky Fortune City Royal Palace faced south. The northern end of town was where most of the mansions of the nobility were, and it was a relatively prosperous location. The south of the city was deserted, especially near the suburbs, where it was quite deserted.

In the southwest suburb, there were some low-rise houses. Although these houses had been here for years, they did not look old. It was just that under the rain, the dull gray tiles, blank white walls, and the shading from the trees, did not have a fresh feeling.

In the midst of all these houses, there was a new shop. The shop’s original owner had returned to the countryside to retire, and had put his shop on sale.

After the new owner took over, the shop doors were painted with fresh new tung oil, and the inside was spotlessly cleaned. There were even some flowers and plants that were placed around; it looked much more elegant.

At this time, in the shop entrance, there was a young girl wearing a simple blue cotton dress. She was quite beautiful, with supple, tender skin; she gave off fresh and crisp feeling. She was fiddling with some cloths on the shelves.

This girl seemed to be in delicate health, and the cloth she was moving appeared extremely cumbersome. However, the girl’s skill was actually high, and she stacked the large and small fabrics neatly.

This girl was Lan Yunyue. Because her engagement contract had become invalid, Lan Yunyue had left the Seven Profound Martial House. She had helplessly walked through Sky Fortune City for an entire day. She was too ashamed to return home, and she did not know where to go or what to do. In the end, she decided to set her foot down in Sky Fortune City.

Therefore, she pawned some of her jewelry, and opened up this small fabric shop.

All of the neighbors ridiculously loved this new young girl.

The girl wore simple blue clothes every day, and she was always busy at work in her small fabric shop. Such a delicate and juicy young girl that was actually willing to endure such hardship was rare. Not only that, but this girl’s hands and feet were deft, her strength was great, and she also cooked a good meal. It stood to reason that such a girl that had endured this hardship since childhood would have rough skin, and both her hands should at least have callouses, but they actually didn’t think that both of this girl’s hands would be soft and creamy like liquid jade. It was simply amazing.

What kind of girl was this?

After knowing that this girl was one person alone by herself, many of neighborhood aunts’ hearts were aroused with overwhelming sympathy. They curiously asked about the girl’s life experiences, but the girl always ambiguously answered in vague terms.

Some of these aunts even wanted to act as a matchmaker for this beautiful young girl, but to these offers, the girl always faintly smiled and refused.

……….

“Young Master, we’re here.” The middle-aged man pointed to a sign hanging over a fabric shop. That sign hadn’t been hanging there for a long time.

“Ha! What an elegant shop! Good!” Zhang Guanyu shook the fan in his hands, and his face revealed a pondering smile as if was looking at a delicious prey.

In order to break Lin Ming’s heart of martial arts, he had to find the flaw in Lin Ming’s heart of martial arts. To Zhang Guanyu, it seemed the only flaw in Lin Ming’s heart of martial arts was Lan Yunyue.

When Lin Ming had spent half an incense stick of time to overcome the Pass of Desire, that person in the dream realm must have been Lan Yunyue.

Although Lan Yunyue’s matter had already passed, Zhang Guanyu still believed that Lan Yunyue was a knot in Lin Ming’s heart.

If, he could take Lan Yunyue, and cultivate his ‘Divine Acacia Power’ with her, what would be the outcome once Lin Ming found out?

Zhang Guanyu very much wanted to know.

In a matter like a duel, if one was defeated, they would be fine to fight a second time. There would not be a situation where their ‘spirit’ would be suppressed and blocked.

But a girl was different. As long as he got her in his bed, that was a forever matter. Zhang Guanyu believed that even though Lan Yunyue betrayed Lin Ming, she still had a place within his heart. If he took Lan Yunyue, then this would forever be a thorn in his mind. This thorn would be something he could never ever erase. Even if Lin Ming defeated him, that thorn would still remain!

If one’s ‘spirit’ wasn’t smooth, then their thoughts would be clouded and their cultivation would be blocked. When Lin Ming tried to breakthrough a bottleneck of his martial arts cultivation, this would be a demon of his heart that stopped him.

And the key to this was, could Lin Ming defeat him?

It was true that the Seven Profound Martial House protected Lin Ming. But, they did not protect Lan Yunyue, and this girl had already withdrawn from the Seven Profound Martial House. If Lin Ming knew that he had obtained Lan Yunyue for himself, would he rush towards him, head full of anger, and ask him to a duel?

If Lin Ming came to his front door, that would simply be too good. At this moment, Zhang Guanyu had a 100% assurance that he could defeat Lin Ming.

Even if he waited four months, he still had 90% assurance that he would win against Lin Ming. This was because recently, his ‘Divine Acacia Power’ had reached the Large Success stage of the first layer, and his strength had grown by a large margin. This was something that Lin Ming did not know.

Zhang Guanyu expected that on the day of that decisive battle, Lin Ming, because of anger, would ruthlessly attack him, with each move desperately aggressive.

In Zhang Guanyu’s imagined scenario, that would be perfect. He would be perfectly justified to use some of the sinister and sadistic styles of the ‘Divine Acacia Power’, and leave Lin Ming to suffer with irreversibly severe injuries; injuries that would seriously impact his future cultivation.

Even if he could not reach that point, he could still make it so that Lin Ming would be confined to bed for at least half a year!

If Lin Ming had to recuperate in bed for half a year, then what would happen?

Could he still pass the Seven Profound Valleys’ core disciple test?

The test’s deadline was in little more than a year. This was his only chance. As long as Lin Ming did not pass the test, in Zhang Guanyu’s eyes he had nothing to fear. In addition to his future achievements and the disparity in their influence, Zhang Guanyu had full confidence that he could suppress Lin Ming for a lifetime!

Chapter 128 – Liao Wenyuan

First, he would snatch the jade virginity of the woman that Lin Ming had loved and use her to enhance his own cultivation. Then on the stage in front of the eyes of everyone, Lin Ming would be defeated by the man who had stolen his woman, and also experience a severe wound that would take half a year to heal from. This would cause him to fail the Seven Profound Martial House core disciple test!

With so many attacks concentrated together, what would happen to Lin Ming?

Would he ever be able to calm down his ‘spirit’? Would he be able to maintain his perfect heart of martial arts?

Zhang Guanyu self-reflected. If he was placed in that situation, he would be wild with rage, and his ‘spirit’ would be disrupted.

If his ‘spirit’ couldn’t flow well, then one’s cultivation would be hindered.

Since ancient times, the frustrated geniuses everywhere that had never recovered from a setback all had one common characteristic. This was that before it had happened, everything had been smooth sailing, and then they would suddenly suffer a disastrous defeat.

“You think your future prospects are limitless, but these are all things given to you by your martial intent. If I take away your martial intent, then you will be nothing! Wait for me to plunder the virginity of the woman you once loved, shatter your martial intent, grievously wound you, and waste your future!”

Thinking of Lin Ming’s inevitable fate, Zhang Guanyu really wanted to let out a hearty laugh. He looked again at Lan Yunyue in her small fabric shop, and the corners of his mouth flashed with a ferocious macabre smile. He lifted his foot and walked forwards her.

“Hello two customers, are you looking to purchase something?” Lan Yunyue sweetly greeted with a smile as she saw the two silk-robed men walk into the shop. Although she and Zhang Guanyu had both attended the Seven Profound Martial House at the same time, Zhang Guanyu rarely appeared in front of others, so Lan Yunyue did not recognize him.

But as they approached Lan Yunyue, her eyes gradually sharpened. The silk robed man who was waving a fan was not some common or trivial person. Not even mentioning the richly brocaded silk fabrics he was wearing, but the jade pendant that he was wearing at his waist was worth no less than 5000 gold taels. It was a top-quality white translucent jade pendant. Not only that, but it had delicate red veins within; it was a very beautiful blood jade. She remembered that not even Zhu Yan had such a high quality jade pendant. To so casually wear a jade pendant that was equal to 1 or 2 treasures on his body, the young man’s family background was simply too terrifying.

Lan Yunyue could not see through this young man’s cultivation, but she could easily see that the middle-aged man accompanying him was at the Viscera Training stage. To have a follower at the Viscera Training stage, just who was this man?

But the key was, why would the son of such a wealthy person come to such a small hole-in-the-wall shop to buy fabric? Although her fabric was decent, it was not something that this young man would ever deem worthy to be glanced at. This kind of person from a wealthy family probably used precious snow silk as his fabric.

Also, those who bought fabrics were usually women. What would two men possibly be buying fabric for?

Lan Yunyue’s mind flashed with all these thoughts, and in her heart she became secretly alert.

Zhang Guanyu looked at Lan Yunyue and revealed a faint smile. He joyously laughed and thought, “What a charming and juicy young beauty. Even though she’s wearing coarse homespun clothing, it doesn’t hide her exquisite makings. No wonder Lin Ming and Zhu Yan were both infatuated with this girl, moreover, I can tell that this girl truly has the body of a virgin. This is perfect, I’ll settle her within my manor and thoroughly cultivate my ‘Divine Acacia Power’ with her. I will certainly enjoy this.”

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, according to customs, a man and woman wouldn’t have sexual relations with each other before marriage. Certainly, this logic did not apply to concubines and maids because one did not need to marry them.

“Are you Miss Lan?” Zhang Guanyu asked straight to the point.

Lan Yunyue’s heart chilled. Sure enough, they were looking for her. Since they’ve come to her door, they have already verified her identity.

She nodded and said, “Yes, I am. What matter do you two have with me?”

“Haha, I’ve seen Miss Lan before. The truth is, the first time that I saw Miss Lan, I was already attracted to Miss Lan. Whether it is appearance or temperament, Miss Lan is truly very charming!”

Lan Yunyue unconsciously stepped back half a step, opening up a distance between her and Zhang Guanyu. The wariness in her heart became heavier.

Zhang Guanyu saw Lan Yunyue step back, and also quickly stepped back himself to show respect. He said, “My apologies, I hope that I was not too offensive and therefore scared Miss Lan. I do not have any other meaning, honestly, I just want to say that I very much admire Miss Lan, but before, Miss Lan was already engaged. My only regret is that I did not meet Miss Lan sooner. I recently heard that Miss Lan has broken her engagement so I took the liberty to visit. I hope that Miss Lan is not offended by my brashness.”

Lan Yunyue saw Zhang Guanyu’s respect and felt a little more at ease. She calmly replied, “My engagement was not broken, but divorced.”

“Haha, Miss Lan is too serious. I actually already knew that Zhu Yan had been expelled from the Zhu Family, how could he possibly be worthy of Miss Lan?  I do not know why Miss Lan decided to open such a small fabric shop in this remote area. If Miss Lan does not mind, how about coming over to my house for a visit? I have some gifts that I must give to Miss Lan.”

Lan Yunyue’s heart began to race. This young man in front of her, his words were appropriate, his smile was gentle, and by all appearances he was a modest and classy gentleman that didn’t give off any ill-feelings. However, Lan Yunyue suddenly felt that there was something wrong about him.

Lan Yunyue knew how sensitive her status was. She was Lin Ming’s former girlfriend. Just on this point alone, even if there was a son of a rich family who had taken a liking to her, they wouldn’t be so crazy as to come here and try to take advantage of her.

Although Lan Yunyue knew that Lin Ming no longer had any relationship with her, those nobles would not think such a thing. This was something that they would never dare to do; in their opinion, this was the same as insulting Lin Ming.

But this young man actually dared to be so flagrantly blatant to court her. There were only two possible meanings to this; he was completely crazy or he was completely opposed to Lin Ming, or even had a grudge with him!

Thinking of this, Lan Yunyue had a very bad feeling, like an unlucky premonition that was slowly creeping up behind her, that someone would try to kidnap her and use her to threaten Lin Ming…

Although she could not see through this young man’s cultivation, she knew without a doubt that she was not his match. In addition to that old servant that stood behind him, she had no chance of escaping!

Zhang Guanyu saw Lan Yunyue tense up and go on high alert, smiled, and said, “I heard that Miss Lan has already withdrawn from the Seven Profound Martial House. It’s really too bad. With Miss Lan’s talent, with good pills supporting, it would be possible to break through to the Pulse Condensation Period. Once someone breaks through to the Pulse Condensation Period, their youth will be lengthened by decades. Isn’t this something that Miss Lan desires?”

Zhang Guanyu lightly coughed, and the middle-aged man immediately handed him a box. He opened it; there were two bottles of pills inside. Zhang Guanyu casually took out a bottle and opened it. The rich and fragrant aroma of high-quality medicines immediately wafted out. These were clearly top-quality medicines.

Zhang Guanyu smiled and handed the pills to Lan Yunyue. He said, “These are high-grade soul gathering pellets, just a trivial little gift not worth mentioning. Miss Lan, please do not reject them. These are only a small gift that I prepared for our first meeting. In the future, I can give you anything you want. With my status, I will not bring disgrace to you. How about it?” Zhang Guanyu knew of Lan Yunyue’s past. He knew what Lan Yunyue desired, and had always wanted. She was divorced now; it was impossible for her to remarry into any respectable family. He did not believe that if he appeared in front of her when she was in such a dire situation and offered so many pills, and even offered to help her break through to the Pulse Condensation Period, that Lan Yunyue would not be tempted by this.

However, he hadn’t expected that Lan Yunyue would simply not take the bottle of pills. She refused them, and directly said, “This young lady understands and thanks good sir for his kind intentions, but must decline. I no longer wish to cultivate the path of martial arts, and would like to live out the rest of my days as an ordinary person. I thank good sir for his kind regards, and ask that good sir please never return.

“Oh, is that so…?” Zhang Guanyu’s smiling visage slowly fell, and an imposing aura from his body slowly began to grow. The middle-aged man behind him stepped forward, blocking the rear door.

Lan Yunyue immediately became flustered, and her pretty face began to pale. “You…what do you want to do?”

Zhang Guanyu said, “It’s a pity that Miss Lan does not seem very interested in returning to my home, but I think that as long as I bring you there, I can make you change your mind by fulfilling your interest of ‘sex’.”

As Lan Yunyue heard Zhang Guanyu bite out this word ‘sex’, she immediately turned ice-cold. This person… he… he dares to rape her!? He was insane! Was he completely ignoring the threat of Lin Ming and abducting her to his own house!?

Was he not afraid of Lin Ming’s retaliation?

Lan Yunyue knew that even if she no longer had any relationship with Lin Ming, if some person was to rape her, Lin Ming would absolutely never let that person off.

Lan Yunyue’s back was already soaked in cold sweat. Her eyes glanced at the booth, and she saw not a trace of the scissors she used to cut fabric with…

“Haha, such a young girl and also so beautiful. Don’t take things too hard; look at the bright side.” Zhang Guanyu’s smiling face became all the more intense.

Zhang Guanyu took a step forward. He revolved a bit of his true essence, and was just about to make a move, when at this moment a hearty laughter suddenly came from the entrance. “Haha, is that not Sir Zhang? Sky Fortune City is such a small place; I can’t believe that I would bump into you here!”

Zhang Guanyu frowned and he turned around. He was surprised to see a man with thick eyebrows smiling at him as he walked over. With every step this man took, he was emitting a strong aura that suppressed him.

Liao Wenyuan!

Zhang Guanyu recognized this person. He was a Pulse Condensation Period master who was a subordinate of the Crown Prince. Not only that, but he was already at the middle Pulse Condensation Period. Even if there were four of five or him, he still wouldn’t be this man’s match!

The Crown Prince actually sent Liao Wenyuan to protect Lan Yunyue?

No, that’s not right. It should be that there was someone following her, and as soon as this shadowy saw that he had come, had used a sound transmitting talisman to immediately notify Liao Wenyuan. With a Pulse Condensation Period master’s speed, catching up so quickly was not a problem!

Damn!

“Mister Liao! What a fortunate meeting!” Zhang Guanyu said as he cupped his hands together in greeting.

“Fortunate meeting, fortunate meeting.” Liao Wenyuan clasped his hands together and returned the courtesy. He calmly asked, “Is Sir Zhang also here to buy fabric?”

“Oh, ah, it’s for the beginning of winter. My family wishes to purchase a batch of winter clothing.”

“Haha, I also have this plan for the coming winter. I came early, but didn’t think that I would meet Sir Zhang also choosing out fabric. This is such a fortunate coincidence, how about Sir Zhang chooses fabric with me?”

“Hehe…” Zhang Guanyu suddenly smiled, but his smiling face contained a faint trace of murderous intention. He coldly said, “Do not trouble yourself Mister Liao. Mister Liao should feel free to choose his own fabric. When the winter comes this year, it will be best if you do not freeze to death.”

After Zhang Guanyu said this, he waved the fan in his hands, flicked his sleeves, and left the shop.

Hearing Zhang Guanyu’s apparent threat before he left, Liao Wenyuan only smiled and yawned. He was a Pulse Condensation Period master, and did not fear the Allied Trade Association. He was also a subordinate of the Crown Prince; what could Zhang Guanyu possibly do to him?

——

Chapter 129 – Medium-Grade Human-Step Sword

It was only when she could no longer sense Zhang Guanyu that Lan Yunyue let out a breath of relief, her fingers trembling. A moment ago, did that man say Sir Zhang? Was it possible that the youth was Zhang Guanyu?

Although she no longer kept thoughts of Lin Ming in her mind, Lan Yunyue had still unintentionally heard news of Lin Ming. She knew that four months from now, Lin Ming would challenge Zhang Guanyu. Was it because of this reason that Zhang Guanyu had wanted to do something so ruthless to her?

But it was nothing more than a challenge, so why would he do this?

Lan Yunyue didn’t understand.

It was not only Lan Yunyue who didn’t understand. It had never even occurred to Lin Ming that Zhang Guanyu would be demented to such a degree, that this person wished to obtain everything in the world. Glory, status, woman; all were his and anyone who threatened to encroach on these would be a thorn in his side!

Any normal person, such as the Tenth Prince, even if they regarded Lin Ming as a thorn in their side they would never dare to move against them. They would outwardly smile and show good will. But Zhang Guanyu was different; anyone that threatened him would receive his mad retaliation.

“Miss Lan, are you alright?” Liao Wenyuan smiled. Although he knew Lan Yunyue and Lin Ming’s past, he did not look down on this girl. In this world, there were two kinds of companions that were worth feeling grateful for. The first was a woman; when everything went downhill, they would still stand by their man and cross the hard times with their husband. The second was a successful man with a rising career who would cross life together with just his first wife.

Running into these two kinds of companions would be one of life’s great fortunes. But, if one cannot meet someone like this, they no one can be blamed either.

“Thank… thank you Senior. My I ask Senior’s name?” Lan Yunyue bit her lip and bowed.

Without a doubt, this intimidating man with thick eyebrows had come to protect her. To be a martial arts master that would protect an ordinary female, he must have some sort of relation to Lin Ming.

“Miss Lan does not need to be polite. My surname is Liao, my name is Liao Wenyuan. Just call me Mister Liao.”

“Senior Liao’s graciousness, this young lady will never forget.”

“Haha, you don’t need to thank me. I was just doing as I was instructed.”

Lan Yunyue hesitated, and could not help but ask, “May I ask how Senior Liao and Mister Lin are…”

Liao Wenyuan heard Lan Yunyue say this and smiled. “Mister Lin? Haha Miss Lan, when you say it like that, how could I not respond. It’s Lin Ming right?”

Lan Yunyue awkwardly nodded. She was now a commoner, and this Liao Wenyuan in front of her was probably a master at the Pulse Condensation Period, and a titled aristocrat. She should refer to him in a respectable manner and call him mister.

But Lin Ming’s status was that of a core disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House, so his status was actually higher than Liao Wenyuan’s. Lin Ming also didn’t have relations with her anymore, that’s why in front of Liao Wenyuan she had called him Mister Lin as a show of respect. Only someone who was incomparably intimate with Lin Ming, such as his younger sister or girlfriend, could call him ‘big brother’, or call him directly by his name.

“I was sent by His Highness the Crown Prince. But before this, Brother Lin has also asked me about you. Miss Lan, your status is quite sensitive now, it is probably impossible for you to ever live a quiet life again. How about this, you come with me back to the Crown Prince’s palace, and the Crown Prince will guarantee your safety, so that something like this will never happen again.”

Lan Yunyue nipped her lips and nodded. In this situation, she had no choice.

So like this, Lan Yunyue arrived at the Crown Prince’s palace in awe and trepidation. Unexpectedly, she was personally received by the Crown Prince, Yang Lin, who politely inquired about her situation. Lan Yunyue was then arranged into an elegant room within the Crown Prince’s palace, and some maids were specially sent to take care of Lan Yunyue.

Here, there was a pavilion with a collection of rare books, rooms to practice calligraphy and painting, and masters that would teach her how. There were martial arts cultivation rooms, and also martial arts teachers.

When Lan Yunyue arrived here, her mood was extremely complex. She did not expect that so many things would happen within a few months, and that in the end she would finally be admitted to the Crown Prince’s palace…

…………………………

In the Inscription Association, the guest inscription master would tailor their inscriptions based upon the customer’s request. Each customer had different requests. Some only wanted to an inscription symbol, some wanted their treasures repaired, or some wanted to improve their treasures.

Everyday, Lin Ming was exposed to a variety of strange materials, and he would face a number of different requests. In the drawing process, Lin Ming’s understanding of the nature of various materials began to slowly become perfect. He also began to further comprehend and achieve mastery of the memories and theories in his mind.

Meanwhile, the soul force also experienced significant growth. His use of the ‘Overbearing Soul Tactic’ became more skillful, even almost as well as his use of the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’. He would frequently push himself to the limit of his ability, then enter into the ethereal martial intent and rely on the true essence stones he had to restore his true essence. This caused Lin Ming’s ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ to steadily progress. Like this, it would only be a matter of time before he achieved the Small Success of the second layer.

He had continuously been drawing inscription symbols for three days, and Lin Ming began to become famous. More and more martial artists of Sky Fortune City came to know of the new guest inscription master at the Inscription Association. They knew that he was young, but his inscription technique approached the pinnacle of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s inscription masters.

The flame brand that Lin Ming placed in his inscription symbols also became a hot commodity. If a treasure had this flame mark on it, its value would increase tremendously.

To a martial artist, a treasure that came from a famous expert was similar to a priceless mink coat to an aristocratic woman; it really was just as addictive and hard to let go.

…………..

In the Seven Profound Martial House, Murong Zi saw Bai Jingyun’s treasure sword, and with eyes shining, said, “Wow Big Bister Jingyun, a medium-grade human-step treasure sword!”

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, a medium-grade human-step treasure was very rare. There were many Pulse Condensation Period martial artists who did not have a medium-grade human-step treasure.

But Murong Zi and Bai Jingyun were only marital artists at the Altering Muscle stage. To an Altering Muscle stage martial artist, a low-grade human-step treasure was already sufficient. A medium-grade was simply overly extravagant.

“Mm, it’s made by Huoluo Nation’s Master Jadelotus. They’ve been open for less than a year, and my uncle gifted this to me.”

Murong Zi said, “So that’s it, it must be great to have such a nice uncle. That sword probably cost 20,000 gold taels.”

“Probably. But this money to you Murong Zi is just some drizzle on a rainy day. Haha, Younger Sister, if you want to order a medium-grade human-step treasure sword, it’s not so easy.”

“Come on! Our family would never be so lavish. Besides, my father is the worst cheapskate of all time. Only if I enter the top ten of the Ranking Stone would get buy something like that for me. To enter the first ten, It’s hopeless to think it will happen in the next year.”

Bai Jingyun smiled, and said, “You’re lazy. As long as you work hard, with your talent, it’s very easy.”

“Oh, I hope so. But Big Sister Jingyun, how come I’ve never seen you take out this sword before?”

Bai Jingyun said with a smile, “Because I couldn’t find a suitable inscription before, so I never took it out. But this time, I heard that there is a guest inscription master at the Inscription Association. He is young, but his inscription technique level has already reached the pinnacle. This person also can create an inscription symbol that suits my attribute. So I want to bring this sword and go to the Inscription Association to have a look.” Bai Jingyun said as she inventoried some materials. These materials had been arranged long ago, but she had never found a time to use them.

Usually a person would be very particular about a medium-grade human-step treasure’s inscription symbol. A lower level inscription master was simply insufficient to draw an inscription symbol upon a medium-grade human-step treasure, and even those inscription masters whose skill was high enough, often because of some reason or another, they could not meet the owner’s demand for what inscription symbol to put on the treasure.

For instance, Bai Jingyun wanted an inscription symbol on her sword that had a water attribute or ice attribute. However, in the Sky Fortune Kingdom’s school of inscription technique, there just weren’t many inscription symbols with attributes, and the only water attribute inscription symbols were the ‘Water Parting Symbol’ and a few others. But Bai Jingyun did not like these inscription symbols, and therefore had put this matter on hold.

Murong Zi curiously asked, “A young inscription master whose technique has reached the pinnacle? How young is he?”

“It is said that he is younger than 20 years old. But I’m not too clear of just how young.”

“What a joke! That’s simply too fabulous a tale; these rumors that people make up are become more and more odd. I don’t believe that there can be a 20 year old inscription master with such a high level of technique. I think that this guest inscription master is and old man who just looks a bit young. Either that or he’s not so high-level as people have blown him up to be.”

Bai Jingyun smiled and said, “Ah Zi, you are just too dismissive of geniuses. When Lin Ming had emerged, you had also looked down on him. What kind of person is he now? Lin Min will become a core disciple soon. Your temper just isn’t good, your jealousy is too strong. You just can’t see those at your age that are better than you.”

“Hey, just who is jealous!? Ah, this young lady has already begun to try her hardest. Big Sister Jingyun, you just wait and see. Even if I cannot compare to that farm animal Lin Ming in the future, I will compete in the Ten Thousand Killing Array match 3 months from now, and  I will not lose to him. If he can really enter the top ten, then I will also enter the top ten and show you just how cool I am!”

“Haha, who was it that just said a moment ago that they would not be able to advance to the top ten within a year?” Bai Jingyun asked with a teasing smile.

“That… that’s because……” Murong Zi blushed, and had nothing more to say.

Bai Jingyun laughed. “Okay, okay, I won’t make fun of you. Do you want to go with me to the Inscription Association?”

“I’m too lazy to go. This thing is just a rumor, even if I go there’s no point. You might as well ask Yuhan’s grandfather to draw an inscription symbol for you! Yuhan’s grandfather is  the best inscription master in Sky Fortune City. If he is willing to help you, then what’s not to like?”

Bai Jingyun said, “I want a water attribute inscription symbol. President Wang does not excel at them.”

There were specializations within the inscription industry. Although Wang Xuanji had many attainments in inscription techniques and was very proficient, concerning the five elemental inscription symbols, he only excelled at fire and metal attribute inscription symbols.

“Then I’ll go first. You practice well; I will wait to see you in the top ten 3 months from now.” Bai Jingyun teased.

“Alright, alright, I’ll go with you. I was just joking around, why are you so serious,” Murong Zi grumpily said. She sent a bullied look towards Bai Jingyun, “I will show you how kind I am at heart and go with you to the Inscription Association. I want to see just how good this guest inscription master is.”

“Mm? Okay.”

Chapter 137 – The Might Of ‘Golden Roc Shattering The Void’

Wooden Puppet Lane was built into the face of a mountain. There were altogether 12 caves, and each could be opened by themselves. These caves were created by Xiantian masters cutting through the mountain themselves; one could still see glaring sword marks.

Wood Puppet Lane was filled with wooden puppets; the deeper one went, the more formidable these puppets would be, and the more there were.

These wooden puppets were from one of the seven inheritances of the Seven Profound Valleys, the masterpieces of the Puppet Faction. The Puppet Faction was a very mysterious faction within the Seven Profound Valleys. Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House did not have any of these factions’ cultivation methods or secret techniques, so they had never had much exposure to it.

Seeing the crowds of wooden puppets increase, Lin Ming did not hurry to attack. He hadn’t even taken out the Penetrating Rainbow spear. After he had reached a location with more than 20 puppets, Lin Ming rushed in, unarmed.

Cha! A wooden puppet aimed a club at Lin Ming. The weapons that these wooden puppets all used were completely made of wood, such as wooden clubs, or wooden sabers. A wooden weapon may not have seemed like a very dangerous weapon, but even so, if one was pounded by a wooden club or saber, they would still be dealt a crushing blow and vomit blood from a severe wound.

Lin Ming watched as a wooden club came at him and waited until it was just in front of him. He closed his eyes and gently pushed with his toes. His body flickered backwards half a step, and as a result, the descending club that would have smashed Lin Ming’s nose was just avoided with not too much or too little distance.

Whiz! Another wooden puppet cut towards Lin Ming’s waist with a wooden saber. This time, Lin Ming leapt into the air. His body floated in the air, and because of inertia, he floated backwards. Another wooden puppet cut towards Lin Ming’s waist from behind, and this attack didn’t seem as if it could be evaded. But then Lin Ming gently waved his sleeves, and his body became like a leaf that was blown away by a gently breeze. It seemed as if he completely violated the rules of physics, and he appeared two feet to the side, dodging that hidden saber by just a hair’s width once more.

Swish swish swish! The wooden puppet continuously attacked Lin Ming, but Lin Ming did not counter. Instead, he dodged the attacks from the wooden puppets as if here was taking a leisurely stroll through a park.

There were more than 20 puppets, but only 7 or 8 were able to attack Lin Ming at the same time. But, these 7 or 8 puppets had very scary attacks. Their moves and combinations interwove with each other, and there almost wasn’t an angle to dodge.

However, Lin Ming was able to mysteriously avoid all these attacks. It was as if the puppets did not have a weapon in their hands, but instead a fan. Lin Ming was like a light feather; each time the wooden puppets brandished their weapons at him, the wind of the passing weapons would blow him away!

This was the concept of wind that Lin Ming had comprehended!

A waving fan would never be able to touch a floating feather, and like this, a wooden puppet’s weapon would never be able to each touch even the hem of Lin Ming’s robe!

“Wonderful!”

“Very good!”

“Come again!”

Lin Ming wholly immersed himself in the depths of the concept of wind; this was the first time that he had applied the ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ movement ability to actual combat!

“These fellows are just a bit too weak!”

As Lin Ming thought this, his body rose like a Roc, rising several dozens of feet before he landed on a cliff and flew towards to depths of Wooden Puppet Lane!

………………….

At this time, outside of Wooden Puppet Lane, the deacon senior apprentice brother was still in shock, as he stared unblinking at the true essence stones in the heart of the major killing array.

Every array formation had an array heart. This was often where the array was supplied with energy from.

The puppets of Wooden Puppet Lane were able to self-repair and regenerate, but this regeneration required the consumption of true essence stones in order to power it. There were some abnormal individuals, like Ling Sen and Ta Ku, who would cause a quick consumption of true essence stones after entering Wood Puppet Lane. Sometimes, just looking at this wasteful sight made the deacon senior apprentice brother’s heart hurt deeply.

But Lin Ming had already gone in for such a long time, yet he had only consumed a small number of true essence stones. Obviously Lin Ming was struggling in dealing with these wooden puppets, and had only managed to take down a few.

Realizing this, the deacon senior apprentice brother let out a soft sigh of relief, “Fortunately, Junior Apprentice Brother Lin isn’t that abnormal. Indeed, it seems that he still isn’t able to challenge the eleventh level of difficulty of Wood Puppet Lane in such a short time!”

“Junior Apprentice Brother Lin is just too impatient. His strength isn’t high enough yet for him to jump straight to the eleventh level of difficulty. But in this Wood Puppet Lane killing array, if the difficulty is too high, one could be easily injured, or might even die!”

“I estimate that another half incense stick of time will pass before Junior Apprentice Brother Lin decides that he cannot last in there any longer, and comes out to change the difficulty to the tenth level…”

The deacon senior apprentice brother picked up the array disk, and waited for Lin Ming to come out and ask him to change the difficulty. But after waiting half an hour, there was no news of his exit.

“What do I do?” The deacon was a bit confused. The array heart was still only consuming true essence at a very slow speed; he even suspected that Lin Ming had encounter some troubles inside and been killed by the wooden puppets.

“What’s going on? Is it possible that Junior Apprentice Brother Lin is hiding in some corner of Wood Puppet Lane? Was that the reason that he had opened the eleventh level of difficulty?”

……………………………

At this moment, Lin Ming had already reached the deepest depths of Wood Puppet Lane. Here, the wooden puppets’ strength was at a much higher level, and they were also large. What was most peculiar though, was that the surface of their bodies was a strange dark red, as if they had been dyed in blood.

Facing so many more advanced puppets, Lin Ming felt an intense amount of pressure. As he dodged the wooden puppets’ intense attacks for a long time, he was beginning to gasp for breath even with the support of the ‘True Prima Chaos Formula’.

“Almost there!” Lin Ming had practiced his movement for almost an entire hour. He felt that this was enough, and thinking this, he turned his hand and extracted the Penetrating Rainbow spear from his spatial ring.

Holding the spear in both hands, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a cold light. The countless tiny units in his body began to synchronise their breathing to the same frequency, as his thick true essence began to shake like a mountain. In that moment, his imposing aura instantly erupted!

“Total Annihilation!”

Boom boom boom boom!

With the formidable strength of Altering Muscle’s cultivation level, combined with his fiercely vibrating true essence, there was an explosion of sounds in succession, as the Penetrating Rainbow spear swept out, and the puppets were all sent flying backwards!

“Oh! Not dead?”

Lin Ming found that besides the puppet that had borne the majority of his attack and shattered to pieces, the other puppets had only fallen to the ground, and were beginning to crawl back up.

“Good resilience!”

No one understood the terrifying destructive power of ‘Flow like Silk’ more than Lin Ming. Back when he was at the Viscera Training stage, a single strike from his spear was able to turn a thick stone column dozens of feet high into nothing more than crumbled rock. Now that his strength had increased even further, he might even be able to split apart a hall with just a few spear moves!

But now that he had struck at these wooden puppets, only one had died!

“The more resilient they are, the better. Today I will enjoy this fight!”

After officially stepping into the Altering Muscle stage, in addition to reaching the Large Success of ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’, Lin Ming really needed a battle to examine his own strength and also allow his body to adapt to the change in his true essence and physical strength.

Bang bang bang! Wooden puppets began to blow up one after another! The Penetrating Rainbow spear was like a purple black dragon that was churning in the ocean waves.

“Haha, fun!”

“Come on, more!”

Lin Ming flourished Penetrating Rainbow with grandeur. Each spear move was imbued with the ‘Flow like Silk’ concept, and every hit would cause a wooden puppet to explode into pieces!

In fact, what Lin Ming did now know was that when other martial artists entered Wood Puppet Lane, most could not even injure these puppets; they could only knock them down.

Even if it was Ling Sen, who had such an abnormally overwhelming combat strength, he could only cut apart a wooden puppet with his sword; he simply could not be like Lin Ming, whose every spear thrust would cause a wooden puppet to burst into fragments.

The wooden puppets could repair themselves, but this repair required the consumption of true essence stones as the energy source. If a wooden puppet was knocked down, it would only be slightly damaged, and be able to repair itself with very little energy. Even if they were cut apart by Ling Sen, it wouldn’t require too many true essence stones to repair.

But when Lin Ming had shattered them his spear, this was truly a tragedy. Not only did the repairs take time, but the consumption of true essence stones would be terrifying for a long time afterwards!

…………………………

Outside Wood Puppet Lane, the deacon senior apprentice brother was still waiting for Lin Ming to come out and lower the difficulty to the tenth level. As he casually glanced at the true essence stones in the array heart, the scene scared and dumbfounded him; he could only helplessly look on at the true essence stones’ energy levels plummeted!

The true essence stones began to change at a speed visible to the naked eye. Starting from its original lustrous crystal like appearance, it gradually turned a dull white, and then after some time, peng! It exploded!

The array would automatically replace it with a new true essence stone, but the result was still the same. In less than half an incense stick of time, another true essence stone exploded!

What… what was happening!?

Even if Ling Sen was here, the consumption rate would not be so high!

Was it Lin Ming? No… impossible!

Absolutely impossible!

The deacon senior apprentice brother looked at the true essence stone at the center of the array heart and constantly swallowed as he panicked. Although logic told him that it was impossible for Lin Ming to be so abnormal, the truth was already placed in front of him.

This… this, just what the hell is this?

The deacon senior apprentice brother cried in his heart. With so many true essence stones being suddenly consumed, he simply could not find a good explanation.

……………………….

“Mm? Where’d they all go?”

Lin Ming had been enjoying destroying all the wooden puppets, but now the originally threatening and aggressive wooden puppets had been reduced to just 2 or 3. They were just as dangerous as cats now, and the rest that still hadn’t shattered yet were missing arms and legs.

“This Wood Puppet Lane sucks, is this everything? It’s the eleventh level of difficulty!” Lin Ming was speechless. In his mind, this eleventh level of difficulty was unworthy of the name.

If the deacon senior apprentice brother knew Lin Ming’s thoughts, he probably would have wanted to smack his head against a wall and kill himself. The puppets of Wood Puppet Lane could repair themselves after they were destroyed, but Lin Ming had exploded them with his spear, and turned them completely into scattered pieces. This repair would just take a long time!

“Although I couldn’t fight to my heart’s content, I’ve about gotten a good grasp on my current strength. Right now I still might not be able to compare to Zhang Guanyu, but I should absolutely not have a problem entering the top ten of the Ten Thousand Killing Array rankings. First I’ll participate in this coming Ten Thousand Killing Array assessment, and take the Heavy Profound Soft Spear before planning my next move.”

Lin Ming put away his Penetrating Rainbow spear, and walked out of Wood Puppet Lane.

Chapter 142 – Heavy Profound Soft Spear!

“Sixth!?”

“Sixth!”

The two top 20 Heavenly Abode disciples said at the same time, surprised.

The Martial House Master had given Lin Ming three months to enter into the top 10 rankings.

But in only two months, he had reached sixth place!

Was this a joke?

Even the two of them, though they were big fans of Lin Ming, didn’t think that Lin Ming would reach the top ten. But then to also kill his way to the sixth rank spot!

Even the fanatical young female apprentice of the Human Hall rubbed her eyes, as if there was something wrong with her sight.

The threshold of difficulty for which the Seven Profound Martial House had set the tasks before Lin Ming would receive a reward was difficult beyond imagination. Three months to enter the top ten, four months to defeat Zhang Guanyu, five months to defeat Ta Ku, six months to defeat Ling Sen!

There were even those who believed that this list of rewards was merely someone poking fun at Lin Ming. But the present result was that when it came to Lin Ming, the difficulty that the Seven Profound Martial House had set the rewards at was too low!

To have Lin Ming advance to the top ten in three months?

They were simply looking down on Lin Ming!

Now Lin Ming had only taken two months to arrive at the sixth place rank.

Wasn’t this just embarrassing oneself?

Now, it was extremely possible for Lin Ming to defeat Zhang Guanyu!

The only requirement for Lin Ming to be a core disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House was that he reach the peak Altering Muscle stage before he was over 16 years old. Everyone was no longer anxious of this test. This difficulty, was simply too low for Lin Ming!

That is, whether or not Lin Ming could defeat Ta Ku or Ling Sen in the future, he was already destined to be a core disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House and reach the Pulse Condensation Period. He would go to Seven Profound Valleys’ main sect for several years, and easily reach the Houtian stage.

Then as long as Lin Ming wished for it, he could return to the Sky Fortune Kingdom and become a Seven Profound Envoy or the Seven Profound Martial House Master. At that time, the Sky Fortune Kingdom would become Lin Ming’s garden, and he could do as he pleased.

This made how many people, how many families jealous to the degree of bleeding!

Lin Ming was also so young; he completely had the possibility to step into the Houtian stage before he was 30 years old. Then, he could casually and freely spend his couple hundred years of youth as countless families and major powers tried to flatter and curry favor with him. Innumerable beautiful young girls would want to marry him; even royal princesses, and proud, arrogant women like Bai Jingyun and Murong Zi would be at his beck and call.

Not only was it the beautiful women of now, but those several dozens of years later, or a hundred years later would all be easily obtained. Compared to this, it was even better than being a mortal emperor by hundreds of times. To the majority of the Seven Profound Martial House’s male disciples, this was simply the pinnacle of living, the pinnacle of life!

Lin Ming looked at the Ranking Stone and understood why he was able to achieve such a result. The first reason was that he had broken through to the Altering Muscle stage, so his true essence and strength had increased by a large margin. The second reason was that he had comprehended the concept of wind, and had successfully learned the movement ability, ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’.

In the past, Lin Ming had rarely moved in battle. No matter how aggressive his enemy was or how threatening their killer moves, Lin Ming never escaped!

His fighting method was to completely meet an enemy head on in a battle of toughness. If he is strong, then I am stronger!

In a battle, Lin Ming’s aura was motionless like a mountain that had existed since time immemorial, as if he was that passing cable in a torrentially surging river.

After Lin Ming had reached the Large Success stage in his cultivation method, so far the only one who had been able to force him back was Zhu Yan.

The reason for this method of fighting was mainly because of how formidable Lin Ming’s strength was, and how vigorous his true essence was. What he excelled most at was meeting an enemy head on, of course, but the other reason was because Lin Ming’s speed was just not that fast.

His attack speed was fast enough, but his body speed actually relied upon the ‘Foundation Movement Technique’. The ‘Foundation Movement Technique’ was only the most basic of movement manuals after all. Lin Ming just hadn’t placed much time or effort into cultivating this ‘Foundation Movement Technique’, thus Lin Ming’s accomplishments in terms of agility had remained limited.

If he only rushed forwards, then by relying on his physical strength and vigorous true essence, Lin Ming could reach a certain speed. But if he were to move at strange angles, drifting about in erratic movements, then he did not excel in this aspect.

But, the ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ was able to completely make up for this insufficiency.

Now that he had comprehended the concept of wind, regardless of whether it was linear velocity or how nimble his movements could be, Lin Ming was already far superior to martial artists at the same cultivation. He could even soar to a stop in the air, and then change direction. These movements completely violated the laws of physics in air.

As he was, he had amazing physical strength, and the true essence in his body was astonishingly thick and pure. Meanwhile, he was a martial artist who had the terrifying ability of ‘Flow like Silk’, and the ghostly speed from ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’. What sort of concept was this?

Words were not enough to describe how powerful he was with all these skills together.

“With my strength as it is now, I don’t know how much worse I am than Zhang Guanyu. If I am weaker, just how much weaker am I? I heard that from the fourth rank on, there was extreme disparity between the fourth rank and Zhang Guanyu’s third…”

The fourth rank and third rank on the Ranking Stone were not even close to the same level.

This time, Lin Ming had not been trying to maximize his score. Otherwise, with his ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ movements, he would have easily been able flit around and kill enemies at the Bone Forging stage, and greatly increase his score. He could have reached the fourth place ranking, and even had the possibility of reaching third!

However, rankings did not mean everything. Even if Lin Ming’s rank surpassed Zhang Guanyu, it would not mean anything. It had already been a very long time since Zhang Guanyu last participated in the Ten Thousand Killing Array assessment. According to the Crown Prince’s information, Zhang Guanyu currently cultivated the ‘Divine Acacia Power’, and his strength had experienced a tremendous rise.

“Right now I am inferior to Zhang Guanyu. I don’t know how much time it will take to surpass him. The Seven Profound Martial House Master gave me four months to challenge Zhang Guanyu, but I think I will be able to in three!”

Lin Ming didn’t consider defeating Zhang Guanyu to be an insurmountable problem.

“Lin Ming, congratulations.” Qin Xingxuan said with a smile. She had been standing not too far off from the altar, and watching the changes in the Ranking Stone.

“Not only in the top ten, but also the sixth place ranking, really… really not something I expected.” Bai Jingyun said as she also walked over, blinking as she steadily gazed at Lin Ming. She hadn’t thought that Lin Ming’s growth would be so drastic in such a short time.

However, Murong Zi’s state of mind was much better. She distantly glanced at the Ranking Stone, and then looked at Lin Ming as he casually talked to Qin Xingxuan and Bai Jingyun in a friendly manner. She muttered in a low voice, “Farm animals are farm animals, it’s impossible to judge a person just by looking at them.”

The second round of the Ten Thousand Killing Array carried on as usual. However, no one was actually paying attention to this. If not for some disciples that had already put down a true essence stone as down payment, they wouldn’t even have wanted to undergo the assessment.

As the second rounded of the assessment began, an old man wearing a long blue gown walked into the Ten Thousand Killing Array’s ashlar square.

The old man appeared silently; many people hadn’t even noticed that he was there. It was as if he had always been standing there, and no one had ever noticed him.

Lin Ming suddenly started. This was the first time that he had seen this blue-gowned old man. This person had appeared out of nowhere like a ghost!

Lin Ming unconsciously took a step back. On this old man, Lin Ming realized that his breath was even stronger than Muyi’s!

“Greetings, senior.” Although he didn’t know who this old man was, but to appear in the Seven Profound Martial House at this time, he should be one of the top elders of the Seven Profound Martial House. It was even possible that he was the Seven Profound Martial House Master!

Qin Xingxuan discovered this old man at nearly the same time that Lin Ming did. Seeing this old man, she was slightly surprised, immediately bowing, “Greetings, Martial House Master.”

The man laughed and stroked his beard, saying, “Young Child Xingxuan, your words are sweet enough. What Martial House Master am I, I am just a deputy.”

The Seven Profound Martial house had a Martial House Master and two Deputy Martial House Masters.

However, Qin Xingxuan was always awkward greeting the Deputy Martial House Masters, so she ended up greeting them as Martial House Master.

Lin Ming’s heart was slightly cold. It turned out that this old man was the Seven Profound Martial House’s Deputy Master, yet he had managed to acquire peak Houtian stage strength.

If the Deputy House Master had such power, then the Martial House Master was certainly stronger.

However, no matter how strong they were, it would be impossible for them to be a Xiantian stage master. The Martial House Master should also be at the peak Houtian stage. Within those at the peak Houtian stage, there were also those that were weaker and those that were stronger.

As Qin Xingxuan greeted this old man, the disciples present also heard. They hadn’t thought that this old man that suddenly came out of nowhere would be the Seven Profound Martial House Deputy Master!

Suddenly, these disciples felt a cascade of emotions at once. They were panicked, flustered, excited, awed, and scared, all at the same time. This was just like when a commoner suddenly saw the arrival of the emperor. They would fear they did not know what the proper etiquette was, but also feel excited and honored to be in his presence. After all, to the common person, the emperor was a legendary character.

To these low-order disciples, the Martial House Master and the Deputy Martial House master were elusive and secretive in their movements; one would feel their presence, but not see them. There were many Heavenly Abode disciples, who in their entire five years at the Seven Profound Martial House, would never catch even a glimpse of the Martial House Master!

“The Deputy House Master personally came!”

“That’s the Deputy House Master of the Martial House! He really is a true master, I never even noticed that he appeared.”

“Why would the Deputy House Master come here? Would it be to congratulate Lin Ming?”

“I doubt it. But if it’s true, this Lin Ming’s face is just too great this time. Even if a new emperor ascended the throne, it would be very difficult to ask the Martial House Master to attend the crowning ceremony.”

As people were speculating in confusion, at this moment, the old man in blue clothes withdrew an overly long box from his spatial ring. Set upright, this box was even higher than the old man; it was almost 10 feet high.

The box was made from sandalwood. It appeared to be extremely aged, and faintly exuded the scent of rustic wood.

As Lin Ming saw this long box, he had a faint guess in his heart.

Sure enough, when the old man opened the box, revealed inside was a long silk cloth. Between the silk, there was a faint shine of something silver. Without a doubt, this was a spear that was wrapped in the silk!

Heavy Profound Soft Spear!

The old man in blue clothes smiled and said, “Boy, take this spear and have a look.”

Lin Ming took a deep breath, pulled off the silk cloth covering, and took the Heavy Profound Soft Spear in his hand.

As his hand touched the spear shaft, Lin Ming felt an immediate rush of coolness, as if this spear was linking with his flesh and blood.

It had an extremely heavy feeling; the weight had to be above a thousand jins!

The spear was bright silver all around. Even the spearhead was also shiningly silver. The spear’s blade was thin, cold, and strikingly sharp.

The spear shaft was elastic, but to shake it actually required a greater amount of strength than what the Penetrating Rainbow spear required. It was clear that the implicit tension and striking force of the Heavy Profound Soft Spear was much higher than dark purple elastic iron.

Feeling this faintly cool trace of the spear shaft, Lin Ming clearly felt slightly ridged trace lines on the spear shaft. They were just like ripples of water and felt pleasant to the touch.

These kinds of trace marks were not for preventing one’s grip from slipping. Rather, they were from a refiner master who inscribed it upon the barrel of the shaft. These lines had already penetrated into the spear shaft and were similar to an inscription symbol. They had long merged into one organic whole with the spear. Relying on these lines, it enabled one to pour their true essence into the spear and circulate it throughout, finally transforming it into a medium-grade human-step treasure.

Chapter 143 – True Essence Manifestation

“There’s no inscription symbol…” Lin Ming thought. He himself was the current most splendid inscription grand master in the Sky Fortune Kingdom. He would have to ponder over what sort of inscription symbol to add to this Heavy Profound Soft Spear, to seek the highest possible promotion of might.

By now, the blue-clothed old man said, “Before the Martial House Master departed, he gave me this spear and told me that as long as you pass the test, this spear would be given to you. This spear was created by the Seven Profound Valleys’ Refiner Faction. If it were not because of the inherent limitations of such weapons, it would be at least a high-grade human-step treasure.”

Weapons like the spear, staff, and bow all demanded both tenacity and elasticity. They were the most difficult of treasures to create. Although this Heavy Profound Soft Spear was only a medium-grade human-step treasure, in terms of value, it was much more precious and valuable than a common high-grade human-step treasure sword!

As Lin Ming held onto the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, he loved it enough that he was almost unable to put it down.

The blue-clothed old man said, “This Heavy Profound Soft Spear weighs 1200 jins. The spear shaft is 9 feet long and made from heavy profound soft silver, while the spear head is 9 inches and made from cold star steel. The total length of this spear is 9 feet 9 inches.

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, the shape of a spear and lance were similar. The general belief was that a spear was less than ten feet, and a lance was longer than ten feet. The spear was a weapon usually used in battles by martial artists, but the lance was almost exclusively used by someone riding on a warhorse. Because the lance was too long, it was difficult to display its strength without riding on the back of a horse.

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, the army provided standard war horses and lances to those in its ranks. The pole of a lance was 10 feet, and the lance point 8 inches, therefore it was known as a 10 foot 8 lance. The lance was once famously used by a tough and valiant general. He had favored the lance, and his strikes would cause the enemies to bleed as if his weapon was a serpent, thus it became known as the 10 foot 8 snake lance.

In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, an average man was 7 feet, and they would have sons that were 7 feet. Of course, there were those that were taller, and might even be 8 feet high or taller.

An 8 foot spear was already the height of a tall martial artist. A 9 foot 9 inch spear was higher than a martial artist by two feet. Using such a long spear, the range of attack would be larger, but the difficulty would also be higher.

Among all the numerals, 9 is the highest. This symbol had been noble and honored since ancient times. A mortal emperor could only be referred to as the royal nine five, but the martial gods of old were actually called the supreme nine nine.

The spear was the king of a hundred soldiers, and a nine foot nine inch spear was the supreme 99 among all other spears. This spear was truly a king among kings. A normal refining master with only a modicum of ability would never dare to rashly refine a 9 foot nine 9 long spear. They would fear their ability was insufficient, and ruin their own destiny.

Even if there were refining masters that were confident in their own refining technique, when creating the spear, they had to quench the flames of its creation with water added with fifth-level ominous beast blood. Only with this sacrifice to the spear would the malignant influences of the spear vanish.

With the Seven Profound Valleys’ deep resources and history, they certainly would have used fifth-level vicious beast blood to quench and temper the spear. Not only that, but they would not have used a small amount. In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, 1 tael of this blood was worth more than 30,000 gold taels, and was difficulty to buy. When Lin Ming had been planning to draw his body inscription, he had spent a tremendous amount of effort in order to collect 2 taels of this blood.

“Thank you, Deputy Martial House Master.” Lin Ming reverently said as he took the Heavy Profound Soft Spear in both his hands and deeply bowed. This spear was simply too precious, and it was also very important to him.

Seeing Lin Ming receive the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, the other disciples of the Martial House had very keen and eager expressions. Although they did not use a spear, if a martial artist saw a good weapon, they would still be envious.

“Show off a few moves. This old man wants to take a look at your spear technique.” The blue-clothed old man wet his lips and chuckled.

“Yes.” Lin Ming held the spear in both hands and bowed. He took a step back, and pressed the spear flat against his arm and pointed it outwards. The 1200 jin Heavy Profound Soft Spear was held perfectly level by Lin Ming. With Lin Ming’s increased strength, this 1200 jin Heavy Profound Soft Spear was just right.

As he felt the weight of the spear, Lin Ming gave the shaft a fierce shake. The Heavy Profound Soft Spear danced like a silver snake in his hands, and the originally sharp point of the spear head vibrated until it looked like a large illusory pearl.

There was a powerful force contained within the Heavy Profound Soft Spear that was very lethal. If an average person touched this vibrating spear head, they would be sent flying backwards by the vigorous tremors. If this spear point touched certain points like the chest or belly, the ribs would fracture, and there was an extreme possibility that the internal organs would all burst and that person would die a miserable death.

“Good spear!”

Lin Ming sincerely praised the spear, and his left hand pat down on the breech of the shaft. He forcefully held down the vibrating long spear and then took a step back. An imposing momentum erupted around him, and the Heavy Profound Soft Spear thrust out like a bolt of silver lightning.

“Flood Dragon Goes to Sea!”

Cha!

The piercing sound in the air was just as if a sharp knife was running across a glass pane. Rippling waves visible to the naked eye congealed in the air, as if light itself was twisting.

This was because the vibrating true essence that was poured into the spear had no place to vent, so it rushed into the air, causing vibrating sound waves that rapidly spread out.

Boom!

A thunderclap sounded in the air, and a stone pillar 100 feet far from Lin Ming suddenly exploded, stone rubble flying everywhere as the column collapsed into dust and rocks.

But Lin Ming’s spear point was 90 feet away from that stone column!

The blue-clothed old man’s eyes brightened, “What a good young fellow, that was true essence manifestation!”

True essence manifestation was an ability within the realm of Pulse Condensation Period martial artists!

Martial artists were able to release magnificent and awe-inspiring martial skills; but, this was not true essence manifestation. True essence manifestation referred to when a martial artist casually attacked, and was able to realize true essence and condense it into reality. Like so, every free strike they made would be comparable to a martial skill from an ordinary martial artist.

The requirement for this was that a martial artist’s true essence must be incomparably thick. Usually, only a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist could achieve true essence that dense.

But the current Lin Ming had only just entered the early Altering Muscle stage; how could that blue-clothed old man not be startled?

It was not only the blue-clothed old man, but also the two elders, Elder Sun and Elder Xu, Qin Xingxuan, and some other master talents present that had noticed Lin Ming’s true essence manifestation.

To Qin Xingxuan, this ability of Lin Ming’s to manifest true essence was much more surprising than him obtained the sixth place rank on the Ranking Stone. Qin Xingxuan found it hard to imagine that an early Altering Muscle stage martial artist could reach the boundary where he could manifest true essence. She was already at the Bone Forging stage, yet she did not yet have that ability.

“What the hell is Lin Ming cultivating? Is this ethereal martial intent really that godly?”

The other disciples had not been able to see the mysterious principles within Lin Ming’s spear strike, but this did not hinder them from exclaiming in surprise at the spear’s excessive vigor.

“Spear wind, that was definitely spear wind!”

“No, that was certainly the legendary spear light!”

“What do you know? That was what ancients called spear-fu!”

The lower-order disciples didn’t know much about the theories of spear wind, spear light, sword wind, sword light, and were somewhat vague on the other speculations. They only knew that Lin Ming’s strike was truly fierce.

With a single thrust of Lin Ming’s spear, he had been able to shatter a stone column. Though this was an unintentional move, he was still incomparably excited.

After Lin Ming had broken through to the Altering Muscle stage, he had reached the boundary of true essence manifestation. But he hadn’t been able to use this to fight his enemies. However, now with the medium-grade human-step treasure, for the first time Lin Ming was able to release his true essence. Even without touching, he could still attack his enemy.

Relying on true essence to create a ranged attack was not difficult. Normally, a martial artist could do this once they cultivated a martial skill. Lin Ming hadn’t yet studied any martial skills, but now, as long as his true essence reserves were enough, he could actually strike out with a force tantamount to a martial skill!

Lin Ming wasn’t satisfied with just a single spear move. When his true essence poured into the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, it had the feeling of a fish swimming in water, and let Lin Ming feel incomparably comfortable.

At this time, the aura around Lin Ming’s body bloomed once again. He received his spear, gripped it in his right hand and fiercely thrust out a dozen times. He turned and stabbed, ‘Flowers in the Storm’!

‘Flowers in the Storm’ was another move within the ‘Foundation Spear Technique’. The strikes of the spear were like a hail of petals, without a single opening, where not even water could enter!

The spear shadow became blurry, and a keening whistle was produced from the terrifying speed of the spear. In the surroundings of the spear shadow, there were ripples once again visible to the naked eye. Anything that this high speed vibrating shockwave touched was torn into shreds!

Lin Ming stabbed out hundreds of times, and finally vented the powerful momentum that he had gathered a moment ago. As he took back the silver spear, Lin Ming’s mind was filled with a great happiness. The strength of this medium-grade human-step treasure was truly outstanding!

If he added an inscription symbol on top of that, the might of the spear would increase by nearly 50%!

Lin Ming already couldn’t wait to battle Zhang Guanyu!

……………………..

The news of Lin Ming reaching the sixth place in the Ten Thousand Killing Array was like a massive bomb that exploded throughout Sky Fortune City. In merely one day, it had spread to every nook and cranny of the land.

Three months to enter the top ten ranks of the Ranking Stone, four months to defeat Zhang Guanyu, five months to defeat Ta Ku, and six months to defeat Ling Sen.

To everyone, this series of tests was as difficult as ascending to heaven! But now, Lin Ming had only used two months to complete the first task. Not only that, but he had eclipsed it – Ranking Stone, sixth place!

Did this mean that after four months he could defeat Zhang Guanyu, and then defeat Ta Ku in the fifth month?

And six months later, subsequently challenge Ling Sen?

Zhang Guanyu and Ta Ku did not count for much, But Ling Sen had already been recognized throughout Sky Fortune Kingdom as being invincible within his stage; it could even be said that he was the top martial artist of those below the Pulse Condensation Period.

He was only a half-step into the Bone Forging stage, and yet he had strength that was comparable to Pulse Condensation Period martial artists. If Lin Ming defeated Ling Sen, then he would have shattered Ling Sen’s legend of being invincible within his stage, and his individual strength would be comparable to a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist!

For someone with cultivation at the Altering Muscle stage to have the strength of a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist, it was terrifying. Not only that, but Lin Ming was so young, and his cultivation speed was completely abnormal.

How many years would he need to break into the Bone Forging stage, or the Pulse Condensation Period?

When Lin Ming reached the Pulse Condensation Period, could he defeat a Houtian master, and seize the throne of being the top martial artist within the Sky Fortune Kingdom?

Like this, could Lin Ming reach the Houtian stage, or even the peak Houtian stage?

With Lin Ming’s cultivation speed, to reach the Houtian stage before he was 30 would not be difficult!

If he were to reach the peak Houtian stage, would he be able to compare to a Xiantian master?

Thinking of this, many people did not dare to presume any further. To them, a Xiantian master was simply a fable that existed only in legends.

Even in the Seven Profound Valleys where masters and powerhouses lurked everywhere, a Xiantian stage master had a pivotal status!

Regardless of if they were a Seven Profound Envoy or a Martial House Master, they would only be at the peak Houtian stage.

Although their status was higher than the emperor of Sky Fortune Kingdom, they still had to give some respect to the emperor. When they were issuing a decree, they also had to mind their tone.

But a Xiantian master was different. They were able to directly discard the emperor, and even set up a new emperor in place of the old!

If one did not obey their orders?

They would kill their way into the Royal Palace at night, and take the emperor’s severed head!

Who would dare to stop a Xiantian master?

Even if everyone knew perfectly well who it was that killed the emperor, who would have the ability to investigate?

Chapter 149 – Life Death Contract

“How about we sign a Life Death Contract? This way, if one of us is wounded or crippled, we cannot be held responsible. How about it?”

Lin Ming’s smile was very bright. The effect that the ‘Pulse Cutting Palm’ created was a little too excessive, so it was a good idea to establish a Life Death Contract in advance.

When Zhang Guanyu heard Lin Ming say such a thing, he was over the moon. This Lin Ming was simply stretching out his neck waiting for him to chip it off. He was so stupid; he had never seen someone do anything so stupid!

“Lin Ming! What are you doing!?” Wang Yuhan anxiously said. She did not use a true essence sound transmission, but had run over instead. To sign a Life Death Contract? That was simply digging his own grave!

“Lin Ming, you cannot sign this!”

Zhang Guanyu laughed, and said with a smile, “Miss Wang, may I ask who you are to Lin Ming?

“I…” Wang Yuhan’s words caught in her throat. There was nothing she could directly say. Her relationship with Lin Ming was only as an inscription master and assistant. Besides that, there wasn’t anything else. What qualifications did she have to interfere in Lin Ming’s decision?

Lin Ming said, “Miss Wang is a friend of mine. Zhang Guanyu, since I said that I will sign the Life Death Contract, I will not renege on a promise I made. Bring me a pen.”

“Good! Wonderful! Servants, bring the writing set!” Zhang Guanyu chuckled.

A servant quickly brought over a set of writing utensils. A clerk came over and quickly wrote down line after line on the paper in small print. These were the words of the Life Death Contract between Lin Ming and Zhang Guanyu.

Zhang Guanyu pressed down a fingerprint, and then taking up a red pen, made a big waving motion as if he were clawing, and the words ‘Zhang Guanyu’ appeared on the Life Death Contract. The ink was bright red like blood, and looked incomparably fierce.

Lin Ming received the ink and red pen, and quietly signed his name. His strokes were not obvious, but it was similar to a long spear and faintly exuded a sharp imposing momentum. Standing on the side, Wang Yuhan could clearly see that the intersecting strokes of Lin Ming had already penetrated the back of the paper and were flowing outwards.

As the Life Death Contract was signed, Zhang Guanyu chortled, and sent Ouyang Dihua a true essence sound transmission. “Mister Ouyang, before we had agreed that you would give me the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead.”

Ouyang Dihua smiled and replied with a true essence sound transmission. “Why, Lin Ming has challenged you so early, and you still want to use the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead? Aren’t you overestimating him?”

Zhang Guanyu quietly replied, “Caution is best, I must ruin Lin Ming to the point that he cannot recover from the failure. I do not want to allow even a little mistake to occur.”

“Haha, this Lin Ming has offended you; he truly does have bad luck.” Ouyang Dihua flicked his finger, and a gray spatial ring suddenly flew into Zhang Guanyu’s waiting hand.

At this time, it was getting late, and Ouyang Dihua’s action was very subtle. This scene was so minor that almost nobody noticed. But after Lin Ming had cultivated the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, his senses were much keener, and he had actually noticed that small movement near Zhang Guanyu.

“What is in that ring?” Lin Ming’s mind went cold, suddenly and secretly on alert. The ring that Ouyang Dihua had thrown was certainly not something minor. “I don’t know what card this Zhang Guanyu has in his hand. I must be careful this fight.”

The Imperial Palace’s military field was just outside the gates. It was large, had a paved floor of blue stone, and it had several dozen acres of space; it was even larger than a horse field.

Because of this duel, all the participants at the grand banquet had come out to watch. Even Murong Zi, who had been hiding, had found an obscure corner to watch together with Bai Jingyun.

Zhan Guanyu had replaced the long silk gown that he had been wearing with simpler clothing and ran onto the military field. In his hand he held an impressive high-grade human-step treasure sword that shined with a dense coldness. This sword was the one that Lin Ming had helped Zhang Guanyu engrave just a month ago.

Seeing this sword, Wang Yuhan sighed. This day, Lin Ming would face the top quality treasure sword that he had personally helped make.

Zhang Guanyu casually flourished the sword in his hand. He smiled, and with a happy expression said, “Mister Lin, do you remember this sword? I must thank you, I did not imagine that this sword would be so perfect. I wonder what it’s like to lose under a sword that you helped to create? How would you feel?”

“The feeling should be the same as yours.” Lin Ming pulled out the Heavy Profound Soft Spear. Above his right hand, the symbol began to glow with a hint of dark red light, as if the blood vessels underneath were congealing.

Zhang Guanyu naturally did not understand Lin Ming’s words. He did not know that the fifth-level vicious beast blood that he had personally handed over was one of the primary materials for the inscription symbol on Lin Ming’s right hand. Otherwise, his feelings would be much more intense than Lin Ming’s.

“Lin Ming’s spear… it… it doesn’t have an inscription symbol!” Wang Yuhan could not believe this as she looked at Lin Ming’s Heavy Profound Soft Spear. She had never thought that Lin Ming, an inscription grand master, would not have given his own spear an inscription symbol!

Just what exactly was his mind thinking?

As Wang Yuhan said this, everyone turned to look at Lin Ming’s Heavy Profound Soft Spear. This spear did not have an inscription?

Usually, a normal martial artist would have no way to judge from a distance whether a weapon had an inscription symbol or not. But Wang Yuhan was an inscription master so what she said shouldn’t be wrong.

Lin Ming obtained the weapon, and hadn’t placed an inscription symbol on it as soon as possible? And now he was planning on using an inscriptionless weapon against Zhang Guanyu? Why would he do such a foolish thing?

They were not optimistic about Lin Ming’s strength to begin with, but now even his weapon was an order lower than Zhang Guanyu’s, and it also lacked an inscription symbol. How could he still fight this battle?

Far away, Qin Xingxuan also watched this, and her delicate eyebrows pressed together. She was clear; Lin Ming was young, but by no means an immature child. Since he dared to challenge Zhang Guanyu at this time, what sort of cards did he have up his sleeve?

“Hehe, I didn’t think that you would be stupid to this degree. You obtained such a fine weapon and hadn’t placed an inscription symbol upon it as soon as you could, yet you still want to cope with me today with it.” Zhang Guanyu greedily licked his lips and smiled.

Lin Ming looked at the Heavy Profound Soft Spear. These days he had been occupied with cultivating the ‘Heretical God Force’ and drawing up the ‘Strife Seal’. He hadn’t been able to set aside any time to give the Heavy Profound Soft Spear the inscription symbol that it deserved. The main reason was that Lin Ming wanted collect some top quality materials to make the most formidable inscription symbol that he could with his current technique and cultivation. To find the materials that were worthy of this Heavy Profound Soft Spear would take some time. After all, he planned to use this spear for a long time.

However, missing an inscription symbol didn’t affect him too much. Lin Ming’s dark purple elastic iron Penetrating Rainbow spear didn’t have an inscription symbol either.

Lin Ming stepped forward, his right hand holding the end of the Heavy Profound Soft Spear as he stretched it out. He could feel that his right hand was full of an explosive force; this was power that the ‘Strife Seal’ had given him.

After he had successfully drawn up the ‘Strife Seal’, Lin Ming’s strength head already reached 7200 jins. This strength was even stronger than early Pulse Condensation Period martial artist’s!

Motionless like a mountain!

With the flare of Lin Ming’s imposing aura, his body began to release a formidable pressure. Some of the young elites of Sky Fortune City with weaker cultivations could not bear it, and backed away. This was just like what an average person would feel when they confronted a wild and ferocious tiger. Even if they knew this tiger would not injure them, they could not help but back away.

“Good! What a commanding aura! Lin Ming’s strong point is his strength and towering manner, and his speed is not so good. But Zhang Guanyu’s strong point lies in his speed and his strength is slightly lower. This could be said to be a duel between a peak strength powerhouse and a peak speed powerhouse! It really makes one look forward to it!”

A distinguished disciple of the Seven Profound Marital House said.

A distinguished disciple of the Seven Profound Marital House said.

“A duel of peak powerhouses? Hehe, the strongest disciple within the Seven Profound Martial House is Ta Ku. Not only is his cultivation at the early Bone Forging stage, but he also as inborn divine strength. Zhang Guanyu is the fastest, Ta Ku is the strongest. When these two fight, that will truly be the match of peak powerhouses.”

“A duel of peak powerhouses? Hehe, the strongest disciple within the Seven Profound Martial House is Ta Ku. Not only is his cultivation at the early Bone Forging stage, but he also as inborn divine strength. Zhang Guanyu is the fastest, Ta Ku is the strongest. When these two fight, that will truly be the match of peak powerhouses.”

“As for Lin Ming, although he is a heaven warping genius, he is still tender and inexperienced. Motionless like a mountain how? I bet that the agile Zhang Guanyu will lead Lin Ming to dance around in circles. With Lin Ming’s speed, I’m afraid that he might not even be able to touch the hem of Zhang Guanyu’s clothes! And since Zhang Guanyu also cultivates the ‘Divine Acacia Power’, his true essence and strength might not be lower than Lin Ming’s. The result of this duel is already undeniable!”

A young aristocratic junior in silk robes sneered as he said this. In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, there were enough young people that idolized Lin Ming that they were like an endless river of carp. But correspondingly, there were no small number of those young martial artists that were jealous of Lin Ming and hoped that he would suffer a loss, and henceforth never be able to recover. This young man in a silk gown was also one of them.

He believed that Lin Ming would one day be able to surpass Zhang Guanyu. But, that was not today. Since Ling Ming had challenged Zhang Guanyu now, he would truly die miserably.

Zhang Guanyu sneered, and mockingly said, “Your imposing aura is good, but what a pity that it is useless against me. I am not Zhu Yan, and I have already seen through your ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’!”

As he said this, the entire audience was startled, particularly Wang Yuhan. Her heart suddenly felt as if it was hanging by strings. The ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ was Lin Ming’s strongest ability. If Zhang Guanyu had already seen through Lin Ming’s ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’, then how could Lin Ming possibly win?

However, Lin Ming completely did not care for Zhang Guanyu’s words and disregarded them. He brightly smiled and said, “You’re just playing mind games. With your garbage perception, you had cultivated the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ for more than half a year and harmed so many women, and yet you still haven’t reached the second layer? You think that you could see through my ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ with your garbage perception? Too laughable!”

As Lin Ming said this, Zhang Guanyu felt deeply aggrieved, and he was very angry. It was true that he had continually cultivated the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ and still hadn’t reached the second layer, therefore he had worried that he would never reach Large Success of the ‘Divine Acacia Power’s’ seventh layer in his entire life, and attain the realm where he would have inexhaustible Yang Essence.

Lin Ming’s words had stamped on his sore spot.

“A person shouldn’t be so unrestrained, now go die!” As soon as Zhang Guanyu yelled out, his figure flashed, and even his shadow was lost. Those present could only hear a series of ta ta ta footsteps and a sharp piercing sound coming out from nowhere. This was the sound of a high speed sword cutting through the wind!

“So fast!”

“Heavens! Even my eyes cannot catch up to his speed! Is this really a speed that a human can hope to achieve!?”

The young heroes and outstanding talents present all had a good ability to judge others’ power. Although they knew that there would be a disparity between Lin Ming and Zhang Guanyu, they hadn’t thought that this difference would be like an endless gulf between them!

This speed was so fast that not even the eye could follow. How would Lin Ming deal with this?

One simply did not know where his sword would come from!

Zhang Guanyu’s speed was just like a rushing wind.

Lin Ming gripped the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, and stood motionless in the same place.

One was an indistinct figure with rapid movements, and the other was standing completely still. Just looking at this momentum, Lin Ming was weaker.

Zhang Guanyu flashed around to arrive at Lin Ming’s back. He grinned fiendishly, and aimed his sword to lop off Lin Ming’s head. His sword reached an extreme of speed; even sound was swallowed within it.

Chapter 152 – Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead

That sword in Zhang Guanyu’s hands was a high-grade human-step treasure. If Lin Ming had been holding the dark purple elastic iron spear, then this sword would have already pierced straight through the spear shaft!

Lin Ming only felt an unrivaled sharp strength vigorously transmit through him, and his body flew back in the air. He tumbled backwards for several dozens of feet before using his own strength to hold himself down, but the blood in his chest was still roiling from the impact.

So strong!

Lin Ming could not help but acknowledge that even though Zhang Guanyu’s true essence was impure, his strength was utterly dreadful!

“That slender sword bent a heavy spear. His sword was flooded with true essence, and with that irresistible strength, that sword forced me back so much. Zhang Guanyu is truly fierce.”

Zhang Guanyu was grinning like demon. He said, “Lin Ming, I told you that I already saw through you ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’! As long as I concentrate my true essence into a thin shape, I can use it to pierce through your vibrating true essence, and expose your weakness!”

“Expose my weakness?” Lin Ming smiled. This move might be somewhat useful to deal with the original ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’, but against ‘Flow like Silk’, it was pointless. The total wisdom of the Realm of the Gods had accumulated for countless millennia and repeatedly tempered into the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’; how could it be something that someone as insignificant like Zhang Guanyu could break?

“Lin Ming, resign yourself to fate. Today, I will end the myth of your genius!” Zhang Guanyu howled like a depraved beast. The sword in his hand began to emit a keening wail, as if there were countless ghosts circling around the blade. With a loud explosion, the stones under Zhang Guanyu’s feet began to crack apart.

“Hehe, just die! Life Severing Dead Bone Blade!”

“Life Severing Dead Bone Blade?” Qin Xingxuan frowned. This was a an incomparably vicious and evil move, and it was also the most powerful maneuver within the first layer of the ‘Divine Acacia Power’.

The ‘Divine Acacia Power’ was a unification of martial skills and heart mantras. It was a demonic art that belonged to the path of evil. This so called demonic art was one that was filled with heretical and diabolical ways. For instance using women, devouring, going berserk, these were all methods in order to increase one’s strength and cultivation in a short time. It was easy for this cultivation method to cause one to be taken over by their darkest obsessions as if they were possessed by the devil. The sword would become slanted, and the style was insidious beyond measure; it could even cause damage to oneself.

The ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’ was a sword move that released countless wronged spirits. Once this blade stabbed into its enemy, their true essence would be reversed, and it could absorb their flesh and blood life essence. If one’s cultivation was poor, then with a stab of the sword, it could even turn an enemy into bleached bones!

Even a martial artist at a high cultivation who had thick true essence would suffer a miserable fate if they were stabbed by this sword. Their body would lose much of their inner vitality, and it would cause the body to atrophy and wither away. The meridians, muscles, and tendons would all be wasted away, until they were finally turned into a disabled vegetable.

This kind of disability could only be cured by the rare material Human Lifedeath Boneflesh. Otherwise, it was simply impossible to cure. And this kind of rare material treasure was actually not something that a large sect like the Seven Profound Valleys could even make!

If one were to be struck by this ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’, then their entire life’s martial arts cultivation would be half wiped out, or even completely ruined.

However, although this ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’ was a perverse and malefic move, one could not freely use it. This sword move would cause whoever used it to have their mind and soul eroded by the unjust ghosts, and it would cause their personality to turn to chaos, until they finally became a mind-touched devil.

“This Zhang Guanyu is truly black hearted; he would actually dare to use this move. He is determined to destroy Lin Ming.” Qin Xingxuan was a core disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys, so she understood what effect the ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’ had.

When she said this, Wang Yuhan’s heart suddenly painfully clenched. Lin Ming’s ‘Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist’ had already been suppressed. How would he confront this ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’?

Zhang Guanyu’s sword had not even thrust out, yet Lin Ming could already feel a chilly wind blowing at him. This icy wind seemed to turn into a mass of aggrieved souls that wrapped around his hands and feet, suddenly slowing down Lin Ming’s movements.

Lin Ming frowned. “Ah? This sword move can actually affect my movements?”

“Haha! This is my strongest move; it is impossible for you to hide!” Zhang Guanyu let loose a demented cackle. His handsome face had already been completely twisted from before, and now it was just a mockery of a human. Countless ghosts emerged from Zhang Guanyu’s body. His hair was completely loose and blown up by the chilling breeze. Like this, he seemed to have wholly become a demon.

“Don’t worry; I will let you keep your life!” Zhang Guanyu cried out like a evil monster, and his sword thrust towards Lin Ming. Those myriad ghosts condensed onto Zhang Guanyu’s sword, and the sword blade completely turned white like bleached bones. It was as if Zhang Guanyu was not holding a sword in his hand, but a white bone!

Seeing this sword thrust reflected in his eyes, Lin Ming let loose a roar. True essence began to rapidly circulate throughout his body, and the Heretical God Seed in Lin Ming’s heart began to issue forth a blazing light. The highly compressed true essence scattered outwards and rushed into Lin Ming’s body and blood.

‘Heretical God Force’ – open!

The first layer of the ‘Heretical God Force’ could instantly increase one’s strength and true essence by 50%. In addition to the increased power from the ‘Strife Seal’, Lin Ming only felt his entire body blazing with fighting spirit!

Not only that, but all the accumulated momentum from his previous collisions with Zhang Guanyu instantly erupted at once. His spear thrust out and swept away the world!

As his unstoppable momentum burst forth, all the haunting ghosts that had affected his speed were blown away without a trace. Lin Ming was instantly restored to his peak speed. However, he did not intend to hide. His body contained a raging war-like thirst. He was like a volcano that had reached the critical point; he must erupt!

“I’ll let you see, the true ‘Flow like Silk’! —“

“Flood Dragon Goes to Sea!”

Lin Ming’s spear flew forwards. With a loud explosion, the ground underneath his feet completely ruptured. The cracks spread like an ever widening spider web. For a time, it was as if a true flood dragon had rushed out from Lin Ming’s silver spear.

True essence rioted and space seemed to be compressed as a terrible strength formed visible ripples in the air. It swept through the broken tiles on the floor, and scattered them like a hurricane!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s spear which contained the peak of his strength struck Zhang Guanyu’s ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’.

In that moment, all the tiny units within Lin Ming’s body began to vibrate together, and instantly turned into 5000 filaments of true essence. These 5000 true essence filaments were just like 5000 ominous, little, and ferocious flood dragons that rushed at Zhang Guanyu.

Cha cha cha cha cha cha!

The ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’ that held so many ghosts was similar to waste paper as the small flood dragons lunged in and bit through!

This was a completely one-sided crushing!

The 5000 true essence filaments broke through the ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’, and immediately rushed into Zhang Guanyu just like a rampaging pack of wild beasts.

Zhang Guanyu had already reached the Bone Forging stage, and true essence had sunk into his bones; his inner body’s defensive capabilities were simply amazing. But how could this keep off 5000 true essence threads of vibrating true essence enhanced by the ‘Heretical God Force’?

“Ah ah ah ah!”

Zhang Guanyu issued a piercing scream that turned into pitiful wails. Many of his organs had been torn, countless blood vessels had ruptured, and fresh blood spurted out from his body. Zhang Guanyu dropped his sword. It was as if his entire body had been turned inside out, and his body was like a broken bag of blood that crumpled to the ground.

There was total silence among the audience. Zhang Guanyu’s strongest move, the most brutal and savage finishing blow of the ‘Divine Acacia Power’s’ first layer – ‘Life Severing Dead Bone Blade’, had actually been sent flying with one thrust of Lin Ming’s spear!

Looking at the arena under Lin Ming’s feet, and the ring of cracks that were like a giant spider web that spread for dozens of feet, this was the utterly cataclysmic power which was created by the overwhelming true essence and strength of a monstrous genius!

The Seven Profound Martial House Master had given Lin Ming a test to defeat Zhang Guanyu in 4 months. Now, he had finished in only two and a half months!

And not only that, but he defeated Zhang Guanyu in his strongest state with the might of a single spear!

Lin Ming’s Heavy Profound Soft Spear did not even have an inscription symbol placed on it!

This was just too terrifying. With Lin Ming, no matter how impossible things seemed, it would become a likely possibility.

………………..

Zhang Guanyu’s five organs had been broken, and he had lost a massive amount of blood. But still, his facial muscles contorted as if they were about to break, and his heart was filled to the brim with agonizing hatred!

“Lin Ming, I will kill you!”

Zhang Guanyu bit his tongue, and reached out a hand to the gray spatial ring he had.

This scene immediately aroused Lin Ming’s vigilance. He clearly remembered that before this fight began, Ouyang Dihua had quietly given Zhang Guanyu a spatial ring; that was the same one he was now reaching for.

With Ouyang Dihua’s background in the Seven Profound Valleys, anything he gave was certainly not some commonplace object.

Lin Ming’s heart was filled with a great sense of crisis. Without a word, he aimed his spear at Zhang Guanyu’s hand, and shot out the Heavy Profound Soft Spear!

Whoosh!

The 1200 jin Heavy Profound Soft Spear broke free with a shrill sound as it flew out; the inherent power within it was extremely horrifying!

Zhang Guanyu had just taken out the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead, when that Heavy Profound Soft Spear pierced the palm of his hand. With mere flesh and blood that had already lost its true essence protection facing such a relentless strength, the results could be imagined!

Poh!

Zhang Guanyu’s pale and slender hand was like a block of tofu that was smashed apart by a heavy hammer!

“Ah ah ah ah ah!” Zhang Guanyu held on to his broken wrist and screamed in pain. At this time, Lin Ming suddenly rushed forwards and aimed a palm at Zhang Guanyu’s back.

‘Pulse Cutting Palm!’

“Stop!”

Lin Ming’s ears rang with the sound of Ouyang Dihua’s shout. But Lin Ming did not listen to him, and still struck his palm towards Zhang Guanyu.

Ouyang Dihua coldly coughed, and his body that had been relaxed and sitting suddenly and violent rushed out. The chair he was sitting in was broken apart by the explosive strength and scattered everywhere.

Ouyang Dihua had wanted to wait for Zhang Guanyu to throw the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead and severely wound or even kill Lin Ming. The Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead was made by an array master of the Seven Profound Valleys; it could kill even an early Pulse Condensation Period martial artist. This sort of treasure could only be produced by a large sect, and it was an absolutely forbidden item within the mortal world.

Ouyang Dihua believed that if Lin Ming were to be directly struck by the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead, then he would meet certain death. Even if it only partially touched him, he would still be seriously injured or disabled.

But he had never expected that Lin Ming would be so decisive. Just at the moment when Zhang Guanyu had taken out the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead, Lin Ming had already thrown the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, and turned Zhang Guanyu’s hand into ground meat!

Now Zhang Guanyu had already lost all of his strength to resist and yet Lin Ming still wanted to use a heavy hand to injure him; how could Ouyang Dihua idly sit by and do nothing? After all, Zhang Guanyu was intimately involved with the acquisition of the 12 Pure Yin girls. If Zhang Guanyu died, then the entire reason that he came to the Sky Fortune Kingdom would be for naught!

“Impudence!”

Seeing Lin Ming simply ignore his orders and still rush at Zhang Guanyu, Ouyang Dihua felt a rising rage in his heart. He raised his true essence and struck out a palm towards Lin Ming.

In this palm strike, Ouyang Dihua had mercilessly used his full strength; it was meant to seriously injure or even kill Lin Ming.

Just when he thought he had reached Lin Ming’s path, and was prepared to kill Lin Ming, Lin Ming’s speed suddenly shot up!

‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’!

Lin Ming used the powered state of the ‘Heretical God Force’ to display the ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’. In that instant, his speed had reached an extreme velocity. Compared to when he had faced Zhang Guanyu a moment ago, he was over 50% faster!

This phantom-like speed had already far exceeded Ouyang Dihua’s maximum speed.

Ouyang Dihua’s palm hit nothing but air!

Chapter 155 – Miniature Thunder Fire Killing Array

‘Since I’ve offended them, what’s done is done, it’s no big deal. Ouyang Dihua might be a little tricky to deal with, but I am not afraid of the Allied Trade Association at all.’

After all, the Allied Trade Association was only a civilian organization. It was true that they had a very deep pockets of resources and a long history, but they still had to comply with the rules of the Seven Profound Martial House.

But Ouyang Dihua was different. Even if he followed the rules of the Seven Profound Martial House on the surface, he might secretly try to murder him.

If the Allied Trade Association wanted to assassinate him, then that would provoke the utter outrage of the Seven Profound Martial House. Qin Ziya would never let this happen. The only result would be that the Allied Trade Association would meet with an apocalyptic disaster.

But if Ouyang Dihua wanted to assassinate him, then that was a different story. Ouyang Dihua had the backing of a Seven Profound Valleys elder. As long as he didn’t leave any evidence, not even Qin Ziya could touch him, and he would finally have to drop the matter.

“I must be careful of Ouyang Dihua. Before I have the strength to resist him, I must go out as little as possible!”

“My top priority right now should be to increase my strength.”

As Lin Ming thought this, he took out two items from his spatial ring – the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead and the Blood Lingzhi.

He was not in a hurry to consume the Blood Lingzhi. Before, when he had taken the Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill and the Golden Snake Scarlet Pill, there had been some pill toxins that were left in his body. He needed to cultivate for a longer period of time and completely refine the impurities out of his body, and wait for his true essence to stabilize before he could consume the Blood Lingzhi and fully absorb its effects.

As for the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead, although it was a one-time use item, its power didn’t seem small, and it was obviously valuable.

Lin Ming looked at this bead. He wanted to search for any clues that would indicate how to use it.

The bead was the side of a longan, and was an icy blue color. It had an extremely cold surface, and it was chillingly cold in his hand. He couldn’t discern anything special about it.

Lin Ming cautiously investigated the bead with his soul force. As soon as he began to probe, his mind moved.

“Mm? Array formation?”

In the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead was a myriad of dense runes. These were array symbols.

“The inscription symbols seemed to have not unified into a complete array formation, it seems to belong to… Mm, I see, I understand…”

In Lin Ming’s memories about array formations, there was more than the one kind that involved inscription symbols.

The second time that Lin Ming had entered into the infinite space of the Magic Cube, he had absorbed the soul fragment of a mighty elder array master. Lin Ming had completely sealed away this array master’s array formation memories, and had not studied them.

The main reason for this was simply that his cultivation was at too low a realm, and he didn’t have the ability or money to create those large arrays.

The original plan was to wait until he reached the Xiantian realm to begin studying the formation array memories again, but now, after having seen the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead, Lin Ming found something that surprised him.

“So an array formation can also be used like this…”

Lin Ming muttered as he looked at the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead.

He understood that this Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead was, in essence, a highly compressed thunder fire killing array.

Lin Ming had originally thought that an array formation had to be arranged in a large manner, and it could only be used passively. A person had to step inside the array formation before it could display its surpassing might.

Even the memories of array formation from the mighty elder from the Realm of the Gods were also like this.

That mighty elder knew many different varieties of complex array formations. If they had to be classified, they would be imprisoning arrays, killing arrays, illusory arrays, sealing arrays, and so forth.

The function of an imprisoning array was to trap the enemy within, a killing array was to kill an enemy, an illusory magic array was to let an enemy be lost in an endless dreamland so they could never awaken or to ruin their mental state, and a sealing array was to make seals.

Lin Ming never knew that an array formation could be condensed into such a small bead, and then thrown at others to attack them.

If the bead contained a killing array, it could kill people. If it contained an illusory array, it would cause the other party to be swarmed by countless phantasmal illusions.

During a battle, even if there was a great disparity in strength between two parties, if the weaker one were to throw a powerful bead like this, then they would likely change the tide of battle!

“What an imaginative idea!” As Lin Ming studied the array formations within the bead, he couldn’t help but praise the Seven Profound Valleys.

The Seven Profound Valleys had a legacy that dated back 600 years. The sect was founded by seven individuals, each with various abilities and strengths, including one that especially studied array formations.

Of course, it was not necessarily only the Seven Profound Valleys that had invented this ingenious method; it was likely that this was spread throughout the entire Sky Spill Continent.

This was the first time that Lin Ming had discovered something that was not found within the Realm of the Gods.

“Any plane cannot be underestimated, even if they have a short history. After all, in these tens of thousands of years, who knows how many geniuses have emerged!

“But of course, this bead is not necessarily something that cannot be found in the Realm of the Gods. It was very possible that the mighty elder array master hadn’t learned it yet.”

The Realm of the Gods was incomparably vast, and its legacies and inheritances were countless; not learning some things was inevitable.

Because of this bead, Lin Ming began to carefully fuse with the array formation memories from that elder array master. This integration took the entire evening and even lasted until late into the next morning. It was only then that Lin Ming finally sorted out all the detailed information.

“So that’s how it is. In this bead, fire and thunder are kept apart from each other. If they were primed with a bit of true essence, the fire and thunder would intersect, and it would explode. If someone doesn’t understand how to use this, it is very likely they would just blow themselves up!

“The energy contained in this tiny bead is extremely potent. If it were to explode next to an early Pulse Condensation Period martial artist, they would die!

“No wonder Ouyang Dihua gave me a strange look when I picked up this bead. He was looking forward to me killing myself in the explosion.”

With the fusion of the memories, Lin Ming had become completely clear on the roles and functions of the different symbols in the bead’s array formation. He even had a degree of certainty that he could produce a replica Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead. Of course, the one he produced would have a much weaker effect; at most it could deal with a Viscera Training stage martial artist.

‘The complexity of an array formation is much higher than that of inscription symbols. If I want to reach some achievements in array formation and produce a bead that has attack power higher than my own, then I will have to put in an extensive amount of time and energy. Right now I’m low on time, so I’ll have to leave this array formation for later.’

Although he was envious of the power of the different possible beads, these things still could not directly increase his strength. Since he needed to spend an overwhelming amount of time to study the intricacies, Lin Ming had delayed this for now.

After a long period of research, Lin Ming even found some ways to improve the Thunderbolt Devilfire bead, and could even enhance the power of the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead by several tenths. Of course, to complete this sort of improvement required that he had a foundation array formation technique that was high enough. At present, Lin Ming was unable to complete this task.

He used an entire night to study the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead. Although he didn’t have any substantial gains, the bead had given Lin Ming a great inspiration, and let him see another way to enhance his combat effectiveness.

Of course, the most fundamental way to enhance one’s own combat prowess was to look at oneself!

The first thing Lin Ming had to do now was to consolidate his Altering Muscle cultivation.

Also, he had to create an inscription symbol for the Heavy Profound Soft Spear.

Early on, Lin Ming had already selected a suitable inscription symbol. This inscription symbol technique had one character – ‘Astral’.

The ‘Astral’ inscription symbol did not have any attribute, but it was able to increase the efficiency of true essence by a mind boggling 50%, while simultaneously have a special skill of inscription – ‘Astral Spear’.

The reason this skill of inscription was special was because it did not increase the combat strength of a weapon. Instead, it extended a weapon’s range of attack.

After one activated ‘Astral Spear’, true essence would enter and become part of the spear. Theoretically, as long as a martial artist’s true essence was powerful enough, the spear could be infinitely extended!

The value of the rare materials required for this inscription symbol was steep. Although it was much easier than looking for those needed in the body inscription symbols, it was not so easy to collect them in a short time.

Lin Ming prepared a list of required materials and sent them to the Inscription Association. He would use his usual method, and trade rare materials for an inscription symbol. Those who wanted one of his inscription symbols would have to bring a rare and precious material that he needed.

…………………………….

Sky Fortune City, Allied Trade Association –

Zhang Guanyu had been lying comatose on the bed for an entire day and night. His face was pale white like funeral paper, and his right hand had been amputated from the wrist down. Unless he managed to find a miracle treasure that could regenerate a limb, he was destined to be forever crippled.

At Zhang Guanyu’s side were six maids carefully taking care of him. Suddenly, Zhang Guanyu’s eyelids moved.

“The Young Master has awakened!”

The maids saw Zhang Guanyu wake up, and immediately went to inform the masters. Soon, a very well maintained lady was heard trotting into the room. As she saw Zhang Guanyu’s miserable appearance, she broke down, and her tears were like a line of beads that rolled down her cheeks.

This lady was Zhang Guanyu’s mother and also Zhang Fengxian’s wife. As the first lady of the Allied Trade Association, she was an extremely cruel and vicious individual. As the saying went; like mother, like son. Zhang Guanyu’s perverse and demented personality was largely inherited from his mother.

“My son!” The lady tearfully wailed.

It seemed as if Zhang Guanyu had not even heard his mother’s mournful cries. He looked at his right arm’s amputated hand and his lips sorrowfully trembled. His hand was gone!

“My hand!”

Zhang Guanyu’s anger filled every fiber of his being, and he spat out a mouthful of fresh blood. As an extremely arrogant person, if he suffered such a major blow, it was easy for him to fly into a rage from the psychological damage. It was possible he might even go mad or berserk.

“No! There is still hope! I can cultivate the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ to the eighth layer or find some medicine that can regenerate limbs! There is still hope!” Zhang Guanyu madly clenched his teeth together and began to revolve the ‘Divine Acacia Power’. The legends said that if one cultivated the ‘Divine Acacia Power’ to the fabled eighth layer, it was even possible for dismembered limbs to be reborn!

But as he began to exercise his power, he only felt as if there were countless needles stabbing through his body!

As soon as he looked within himself, he found his meridians…his meridians had all been torn to shreds!

“No!!!”

Zhang Guanyu let out a roar, his vision went dark, and he immediately fainted.

As Zhang Guanyu fell into a coma again, his mother and the several maids were all thrown into immediate confusion. Ouyang Dihua was standing outside, and his look was gloomy throughout all of this. He understood; Zhang Guanyu was now crippled for life.

Now that Zhang Guanyu was crippled trash, half the plans that he came to the Sky Fortune Kingdom for were ruined!

It was now impossible to collect the 12 Pure Yin girls.

It was the Allied Trade Association that handled to purchasing and selling of maids throughout the various countries. They were the only ones who could cobble together 12 Pure Yin girls with the correct horoscope.

Ouyang Dihua clenched his fist. All of this was thanks to Lin Ming!

Not only did Lin Ming wreck his own good plans, but he had also ruined what face he had in front of everyone, ignored his commands, and had severely wounded Zhang Guanyu.

And what was most shameful was that he had not been able to strike Lin Ming, and his oppressive aura had no effect on him…

There was no way he could endure this insult.

“Lin Ming… I will definitely kill you!”

Chapter 156 – Devouring Lava Fire

The news of Lin Ming crippling Zhang Guanyu quickly spread throughout Sky Fortune City.

Prior to this, Zhang Guanyu was a martial artist whose talent was only inferior to Qin Xingxuan throughout the entire Sky Fortune Kingdom; he was simply a favored child of the heavens. Now, in just a single night, he had been completely wasted! This was an astonishing matter!

Moreover, when Lin Ming had crippled Zhang Guanyu, it was in the presence of Ouyang Dihua. Ouyang Dihua, whose cultivation was already at the Pulse Condensation Period had personally moved, but he still had not been able to stop Lin Ming.

Afterwards, when Lin Ming faced Ouyang Dihua, he was not even forced back a tiny step by his oppressive aura. If it were not for the timely arrival of the Seven Profound Martial House Master, there would have been no end to that night.

This chain of events caused Lin Ming’s public image to suddenly become decisive and ruthless.

In just two and a half months of time, he had defeated Zhang Guanyu. There was no longer any doubt that Lin Ming would surpass Ling Sen and Ta Ku in the future. He was only 15 years old; his future achievements could only be imagined.

If such a fierce person was also so decisively ruthless…

Thinking this, everyone could not help but grow a thought in their mind. They absolutely could not provoke Lin Ming.

……………………..

Seven Profound Martial House, Skyrage Mountain —

This volcano was located 700 miles west of Zhou Mountain.

This was Sky Fortune Kingdom’s most active group of volcanoes. If one walked around the craters, the thick pervasive sulfuric gas would choke their nose. These heated rocks underfoot could be used to fry eggs, and in the rivers of flowing lava, one could see dark red magma bubbles with molten iron chunks floating within.

Even if the ground didn’t appear to have any problems, one could not hastily step on it. Because the ground could be a shell of cooled magma, if a foot stepped on it, it was possible to crush that layer of cooled magma, and lava would spew out and immediately devour whoever stood there.

This was the fire array of the Seven Profound Martial House’s seven major killing arrays – Lava Cave.

As soon as Lin Ming arrived via the Seven Profound Martial House’s transmission array, he immediately felt a sweltering heat wave crash into him. The rocks underneath were red like garnet crystals; a normal person would simply not be able to put a single foot down.

“Good Lava Cave!” Lin Ming highly praised. The Lava Cave and Icy Pond Waterfall were just like their names; one was extremely hot, the other was extremely cold.

Both had a similar function, but were slightly different.

The Icy Pond Waterfall focused on tempering the body. A martial artist would resist the cold, and the true essence would thoroughly penetrate through to every inch of skin, flesh, and blood.

But the Lava Cave tempered true essence. For any number of reasons, when a martial artist cultivated martial arts, their true essence would always contain some impurities, and would not be pure. The function of the Lava cave was to force a martial artist to use their true essence to resist the scorching heat, and the burning heat would smelt away the impurities within the true essence.

What Lin Ming cultivated was the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’; the true essence within him was already thick and extremely pure, so there was simply no need for him to enter the Lava Cave.

However, Lin Ming had eaten the Crimson Gold Dragon Marrow Pill and the Golden Snake Scarlet Pill. These two pills had directly increased his cultivation and even further increased the rate of his cultivation for a period. But they had still left behind some impurities and pill toxins in Lin Ming’s true essence.

Through these recent days of cultivation, Lin Ming had constantly been refining out these impurities from his body, but there were always some left behind and they were not completely removed.

Now that Lin Ming needed to take the 500 year old Blood Lingzhi, he had to ensure that the true essence within his body was as pure as possible. Otherwise the impurities would accumulate, and it would become ever more difficult to eliminate them.

“Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, you came!” The deacon senior apprentice brother responsible for the Lava Cave said with a laugh. Guarding the Lava Cave was a chore. Although they did not fear the blistering heat waves, that didn’t mean that they liked to stay in a steamer all day long.

“Eleventh level of difficulty, two hours. Thank you, Senior Apprentice Brother.”

Since this was the first time Lin Ming had come to the Lava Cave, he planned to choose a difficulty in accordance with his own abilities. As for the twelfth level of difficulty, that was a setting that not even Ling Sen could persist in, so he had no interest in trying it yet.

“Mm. Okay!” The deacon did not believe that Lin Ming would have any difficulties in the eleventh level of difficulty.

In the seven major killing arrays, the array formation was usually placed there to increase the natural forces within. For instance, the array formation in the Icy Pond Waterfall would cause the force of the waterfall to be stronger and the icy pond to be colder. The Violent Wind Tunnel would have more violent wind and all sorts of various vortices and turbulent tornados.

But the Lava Cave was the exception to this. The main role of the array formation was actually to weaken the natural force, so that the temperature of the lava would fall.

The temperature of ordinary lava was at least ten times hotter than boiling water, and Skyrage Mountain’s lava was even hotter than that.

Because Skyrage Mountain also produced darksteel, the lava had mixed with darksteel ore. The temperature of it was higher; it was about 20 times hotter than boiling water.

Not to mention a mere Body Transformation martial artist, but even if a Houtian realm martial artist were to jump in, their bones would be fried to a crisp!

Lin Ming had chosen the eleventh level of difficulty; the temperature of the lava was a full 8 times hotter than boiling water. Still, this temperature could already melt many different metals.

As he arrived inside the Lava Cave at the eleventh level of difficulty, Lin Ming stripped himself of all his clothes. If he stepped into the lava pond with his clothes on, they would all be immediately burnt to cinders. Naturally, he had to be naked for this.

Barefoot, he walked on the blistering hot rocks towards the lava pond. The red-hot lava was just like boiling molten iron, and it reflected on Lin Ming’s face, giving him a tomato-like appearance. Occasionally a huge bubble emerged from the lava, burst open, and sprayed hot and toxic gases as it issued a dull sound.

To jump into this pool of lava required great courage and a firm heart. A martial artist whose mind was not tenacious would not even dare to cultivate within the Lava Cave.

Lin Ming revolved his true essence to the limit, took a deep breath, and jumped into the lava pond.

Splash!

Lin Ming’s feet had just fallen into the lava. However, his body was sinking at a very slow rate. The lava had an unusually viscous texture. If a martial artist were quick enough, they might even be able to run atop the lava.

“So hot!”

Lin Ming felt as if his legs had stepped into a blazing brazier. Although he was protected by his true essence, the burning ache was like a blazing knife was cutting through him, almost  unbearable.

The resistance of the lava began to decline. Taking a deep breath, Lin Ming’s entire body immediately plunged into the fiery lava pond.

In the world of lava, scalding hot glowing red light was everywhere; visibility was zero. Lin Ming couldn’t even see his hands.

He revolved his true essence to condense into a sort of true essence clothing that covered his body. Even with this though, Lin Ming could still feel pain like sizzling needles as the flow of heat traveled through his true essence clothing.

In the Icy Pond Waterfall, once a martial artist physically contacted the icy cold water, they could direct the frosty energy to enter their body and temper their organs, blood, and skin.

But in the Lava Cave, no matter how fierce a martial artist, they were not dumb enough to let their body directly touch the hot lava. Inside the lava, there was also a toxic heat. If one breathed in a few mouthfuls of this smoke, it was possible that they would immediately die.

Therefore one had to form true essence clothing and isolate themself from the lava. Then, meticulously, they would slowly introduce the fire of the lava into their bodies, and burn away the impurities contained within their true essence.

This was an exceptionally perilous method of cultivation. If one didn’t have a sufficient level of cultivation and jumped in, they could easily burn their meridians and cause irreparable damage.

Even if one had a high enough level of cultivation, it was easy to leave hidden injuries after long-term use of tempering true essence with fire.

Because of these reasons, of the seven major killing arrays, the Lava Cave was the loneliest. One didn’t even need to make an appointment; they just had to come and momentarily wait to have a position.

Chi chi chi chi chi!

Lin Ming could even hear the sound of true essence burning against the hot flaming lava. But Lin Ming was in a hurry to introduce the lava’s fire into his body. He shut his eyes in meditation, and adjusted his mental state for half an incense stick of time. He let his mind completely relax, and entered into a deep ethereal state before he began to gingerly introduce the fire of lava into his body.

As soon as a small flame entered Lin Ming’s body, it was like a fierce crimson fire flood dragon that tried to rush left and right. However, Lin Ming’s true essence was incomparably thick, and no matter where it rushed, it was unable to create any damage.

Lin Ming quickly subdued the wisp of lava fire, and it obediently circulated through the meridians in his body, burning away the impurities.

Lava fire not only burned away impurities, but it also burned away pure true essence. However, true essence was able to quickly regenerate; the accumulated impurities could not.

Lin Ming introduced wisp after wisp of lava fire into his body. Gradually, there were dozens of fire wisps inside of Lin Ming’s body.

A small flame did not count for much. However, there were so many flame wisps that were rushing about, that even though Lin Ming’s true essence was so thick and pure, he still felt that it was difficult to control.

His face was very red, and the blue veins of his forehead were bulging from the intense pressure he was feeling. He continuously exuded large beads of sweat, but as soon as these beads met the sizzling heat, they immediately evaporated before they could even fall.

Because of the atrophy of the true essence clothing, Lin Ming’s hair had been singed by the heat; it broke upon a light touch.

Lin Ming withdrew a true essence stone from his spatial ring and placed it in his hands. He began to absorb the true essence from the true essence stone as he grinded his teeth together and forcefully revolved the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’.

Under such a difficult state, the impurities in Lin Ming’s body began to melt away at a very slow rate…

Again and again, the impurities continued to decrease, and true essence stones were completely used up one after another.

In half an hour he had used a pure true essence stone. This kind of excessive method of burning away money was something that not even the juniors of large aristocratic families could do.

A pure true essence stone costed 1000 gold taels; it could be considered half a treasure.

The lava fire in his body began to grow more and more wild. The countless tiny units in Lin Ming’s body began to breathe at the same frequency, suppressing the restless wisps of fire. But even so, Lin Ming was finding it more and more difficult to persist.

At this point, Lin Ming was considering temporarily leaving the lava pond. Otherwise, if he stayed down any longer, it was possible that he would damage his meridians, or even be burned to death!

But if he left the lava pond halfway, the amount of impurities that would be burned away would truly be reduced by a great deal.

Lin Ming struggled with his hesitation, when at this moment, a wisp of fire lava burst into the aorta near Lin Ming’s heart.

“This is bad!”

Lin Ming was shocked. The heart was the center of the blood. If it was damaged, he would suffer a life threatening injury.

He began to move true essence to stop the flame but it was already too late. The violent lava fire broke through the ventricle and rushed around, as if it were trying to create a hole in Lin Ming’s heart.

But at this moment, the sleeping Heretical God Seed in Lin Ming’s heart suddenly burst out. A surge of highly compressed fierce and brutal true essence instantly surrounded that wisp of lava fire. With a light puff sound, that wisp of lava fire had been directly devoured by the Heretical God Seed!

“Mm?”

Lin Ming’s mind blanked for a moment. The Heretical God Seed could actually devour the fire of lava?

Lin Ming probed with his soul force, and was utterly shocked to find that the lava fire had already fully integrated into the Heretical God Seed, and had become a part of the Heretical God Seed!

Chapter 159 – Thunder Soul

Not only that, but Lin Ming also knew that within the body’s countless tiny units, there was an extremely complex and mystical electric current that ran through. These electric currents were very weak, but they were a vital intermediary for the countless small units to contact each other and the body.

If one did not have these tiny and weak electric currents, then the many activities of the human body would simply cease to function.

Therefore, there were some mighty elders who studied unusual methods of cultivation that would fly into thunder clouds and direct the thunder and lightning to temper their body. They would cross the calamity of thunder, and use it to enhance their own strength.

However, while thunder was a force that gave birth to life, it was also a destructive force that destroyed life. It was able to turn flesh and blood to ashes and burn down vast forests.

The way to control this power all rested in a martial artist’s own hands.

The Seven Profound Valleys’ Thunder Valley simultaneously had the tiger leopard thunderclap and also lightning to temper the body. An ordinary disciple simply could not practice in such a maniacal and deranged way, that was why only the disciples that were in the top 20 ranks of the Ranking Stone would dare to enter.

But not even the top 10 ranking disciples would dare to cultivate in Thunder Valley like Lin Ming did. He walked into that that mass of chaotically twisting electric snakes and let the power of lightning penetrate into his body.

Lin Ming began to feel the extremely uncomfortable feeling of having his entire body go numb. But soon, this numbness evolved into a thrilling and exciting feeling that caused Lin Ming to wish that a more violent thunder would descend upon him.

Like this, the Heretical God Seed in Lin Ming’s body devoured the lightning like a sponge absorbing water.

The mung bean-sized Heretical God Seed began to slowly grow, and a faint violet light began to reflect upon its surface.

Lin Ming stayed in the magnetic darksteel chamber for most of an hour. Slowly, he began to feel the surrounding power of thunder weaken, and also the roaring tiger leopard thunderclaps weaken; they were no longer as deafening as they were at the start.

“Mm? Was the power of thunder in this magnetic darksteel chamber absorbed cleanly by me?”

Lin Ming opened his eyes and discovered that there were only 2 or 3 of the spasmodically dancing electric purple snakes along the walls, and not only that, but they had a rather dim and fading appearance. If Lin Ming stayed here for another quarter hour, then those 2 to 3 electricity snakes would probably be finished.

Thunder Valley was different from the Lava Cave. The Lava Cave’s lava pool was directly connected to a deep semi-active volcano below the mountain, so the lava fire was able to flow with a nearly inexhaustible supply. No matter how much was consumed, it would immediately be replaced by more.

But Thunder Valley’s magnetic darksteel room was sealed by a massive amount of magnetic darksteel, so that it was able to steer the thunder from a thunderstorm into the array and store the power of thunder and lightning.

The amount of lightning that was stored was limited, so how could it withstand such a sweeping absorption by Lin Ming?

“I guess I’m done here. I should move to the twelfth level of difficulty.” Thinking this, Lin Ming left the magnetic darksteel chamber.

Although Lin Ming had sucked dry most of the thunder power within the magnetic darksteel room, as long as there was another thunderstorm, then the power of thunder within the magnetic darksteel room would be replenished. Because of this, Lin Ming had no plans to be conservative with how much of the thunder power he absorbed, or to mention it.

“Junior Apprentice Brother came out so quickly; it’s only been less than an hour. Would you like to take a rest?” The Thunder Valley deacon saw Lin Ming exit from the magnetic chamber and greeted him with a smile. Lin Ming would become a core disciple sooner or later, so naturally he wanted to curry some favor with him.

“Junior Apprentice Brother, I have some Clarion Mind Pills here. If you take them it may clear up some of the numbness within your body.” The deacon pulled out a small jar from a pocket as he said this and attentively handed it to Lin Ming. He believed that Lin Ming was unable to withstand the intense stimulation from the tempering of thunder and lightning upon his body, and had left the chamber. In fact, even if it were the top ten ranked disciples, or even someone in the class of Zhang Guanyu, they would not be able to persist for too long within the magnetic darksteel chamber. Even they would need to absorb true essence stones and also take a Clarion Mind Pill in order to barely hold on inside.

The eleventh level of difficulty in Thunder Valley far outstripped the difficulty of the other six major killing arrays!

Lin Ming smiled and waved. He said, “I thank Senior Apprentice Brother for his kindness, but I do not need the Clarion Mind Pills. I want to change the difficulty level.”

“Uh… this… well, does Junior Apprentice Brother Lin not know that Thunder Valley only has two difficulties? They are the eleventh and twelfth levels. Because the nature of the power of thunder and lightning is simply too rebellious, the original array master who set this array formation did not have any way to force this power into obeying, so there are only two levels of difficulty.” The deacon managed to awkwardly say; he thought that Lin Ming wanted to switch to a lower level of difficulty. “Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, with your cultivation, as long as you take a Clarion Mind Pill and true essence stones, it is absolutely no problem for you to be able to withstand the eleventh level of difficulty.”

Lin Ming laughed and said, “Mm, I know. I was going to ask to change to the twelfth level of difficulty.

“What?” The deacon was stunned. “You… you want to enter the twelfth level of difficulty?”

Lin Ming nodded.

The deacon remained silent; he simply couldn’t find the language to say anything. He knew that Lin Ming was very formidable, and had even defeated Zhang Guanyu, but the power of Thunder Valley’s twelfth level of difficulty was simply incomparably abnormal. Even a veteran Pulse Condensation Period martial artist wouldn’t be able to hold on inside!

In fact, ever since the deacon had begun managing Thunder Valley, he had only opened the twelfth level of difficulty a handful of times. Ling Sen had tried one time, but not even half an incense stick of time had passed before he scurried back out, his entire body scorched black.

Besides him, there were also several core disciples who had tried. Although their natural talent was superior to Ling Sen’s, their combat prowess was much lower, so their result was even worse and the electric strength had burnt off all their hair.

The power of thunder within the twelfth level of difficulty combined with the tiger leopard thunderclap was not a joke!

Lin Ming was fierce, but could he be fiercer than Ling Sen?

“Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, the twelfth level of difficulty in the magnetic darksteel chamber is something that not even a senior Pulse Condensation Period martial artist can persist in. Not only that, but the array formation does not reduce the power of thunder inside. If Junior Apprentice Lin is injured then…” The Thunder Valley deacon laid it out mildly. He was quite scared that Lin Ming would be electrocuted within and experience a tragedy.

Of the seven major killings arrays of metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, and lightning, all of them besides the lightning killing array had a certain capacity to independently judge a situation. If a martial artist were on the verge of death, the killing array would promptly stop. This was why there were only a few disciples that had died so far.

But Thunder Valley was different. The snaking electricity flew in all directions; it simply wasn’t something that could be stopped or fettered by the array formation. If one blacked out from the overwhelming electrical energy, then they would die.

If the genius of the Seven Profound Martial House that was only seen once a century was to tragically die in Thunder Valley, then that would simply be too hilarious.

Lin Ming sheepishly grinned, “Well, I just want to give it a try. If I have any problems inside, then I will immediately come out. How about that?”

“Well… alright.” The Thunder Valley deacon could only agree to let Lin Ming try and give up afterwards. Ling Sen had been able to last half an incense stick of time. Since Lin Ming was inferior to Ling Sen, then he would probably be able to persist for a few dozen breaths without any problems.

After all, Junior Apprentice Brother Lin wasn’t some silly little child. If he had problems, then he would definitely come out.

Thinking this, the Thunder Valley deacon opened the last magnetic darksteel chamber gate.

Lin Ming entered the twelfth level difficulty magnetic darksteel chamber. This magnetic chamber was a full 300 by 300 feet square. This was also the first time that he had ever stepped into the twelfth level difficulty of a major killing array.

The twelfth level difficulty truly was extraordinary. After Lin Ming stepped into the magnetic chamber, even though he was using true essence to protect his ears, the rumbling sound of thunder was enough to shock his ears with a deeply stinging pain. Long, thick, electric snakes several dozens of feet long waves back and forth like living lightning. Chi chi chi chi. The detonating sounds of the electricity in the room made one’s scalp tingle.

Seeing such a thick electric snake, even Lin Ming felt a little jumpy. It was no wonder a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist could not last in here. If such a thick electrical snake flowed through the human body, its powerful effects could be imagined.

Lin Ming let out a light breath and began to revolve the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’. Then, he walked into that mass of electricity.

Boom!

As the electric current entered Lin Ming’s body, he began to violently shake, nearly fainting. However, at the same time, the Heretical God Seed his heart began to become active again.

As the Heretical God seed bathed in the power of thunder, it began to emit a faint whimper of excitement. Countless flows of electrical current began to converge at his heart and flow into the Heretical God Seed, as if it was a parched man gulping down water.

“What a strong power of thunder!”

Lin Ming thought with amazement.

Along with the influx of electricity into his heart, the Heretical God Seed began to riotously vibrate. Lin Ming locked onto it with his soul force to prevent any accidents, but it seemed that his concern was unnecessary.

In the Heretical God Seed, the three compressed forces of true essence, flame, and thunder were able to peacefully coexist with each other. Lin Ming was simply amazed by the mystery of the ‘Heretical God Force’.

At this moment, outside of the door leading to the magnetic darksteel chamber, the deacon’s voice sounded out. “Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, are you alright?”

Lin Ming found this funny. He replied with a laugh, “I’m fine!”

In any case, the Heretical God Seed was able to spontaneously absorb the power of thunder; he wasn’t worried about being distracted by responding.

After another while, the senior apprentice brother deacon came up again and asked, “Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, are you still alright?”

“I’m okay!” Lin Ming responded again.

After another quarter hour crossed, the deacon’s voice sounded behind the door again. “Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, if you cannot withstand it, you should come out first. Don’t force yourself!”

Lin Ming was speechless. This deacon senior apprentice brother was long-winded enough.

…….

Time passed minute by minute, second by second. Soon, two hours had quietly gone.

In the twelfth level difficulty magnetic darksteel chamber, that mass of windingly thick electric snakes had already been evaporated, and what was left over were only a few, weak electric  currents that were still sparking as they passed along the walls.

In Lin Ming’s heart, the Heretical God Seed had grown to the size of a soybean, and the surface was covered with a layer of crystal clear violet light. It had combined together with that garnet from the compressed flame essence, and was incomparably beautiful as it glimmered with a translucent sheen.

Around the Heretical God Seed, a faint electric spark appeared. In the midst of the dim electric spark, there seemed to be a thin purple snake made from lightning flittering about as it traveled around the Heretical God Seed. From time to time, it would circle around the Flame Essence, playing with it, as if it had some deep spiritual intelligence.

Thunder Soul!

The power of thunder and lightning inside of the magnetic chamber had finally condensed into a Thunder Soul!

Lin Ming was extremely joyful. A Thunder Soul was much more precious than Flame Essence; there were only a few martial artists who had a thunder attribute.

Moreover, inside of the Heretical God Seed, the Thunder Soul had unlimited possibilities for growth.

The magnetic darksteel chamber contained the power of lightning and thunder. However, this power was only the most ordinary and natural of thunder forces which came from a thundercloud. It was only able to create a Thunder Soul, it could not help one grow.

Looking at the small snake-like spark in the electric light, Lin Ming had a deep sense of achievement that soaked through him.

Flame Essence!

Thunder Soul!

The Heretical God Seed was truly marvelous. If the Flame Essence and Thunder Soul continued evolving, what other changes would occur inside of the Heretical God Seed?

At this moment, outside of the magnetic darksteel chamber, the Thunder Valley Deacon was anxiously watching the hourglass with a very scared and bewildered expression.

“Did I make a mistake? Two hours?”

The Thunder Valley deacon was unable to believe such an unthinkable fact; even a peak Pulse Condensation Period martial artist would not be able to last inside for so long!

Chapter 160 – The Power Of Thunder And Fire

The Thunder Valley deacon was unable to believe such an unthinkable fact; even a peak Pulse Condensation Period martial artist would not be able to last inside for so long!

Lin Ming truly was a frighteningly fierce individual, however, there had to be a limit!

‘You had just entered the Altering Muscle stage and yet you can already favorably compare to a peak Pulse Condensation Period martial artist, or even reach a Houtian realm martial artist; isn’t this just a bit too ridiculous!?’

The deacon had been waiting for Lin Ming to realize that the difficulty was too hard and then to leave the magnetic chamber. But now the moon had already come out, and yet there still wasn’t any disturbance in the magnetic chamber.

The deacon even went knocking on the door at regular intervals to ask if Lin Ming was alright; he really suspected that Lin Ming had been shocked silly inside and was in urgent need of care.

Then after a while when the sand in the hourglass had cleanly leaked through to the bottom, he had to flip the hourglass over again. “What the hell, this is just too preposterous. Did the force of thunder inside the magnetic chamber leak out?”

The deacon kept imagining different scenarios of what could have occurred, but at this moment, the door to the magnetic chamber was pushed open, and Lin Ming hopped out, a cheerful smile plastered on his face. After he had successfully cultivated the Thunder Soul, he was in a very excellent mood.

Seeing Lin Ming come out, the Thunder Valley deacon stared at him with round eyes, looking Lin Ming up and down.

Even his clothes had all been burnt off…

The Thunder Valley deacon gulped. What had this daring fellow done inside? He had actually stayed in the twelfth level of difficulty for so long, yet he didn’t seem perturbed or even the least bit concerned. Was this Lin Ming struck by thunder as a child, gaining some mystic ability, and thus did not fear lightning anymore?

“Junior… Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, are you alright?”

“I’m great. Sorry for troubling you, Senior Apprentice Brother. I will go back first.”

“Uh… yeah… you go back first…” The deacon no longer knew what to say.

After seeing Lin Ming out, the Thunder Valley deacon immediately dashed into the magnetic chamber. He took a deep breath, revolved his true essence to its limit just in case he was hurt by the heavy hail of lightning, and then pulled open the door to the magnetic chamber…

In a moment, his eyes had gone perfectly round.

In the magnetic chamber, he only saw a few wisps of tiny electric currents running around, as if they were just barely able to maintain their existence. The other usual lightning snakes had already disappeared into thin air.

The deacon rubbed his eyes, making sure he hadn’t gone blind or daft. This wasn’t right; where was the thunder inside of the magnetic chamber?

….

As he left the entrance to Thunder Valley, seeing no one around, Lin Ming was impatient and wanted to immediately try out the power of the Thunder Soul.

Although the inherent nature of lightning was filled with a terrifying energy, it was only a fleeting moment, and couldn’t last long. However, the Thunder Soul was actually an immortal spirit; it would never be extinguished. As long as he had enough true essence or Heaven Earth Yuan Qi, then he could release an unlimited amount of lightning that would never weaken.

The Thunder Soul was similar to the Flame Essence; it would only have a extremely low chance to be birthed in an area where thunder and lightning had existed for time immemorial.

A Thunder Soul was scarcer than a Flame Essence. That was because in this world, finding lands of thunder was much rarer than finding lands of flame.

With a shake of his long spear, tiny wisps of violet lightning appeared on the silver-white spear shaft; it was really quite beautiful.

“If I trigger the flame true essence and the thunder true essence at the same time, while revolving the ‘Heretical God Force’ so the power of true essence increases by 50%, what would happen?

As Lin Ming thought this, he began to stimulate the Thunder Soul and the Flame Essence within the Heretical God Seed at the same time.

Immediately, the highly compressed Heretical God Seed erupted like an active volcano.

Flame on one hand, thunder on the other. The flame and thunder intersected; each were as fierce as the other, and as violent as the other!

The two kinds of energies began to circle and intertwine around each other. Coupling with the increased power from the ‘Heretical God Force’, the rising energy caused a turbulent vibration in the air, as if the atmosphere itself was being torn apart by these powerful energies.

In that moment, Lin Ming felt as if he could not control these two energies. If it continued, then something dangerous would occur.

As he was about to forcefully withdraw the true essence, a memory suddenly flashed in Lin Ming’s mind. He suddenly recalled the principle of thunder and flame behind the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead.

This idea gave him pause. “If… I let the two different energies in my hands follow the same concept as the Devilfire Thunderbolt Bead… would it have the same might as the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead?”

To rashly test such a hypothesis was dangerous. Not only that, but he was barely in control of these two energies, and was already stretched to the limit of what he could handle. Still, Lin Ming could not suppress this intensely tempting thought in his heart.

“Flame becomes an eddy, thunder becomes a snake…” Lin Ming recalled how the thunder and flame inside of the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead would revolve. As he did this, he also desperately urged all his true essence out, and revolved the wild flame and thunder according to this method.

The Heavy Profound Soft Spear began to shine with light from an electric bolt that twisted around it. Snakes of fire wound around the shaft, and the crackling sounds of lightning and churning flames filled the air with a sound that was absolutely frightening.

Lin Ming’s face flushed red, and blue veins began to jut out from his forehead. Just as the potent power was about to break free of its shackles, Lin Ming let out a roar and fiercely thrust out the spear. The power of thunder and the power of flame interweaved into a ball of light that shot outwards with incredible speed, almost straight upwards at a 100 foot high cliff.

Bang!

There were only the deafening sounds of loud explosions and countless rocks scattering in all directions, and dust filled the air. There was a rumbling sound that lingered, and then the 100 foot high cliff collapsed in an avalanche of stone!

Seeing this power, Lin Ming was stunned silly.

What terrifying strength!

This explosion could instantly kill an early Pulse Condensation Period martial artist, or even a middle Pulse Condensation Period martial artist!

His cultivation was only at the early Altering Muscle stage, yet relying on the power of the Heretical God Seed, he could actually produce such a horrifying killing move!

This ‘Heretical God Force’ secret technique simply went against the will of the heavens!

Lin Ming had thought that the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ which he cultivated was already heaven defying. After all, contained inside were the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, ‘Flow like Silk’, the Tempering Marrow realm, Eight Inner Hidden Gates, Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, and all sorts of other strange and miraculous cultivation methods.

He had only cultivated it a bit, and yet he was able to cross a whole stage and a half to fight with enemies at the peak Bone Forging stage. But now, when he compared that to the ‘Heretical God Force’, Lin Ming felt that the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ was just some commonplace cultivation technique!

“It seems so. After all, while the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ is a top-tier Body Transformation cultivation method manual within the Realm of the Gods, this cultivation method manual cannot be considered a forbidden technique that cannot be passed down. There must be many people who are familiar with the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’! For instance, in the sect of the mighty elder who had learnt the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, as long as you were a core disciple at the sect, you would be able to learn study this cultivation method.”

“But this ‘Heretical God Force’ is actually unique within the entire Realm of the Gods. That second mighty elder who died had only discovered this secret technique within an ancient ruin in the Realm of the Gods. It has a very high possibility that it was left behind by an ancient evil god. It is not a cultivation method or martial skill or movement ability. It can only be called a mystical secret technique. Such an amazing ability is naturally not something that the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ can compare with.

“With this martial skill that I created by accident and with luck, although I can guarantee it can kill an early Pulse Condensation Period opponent, the consumption of energy is simply too large. The true essence within me has lowered by 40 or 50 percent. It’s impossible to use this ability in succession.

As Lin Ming was lost in his thoughts, the Thunder Valley deacon frantically ran out of the entrance.

He had been standing in a daze inside that last magnetic chamber looking at the few small electric snakes that were remaining. Then he had heard a tremendously loud explosion that had scared him awake; he had thought that the array formation had exploded.

As he was running out of the entranceway, he happened to see Lin Ming in front of all the falling debris, looking a bit confused.

This… this was originally a 100 foot high cliff…

The deacon had already protected Thunder Valley for many years; he was now well acquainted with the terrain around Thunder Valley. He could only look at Lin Ming incredulously. Could it be… that this 100 foot high cliff was collapsed by Lin Ming?

He glimpsed the Heavy Profound Soft Spear that Lin Ming was casually holding in his hands. There was a faint flash of true essence on the spear point.

Did he just make a move with his spear a moment ago that caused a 100 foot cliff to collapse?

Heavens!

The Thunder Valley deacon already thought that his timid heart had experienced enough excitement for today. This was just too terrifying. If he experienced a third shock, then he just might have a heart attack.

‘The rocks of the cliff had magnetic darksteel mixed in it! Who knows how many times harder it was than ordinary rock? How could this be possible!?’

“Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, what is all this? What happened here?”

Lin Ming slowly shrugged and said, “I’m sorry, I was not careful and the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead that I was examining exploded…”

Lin Ming had used the power of thunder and flame to release this move. Moreover, the concept behind this skill was the same as the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead. Perhaps even the man who created the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead would have difficulty discerning the difference between the effects of the bead and Lin Ming’s new ability.

“Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead?” The Thunder Valley deacon was surprised for a moment, and then he remembered what had happened recently. After Zhang Guanyu had been crippled by Lin Ming, news of the event had spread throughout the entire Sky Fortunate City.

At that time, when Zhang Guanyu was dueling Lin Ming, he found that his own strength was inferior, and he was already in a situation where he was defeated. Because of this, he tried to ambush Lin Ming with the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead, so Lin Ming had wasted him in response.

“So that’s what happened…” The Thunder Valley deacon exhaled; so this explosion was caused by the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead. If Lin Ming had thrown it then it would have collapsed the cliff. However, this Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead was simply too perverse. If a 100 foot high cliff could explode and end up looking like this, what would happen if it was thrown at a person? Would that person explode too?

Thinking this, the Thunder Valley deacon recalled the magnetic chamber and the thunder inside that had disappeared. His curiosity was piqued again, but Lin Ming had already made the first step and said, “Senior Apprentice Brother, it’s getting late, I should head back first. Thunder Valley should shut down about now. If there’s a chance, we will meet again.

Lin Ming didn’t wait for the Thunder Valley deacon to respond; he had already started moving after he finished his sentence. Since he had comprehended the concept of wind, Lin Ming’s speed was extremely swift.

“Oh, Junior Apprentice Brother Lin, hang on, about the matter of the thunder inside the magnetic… chamber……

The Thunder Valley deacon’s words trailed off halfway. Lin Ming had already disappeared beyond sight. This left him speechless. He had wanted to understand just what had happened inside that magnetic chamber in Thunder Valley…

Fortunately, there was always thunder and lightning in Thunder Valley throughout the entire year. It just so happened that there had also been a thunderstorm that evening, and Lin Ming had managed to absorb almost half of the thunder energy from there.

Since the Thunder Valley deacon could not find a reasonable explanation, he dropped the matter.

But by the second day, the news of the explosion that occurred outside of Thunder Valley had already been passed on to Ouyang Dihua.

“Your luck is quite good! The explosion from the Thunderbolt Devilfire bead actually didn’t kill you! However, you have now used up the Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead; what else can you do to resist? Now when I kill you, it will be as easy as slaughtering a dog or chicken!”

Ouyang Dihua had already contacted the disciple of the Refiner Faction who had been expelled from the Seven Profound Valleys for violating sect rules. To Ouyang Dihua’s delight, that disciple had already taken a half-step into the Houtian realm, and had now surpassed even himself in strength.

It would be a breeze for a martial artist a half-step into the Houtian realm to deal with Lin Ming who was only at the early Altering Muscle stage.

“Lin Ming, your death has already been decided!”

Chapter 162 – Trap

Lin Ming asked Wang Yuhan, “Did Senior Apprentice Sister Bai leave any message when she stopped by to deliver the materials? For instance, did she ask me to create an inscription symbol for her or something like that?”

Wang Yuhan said, “Jingyun didn’t say anything. She just left the materials here then departed.”

“Oh… hm, do you have Bai Jingyun’s sound transmission information? I would like to use a sound transmitting talisman to ask her.”

Wang Yuhan said, “Yes, but Jingyun recently left Sky Fortune City. She’s already put in a request for a 5 month leave of absence from the Seven Profound Martial House. I don’t think that she’ll be back any time soon.”

A sound transmitting talisman had a limit to the distance that it could reach. If it was a very long distance, there had to be a preplanned relay system set up ahead of time, and multiple sound transmitting talismans had to be used in series.

“Leave of absence?” Lin Ming thought this was quite peculiar. The time one had to practice at the Seven Profound Martial House was very valuable; what sort of reason would there be for Bai Jingyun to request a five month leave of absence?

Lin Ming was not accustomed to owing a debt to others. As for the Crown Prince’s help, it was fine since he was helping him in the struggle for the throne. But why would Bai Jingyun collect these materials, and then leave for a long journey without leaving a note? It really was confusing.

“Then, if Senior Apprentice Sister comes back, I’ll trouble you to inform me.”

“Alright.”

“So… Miss Wang, if I could ask you to help me prepare an inscription room. I would like to draw up the customers’ inscription symbols first.”

“Mm. Okay!”

………………………….

Two days later, in the middle of the night –

Outside of Sky Fortune City in a shaded area of the woods, Lin Ming was wearing all black clothes as he rode on the back of a large gray eagle. This was a top-quality mount that a common person would usually never see in their lives, a Heavenly Wind Eagle.

The Heavenly Wind Eagle had a wingspan of 40 feet, and it could fly a huge distance of 8 thousand miles every day. It was a third-level vicious beast, and it was only tamable by those martial artists in sects that were proficient in beast mastery. This kind of eagle mount had a value of at least 200,000 taels of gold, and it wasn’t something that money could easily buy.

Tonight, he would ride this Heavenly Wind Eagle and go towards the Huoluo Nation’s Seraphic Pond Mountain.

Lin Ming had already finished drawing the ‘Astral’ inscription symbol, and the drawing process had proceeded very smoothly, without any problems. After completion, the range of true essence within the Heavy Profound Soft Spear had increased by 50%.

The skill of inscription ‘Astral Spear’ had also been successfully attached. As soon as he willed it, true essence would condense into a part of the spear, and theoretically, as long as a martial artist’s true essence was powerful enough, the spear could extend to an infinite distance!

With Lin Ming’s current strength, in a situation where he was in a battle, he was able to extend the Heavy Profound Soft Spear by a little more than 100 or so feet.

At this moment, by Lin Ming’s side, there was also a martial artist that looked to be around 30 years old. He was wearing very flashy clothing, and carried a heavy sword on his back. There was a long scar from a knife wound that curved down his face in the shape of a snake.

This person’s cultivation was at the peak Pulse Condensation Period. He might even have taken a half-step into the Houtian realm. He was also riding a Heavenly Wind Eagle.

This was the martial artist that Qin Ziya had sent to protect him three days ago.

After Lin Ming had arrived at Travel Peak at the agreed time, he had already been waiting there for him.

When Lin Ming saw this person, he was stunned. Qin Ziya’s disciple was actually a martial artist that was a half-step into the Houtian realm. And not only that, but this person had very pure true essence, and an extremely powerful aura. His strength was probably higher than a martial artist at the same level of cultivation. With this person here, the Allied Trade Association would definitely not dare to do anything.

“Hello, Senior Apprentice Brother.” Lin Ming greeted.

“Mm.” The man replied with a lukewarm tone. “Are you prepared? We are leaving tonight.”

“Yes.” Lin Ming had wanted to ask for the senior apprentice brother’s name and gain some understanding into the reason he was going to Huoluo Nation, but felt that this man didn’t want to speak any more, so he reluctantly dropped the topic.

The man let out a strange whistling sound, and suddenly, two Heavenly Wind Eagles heard that whistling and soared down!

The Heavenly Wind Eagles flew down faster and faster, and Li Ming could only hear the howl of wind in his ears as the incoming turbulent air current sent his clothes fluttering about.

Lin Ming used his true essence to condense a wind shield in front of himself to block the intense winds. His eyes stared at the back of the Pulse Condensation Period martial artist in front of him, and he fell back into rumination.

This was an absolutely unwise time to leave the Seven Profound Martial House. If he was able to keep his whereabouts completely hidden, then it would be fairly safe. However, if there was even the slightest leak as to where he was, then the situation might become a bit dangerous.

“Martial House Master Qin has credibility. He shouldn’t be trying to harm me, but I should still be careful. But even if I say that, if Martial House Master Qin wanted me dead, then I wouldn’t be alive today either.”

The first time that Lin Ming had met Qin Ziya, he had felt a faint aura of righteousness from him. In general, those gentlemen that were accomplished in the fine arts were usually never hypocritical or malicious; otherwise it would be profoundly difficulty to have any attainments in the fine arts.

The two Heavenly Wind Eagles flew for one day and one night. After a brief two-hour period of rest, they then departed again for another 8000 miles.

This surrounding landscape became gradually more desolate the further south they went. This was south of Sky Fortune Kingdom, and it was close to the Great Southern Wilderness.

Lin Ming found that the Heavenly Wind Eagles didn’t directly fly to Huoluo Nation. Instead, they took a detour. Even with the amazing speed of the Heavenly Wind Eagles this detour would still take half a day.

“Is this because of safety concerns?” Lin Ming began to doubt in his mind. Relatively speaking, it was very safe to ride a Heavenly Wind Eagle. A Heavenly Wind Eagle flew at an altitude of thousands of feet, and it was difficult for someone who wanted to kill him to intercept him at such a height.

“It would be really easy for a murderer to dump a corpse here…” Lin Ming heart began to have a faint sense of foreboding, and he secretly went on alert. His mind linked to the Heretical God Seed, feeling the terrifying compressed power of thunder and fire within, and felt slightly more at peace.

At this moment, Lin Ming, who had been highly focused the entire time, suddenly felt ice cold. He felt that the Pulse Condensation Period martial artist in from of him was emitting a faint murderous intent. And this murderous intent was directed at him!

This caused all of Lin Ming’s four limbs to immediately become cold!

This was a martial artist who was a half-step into the Houtian realm. He was someone that not even Thunderfire Annihilation would be able to match up against!

………………….

At this time in a valley at Zhou Mountain, it was night, and the shaded trees lent an eerily dark feeling to the valley.

“Is it done?” The voice abruptly sounded. The one who spoke was Ouyang Dihua.

“It was only a trivial matter. Huo Gong should begin any time now.” The feminine voice of Bi Luo said as he slowly emerged from the woods.

Huo Gong was Ouyang Dihua’s junior apprentice brother. He was a disciple of the Refining Faction but had been expelled from the Seven Profound Valleys. He was the martial artist riding the Heavenly Wind Eagle alongside Lin Ming that was a half-step into the Houtian realm.

Ouyang Dihua cruelly smiled and said, “Senior Apprentice Brother’s illusions are truly superb. I’m afraid that not even Qin Ziya would be able to see through them.”

Bi Luo was from the Mirage Faction of the Seven Profound Valleys, and what he was best at were illusions, particularly disguises. Not only he could transfigure appearances, but he could also mimic voices and personalities. It was to a level that not even a peak Houtian realm master would be able to see through them.

Three days ago, Bi Luo had transformed into Qin Ziya, and had ordered Lin Ming to leave the Seven Profound Martial House.

“He used to not to be able see through my illusions, but these years Qin Ziya had been roaming the world and his zither heart has already reached the point where it is like a mirror; the stage where his heart is spotless and resolute. His cultivation is also a half-step into the Xiantian realm. It shouldn’t be difficult for him to see through my illusions. Fortunately, that eyesore Qin Ziya left the Seven Profound Martial House after the grand banquet had ended. He will continue to roam around and polish his zither heart, so there won’t be any problems since he won’t be coming back any time soon.”

“Mm. As long as Qin Ziya isn’t here and we can make Lin Ming leave the Seven Profound Martial House, killing him would be as easy as killing a chicken. Huo Gong wasn’t needed to begin with. As Long as Lin Ming falls down from the Heavenly Wind Eagle, he will meet a violent, crushing death! Let alone a mere little boy at the Altering Muscle stage, even a Houtian master would be finished!” Ouyang Dihua diabolically grinned as he said this.

If he tried to move against Lin Ming in the Seven Profound Martial House, then it would alarm many people. Even if he could successfully kill him, after he died there would most likely be several traces of evidence that one could use to trace back to the murderer.

However, if Lin Ming was to leave the Seven Profound Martial House and even leave Sky Fortune City, and then if he was to disappear, most others would chalk it up to him dying while on an adventure somewhere. This way, even if the Seven Profound Martial House wanted to investigate the situation, they would have no idea where to even begin.

“The great Southern Wilderness is a land of endless vicious beasts and poisonous insects. Once he plunges to his death, there won’t even be dust left over from his bones once the vicious beasts are done tearing through him. That is truly the best place to kill a man and destroy his corpse without leaving any evidence!”

Ouyang Dihua greedily licked his lips, and impatiently waited in anticipation of the good news that Huo Gong would send to him.

……………..

Southern Wilderness –

As he rode on the Heavenly Wind Eagle, Lin Ming heard the snake-scarred martial artist let out a sharp whistle. Suddenly, when the Heavenly Wind Eagle under Lin Ming heard this whistle, it rolled over midflight, trying to make Lin Ming fall off its back!

“Beast!”

Lin Ming held onto the eagle’s feathers. Taking advantage of his strength, he took a firm grip with one hand on the eagle’s body, and with a flick of his wrist, the 1200 jin Heavy Profound Soft Spear had already jumped into his hands.

Although the Heavenly Wind Eagle was very strong in flight, how could it maintain flight with a 1200 jin weight on its back?

As Lin Ming tightly gripped onto the eagle’s back muscles and pulled out his spear, the Heavenly Wind Eagle immediately let out a whining call of pain and desperately flapped its wings. Even so, the Heavenly Wind Eagle immediately plunged downwards in a straight vertical drop before catching itself!

“Hehe, sorry young boy. I have had no past injustice with you and no present grudge. I’m only doing this because someone offered me some benefits, and they wanted you to completely disappear. I’m sorry, but don’t blame me.”

Huo Gong stood on the back of the Heavenly Wind Eagle and grinned heartlessly. The snake-like scar wound on his face looked especially ferocious as he laughed.

“Who asked you to kill me? Qin Ziya?” As Lin Ming asked this he immediately rejected it. No, something was strange, but he didn’t know just what was strange.

“Haha, you think that it’s Qin Ziya? Think as you like, I have no interest in meaninglessly chitchatting with you. I will let you be a confused ghost as well!”

You think that it’s Qin Ziya…

These words resounded in Lin Ming’s heart, and made him go cold…

At this point, he didn’t have any time to reflect on this. There was another strange whistling sound that was sent from Huo Gong, and the man sat down on the Heavenly Wind Eagle as he turned around and flew at Lin Ming to kill him!

“Have a peaceful journey to hell!” Huo Gong took out a strangely shaped long saber from his back, and sent that long saber careening towards Lin Ming’s back to behead him!

Clang!

Lin Ming lifted his spear to resist Huo Gong’s strike with everything he had.

However, the strength of a martial artist at the peak Pulse Condensation Period was simply too formidable. As they exchanged a blow, Lin Ming only felt a strong force transmit through his body as he was sent flying backwards.

With a cough, Lin Ming tore off a hunk of flesh from the Heavenly Wind Eagle’s back as he was sent soaring backwards by the strength of the blow.

The Heavenly Wind Eagle issued a pitifully keening cry. From an altitude of thousands of feet in the air, Lin Ming plummeted downwards!

Chapter 162 – Trap

Chapter 169 – Fatebound Heartcrush Bug

Lin Ming lightly smiled and said as he cut the tall grass, “Do you think that if I hadn’t given them the sabers that I would be able to run away?”

Na Yi paused. Indeed, Lin Ming was only a young boy at the Altering Muscle stage. Even if the bald man and monkey-faced man were unarmed, Lin Ming would still not be a match for those two deviants.

However, since Lin Ming was aware enough of the situation to remark in such a way, that proved that at least he wasn’t too stupid. Na Yi was silent for a moment, and then said, “Then what are you planning on doing? Drug them? Do you think that will have any meaning?”

Lin Ming responded, “I’m not sure if it will, but I still have to try. In the end, aren’t you the same as me? I thought that the bald man and the monkey-faced man knew the way to this so called ‘ancient site’, but it seems that you are the one guiding them. If you help them, do you actually believe that they will let you and your sister go after taking the treasures?”

Na Yi’s lips twitched. Of course she had thought of these things that Lin Ming had said. She coldly replied, “You do not have to worry about that!”

“Of course I’m worried. I’m afraid that you will have a sudden change of heart and bring us to some trap in the middle of nowhere, where we will all perish together. If that happens, then I’ll really have died unjustly.”

Na Yi coldly said, “When my parents died, I swore two absolute oaths. The first was that I would thoroughly protect my little sister and keep her safe no matter what happens. So you don’t need to worry, I won’t let my sister die.”

Na Yi finished speaking here, and no longer uttered another word. These two oaths she had made were the secret of her heart. She would never have spoken about them to a stranger, but now, at the edge of death, how could she ever carry out these two oaths?

Lin Ming’s heart was stirred. He looked back at Na Yi with a bit of surprise, and saw that innocent looking girl quietly turning her head to gaze into the distance. Her body hadn’t fully developed, and even when riding a horse, her line of sight was just above the tip of the grass.

Just by looking at her youthful appearance, it was hard to imagine that she already carried such heavy burdens on her tender shoulders. Since she had made two oaths, then was the other to avenge her parents?

Lin Ming was quiet as he silently chopped the grass. At this moment, he suddenly felt a chill in his heart. He felt that a few dozen feet away was a giant snake. Its darkly patterned, scaled body was the as thick as a water basin, and it was over 50 feet long. In the Southern Wilderness, the venomous serpents were of the most deadly variety.

For such a huge fellow to also be so toxic, it was creepy just thinking about it.

Lin Ming maintained his composure, but secretly stayed on high alert.

After the group walked forward another 100 feet, the bald man suddenly raised the hand which held the saber. Apparently, he too had discovered this large snake.

Although the bald man and the monkey-faced man were scum, they did have a very rich knowledge of the jungle and the land. Otherwise, it would have been impossible to wander the wide Southern Wilderness for so many years.

“A patterned anaconda. Sh*t, what bad luck. Looking at how thick this fellow is, I think his strength should be equal to a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist.” The bald man frowned, and then pulled out a strange looking musical instrument from his knapsack. It looked like a reed pipe, but it also had additional strange holes that weren’t found on a normal reed pipe.

The bald man jumped down from his horse, raised a bit of true essence, and began to play the strange reed pipe.

A hoarse and scratchy sound passed along with the notes, and a faint hint of true essence fluctuated within the melody. As the bald man blew on the reed pipe, he began to march to a bizarre beat, legs swaying from side to side. His entire face had an extremely ugly look as he shivered with the effort of this display.

To Lin Ming, seeing the bald man with his dancing movements was a bit funny. But to his surprise, just a moment later, the big snake seemed to fall under a strange hypnosis as it swayed from side to side before eventually writhing away.

“Interesting…” Lin Ming had seen and experienced many different methods that the people of the Southern Wilderness had used to handle the vicious beasts and poisonous creatures. He had been anticipating that they would have a fierce battle, but in truth, the majority of vicious beasts were repelled by these two fellows using fascinating and unusual methods. Only when they were against a much weaker foe would they attack and kill.

So along the way, there was no surprise nor was there danger.

With these two people leading the way, Lin Ming had truly saved a great deal of effort.

The bald man seemed to have consumed a lot of energy from playing that reed pip; he was very haggard looking. The bald man pulled out some medicinal herbs from his backpack and began to chew and swallow them.

This type of medicinal herb was able to restore true essence, though it didn’t have much of an effect. However, it was cheap. As for true essence stones, those were dozens of times more expensive, so those were something that these two men would never be able to use.

“Let’s go.” The bald man said proudly as he licked his lips. He was quite satisfied with his success.

The group safely passed all the way to the evening. At that time, the group of five finally came to the foot of a cliff. Lin Ming looked up and was surprised to it was over 1000 feet high. If one fell down from there, they would really experience a tragic death.

At this moment, Na Yi, who had been silent up until now, spoke up. “It’s here. We can enter the Sorcerer Holy Land from here.”

“Mm?” The monkey-faced man smiled in happiness. “Where is the entrance? How do we go in?”

However, Na Yi did not respond.

The monkey-faced man frowned and said in an icy voice, “Little girl, don’t you dare think about playing tricks on me. Tell me, where do we go?”

“Release my little sister and I will tell you.” Na Yi said.

“Impossible. I already said that I would only do so once I obtained the power of the Sorcerer and I safely leave the Sorcerer Hold Land. Otherwise, I cannot release your little sister. Don’t think I’m some idiot for you to play games with. Since only the chosen are allowed to enter the Sorcerer Holy Land, who knows what sorts of traps and mazes could be in there. If I release your little sister and you lead us into a deathtrap, who knows how we will die.”

“I’ll say it again. If you release my sister I will swear an oath upon the Sorcerer to lead you to obtain the power of the Sorcerer! Otherwise, you get nothing at all.”

“Hehe, what can’t I get?” The bald man smiled lewdly. “No, even if us brothers cannot take the power of the Sorcerer, we will still be merry. You little bitch, do you really want your sister to be…hahaha!”

As the bald man said this, Na Shui paled, and cowered behind Na Yi.

Lin Ming frowned. He couldn’t move against these men yet; he still needed them to fulfill their purpose.

Na Yi didn’t speak, she merely stood there in a cold standoff. She had no intention of backing down.

At this moment, the monkey-faced man said to the baldy, “Old Second, stop saying so much. Once you have fame and power, what sort of woman can you not have?”

He turned to Na Yi and said, “Since you led us to the Sorcerer Holy Land, then you have already betrayed the Sorcerer, and yet you still wish to swear an oath upon his name. How can I believe you?”

Na Yi was silent for a moment. Finally, she tore up her sleeve and revealed her healthy and smooth arm. On her upper arm, there was a red dot; this was a purity mark.

And beneath the purity mark, there was a pair of golden dots.

Na Yi gently swiped her finger and the two golden dots came off. Lin Ming was able to clearly see that these two small dots were actually a pair of small gold-colored beetles. Before, they had rolled up, so it had looked as though they were a pair of golden beads.

“Fatebound Heartcrush Bug?”

As the monkey faced man saw the pair of golden beetles, his complexion changed and he whispered this name.

The people of the Southern Wilderness specialized in the art of witchcraft. There were many different types of poisonous bugs, and there were also those who were capable of raising them.

“What is the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug?” The bald man asked. He had never heard of such a thing.

The monkey-faced man said, “The Fatebound Heartcrush Bugs are monogamous, and only form a pair. They must be attached to a human body and drink live human blood in order to live. If they drink the blood of a dead man, they will wither and die. In the life of a Fatebound Heartcrush Bug it will only have one companion. Once this companion dies, the other will quickly accompany it in death. After dying, their bodies will rot and unleash an immense amount of poisons.

“…What’s that supposed to mean?” The bald man didn’t understand the implications of this.

The monkey-faced man said, “She is thinking of placing a Fatebound Heartcrush Bug inside the body of her little sister and in one of us. The Fatebound Heartcrush Bug must drink live blood to in order to live. If the little sister dies, then the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug will also die wither her, and afterwards, the other Fatebound Heartcrush Bug in one of us will die, and release a deadly poison that will kill us!”

“It’s that ruthless?” The bald man turned white. He felt a bit apprehensive as he looked at the two small golden bugs.

Na Yi said, “A human may make promises, but in the end they are unpredictable. However, poison is poison, and is unwavering in loyalty! With this Fatebound Heartcrush Bug it will be impossible for me to kill you. If you die, then my little sister also dies. If you agree to the terms, I will place a Fatebound Heartcrush Bug in one of you and continue leading you. If you don’t agree, then I will kill myself here and now!”

The monkey-faced man looked at the golden beetles with a cloudy expression. He hesitated for a moment before finally clenching his teeth and saying, “You can use the bugs. But first, you must place it in your little sister.”

Na Yi nodded, “Na Shui, give me your arm.”

Na Shui bit her lips and stretched out her arm.

Na Yi placed the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug on top of Na Shui’s arm. Then the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug chewed through Na Shui’s skin, and drilled its way in.

“Ah!…” Na Shui quietly cried out in pain.

A small bump appeared on Na Shui’s arm. This bump travelled along her arm and upwards until it entered into Na Shui’s blood vessels, then it followed the bloodstream to the heart.

Na Shui’s lips trembled and her small face was pale. To a little girl, this scene was frightening. The pain and tingling of the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug drilling through her bloodstream to her heart was unbearable.

A moment later, Na Shui tightly clutched her chest, her face blue. Obviously, the taste of having a beetle bore into her heart was not pleasant.

Na Yi comforted her and said, “Ah Shui, it’s all right. After three years the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug will emerge from your heart through your blood flow. It won’t hurt you.”

“Mm.” Na Shui reluctantly nodded.

Lin Ming had been keenly watching from the sidelines. Although he had never heard of the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug before, he was able to understand from their conversation that it was a contract of some sort. However, from the sound of it, this contract wasn’t necessarily binding or strong. Even Lin Ming had means to avoid the contract of the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug and scrap it.

Chapter 171 – [Killing The Double Devils]

Lin Ming shrugged and didn’t respond. He concentrated on pouring his true essence into the black sphere.

The black sphere was like a bottomless pit. Even though it had already swallowed a colossal amount of energy, it still didn’t give any response.

Slowly, the bald man began to pant as if he had trouble breathing, and the monkey-faced man was also flushed and sweating. However, Lin Ming with his extreme restorative ability and resilience appeared the most relaxed, but as he revolved his true essence, on the surface he appeared to be a bit red and a little sluggish.

“A little more, we’re almost there!” The monkey-faced man said. The black sphere began to emit a faint light and the entire chamber began to shake. With a deep rumbling sound, the door to the Sorcerer Pagoda finally swung open. A magnificently iridescent jade pagoda that glowed with a milky light appeared in front of everyone’s awed gazes.

“Hahahaha!”

The monkey-faced man saw the Sorcerer Pagoda and began to wildly laugh.

Lin Ming was stirred. This pagoda appeared somewhat similar to the Seven Treasures Exquisite Pagoda that he had entered during his time at the Seven Profound Martial House’s entrance exam.

“We’ve finally succeeded! Hahaha!” The bald man impatiently rubbed his hands together, “Big Brother, let’s go in together!”

“Mm. Good. Let’s see which one of us two brothers can reach a higher level. But… before that, there is a little matter that we have to attend to.”

The monkey-faced man turned to Lin Ming, smiling, but in that smile was contained a wild killing intent.

“I told you to leave, why didn’t you leave!?” Na Yi anxiously asked Lin Ming through a true essence sound transmission. She was flustered; was this boy an idiot?

Lin Ming responded, “The reason I came here is for the power of the Sorcerer, but also because I want to help you. I just said a moment ago, that even though you have the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug, you two sisters might not escape here alive.”

“Wh… what? Do you really think you are going to…?” Na Yi found it incredible. Did Lin Ming really want to deal with these two people? He was an Altering Muscle stage martial artist while they were at the peak Bone Forging stage! There was a difference in their cultivations of a stage and a half! Not only that, but there were two!

The bald man and the monkey-faced man walked around Lin Ming’s right and left sides, encircling him.

“Little Brother Mo, you’ve worked too hard.”

Lin Ming had dropped down to his knees, and was taking big gulps of breath as if he had been drained of all strength. He used his elbows to wipe away his sweat and said, “You two big brothers are too kind. Since you’ve been dealing with so many vicious beasts, it’s you two that are working the hardest. I was just taking a trip to accompany you two.”

In this posture, he looked like a very unsuspecting idiot victim. However, his soul force had already locked onto the two men’s every action and movement. While leaning down, his finger was already tracing his spatial ring.

Since it was two peak Bone Forging martial artists against one at the Altering Muscle stage, he would first have them lower their guard, and then try kill one in a single stroke. The other he could slowly contend with.

In contrast, if he failed to instantly strike down the first, then the two would be on full alert, and might even separately escape. With so many possible traps in the Sorcerer Holy Land, it would be too troublesome to hunt them down here.

Not only that, but since the monkey-faced man had the Fatebound Heartcrush Bug within him, trying to cope with him would be much more tricky.

The monkey-faced man said with a smile, “Little Brother Mo, you see where we are, there are simply countless traps layered on top of each other. This place is deep underground; it’s quiet and safe. It’s simply like a natural tomb!”

Lin Ming gasped, looking lost, “What do you mean by saying that?”

“What do I mean? Hehehe, my meaning is that since the scenery here is so beautiful, then us brothers will let you safely rest here forever!” As the monkey-faced man said this, his expression suddenly turned wretched. He gripped the short axe on his back, and had already moved to chop off Lin Ming’s head. At the same time, the bald man had also taken out the mace on his back and was sweeping towards Lin Ming’s waist!

These two tandem attacks had instantly sealed off Lin Ming’s ability to dodge in any direction.

Na Shui cried out in alarm!

“Die!”

As the monkey-faced man’s axe cleaved down, in that moment, Lin Ming’s form had suddenly vanished!

Puff!

The bald man’s mace was just halfway down, when he suddenly felt a piercingly cold feeling in his chest. A shimmering silver object was protruding from his chest. He blankly looked down at this object. It was the spearhead of a long spear. Even though there was some blood on it, the blood did not stick to the spearhead. Instead, it flowed down along the ridge of the spear before collecting into crimson drops and dripping onto the floor.

Drip drip drip…

In the deep quiet of the chamber, the sound of blood dripping onto the floor was especially piercing.

The monkey-faced man still had his fierce expression. He wasn’t able to respond to such a sudden change in events. “Second… Second Brother… you…”

“I… I……” The bald man reached out his as if he was trying to reach something, but his eyes were becoming gradually more lax.

Peng!

Then there was the sound of an explosion and the bald man’s body erupted into a spray of bloody fog. In that moment, 5000 true essence filaments had destroyed his organs and completely smashed apart all of his bones and muscles!

The bald man’s corpse poured onto the ground like mud. Behind him was Lin Ming, exposing nothing but a calm and indifferent expression.

The monkey-faced man was completely shocked. Looking at Lin Ming’s face, it was as if he had suddenly become a terrifying stranger!

Even though it seemed impossible to escape both attacks at once, he had appeared like a ghost behind the bald man and had slain him with a single thrust of his spear!

How could this possibly be the cultivation of a boy at the Altering Muscle stage!?

The monkey-faced man began to tremble in fear. Was this youth really a human? Or was he some sort of demonic monster?

In the legends, there were said to be evil beings that could assume the forms of humans. This dark creature could fly at will, and kill at will; they were a terrifying existence!

Not too far away, Na Yi had seen everything. She had seen Lin Ming instantly disappear and then reappear behind the bald man. Yet, she wasn’t able to clearly see Lin Ming’s footsteps!

Just who is he…

Na Yi held her breath; was this really a 15 year old boy?

The monkey-faced man grasped his short axe, his whole body rapidly revolving true essence. He slowly stepped back. His forehead was already dripping with sweat. He didn’t know whether or not Lin Ming was hiding his cultivation or what other secrets he had.

Seeing Lin Ming’s ghostly movements, the monkey-faced man already realized that there was no point in running away; he would only die sooner.

Lin Ming held the Heavy Profound Soft Spear. Though that last strike seemed as if it had easily killed the bald man, the truth was that was because the bald man had lowered his guard, and didn’t utilize much true essence to protect himself. That was why Lin Ming had so easily succeeded.

Now however, the monkey-faced man was on complete guard. In this critical life or death situation, Lin Ming was still able to kill him, but he had to put in some effort.

“Don’t kill him!”

At this moment, Lin Ming’s mind resounded with Na Yi’s true essence sound transmission.

It was as if Lin Ming hadn’t heard. With the concept of wind at this back, this little distance seemed to have lost all meaning.

A spear struck out, lightning flashed.

Clang!

The monkey-faced man had used his short axe to fend off the spear. However, the electric snake that circled the long spear was like a bug that drilled into the monkey-faced man’s body. In that instant, his entire body had been paralyzed.

This was the power of the Thunder Soul!

Heretical God Force – Open!

Lin Ming shouted. With a sweep of his spear, his activated Flow like Silk. The vibrating true essence was like a high tide that gushed out in all directions.

In that moment, the monkey-faced man had been paralyzed, but his survival instinct kicked in. He savagely bit the tip of his tongue and forcefully restored his mobility.

He already knew it was impossible to fend off this blow. He could only bet his life and fight against Lin Ming. His short-axe suddenly viciously struck out at Lin Ming!

Puff!

The long spear swept past the monkey-faced man’s thighs. With Flow like Silk combined with the explosive power of the Heretical God Force, the monkey-faced man’s legs were broken apart as his meat turned to mush and his bones shattered!

However at this time, that chopping axe was approaching Lin Ming’s head!

“Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist!”

Lin Ming punched out! He had actually planned to use his flesh and blood body to fight against a treasure axe with true essence poured into it!

Peng!

The axe was bounced off by vibrating true essence!

And Lin Ming’s fist was unharmed!!

“This… what…” The monkey faced man’s eyes had gone wide at this unthinkable sight. Was this invulnerability!?

As he thought this, he was already sent flying upwards. His lower body had already lost all feeling. Looking down, he could see his feet still on the ground, and his legs had been completely shattered!

“Ah ah ah!”

The monkey-faced screamed out painfully. His body was like a broken sack as it fell and crashed against the ground, blood gushing everywhere like a fountain!

“No… don’t kill me! If I die, the little girl also dies!”

It was as if Lin Ming didn’t care. He grinned like a demon, and shook his spear. “Do you think that I care?”

“You… you… good! Since I’ll die anyways, then let’s die together!” The monkey-faced man clenched his teeth, preparing to forfeit his meridians and commit suicide. However at this moment, Lin Ming was like a ghost that appeared by his side, his palm already falling down.

Pulse Cutting Palm!

Puff!

Lin Ming’s palm struck against the monkey-faced man’s chest. The true essence that was filled with destructive power rampaged across the monkey-faced man’s meridians, and completely twisted and broke apart all the meridians!

“Ah!” The monkey-faced man let out a miserable cry. To his amazement and dismay, he found that he was unable to summon the true essence within his body. It was as if some mysterious force had dispersed all of his will; it simply didn’t listen to his signals!

“You want to forfeit your meridians? Then why don’t I lend you a hand.” Lin Ming withdrew his palm. Since the Pulse Cutting Palm was a weak martial skill, it didn’t have much value in actual combat. It was used by that mighty elder to torment his enemies; how would such a martial skill give the enemy an opportunity to commit suicide?

This martial skill would cause the enemy to lose all of their skills and they would become a eunuch. Not only that, but they would then be imprisoned and endlessly tortured. One could not beg for life, and one could not even beg for death!

In that split second from when the electric light had sparked, Na Yi had been left scared and shocked senseless. She had thought that Lin Ming was really planning on killing the monkey-faced man, but not it seemed that using some unknown method, he had taken complete control of the situation. She let loose a breath she didn’t know she was holding. She looked at Lin Ming again, her eyes filled with an incomparably complex emotion.

Who was this young boy? His cultivation was only at the Altering Muscle stage; how could he have this sort of terrifying strength?

He had leapt past the barrier of a stage and a half difference in cultivation and played with these Bone Forging martial artists as if they were nothing but toys in his hands. They didn’t have the ability to commit suicide by destroying their own meridians. Even a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist wouldn’t be able to accomplish this!

Na Yi had never heard of any genius or talent within the Southern Wilderness that had this sort of incredible combat ability. This included Na Tribe’s first generation tribal chief!

If he was really 15 years old, then his future accomplishments would simply be limitless. This man, his potential was too alarming!

If… if she had his help, in addition to the undiscovered legacies of the Sorcerer Holy Land, it wouldn’t be impossible to recreate Na Tribe!

Thinking this, Na Yi gasped, but she immediately shook her head and sighed. Why would he possibly help her……

Chapter 171 – Killing the Double Devils

Chapter 177 – Legend Of The Divine Kingdom

“What? Is this for real!?” Lin Ming was shocked. This was the first time that his Flow like Silk had been resisted. The Witch Slave had actually devoured all of the Flow like Silk filaments. This proved that the defensive power of its organs, skeleton, muscles, and skin were on a completely terrifying level!

“It really is a monster!”

Because of that Flow like Silk attack a moment ago, the Witch Slave seemed to be mad with anger. It drew out the large, thick chains that wound around its body and slashed down at Lin Ming!

The long chain was just like a black flood dragon. With a roaring power, it heavily smashed upon the ground.

Bang!

Countless rocks were sent flying into the area. That attack had even created a giant pit in the huge arena; this Witch Slave’s strength was simply difficult to imagine!

Lin Ming had already avoided the attack earlier using the Golden Roc Shattering the Void movement ability. As soon as the Witch Slave missed, it flick its arm and gathered the chain before firing it at Lin Ming once again.

“Power of Thunder!”

Lin Ming’s silver spear shined with a purple arc of lightning. The spearpoint met the chain, and that lightning arc was like a fierce purple snake that threaded up the chain and directly plunged into the Witch Slave.

Cha!

The Witch Slave was struck by the lightning. Countless arcs of electricity crackled on its body, and its purple skin charred a bit.

However, it had only been burnt a little. Once the power of thunder disappeared, the Witch Slave bellowed, brandished the chains, and attacked again.

This time Lin Ming was left completely speechless. He was simply dumbfounded by the Witch Slave’s amazing defensive power. Not only could it defend against true essence manifestation combined with Flow like Silk, but it could also resist lightning attacks.

With such a prodigious defensive power, perhaps even opening the Heretical God Force would be useless.

Did he really have to use his last resort, Thunderfire Annihilation?

As Lin Ming avoided the chain attacks, his mind began racing with thoughts. “This is the fourth trial. If I use Thunderfire Annihilation now, then how will I cross the next three? But if I don’t use Thunderfire Annihilation, then none of my other attack methods will work against this monster; this fellow’s defensive power is simply too abnormal.

“Fortunately, only its defensive capabilities are unbelievable. its attack patterns are very simple and predictable, and its speed is also slow.

“There’s no point in dragging this one. Once I open the Heretical God Force, I’ll be able to know if it even has any effect. However, once I use up the compressed true essence of the Heretical God Force, then it will take a long time to restore. I might as well use Thunderfire Annihilation to kill it now! As for the later trials, if my strength is not enough, then there’s nothing left to say.” Lin Ming clenched his teeth. Flashes of lightning began to flitter on his long spear, and a lotus of flame sparked into life. As the thunder and fire intersected, there was a terrifying explosive sound as if an unstoppable tide was approaching.

Lin Ming shouted, and thrust out his spear towards the Witch Slave!

The roar of flame and thunder swallowed every other sound. An incomparably keen true essence flashed out like a bolt of white light as it tore through space. Thunder and fire interwove into a brilliant sphere of red and purple light that flew forwards like a blazing meteor!

The Witch Slave bellowed and waved its chains to attack the glowing ball of thunder and fire.

Bang!

There was a earth shattering sound just like a clap of thunder. The brilliant light was like 10,000 golden swords that shot out in all directions. Countless rocks were sent scattering into the air!

The arena had turned into a giant pit. The arm that the Witch Slave had raised was now completely broken, and blood spewed from it like an endless crimson fountain.

It cried out with a muffled roar, its enormous body trembling. Its chest was soaked with blood even as more blood sputtered out endlessly from its body.

“It’s still alive?” Lin Ming was shocked. This was definitely the most durable being that he had ever encountered so far.

“Die!”

Lin Ming’s feet tread the ground and his body flew forth like an arrow. Under the effects of Golden Roc Shattering the Void, Lin Ming’s speed had reached the pinnacle!

Puff!

The spear pierced into the wound on the Witch Slave’s chest that had been opened by the Thunderfire Annihilation attack. The spear finally managed to break through the torn flesh, Flow like Silk erupted within the monster and rushed towards the heart of the Witch Slave. With a new injury added to the old, the Witch Slave gave one final roar as it unwillingly went down.

Its corpse rapidly dissolved, turning into a green energy that poured into Lin Ming’s body.

“Mm… this energy is…”

Lin Ming felt that the green energy was extremely oppressive and tyrannical. Before, whether it was the energy of blood vitality from the blood demon or the soul force from the hungry ghost, or even the vicious beast’s energy that was able to transform the strength of a human’s body, it was all very gently and effortlessly absorbed.

But this green energy was extremely savage. It brutally rampaged through his body, and sent waves of agonizing pain rolling through its path. Lin Ming’s forehead began to drip with large beads of sweat.

Dense crackling sounds resounding within his body, as if the bones of his skeleton were striking each other. Hearing this, even Lin Ming was feeling a bit fearful.

At this moment, the space in front of Lin Ming began to distort, and Yan Mo appeared.

Yan Mo looked at Lin Ming and said without any emotion, “Congratulations. In this smelting trial, you are the first martial artist in the last 6,000 years to pass the trial of the Witch Slave.

“You do not need to fear. This energy has simply been saved up for too long; a full six millennia of time. Therefore, it is a bit overbearing. It will only transform your body; it will not bring you harm.”

“Six… six millennia?”  Lin Ming found it difficult to speak through the pain.

“Yes. 6,000 years ago there was a man named Qin Yu that was able to pass the fourth level of the smelting trial. However, he was defeated in the fifth level, the Mortal trial. After he went back, he founded a vast empire in the Southern Wilderness, and was called the Feather Emperor by the people of the South.”

Right… so it had already been 6,000 years since someone managed to pass through the Witch Slave trial. This wasn’t too surprising. It was only because he had accidently comprehended the Thunderfire Annihilation skill that he would have such an abnormal striking power. A normal martial artist would never be able to get past the freakish defensive capabilities of the Witch Slave.

Slowly, Lin Ming found that the green energy had fused into his skeleton. His skeleton had become denser, and his muscles had become tougher.

The physical defense had experienced a crazy increase in power.

Before now, Lin Ming’s body strength was formidable. However, that did not mean that his defensive power was similarly formidable.

For instance, an iron armored cow could easily break steel plate, and if a sharp axe were to fall on their body, it wouldn’t leave any damage.

If Lin Ming wanted to fend off a sword with just his bare hand, he could only rely upon his Flow like Silk technique to vibrate the weapon and send it flying away. If his fist really did meet the blade of a sword, then his hand would simply be split in two.

But now, Lin Ming had absorbed the green energy which had augmented his body, and he felt his body grow more solid, and his defensive capabilities increased. Now if he faced a martial artist on the level of Zhang Cang, Lin Ming believed that he wouldn’t even need to use true essence; he could simply use his own bare hand to stop the other’s attacks.

As Lin Ming unceasingly integrated with the green energy, the aching pain he felt gradually weakened. Lin Ming’s entire body was covered in sweat, and mixed within the sweat were black, oily drops. These were clearly the impurities that were in Lin Ming’s body.

In the past, Lin Ming had taken the Golden Deer Pills to temper his body. However, that was only the lowest level of medicine used to temper one’s body; it naturally wasn’t able to be compared to something so fantastic like this green energy.

After his muscles and marrows were purified, Lin Ming collapsed to the ground.

Yan Mo said, “After passing the fourth trial, from here on out, you will have three hours of rest between each trial. You may use that period of time to restore your body to its best condition.

“I wish you good luck, smelting trial human.”

As Yan Mo said this, its body began to twist in space as it gradually faded away.

Lin Ming exhaled one long breath and plopped down on the ground. Luckily, he had time to rest.

Three hours should be enough.

……………….

At this time, outside of the Sorcerer Pagoda, Na Yi was standing within the library of the Sorcerer Holy Land. She held an ancient volume within her hands. Not too far away, slowly burning candles flickered as they emitted a faint yellow light.

The Sorcerer Holy Land was a massive underground mausoleum. It also had a special library. Na Yi had taken her lit candle and searched the library for a long time, and finally found a record of the legendary Divine Kingdom on a yellowed sheepskin manuscript.

Because the manuscript was simply too ancient, the pages were already worn down, and the threads binding them were rotted. The pages could easily be broken apart.

Na Yi carefully skimmed through the notes in that ancient manuscript, and finally found a detailed record of the Divine Kingdom.

This record was from 1,500 years ago, and was written by a peerless powerhouse of the Southern Wilderness named Na Yanda. 1,500 years ago, not even the Na Tribe had been founded.

The page in Na Yi’s hands was only a handwritten copy. Still, even if it were a handwritten copy, it was 7 or 8 hundred years old.

Na Yanda was a sorcerer. He left behind countless illustrious achievements in the history of the Southern Wilderness, along with countless legends and tales.

He had founded the giant Nagu tribe, and to this day, that tribe was one of the top ten most powerful tribes within the Southern Wilderness.

At the time, the Southern Wilderness was under the leadership of Na Yanda. They had invaded the north and caused numerous nations to submit. The Southern Wilderness had experienced one of its most prosperous times in millennia. It was said that Na Yanda had reached the limit of the Xiantian realm, or might have even gone higher!

For those reasons, Na Yanda was considered one of the ancient heroes of the Southern Wilderness, and was worshipped and respected by many people. Even Na Yi had heard of Na Yanda’s glorious tales as a child. Towards the stories of this legendary figure, she had been filled with yearning.

Na Yanda had recorded the complete process of his entry into the Sorcerer Pagoda. He wrote that he had rushed upwards, but had been chosen by the Sorcerer, and then sent to the Divine Kingdom.

The Divine Kingdom had seven levels. The first level was a blood red hell, the second was a land of gloomy yellow ghosts, the third was a world savage vicious beasts, and the fourth was an arena of the Witch Slave. As for the last several, Na Yanda hadn’t seen them.

Na Yanda saw the God of the Witch Eye within that bloody hell. The God of the Witch Eye had given him seven tests, and each level of the Divine Kingdom corresponded to a test.

However, Na Yanda had only been able to complete three trials, and was defeated at the fourth. Therefore, Na Yanda had only reached the fourth level.

In the writings, it also said that the difficulty of these seven tests was much higher than the Sorcerer Pagoda. In particular, from the fourth, the difficulty would increase each time. Even the child of a god or a demon would be unable to do anything in the face of such a trial.

Even the Feather Emperor from 6,000 years ago had only barely completed the fourth trial. As he went to the fifth, he was also defeated.

Seeing this, Na Yi was surprised.

The Feather Emperor of the Southern Wilderness had once dominated the entire land 6,000 years ago, and had founded a vast empire.

The Feather Emperor’s strength was immeasurably deep, and was said to have surpassed the Xiantian realm.

At that time, the Feather Emperor had created the Faith of the Sorcerer; the faith had been equal to a grade-three sect. It was not inferior compared to the Seven Profound Valleys of the north!

One could only imagine the prosperity that the Southern Wilderness had achieved during this time!

“Even His Majesty the Feather Emperor could not pass through the fifth trial? The Divine Kingdom’s trials are simply too difficult. Is there even any significance in the sixth or seventh trial?”

Chapter 178 – [True Essence Bone Forging!]

Chapter title is a spoiler, highlight it to read it now, or see it at the bottom.

To those living within the Southern Wilderness, the Feather Emperor was the equivalent of a second god; he was only second to the belief in the Sorcerer.

There were many followers of the faith that stubbornly believed the Feather Emperor hadn’t yet died. Instead, he had soared into the heavens to join the Sorcerer.

In Na Yi’s opinion, if even the Feather Emperor could not pass the fifth trial, and the sixth and seventh trials were even more difficult, then they had no value at all.

Who could possibly overcome them?

…………………………

Time passed one minute and one second at a time. Lin Ming pulled out a true essence stone and revolved the True Primal Chaos Formula to slowly recover his true essence. The power of thunder and flame that he had consumed to use Thunderfire Annihilation was also slowly being restored.

Because Lin Ming had an extremely formidable blood vitality, his current ability to recover was far above a normal martial artist. In just half an hour, he had been completely restored to his top condition.

“Start the fifth trial!” Lin Ming shouted to Yan Mo who had since disappeared.

“Good. Then it shall be as you wish. This fifth trial, the Mortal World, has not been passed for 10,000 years!”

“10,000 years…”

Lin Ming didn’t think this was too unusual. Since nobody had passed the last trial in 6,000 years, then it would be normal if no one passed this trial in the last 10,000 years.

The surrounding space began to darken. Lin Ming arrived at a vast empty space that did not contain a single thing. Underneath him was the endless earth, and above him, the twinkling bright stars shining in the sky. Around Lin Ming, there were 18 shades. These were human martial artists. They wore black clothes, and carried a variety of weapons; there were swords, sabers, spears, staffs, and so on. It could be said that every weapon was collected in these 18 shades.

As Lin Ming noticed the cultivation of these martial artists, his heart suddenly sank. Among these 18 individuals, 12 were at the peak Bone Forging stage, and 6 were at the Pulse Condensation Period!

How could he confront this?

Lin Ming was speechless. No wonder no one had passed through this trial in the last 10,000 years!

Of the 6 Pulse Condensation Period martial artists, 5 were at the early Pulse Condensation Period, and there was even one at the middle Pulse Condensation Period. Of the 12 peak Bone Forging stage martial artists, every single one of them was a half-step into the Pulse Condensation Period. Each one was much more powerful that the monkey-faced man and bald man!

Lin Ming could not help but wonder if there could be found a 15 year old youth in the entire Sky Spill Continent that was so abnormal as to be able to defeat 18 of these martial artists at once.

Were there really people that were able to pass this sort of trial?

Listening to Yan Mo, it seemed that 10,000 years ago there really was someone that had passed through this hurdle… simply incredible!

From the third to the fourth trial, the difficulty had already dramatically risen by a large amount. If it wasn’t for Thunderfire Annihilation, then it would have been impossible for Lin Ming to break past the fourth trial.

He didn’t expect that in the fifth trial, the difficulty would once again dramatically rise. If it was like this, then how could one possible pass the sixth and seventh trials?

“The difficulty of this life and death smelting trial is just too abnormal. Before I entered the life and death smelting trial, I could barely cope with a Pulse Condensation Period martial artist. Now, there are actually 6 of them! And there is even one at the middle Pulse Condensation Period. There are also the 12 Bone Forging stage martial artists to pin me down, they really do think highly of me.” Lin Ming gripped the Heavy Profound Soft Spear horizontally, and let true essence revolve within his entire body. Although he had little hope he could overcome this trial, he would still try to break through with everything he had!

“This life and death smelting array is a true killing array. I must be cautious. If I lose, I must give up. Otherwise, if I lose focus, I might really die here.”

Facing so many masters on all sides, Lin Ming did not dare to do like before and directly rush into the enemy like a tiger in a flock of sheep. If he did that now, it would simply be suicide.

Whoosh!

A martial artist holding a long staff had already attacked Lin Ming. The staff was already sweeping towards Lin Ming’s knees. At the same time, another martial artist armed with a brilliantly snow-white saber stepped forwards. They had already sealed off all of Lin Ming’s possible evasive routes.

“Golden Roc Shattering the Void!” Lin Ming launched into his movement ability and threaded through the two martial artists’ attacks like a fish. Although he was able to block these two attacks, he dared not fight here, otherwise he could be caught up in the battle and become trapped in the encirclement.

His body formed a series of illusory images, his speed reaching an incredible degree. He survived 4 attacks in a row, and then, like a ghost, he appeared behind a martial artist that was using a meteor hammer.

The meteor hammer was a rarely used weapon. It was suitable for long-range attacks, but in close combat, it would be constrained and restrict movement. Therefore, Lin Ming had chosen this martial artist as his first target!

“Flood Dragon Goes to Sea!”

Lin Ming’s spear thrust out. The meteor hammer-wielding martial artist was only at the peak Bone Forging stage, but his response was very quick. The martial artist had flicked his hand, and the meteor hammer tied its chain around the Heavy Profound Soft Spear.

Kacha!

The sturdy chains had already wrapped around the spearpoint of the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, miring it in place.

If Lin Ming’s weapon was even caught for just the time it took for a few blinks, then Lin Ming would face simultaneous attacks from 18 martial artists at once. He could only abandon his weapon, otherwise there was no way he would be able to dodge.

At this point, Lin Ming grinned. A thick arc of lightning jumped out and sped down the metal chain towards the meteor hammer-wielding martial artist.

Zizizi!

The meteor hammer martial artist was electrocuted by the attack, and his entire body was paralyzed. Lin Ming seized this opportunity, and with one shout, his strength of 10,000 jins erupted at once. His right hand gripped the base of the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, swung the chain open, and thrust a fierce attack towards the meteor hammer martial artist, stabbing his throat.

Puff!

One spear had severed the throat!

Having killed the peak Bone Forging martial artist in a single stroke, Lin Ming did not dare to pause and pulled out his spear to retreat backwards.

Whiz!

A halberd with the thickness of a baby’s arm slammed into the spot where Lin Ming had just been. A loud explosion occurred, and the rocky ground where he stood had collapsed. This was the attack from the middle Pulse Condensation Period martial artist.

Lin Ming broke out into an anxious cold sweat. This was a true killing array. If he had even been half an eye blink late a moment ago, then he would have already been left with only half his life. The subsequent instant attacks from the other martial artists wouldn’t have even given him the chance to give up within the smelting trial.

But at this moment, Lin Ming suddenly felt an extremely pure and potent heaven and earth origin energy surge into his body. With this heaven and earth origin energy, Lin Ming’s true essence reached a critical point that allowed him to break through the limit and officially step into the peak Altering Muscle stage!

“Mm? This Mortal world increases true essence and cultivation?

Lin Ming was overjoyed. Before, in the worlds of Hell, Hungry Ghost, Animals, or even the Witch Slave, none of them were able to directly increase his cultivation. They gave such bonuses like augmenting blood vitality and soul force. Although it would be of great advantage to Lin Ming’s future cultivation efforts, it was not able to greatly boost his immediate combat prowess. Rather than increase his cultivation from one stage to the next, it had been a qualitative change in his body.

“I’ve only killed one and yet I reached the peak Altering Muscle stage. If I kill them all, then just how far will my power increase?” Lin Ming’s heart rallied with a sharply rising fighting spirit. “I’ll kill the Bone Forging stage ones first, and then those at the Pulse Condensation Period!”

After reaching the peak Altering Muscle stage, Lin Ming’s strength had drastically risen, and his speed was also higher. Now, with the power of Golden Roc Shattering the Void at his back, his body was just like a passing ghost; not even the attacks of a Bone Forging stage martial artist could injure him.

It could be said that Golden Roc Shattering the Void was the trump card that Lin Ming relied on in this trial. Otherwise, if he fell into an encirclement of martial artists, he would immediately be defeated.

Because of his extreme agility, Lin Ming launched into pseudo-guerilla warfare, and the debilitating power of thunder attached to his Heavy Profound Soft Spear was the murder weapon.

If a martial artist and Lin Ming were similar in strength, then a touch of this electrical force was enough to paralyze them for just a moment. However, in a battle between masters, that moment of paralysis was enough to spell their doom.

Puff!

Lin Ming swept his spear and took off a Bone Forging stage martial artist’s head. The true essence within his body rose by another level.

“The limit of Altering Muscle!”

Lin Ming was jubilant. He had only just broken through to the Altering Muscle stage a little more than a month ago, and now he had already taken strides towards the Bone Forging stage.

But at this moment, Lin Ming suddenly felt as if his entire body had fallen into some quagmire; every movement he took seemed to be affected by some strange invisible traction, slowing him.

He turned and saw that the middle Pulse Condensation Period martial artist that wielded a halberd had stuck that halberd into the ground. Thick true essence condensed within his body and unceasingly fluctuated from him.

“Gravity manipulation?”

Lin Ming had just thought of this, when the sword wielding Pulse Condensation Period martial artist flashed behind him, sword striking. The deep blue sword wind sliced at Lin Ming!

“Damn!”

Lin Ming lifted his spear to block but that sword wind was too relentlessly sharp. Even though some was blocked, some of the sword wind had passed the spear shaft and cut into Lin Ming’s body.

Cha!

Lin Ming’s upper clothing was torn apart, revealing the Purple Gold Flexible Armor underneath. Potent true essence broke through that flexible armor and mercilessly stabbed at Lin Ming’s organs.

Lin Ming gave a stuffy cough and was set flying back. He quickly stabilized himself and probed his body, actually taken aback by what he found.

“Eh? Nothing’s wrong?”

Although there was a slight aching feeling, his internal organs hadn’t suffered any injury. The defensive power of his body was so incredible that even Lin Ming found it hard to believe. “At the fourth trial when I killed the Witch Slave, its energy truly changed my body in an abnormal manner. That was an attack from a Pulse Condensation Period master. Even if it’s just the sword wind, it should be enough to kill a normal Altering Muscle stage martial artist, yet I was able to resist it and also wasn’t injured.

The sword-wielding martial artist was only a puppet that was condensed from heaven and earth origin energy. He did not understand emotions such as surprise. Once he saw that his strike had no effect, he raised his sword to attack again.

Lin Ming would naturally not fight with him. His body flashed as he displayed  Golden Roc Shattering the Void. Lin Ming instantly appeared behind two peak Bone Forging stage martial artists.

Chi! Chi!

Two heads flew! Two martial artists were killed!

After Lin Ming had reached the limit of Altering Muscle, killing peak Bone Forging martial artists was nothing but an easy task.

Two pure energies poured into Lin Ming’s meridians. Lin Ming began to tremble, feeling his entire skeleton go numb as if something had gotten into his bones.

His skeleton had become more dense and resilient.

“True essence enters the bones, Bone Forging stage!”

At this moment, Lin Ming had officially stepped into the Bone Forging stage.

Incomparably powerful true essence poured into all of his limbs and bones and spread throughout his body. Lin Ming felt his strength soaring into the sky. He felt as if something had lit within his body, and endless amounts of blood began to surge within him.

Seeing that sword-wielding Pulse Condensation Period martial artist send a slash of sword wind at him, Lin Ming let out a shout and thrust out his spear.

“Flow like Silk!”

Bang!

5000 vibrating true essence threads erupted outwards, each one several times thicker than in the past. In the face of such compelling true essence, that Pulse Condensation Period’s sword wind was torn apart!

Chapter 178 – True Essence Bone Forging!

Chapter 181 – Gravity Cage

“To defeat him, I can only use Thunderfire Annihilation. But I can only use Thunderfire Annihilation once. Since this light shadow martial artist is a Houtian realm master, will he be able to defend against Thunderfire Annihilation? Once Thunderfire Annihilation is blocked, I will have spent a massive amount of true essence, and I’ll be defeated soon after.”

Lin Ming’s mind began racing through different scenarios; there was no way that he could defeat the enemy with a surprise attack of some sort.

The light shadow martial artist didn’t attack for a while. His brows furrowed; he was obviously not satisfied with his own performance so far. “You can’t keep hiding and you can’t keep defending. Do you really plan on going through a war of attrition to waste my strength? An innovative idea. However, do not forget that you are only at the Bone Forging stage, and I am at the Houtian realm. If you want to compare true essence reserves and drag out this fight, then the first person to falter will surely be you.”

The light shadow martial artist raised his sword once more, and the two exchanged dozens of moves!

Lin Ming clenched his teeth. Although he danced on the edge of disaster; he still wasn’t defeated!

Such tenacity shocked even the light shadow martial artist.

The light shadow martial artist had thought that Lin Ming’s stamina was deficient, and he would be unable to persist and lose soon after. However, he hadn’t expected that Lin Ming would be as stubborn as a weed.

Unwittingly, the blood vitality energy within Lin Ming’s body that hadn’t yet been fully absorbed by him began to gradually melt and spread through his limbs, circulating through all of his blood vessels.

By the virtue of this thick and powerful vitality, Lin Ming’s battle tenacity rose. The true essence that he consumed was constantly replenished by the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ and his blood vitality, barely maintaining a balance point. Even if he was occasionally injured, Lin Ming’s deceptively strong recovery abilities were able to slowly regenerate his wounds in the midst of battle.

After hundreds of moves were exchanged, the light shadow martial artist had no choice but to admit to the most ridiculous and absurd reality of the situation. That was, Lin Ming’s endurance was far greater than his!

A peak Bone Forging martial artist’s true essence was actually so thick and pure to the degree that his resiliency could compare to that of an early Houtian realm master; was this even possible?

Lin Ming was able to rely on his true essence manifestations and ghostly agility to dodge the majority of attacks. Coupled with turtle shell-like defensive power and extreme regenerative capabilities, he was able to compete. Even though his battle prowess was far inferior to his enemy’s, he was still able to persist in this dogfight.

This feeling of not being able to defeat Lin Ming made no sense to the light shadow martial artist.

‘Even if he absorbed the blood vitality energy in the first level of the life and death smelting trial, he still shouldn’t be so relentless. Is there something special about this boy’s body?’ The light shadow martial artist scowled, ‘I have to settle this soon. Otherwise if this drags on, it’s not certain who will be the first to fall. His speed is simply too fast. If I want to attack him, I have to limit his movements first.’

‘I only have one ability that can lower his speed. But if I use this move, then I’ll place major restrictions on myself. But now, there is no other way…’

Thinking this, the light shadow martial artist placed his sword in front of him, turned towards the ground.

“Gravity Cage!”

Cha!

A vast flood of true essence poured into the ground. Lin Ming suddenly felt a strange pull of gravity all around him, restricting his movements. “Mm? It’s this move?”

During the fifth trial, the Mortal World, the halberd-wielding Pulse Condensation Period martial artist had also used this move, forcing Lin Ming to be unable to dodge attacks.

Now, this was the same move that was used. But because it came from the hand of a Houtian realm martial artist, it was far more powerful. Lin Ming felt as if a giant magnet was pulling him to the floor; even walking was a hard-fought struggle.

‘This is bad.’

The reason that Lin Ming was able to last this far – besides his strong defensive power and formidable regenerative capabilities – had been because he was able to fall back upon the Golden Roc Shattering the Void movement skill. Using that, he had managed to avoid the majority of attacks. However, now that his movements were restricted, Lin Ming was in a very dangerous situation.

‘Mm? No, if he wants to use this move then he also has to use a similarly large amount of true essence.’

Lin Ming discovered that the true essence within the light shadow martial artist’s body was significantly weakened; he was spending a large portion of his power to create this gravity cage.

Lin Ming instantly understood that this Gravity Cage martial skill was only suitable for use in group battles and in coordination with others. One person used Gravity Cage while another attacked. If there was only one person using this skill though, if he also wanted to attack, then the power he would be able to call down was also extremely limited.

Seeing that light shadow martial artist begin to gather his own killing move, Lin Ming was delighted. ‘This is my chance. This fellow simply didn’t know that I also have Thunderfire Annihilation as my own final killing blow.’

‘Originally, I had worried that you would be able to defend against Thunderfire Annihilation with your full strength. But now that you can only use a part of it, you’ve simply dug your own grave!’

Lin Ming’s lips curved in a smile, and a lotus flame kindled on the Heavy Profound Soft Spear.

Just by looking at this dark red flame, it didn’t seem as if it was dangerous. The light shadow martial artist presumed that this little flame was unable to pose any threat to him. In fact, the few attacks that Lin Ming had used hadn’t yet managed to break through the true essence protection of his body.

The light shadow martial artist only thought of how long it would be until he defeated Lin Ming; he never once imagined that there was a possibility he would be defeated himself.

“Power of the Sorcerer!”

The light shadow man shouted, and a layer of blood-red light covered his sword. Behind the man, a gray ghost appeared. This ghost resembled the ancient demon spirit that was depicted on the murals within the Sorcerer Holy Land. The ghost had three heads and six arms. The three heads were grim and smirking, and the six arms were like the claws of the devil, each holding a different weapon.

As this gray shade appeared, the momentum of the light shadow martial artist rose to a crescendo.

“Die!”

Lin Ming’s movement technique was restricted; this strike had no chance of being dodged.

Lin Ming was shocked as he saw the gray ghost that had appeared. This weird three-headed, six-armed being was seen in the art of the Sorcerer Holy Land. Was it possible it was also a servant of the Sorcerer?

The light shadow martial artist’s sword cut down. Lin Ming had no time to think anymore, he could only react. He completely released all of the compressed energy that was contained within the Heretical God Seed.

Heretical God Force – Open!

Lin Ming’s true essence instantly soared!

The Flame Essene and Thunder Soul began to whine in excitement. Unbridled fires and violent surges of lightning swelled outwards from Lin Ming’s body.

In that moment, the light shadow man realized that something was wrong. This boy had actually been hiding his true strength?

However, the light shadow man had already passed the point of no return, he had no choice but to send out this move of his. The man clenched his teeth and forcefully withdrew a small portion of the true essence that was maintaining the gravity field. The gray shadow image behind him became more solid and realistic, and the blood-red sword in his hand glowed with an even more beautiful light.

Under the constraints of time, he was unable to fully gather his energy. Even so, he didn’t think that Lin Ming’s little thunder and flame could resist the Power of the Sorcerer.

But at this moment, the flame and thunder on Lin Ming’s spear suddenly interwove in the same spot…

Thunderfire Annihilation!!!

“This is…!” The light shadow martial artist’s pupils suddenly widened. His vision was completely filled with nothing but a blazingly bright white light. The blood colored sword that he had struck towards that incandescent light was instantly shattered!

Bang!!

There was a deafening explosion just like a thunderclap within a raging storm. The light shadow martial artist was struck by the Thunderfire Annihilation. The terrifying flurry of thunder was like a silver snake dancing within an inferno of dazzling red flames.

A vicious shockwave reverberated in the air like the rough waves of the ocean during a storm. An incomparably vast tsunami of true essence billowed outwards in all directions; it shattered the jade floor as it swept through the entire temple!

Lin Ming and the light shadow man were simultaneously sent flying backwards.

As soon as Lin Ming had released Thunderfire Annihilation, he had already been revolving all of his true essence to resist the incoming shockwaves. He vomited blood as the shock pierced through his body and the bones of both of his spear-holding hands were broken.

However, the light shadow man was in an even worse situation. He hadn’t prepared for that move, and his sword had also cut into the ball of thunder and flame. At such close distance – even though he was a Houtian realm master – his chest had blown up and he was covered in blood, simply a mangled mess.

“Damn!”

The light shadow man supported himself with his longsword. He had been too careless. He didn’t think that he would be forced into such a miserable state by a mere Bone Forging martial artist and be humiliated. He spat a mouthful of blood; at least half of the ribs in his chest had been shattered.

“He’s not dead…” Lin Ming’s pupils shrank as he staggered backwards. A Houtian realm master was simply too strong. Even though he had used most of his strength to power the Gravity Cage, he had actually managed to fend off Thunderfire Annihilation.

Lin Ming’s heart sank. Although the light shadow man was heavily injured, Lin Ming had already used up the Heretical God Force and Thunderfire Annihilation. If they continued to fight, then he would be put into an even more dire situation.

However, at this moment, Yan Mo’s voice suddenly resounded above the shattered temple. “The sixth level, cleared!”

Hearing this, the light shadow man seemed very unwilling. He glared at Lin Ming with indignant anger, grabbed his sword, and walked back to the temple.

“I passed?”

Lin Ming found this unbelievable.

At this time, space twisted in front of Lin Ming, and Yan Mo appeared before him. “Congratulations. You are the first one in the last 19,000 years to pass the sixth smelting trial.”

Lin Ming was puzzled. He asked, “I didn’t kill the enemy of the sixth floor, how could that be regarded as passing?”

Yan Mo said,  “As long as you defeat the guardian of the sixth level, then you have passed. If your move truly would have killed him, then I would have blocked the attack. The guardian of the sixth level is different from the first five; he is a true soul, and has a soul brand as well as his own independent consciousness.”

Sure enough, this was also something that Lin Ming had guessed, so it wasn’t too surprising.

Yan Mo said, “There are several guardians of the sixth level. Their cultivations range from the early Houtian realm to the limit of the Xiantian realm. In the past, they were once the Sorcerer Envoys of large tribes within the Southern Wilderness. However, even in the Southern Wilderness there were constant wars, and occasionally, even these Sorcerer Envoys would be killed. These individuals were also once wounded and on the verge of death. They were rescued by me in exchange for guarding the sixth level of the smelting trial with their souls.

“So it’s like this…” Lin Ming suddenly realized. The so called Sorcerer Envoys were truly worthy of their reputation. Out of all the Sorcerer Envoys, the one he had dealt with was the weakest of them all. This was only because he was 15 years old. If he was any older, than he would have had to face a middle Houtian, or even late Houtian realm master.

“You may rest for three hours, and then carry onto the seventh smelting trial!

Yan Mo said this, and then immediately vanished.

Lin Ming could only force a grim smile as he listened to this. How could he pass through the seventh floor?

The sixth floor was already a measure of his luck. With his current strength, he was simply not a match for a Houtian realm master. If it wasn’t for the guardian losing his patience and trying to forcefully limit his movements, thus leaving an opening in his defense, there was simply no way for Lin Ming to have won.

Now, his strength hadn’t increased, and he had to pass the seventh trial. How could he do this?

Starting from the fourth trial, the difficulty of every following one had increased by a ridiculous degree. If it went as expected, then the difficulty of the seventh level would greatly surpass that of the sixth.

How should he proceed from here?

If he couldn’t, then the strange red quartz would turn into a dream, and he wouldn’t even receive the reward for passing the sixth trial.

In any event, he had to put forth his total effort. Even though there was only the slightest glimmer of hope, he still had to stride forwards.

Chapter 182 – The Mysterious Seventh Floor

Lin Ming restored his mood to tranquility, took out two pure true essence stones, and sat down in meditation as he began to recover his strength while slathering bone recovering medicines on his arms.

A moment ago, he had fractured the bones within his arms that were holding the spear, and they had turned into a bloody mess. This kind of injury would normally be impossible for a martial artist to recuperate from even within half a month. However, Lin Ming’s resilience, recovery rate, and blood vitality had all been greatly enhanced. In addition to the effects of two priceless bone recovery pastes, his arms were completely recovered within two hours.

In the last remaining hour, Lin Ming restored his true essence and physical strength to its optimum condition, and adjusted his mood to be tranquil and serene.

Finally, he began the seventh and last trial.

A light flashed, and the temple disappeared around him. Lin Ming entered into a dazzlingly bright white world filled with luminous light, and countless scenes formed and twisted around him.

“The seventh trial… in 19,000 years, no one has ever set foot here.” Lin Ming clenched his fists, and completely calmed down.

Prior to this, Lin Ming had repeatedly imagined what sort of scenario would play out in the seventh level. However, now that he had truly set foot in the seventh level, what he saw here left him utterly stunned.

Of the first six levels, each world and corresponded to its name. For instance, the first level of Hell had been a blood lake. The second level was Hungry Ghost which corresponded to the Yellow Springs. The third level was Animals which corresponded to the vast wilderness. The fourth Witch Slave level had corresponded to an arena…

Lin Ming believed that since the seventh level was the World of the Sorcerer, the scene he expected to see should have been similar to some land within the Realm of the Gods.

But, he didn’t expect to come to a normal human city. Around Lin Ming, there were lively crowds and peddlers hawking their wares. There were little children playing around, and the faint hint of dust and fragrant flowery perfume mixed in the air. Everything seemed to be an absolute reality.

But none of these had surprised Lin Ming. What had shocked him beyond speech was the place where he now stood.

He stood before a fancy, yet somewhat old restaurant.

The clay tiles were no longer bright, and the red lacquered pillars were faded with time. The old windows sagged, and the roof was tilted. Everything exuded a vague flavor of endless years…

Lin Ming was far too familiar with this restaurant. Since as long as he could remember, he had been running within the lobby, listening to storytellers weave their fantastic tails and roaming bards singing their glorious songs. He had watched as people played chess, and had eaten candy with old and frequent customers.

The covered tea-cups, the sugar-coated candied haws, the towel draped over the shoulder of a waiter, the delicious food that his mother had made… all of these were exactly the same as those within his memories.

This… was his home.

“This is the Lin Family restaurant of Green Mulberry City. I’ve lived here for more than a decade of my life. I… how did I end up here?”

Lin Ming couldn’t help but slowly lift his foot to enter into the restaurant. But just as he passed the threshold, in that moment, he froze. Lin Ming stood where he was, his heart like a billowing unsure wave.

He saw a young man dressed in elegant silk clothing, about 18 or 19 and holding a fan, smile and walk out from the kitchen.

But this person wasn’t some stranger. This person was none other than Lin Ming. To be exact, this was Lin Ming a few years later.

However, looking at this man, Lin Ming could see that he had no hint of cultivation within his body. He had a bookish and scholarly appearance; he had apparently never cultivated martial arts in his life.

Not only that, but the two were completely incompatible in demeanor and temperament.

Even when Lin Ming held his breath, there was still a sharp air that was present between his brows. This air seemed as if it was ready to erupt at any moment and pass through the sky, unstoppable.

But this young man in front of him only held a cynical smile, and in that smile was even a touch of evil. He had the elegance of a scholar’s son.

‘This… is this really me?’

Lin Ming could not believe this.

“Little Lizi, prepare a sedan for me. Miss Su of the Teal Flower Hall is holding a performance tonight. Go reserve a card for me; I shall go down in support.” The young man snapped as he quickly swung his fan.

“This… this is not good…” The small servant named Little Lizi looked embarrassed as he said, “Young Master, the second lady of the Tian Family is holding a feast tonight and personally requested that you attend by name.”

“Attend your face. If she’s holding a feast then she’ll want a chef. What use is there in me going?”

“This…” Little Lizi seemed pained. “The second lad of the Tian Family would like to request that Young Master leave behind a painting at the birthday banquet tonight, with a poem. You are currently the new chosen scholar, your poetry is definitely number one within Mulberry City…”

“Moreover, Young Master, this second lady of the Tian Family is very beautiful and virtuous. The last time Madame saw her, she liked her very much. Perhaps in the future…Young Master, hey, Young Master, don’t go!”

Before Little Lizi had finished, the youth had already stepped out the door without even a backwards glance. He said, “If my father asks where I went, tell him I went to drink.”

Before the words had finished, he was already gone. Little Lizi’s face was like a bitter eggplant that was squashed. He was simply finished. If the Master or the Madame found out about this, then he would certainly be scolded.

The second lady of the Tian Family had a good impression of the Young Master. Not only that, but the second lady of the Tian Family was kind, beautiful, had a good background, and was a natural fit to the Young Master, who was the chosen scholar.

But Young Master Lin had actually taken a liking towards Miss Su of Teal Flower Hall, it really was impossible to understand his mood.

The truth was, Teal Flower Hall was actually a brothel, but it was a higher class, more elegant brothel. The majority of the prostitutes inside were well groomed and mannered, and sold their skills not their bodies. They had elegant and refined appearances, and were proficient in poetry and painting. These talented ladies could be considered stunning and rare beauties within the world.

And Miss Su was the main attraction of Teal Flower Hall. Although she still maintained her pure body, she was still a prostitute of a brothel. With her cheap origins, how could the Master and Madame possibly allow her to marry into the family?

“I’m dead I’m dead, if the Master becomes aware that the Young Master has gone to Teal Flower Hall, then not only will the Young Master be finished, but I will also suffer bad luck.” Little Lizi had a face of suffering. He didn’t know whether he should honestly report this matter to the Master and Madame, or if he should try to conceal it.

Lin Ming had been silently standing outside of the restaurant, quietly watching the scene unfold. Just now, the young man had brushed past Lin Ming, but hadn’t even glanced at Lin Ming once.

Lin Ming understood. He did not belong to this world; he was simply a passerby. There wasn’t a single person in this world that could see him.

“What’s going on here? Why is there another me?”

“When I was eight years old my parents let me go to school to study. I went to the capital and in order to study for the preliminary examination, I studied and read books for four years until I was 12 years old. At that time, I threw away all my books and whole-heartedly abandoned everything to pursue the martial path. Because of this, I fought a bitter dispute with my parents, before I finally wore them down. The Lin Ming that I became in this world did not abandon his books for martial arts. Instead, he entered into the preliminary exam and turned from a scholar into a candidate of the imperial court.

“Why is there such a world? Is this a true parallel world? Or is this an imaginary world that stems from my mind?”

“If this is the seventh trial, the Sorcerer World, then what does it test? Does it test my heart of martial arts? If it tests my heart of martial arts, then what is considered as passing this trial?”

“Since this is the Sorcerer World, then why did I come to the human world?”

Lin Ming’s mood was complex; he just stood within the lobby of the restaurant. Like this, he stood for several days.

People came and went, and no one saw him. There were even those that passed through his body…

On the streets there were peddlers hawking their wares, street entertainers singing bright and cheerful songs, the rich aroma of food and wine, and there were also even the weathered faces of his parents…

Everything around him seemed so real and yet unreal.

All of the people around him were familiar, and yet they also seemed like strangers…

In this noisy and hectic world, Lin Ming seemed like a gray existence. His shadow was alone, and he was incomparably desolate.

“This world is an illusion, and I am real?”

“Or maybe…This world is real, and I am an illusion?”

“No, this is wrong. This isn’t my world. This is only a demon within my heart!”

Lin Ming’s eyes suddenly flashed open and flourished the Heavy Profound Soft Spear.

Peng!

Lin Ming could only hear the sounds of countless panes of glass shattering at once. In front of him, the restaurant along with the customers had all completely vanished!

However, Lin Ming did not return to the life and death smelting trial. Instead, he had arrived within a bloody battlefield. Loud war drums sounded in the distance, and glorious flags fluttered in the air!

“This is…”

Lin Ming saw armored cavalry soldiers in front of him. He felt a chill and his heart went cold. He suddenly realized something.

Lin Ming’s soul force was like a tide as it spread out in all directions. In a moment, it had locked onto the form of a youth. Lin Ming furrowed his eyebrows; this was really true!

Lin Ming moved. In a mere moment, he had appeared inside a barracks. Inside, there was a 15 or 16 year old youth wearing a simple suit of armor. He held a plain iron spear in his hands, and his expression was filled with intense fear and fretfulness.

Seeing this youth, Lin Ming gave a complex look before closing his eyes.

It was himself, it was really himself!

Why was this?

At 12 years of age, he had gotten into a dispute with his parents. Finally, he had been allowed to practice martial arts. At this time, Lin Ming said that if he couldn’t achieve the First Stage of Body Transformation before he was 15 years old, then he would join the army, establish himself there and perform countless services, and return home a hero with riches and honor!

In light of this, it seemed that this was when he would have joined the army!

This was another Lin Ming within another world!

……

In the barracks, the youth was sitting on a bench. He took out a thin piece of oilcloth and began to silently wipe down his spear. Compared to his size, the spear was much longer than it should be.

“Hey, newbie, is this your first time on the battlefield?” A veteran over thirty years old with a simple face said, as he walked over carrying a bowl of rice.

The youth sheepishly nodded and said, “Ah, yes, I am a new recruit.”

“Haha, new recruits on the battlefield are always so tense and anxious. It’s alright. Since we’re in the same barracks, we will be sent to the same place. Just follow behind me; I will protect you!”

“Good… great…” The youth had a somewhat juvenile and innocent expression. He nervously squeezed out a grateful smile.

When war broke out, tens of thousands of soldiers rushed forwards, their vast and dominating auras even washing away the clouds.

Smoke rose from all directions, fierce combat resounded in every corner, and a spear broke off a halberd.

The youth returned in the triumphant army. However, that simple-faced veteran hadn’t come back…

When soldiers died together, they were also buried together. Without a grave, that youth didn’t even know the veteran’s name…

With each passing day, that youth’s expression became less and less tender, and increasingly filled with a fierce and firm determination.

Slowly, from a recruit he became a corporal. From a corporal he became a captain. And from a captain he became a battalion leader…

His spear skills became more and more refined, his strength increasingly grew, and his military knowledge and appearance became more and more mature.

Gradually, this youth also became a veteran. He would look at every new recruit, and say to them, “It’s all right. When we charge forward, follow behind me; I will protect you!”

That once naïve and innocent boy had harbored a dream to join the army. With each excursion into foreign lands, he saw more and more people become nothing but bleached bones. After having survived through life and death, he had been hardened; he was just like the veteran.

Like this, the days endlessly continued. Each soldier had a dream of being a general. But, they were more likely to follow the steps of their predecessors, dreaming of those that had passed away…

……

Lin Ming silently watched the world change before his eyes. He finally began to understand. This life was not an illusion, nor was it real.

To the people of this world, he was an illusion. And to him, the world was an illusion.

Life was like a dream. Dream was like life. True or false, real or fake, originally there was never anyone who could tell which was which.

Perhaps the seventh level was not a test. Rather, it was an opportunity, a chance, a feeling, and a profoundly deep understanding into the heart of martial arts.

Realizing this, Lin Ming no longer decided to destroy the world. Instead, he would only follow in its footsteps and look on.

He was merely a passerby. He would observe the changes of time, take a step back, and see the endlessly vast dream that was painted.

………………….

Outside the life and deaths melting trial, in a place of darkness, Yan Mo was calmly looking into the endless void, a giant eye that was without an expression.

“He became aware…”

“Extraordinary. It is only the second world, and yet he has already understood the truth. Now it has been one day and one night. This young man’s grasp of the heart of martial arts is simply startling!”

The seventh trial was exactly one that tested one’s heart of martial arts. Although this was a trial, it was also a great fortuitous opportunity!

If one was able to comprehend the original intent behind the trial, then they could experience the endless worlds and temper their mind. The benefit from this was limitless!

Although there had never been anyone who had entered into the final level of the life and death smelting trial for the last 19,000 years, Yan Mo knew the truth. The truth was that the array formation that the Sorcerer left behind could also be found within the Realm of the Gods!

Its name was – Samsara.

Even those favored by the heavens within the Realm of the Gods would often lose themselves after entering into the Samsara.

Most would assume that the worlds were a product of the demon with their hearts, and they would constantly undermine and destroy these worlds. However, when new worlds would emerge endlessly, and they would see countless reflections of themselves, then they would lose their heart and become dazed. In the end, they would not be able to distinguish between what was reality and illusion, and ultimately wouldn’t even know if they were themselves real.

Once they were lost, their heart of martial arts would be damaged and this might even affect their future cultivation.

Even if a heavenly genius was to realize the meaning of the Samsara, they would often have to go through several – or even dozens of worlds as they slowly grasped the truth.

But Lin Ming had been able to see through what was true and what was false in only the second world, and comprehend the meaning behind the Samsara. How could Yan Mo not be surprised by this?

“Unfortunately, Master has probably already passed away. Otherwise, he would certainly be willing to accept this youth as his apprentice. I had thought that his young man’s natural talent was ordinary, and the only reason he was able to have such achievements was because he had a fortuitous encounter. I didn’t think that his perception in the heart of martial arts would be at such a state. He truly is a talent in this aspect!

“I will take a good look at just what he can realize from these 100 Samsaras.”

Samsara definition and information.

Chapter 186 – Wolf Toxin

Outside of the Sorcerer Pagoda, seven days and seven nights had already passed.

“Awoooo!”

In the dark and silent halls of the Sorcerer Holy Land, a wolf suddenly howled. A Corrupt Wolf the size of a small cow rushed forwards, bits of carrion flesh hanging from its cruel jaws. Its body reeked of death, and its bright white fangs were exposed and dripping saliva. In the darkness, its luminescent green eyes were especially bright.

In front of the Corrupt Wolf, a little girl was quickly running. This little girl was Na Yi.

At this point her innocent face held no fear or panic. Instead, her teeth were clenched as she desperately pushed her true essence to the max and displayed her fastest speed.

However, Na Yi was only at the Viscera Training stage. Not only that, but a human was already inferior in running to a vicious beast; how could she compare to the peak Altering Muscle Corrupt Wolf?

The Corrupt Wolf closed in, almost overtaking her. Na Yi could already hear the sounds of whistling wind from behind her back and even feel the rancid breath of the Corrupt Wolf.

Roar!

The Corrupt Wolf pounced forwards, its sharp wolf claws piercing straight towards Na Yi and scratching her delicate back.

“Ah!”

Na Yi forced the last vestiges of her faltering strength to the forefront and suddenly leapt forwards. However, the wolf’s claws had ripped open her back, her clothes had been broken and she was covered in blood!

Crash!

Na Yi fell onto the ground, her body rolling around. The Corrupt Wolf once again pounced forwards, this time aiming its razor sharp claws towards Na Yi’s throat!

At this juncture of life and death, a cold light flashed in Na Yi’s eyes.

Whiz!

The sound of a sharp piercing sound suddenly rang in the air. A darksteel javelin as thick as thumb flew out from a hole in the wall, and stabbed the Corrupt Wolf, sending blood flying everywhere!

“Aowoo….” The Corrupt Wolf pitifully yelped. The javelin had a tremendous force contained behind it as it shot out, and it had nailed the Corrupt Wolf to the ground. But this was not the end. Just as the Corrupt Wolf fell on the ground, rows of sharp knives immediately stabbed out from underneath, their piercing cold blades stabbing into the Corrupt Wolf’s body.

Puff!

The Corrupt Wolf was like a dead dog that had been stabbed through the heart with a thousand knives. It was deader than dead.

Seeing this, Na Yi let loose a breath of relief and collapsed to the ground. Her back was slick with blood; the wolf had left three bone-deep claw wounds on her back.

Bursts of pain came roaring at her like the tide of an ocean. Na Yi’s forehead began to seep with sweat.

“Big Sister!”

Na Shui rushed over to tend to her injured big sister. Her tears were freely falling, an unstoppable waterfall.

To Na Shui, her big sister was her only hope, but also the sustenance that kept her spirit running and alive. If something was to happen to Na Yi, then she would lose all courage to continue living.

“I’m fine… I… just need a rest.” Na Yi forced out a smile, feeling extremely bitter within.

She had underestimated the speed of the Corrupt Wolf, and finally received such a heavy wound.

There was also another Corrupt Wolf outside. With her current condition, how could she possibly kill it?

There was only enough food left over for a day.  Na Yi still hadn’t gone to the Sorcerer Pagoda. She estimated that with her own strength, she could at most pass the third floor and enter into the fourth. After that, any further progress was simply far too difficult.

She could only enter the Sorcerer Holy Land one time. It was also the most important opportunity in her life. If she could only reach the fourth floor, then how would she ever find the power to avenge her parents in the future?

She had made two oaths to the heavens. One was to protect her little sister, and the other was for revenge. She had never thought to give up either of these goals.

If she could cultivate for one year in the Sorcerer Holy Land and reach the Altering Muscle stage, then when she entered the Sorcerer Pagoda, Na Yi had faith that she could enter at least the fifth floor and break through to the Bone Forging stage inside the Sorcerer Pagoda. Then, even if they didn’t have horses, she had some assurance that she would be able to lead her little sister through the wild jungle.

But the major problem she was confronted with now was her lack of food. Her only solution was to kill the two Corrupt Wolves.

Na Yi was not a match for the Corrupt Wolves; so she made a crazy decision that seemed rational to her. She would use herself as bait, and lure a Corrupt Wolf into the Sorcerer Holy Land. Once there, she would utilize the traps within to kill it!

She knew that if she was to enter the Sorcerer Pagoda and enhance her strength, that it would be much easier to lure the two Corrupt Wolves into the traps. However, Na Yi was not willing to do so. She could not reconcile with the fact that because of these two Corrupt Wolves, she would have to waste her one chance at the smelting trial, the most important opportunity of her life.

She would make this one gamble!

Corrupt Wolves were scavengers that usually ate carrion. However, they would also eat living creatures. Na Yi took advantage of the time when one of the wolves went to look for live prey and lured the remaining one it. She would guide it to the traps and kill it!

But her gamble had already half failed from the start. She had underestimated the speed of the Corrupt Wolf, and had been seriously injured due to her own overconfident negligence.

The claw of a Corrupt Wolf was toxic!

A Corrupt Wolf ate carrion year round. Their bodies contained corpse gasses and corpse poison. Once scratched by them, one would be infected by the plague and die afterwards!

Now they were running out of food, and there was also another Corrupt Wolf outside. Having been scratched by a Corrupt Wolf, how could she escape death in this situation?

Na Yi bit her lips and pulled out a dagger strapped to her thigh. She threw it at her little sister and said, “Ah Shui, there are many books in the Holy Land’s Library. Look for some that don’t have much value and gather them here. Create a fire and heat up the dagger. Then, cut out the carrion toxin from my back wound…”

Hearing Na Yi say this, Na Shui was frightened out of her wits. She looked at the bloody wound on her big sister’s back. How could she do this!?

“Big Sister… Big Sister…”

“Quickly! The wolf claws are toxic, go before it’s too late!”

“I… I understand.” Na Shui clenched her teeth. She turned around and ran towards the Holy Land Library and gathered some worthless books there. Then, as Na Yi had said, she set that pile of books on fire and used it to heat the dagger.

With the dagger in her hand, Na Shui began to violently tremble. She was a gentle soul; she had never even killed a chicken. Now she must use this knife on her big sister’s back, and this knife was even blazing hot.

“Ah Shui, you can do it. I believe in you. If the corpse toxin spreads, then it will be too late!”

Na Yi tightly bit down on a piece of cloth, waiting for the harsh pain to come. If it wasn’t for the wound being on her back, then she would never have asked Na Shui to do this.

As Na Shui’s eyes flowed with tears, she tore away the clothes on her big sister’s back. There, she could see the wound oozing black blood. Indeed, it was just as Na Yi had said. The wolf’s claws were toxic.

Na Shui found her breath coming out in gasps. She didn’t want to do this, but she had to, otherwise her big sister would die.

Just as she began to swing her dagger down, Na Shui suddenly heard the sound of footsteps behind her. Startled, she jerked around, her dagger leading the way.

“Who is it?” Na Shui was already jittery; even the slightest sound frightened her.

But as she turned around and saw who it was, Na Shui suddenly froze in shock. Behind her stood a ragged young boy. Although he had a pitiable expression, there was a surge of confidence and a calm temperament between his brows.

Mo… Mo Lin…

Na Shui went slack, and then the tears down started falling down. If it wasn’t for the current situation, she would have rushed towards him and cried in joy. “Mo… Big Brother Mo, please, please can you save my big sister? She was poisoned by a scratch from a Corrupt Wolf!”

Na Yi also saw Lin Ming, and her heart was filled with an incredible amazement and relief. Mo Lin was still alive!?

How could this be? In Na Yanda’s records, Na Yanda had only stayed within the Divine Kingdom for a few hours. But Lin Ming had been inside for 7 days and 7 nights!

7 days and 7 nights… and he had actually returned safely?

Lin Ming looked at the wound on Na Yi’s back; the blood there was already starting to become a rancid black.

Lin Ming pressed his hand against Na Yi’s back, and a flux of true essence merged into Na Yi’s body. Lin Ming’s manipulation of true essence had already reached a degree of near perfection. Several thousand filaments of true essence wove into a net that covered the wound.

Puff!

A stream of black ichor began to pour out from Na Yi’s back. In just a few minutes, Lin Ming had already completely forced out all of the toxins within Na Yi’s body.

Then Lin Ming took out a small jade bottle from his spatial ring and sprinkled a handful of powder on Na Yi’s back. This was top-tier quality healing medicine; one tael cost several hundred gold taels.

Lin Ming gave the small jade jar to Na Shui and said, “Apply this medicine on your big sister.”

Na Yi was missing half of her clothes; Lin Ming felt it a little inconvenient to apply the medicine himself.

“Oh… okay.” Na Shui whispered before rushing over to help her big sister apply the medicine. As she applied the medicine, she couldn’t help but sneak peeks towards Lin Ming. The way that Lin Ming had forced out the poison from Na Yi’s body a moment ago had left a profoundly deep impression within her young heart.

This scene was even more memorable then when Lin Ming had eliminated the monkey-faced man and the bald man, saving them.

She thought that Lin Ming was only proficient in his combat prowess. She hadn’t expected that he would also have such a mysterious way of curing wounds.

Unknowingly, Lin Ming had already become an omnipotent figure within Na Shui’s impressionable mind.

Once the medicine had been applied to the wounds, the pain in Na Yi’s body was instantly lessened.

A moment later, she felt the wound itch a little. This itching feeling was only when a wound began to regenerate.

“What happened? Why is there a vicious beast here?” Lin Ming noticed the corpse of the Corrupt Wolf that was off in a corner. How did this strange vicious beast enter the Sorcerer Holy Land?

Na Shui dried her tears and explained the long and sordid matter to Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming listened, he felt some guilt and regret. He hadn’t thought that he would have been in the life and death smelting trial for 7 days, and cause such a crisis for the two sisters.

Lin Ming took out barbecued meat, fresh fruit, and steamed buns from his spatial ring, giving these to Na Shui and Na Yi. “Everything’s fine now. Eat a little first, and then we’ll leave here.”

One of the benefits of a spatial ring was that everything inside could maintain its freshness. No matter how long food was placed within, it would remain fresh, and never rot.

Na Shui stared at these delicious foods like a zombie, and unconsciously swallowed saliva.

These past days, the two sisters had been eating hard dry food; it was simply like chewing on wax. Not only that, but they could only eat a little every day, and they were always haunted by pangs of hunger.

Now with so many fresh and delicious delicacies placed in front of them, Na Shui’s mouth had already started watering.

She rushed to hand a steamed barbecue bun to her sister, and also grabbed one for herself. She wanted to wolf the whole thing down, but remembering that Lin Ming was looking on from the side, she suddenly flushed red with embarrassment. Instead of taking a big bite from the barbecue bun, she only tore off a small piece.

In front of Lin Ming, Na Shui unconsciously maintained her girly image.

Lin Ming thought that was quite funny. He deliberately said, “You eat first, I’ll go to the exit and have a look.”

With that, he rose up. He wanted to go out and solve the problem of the Corrupt Wolf, but remembering the layers of traps within the Sorcerer Hold Land, he dismissed this idea. It was better to wait for Na Yi’s wounds to heal and leave together.

Na Shui blushed. But this time she didn’t care so much, and she ate in massive gulps.

Na Yi also ate a lot. The two sisters were indeed extremely hungry.

Chapter 194 – Sacred Flame’s Flame Essence

As Chi Guda died, the several thousand Fire Worm soldiers were completely cowed. Lin Ming stood within the army, but there wasn’t a single one among them that dared to move against him.

An ordinary soldier usually had a second-grade martial talent. They could practice for several years, but their cultivation still wouldn’t have surpassed the Second Stage of Body Transformation. A middle-level officer could reach Viscera Training or even Altering Muscle, while a high-ranking officer could achieve Bone Forging. However, in front of Lin Ming, they would all fall at the first blow.

Besides Chi Guda, the only ones whose strength was at the Pulse Condensation Period were the Left General and the Right General.

The Left General had already been sent to capture the people that had fled. Only the Right General was left, his entire body covered in a sheen of cold sweat. With the atmosphere now, he didn’t even dare to breathe. He feared that Lin Ming would suddenly come to kill him, and he wouldn’t even be able to escape death.

In front of Lin Ming, the several bodyguards could only been considered as decorations. It could be said that with Lin Ming’s strength, even these thousands of soldiers could not stop him!

Lin Ming didn’t even bother with the Right General. He glanced towards the group of prisoners that had been captured. These prisoners looked at Lin Ming with eyes full of hope and pleading. To them, Lin Ming was a war god that the Sorcerer had sent down from the Divine Kingdom to save them.

Lin Ming’s heart was gloomy and morose. Even if he killed Chi Guda, it was impossible for him to change the fate of these prisoners. After all, he was just one person. He couldn’t stop an entire tribe. All that waited for these prisoners was a lifetime of suffering, slavery, and death.

Lin Ming’s vision swept over the chief’s twins. He hesitated for a moment, and then his figure flashed as he arrived beside the two of them.

He took one in each hand, and instantly launched Golden Roc Shattering the Void, flying forwards.

They could not stay here. Otherwise if the Fire Worm Tribe’s Houtian master arrived, things would become decidedly dangerous.

Rescuing the chief’s twins was the only kindness that Lin Ming could offer, and could be regarded as leaving behind a little hope for the Blackmarsh Tribe. If these two people made every effort possible, they might be able to rebuild their Blackmarsh Tribe in the future and then avenge their tribesmen.

“Go!”

As Lin Ming departed from the chief’s quarters, no one dared to stop him.

Lin Ming sped away, ready to send these two to a small tribe so he didn’t have to manage them. But at this moment, his expression changed. He turned around and saw a bright red light speeding towards him.

“Flame?”

In a flash, Lin Ming could tell that the red light was from a flame. After Lin Ming had formed a Flame Essence from the Heretical God Seed, Lin Ming was no longer afraid of fire. True essence flooded into his right hand, and he aimed towards that red light, ready to slap it down.

Pof!

The red light blew up. But Lin Ming’s expression changed. He felt the power of the flames within it break into his meridians, wreaking havoc! No matter how he tried to vibrate the flames within his body, he was unable to control this flame!

“What’s going on?”

Back in the Lava Cave, no matter how much lava fire there was, the Heretical God Seed was still able to tame it. But now, something like this was actually happening.

Lin Ming revolved all the true essence within his body and suppressed the flame. At the same time, Lin Ming’s mind stirred and he looked forwards.

A hundred feet away in the air, a mass of crimson flames coalesced, forming a shape of flames in the figure of a three foot tall little boy that floated in the air.

The little boy’s entire body was a deep red, and swirls of flame wound around his hands and feet. His small face had a laughing expression, but that smile was tainted with evil.

Lin Ming’s eyebrows furrowed. What was this?

He could feel that the boy’s body contained a very powerful flame attribute true essence; it was much more powerful than his own. No wonder he hadn’t been able to suppress that flame from a moment ago.

Was this little boy the Fire Worm Shaman?

No, that wasn’t right. Even if the Fire Worm Shaman trained in some strange cultivation method that turned his appearance into that of a little boy, he would still have a mortal body. This little boy’s body was clearly composed of fire. Otherwise, it would also be impossible for him to float in the air.

This is…

Lin Ming’s mind went cold. He said to the Blackmarsh twins that he had been carrying, “You’re on your own now. I can’t help you any longer.”

The two siblings listened to Lin Ming, and a bit of despair crossed their expression. The girl opened her mouth as if she wanted to say something, but stopped before the words came out. She knew that at this moment, Lin Ming could no longer save them. They had to run away from the Fire Worm army before they were caught, and had to depend on themselves.

Lin Ming released their hands, and the two siblings silently thanked him before they ran off into the depths of the jungle.

The little flame boy darkly smiled. Flames swirled within his little hand, and he threw a fireball straight towards the two siblings.

Lin Ming coldly snorted, and the Heavy Profound Soft Spear pierced out like a lightning bolt towards the fireball. 5000 vibrating true essence filaments broke into the fireball and there was the sound of an explosion as it turned into a mass of fireworks.

The two siblings were shocked out of their minds. The girl looked back and sent a look of gratitude towards Lin Ming. Without another word, they lowered their heads and continued to run into the jungle.

Seeing this, the little flame boy no longer chased after them. Compared to those two siblings, Lin Ming was the true threat.

The little flame boy’s hands crossed against its chest, and it wickedly smiled as it looked at Lin Ming. The flames swirled on its face, turning into a playful expression.

Lin Ming sneered. “You are the eternal flame’s Flame Essence. The Flame Essence has a soul. After the Fire Worm Shaman fused a part of his soul into the Flame Essence, it formed you. Something neither human nor monster, in the end you’re a Flame Essence that became the Fire Worm Shaman’s avatar.

The little flame boy’s face revealed a stunned expression. But right after, it snickered again and said, “Your soul force is good. You can actually recognize that I am an avatar. I’m more and more interested in you! Today, you stay behind!”

The voice of the Flame Essence avatar was extremely hoarse. Coming from a little boy, it sounded absolutely bizarre.

“Stay here? Who’s going to make me? If your true self comes, then I would have already lost. But you are only an avatar, and you still think you can keep me here?”

Lin Ming spoke to here and then shouted. The aura of his body suddenly rose and he flourished his spear. True essence condensed into an Astral Spear several tens of feet long, thrusting towards the little flame boy’s neck!

He wanted to ruin the soul mark that the Fire Worm Shaman had left in the Flame Essence. If he could do this, then the Flame Essence wouldn’t be possessed by anyone.

As the Astral Spear howled forwards, the little flame boy wildly laughed and its body suddenly disappeared. Its speed was no less than Lin Ming’s!

“You want to break my soul mark? Dream on! Die!”

The little flame boy thrust his hands forwards. The power of fire spewed out from his palms, turning into thousands of twisted red lights that converged on Lin Ming from all sides.

However, the little flame boy didn’t expect that after Lin Ming had thrust out his spear, he would have not even have the desire to fight. Lin Ming immediately launched his movement technique and ran away.

Puff puff puff! The attack of the little flame boy missed. The red lights were like crimson rain that fell upon the ground piled high with leaves. The ground immediately turned into scorched earth upon contact.

“Humph! At least you’re smart. But do you think you can actually escape my grasp? What wishful thinking!” The little flame boy maliciously grinned and started to chase after Lin Ming.

Lin Ming rapidly moved. He displayed the full force of Golden Roc Shattering the Void without any reservations.

If he managed to erase the soul mark that the Fire Worm Shaman had placed in the Flame Essence, then the Flame Essence would lose its consciousness. Then, Lin Ming would have a chance to absorb it!

This idea had an incomparable allure. However, Lin Ming knew that at this point the Fire Worm Shaman was coming. If a true Houtian master arrived, then he wouldn’t be able to escape even if he had wings!

Much less, this little flame boy’s true essence was excessively powerful. As for himself, he had already used Thunderfire Annihilation and had also opened the Heretical God Gate. 40% of his true essence had been consumed. If they fought, he wasn’t sure who would come out on top. To wish to stay here and destroy the soul mark that the Fire Worm Shaman had left in this little flame boy was no different than a moron speaking utter nonsense.

If he didn’t leave now and was delayed for a few more minutes, it would be too late!

Lin Ming’s speed became faster and faster. It was as if his body was weightless. The tips of his toes traced the tops of trees, and his body was like an arrow that had been shot out. After several ups and downs, Lin Ming’s body became increasingly high, until he no longer had the borrow leverage from the treetops, and then completely flew off!

After reaching the peak of Bone Forging, Lin Ming’s true essence had become even thicker and purer, and his movements became increasingly close to true flight.

This time, the little flame boy was completely strunned as it looked at Lin Ming. It could fly too, but that was only because he didn’t have a body, and was only a mass of flames. But that boy was clearly at the peak of Bone Forging. So why was he able to fly?

Did he have some rare flight-capable treasure on his body?

Thinking this, the little flame boy’s eyes flashed with a fierce ominous greed. In any event, he had to make sure this boy stayed. He definitely had some sort of secret!

The wind whistled in Lin Ming’s ear as he flew forwards. He didn’t look back; his soul force had already locked onto the little flame boy behind him. Not only was he not able to ditch him, but he had been getting closer and closer.

“Damn, this fellow is just like a haunting ghost!” Lin Ming frowned. His Golden Roc Shattering the Void was a top-tier movement technique. But, this little flame boy’s body was wholly composed of flames. He was weightless, so he was faster.

“Humph! You’re staying!”

The little flame boy pursued Lin Ming from 100 feet behind. It balled its hands together and several dozens of finger-thick flame columns came shooting towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming twisted his spear behind him without looking.

Peng!

The pillars of flame crumbled apart and then exploded into a rain of red light. But during this time, the little flame boy had already caught up to Lin Ming from behind. It evilly smiled as it stretched out its hands, and the power of fire flashed in its palms. “With my avatar delaying you, don’t even think of running away! Flame Cage!”

Fu —

Strips of crimson flames flew around Lin Ming. The columns of flame interlocked together and formed a cage of fire, trapping Lin Ming within.

Lin Ming stabbed out at the flame cage, but it failed to pierce through!

“Damn!” Lin Ming felt anxious. This little flame boy had made it clear that he was only delaying him. As soon as the Fire Worm Shaman’s true self arrived, then he would be in an extremely dangerous situation.

But this little flame boy’s true essence was thicker and his speed was faster. He couldn’t kill him if he wanted to, and he couldn’t lose him if he wanted to. With this fellow following him, he would catch up sooner or later.

Lin Ming clenched his teeth. The true essence within his body began revolving to the limit, and the power of the dragon blood within his heart suddenly erupted in a blaze of glory.

“Break for me!”

Lin Ming screamed, and thrust his spear out. The true essence within his body that held the power of the dragon blood began to endlessly grow. Even the fire of a Flame Essence would not be able to easily destroy it!

Cha!

The flame cage was completely torn apart. Lin Ming sprung forwards and soared straight into the sky!

The little flame boy was stunned. It hadn’t expected Lin Ming to be able to break out of the flame cage so quickly. But like this, it was even happier. This meant that the secret on Lin Ming’s body was even more valuable.

Chapter 195 – Prestige Of The Saint Beast

Sky Fortune Kingdom, Seven Profound Martial House.

At that time, it had been one month since Lin Ming left Sky Fortune City.

It was a chilly winter afternoon, and a light crop of snow carpeted the earth. The cloud had scattered, and the bright sun was high in the sky, slowly melting the soft snow and filling the air with an icy humidity.

In the northwest corner of the Seven Profound Martial House, the deacon responsible for the Martial House Registration Office was lazing around in ennui, casually flipping the pages of a novel.

Working in the Martial House Registration Office was quite a boring affair. It was mainly recording when disciples of the Martial House would go out for adventures and experience, or recording the time and location for missions they were on. This was to ensure the disciples’ safety. Otherwise, if they were missing for too long without an adequate explanation, then the Seven Profound Martial House would initiate an investigation.

Because there weren’t many disciples of the Seven Profound Martial House that would often go out for adventure or to experience the world, even three or five disciples coming in to register was considered a lot. This boring and tedious work was considered a dead end job with no possibility for future progression; it was work that powerful martial artists would never debase themselves to do.

Sun Liang was a superior second-grade martial talent. Although he couldn’t compare with juniors of large aristocratic families, he was still so-so. Relying on his connections, he had entered into the Sky Fortune Martial House to cultivate for several years before just barely reaching the Viscera Training stage. Afterwards, he became too lazy to practice and turtled himself in the Seven Profound Martial House Registration Office where he became a deacon.

The novel was reaching a satisfying peak. Sun Liang’s expressions couldn’t help but change as he followed the rises and falls of the protagonist’s fate. Sometimes he giggled, sometimes he was tense, but his mood was always engaged. Suddenly, he felt the light dim as a figure blotted out the sunlight.

Sun Liang thought that it was a disciple who had come to register for a leave of absence. He was somewhat dissatisfied as his good mood in reading the novel was interrupted. He looked up, and just when he was about to ask when this disciple was planning on going and where, he suddenly froze in place.

In front of him was a middle-aged man wearing a flowing white robe and carrying a long zither on his back. He was slender, and his thick eyebrows were wise. He had a temperament like clouds in the sun, and was simply an elegant existence.

Pah.

Sun Liang’s novel fell on the ground. Quivering, he stood up and opened his mouth to speak. His voice was dry as he said, “Martial… Martial House Master…”

Sun Liang felt faint at heart. Why would the Seven Profound Martial House Master Qin Ziya be here?

Qin Ziya smiled. Naturally, he did not intend to bother with such minor matters like Sun Liang reading novels during his job. He said, “A month ago, did Lin Ming record where he was going here?”

Sun Liang quickly nodded. There weren’t many people that registered. Lin Ming’s status was unique, so he had definitely remembered him.

“Let me see.”

“O… okay.”

Sun Liang trembled as he flipped through the records, combing the ordered files before finally pulling one out. He thanked the heavens that he didn’t encounter a situation in which he couldn’t find the record, otherwise he really would have wanted to hit his head on the wall and kill himself.

Qin Ziya glanced through the paper records and saw Lin Ming’s travel time and signature. He frowned.

He would go out to adventure for two months, location unknown…

“I know.”

Qin Ziya closed the file before turning around and walking away.

Lin Ming had already disappeared for one month. Although the record had clearly stated that he voluntarily went out to adventure and experience the world, Qin Ziya felt that something was strange about the matter.

Lin Ming had simply offended too many people. It was absolutely an unwise decision to go out and adventure during this time period.

Once his whereabouts were leaked out, he could even encounter a fatal disaster.

Not only that, but there simply weren’t any good areas near the Sky Fortune Kingdom to go out and adventure in. Going out anywhere would be inferior to the quick cultivation within the Seven Profound Martial House. Even the Seven Major Killing Arrays had their doors opened wide for Lin Ming; where could he find such good practice locations outside?

The only thing that the Seven Profound Martial House lacked was true life and death killing situations. If Lin Ming wanted to experience this, then he could have joined the army for awhile. But Qin Ziya had already asked the military, and Lin Ming hadn’t joined them.

This made Qin Ziya’s heart fill with doubts. Just what was Lin Ming doing?

The reason that Qin Ziya had come back this time was to prepare for the upcoming Inter-faction Assembly Tournament.

Two months from now, the Seven Profound Valleys would call down the Martial House core disciples from all the nearby countries and hold a martial gathering.

The martial gathering occurred every three years. At that time, the core disciples of all the countries would gather together and drink tea while appreciating and comparing martial arts.

This was an assessment of the various nations’ core disciples, but it was also an assessment of the Martial Houses themselves. Even Qin Ziya, who rarely cared or worried about the internal affairs of the Martial House attached a serious importance towards this assessment.

When Lin Ming had been passed down the Seven Profound Decree, Qin Ziya had taken advantage of that time to give Lin Ming many benefits. He hoped that Lin Ming would be able to quickly grow in that short time and blossom, shining with radiant glory at the martial gathering.

If his result was good, then not only would he receive rewards as a core disciple, but even the Martial House Master would receive a reward.

The most precious reward was a Heaven Opening Pill.

A Heaven Opening Pill was the miracle medicine that a peak Houtian realm master would take when they were attempting to break into the Xiantian realm. It would remove the foul Houtian air within them, wash their muscles and marrow, reproduce a Xiantian-like state that would allow them to return to their natural state, and finally step into the Xiantian realm.

No matter how awe-inspiring one’s talent was, they still had to take a Heaven Opening Pill in order to step into the Xiantian realm from the Houtian realm.

The difference between the Houtian realm and Xiantian realm was the Xiantian breath within oneself. With this, one’s soul would enter into a tranquil state, and they would be able to communicate with heaven and earth origin energy. They could use their soul to understand the wisdom of the world and use their true essence to move the power of the heavens and earth.

When a baby was still in the mother’s body, they would rely on the umbilical cord transporting blood in order to breathe; this was the Xiantian breath.

After a baby was born, they changed to breathing from their mouths and nose. Inevitably they would breathe the foul Houtian air, and there simply wouldn’t be any Xiantian breath.

From Houtian to Xiantian, one had to rid themselves of worldly roots and change their Houtian breath to Xiantian breath.

In order to do this, one had to wash their muscles and marrow and reproduce the Xiantian breath with the Heaven Opening Pill!

In theory, it could be said that a naturally peerless martial talent could get rid of their body’s Houtian air through their own strength, and wouldn’t need to depend upon a pull to step into the Xiantian realm. However, this was only a theory. The truth was that no one had ever managed to accomplish this.

The Heaven Opening Pill was an incomparably precious treasure within the Seven Profound Valleys. Not only in the Seven Profound Valleys, but the Heaven Opening Pill was extremely scarce even in other large sects.

The materials for the Heaven Opening Pill were too difficult to find. Even if they were all collected, there was still a small chance that there would be a failure during the alchemical refinement of the pill.

The Seven Profound Valleys would refine a batch of Heaven Opening Pills every three years. In the end, they would have around 20 or 30 pills.

The more than 20 pills were insufficient to be divided among so many disciples.

The rules of the Seven Profound Valleys stated that the Heaven Opening Pill could only be rewarded to peak Houtian masters with outstanding talent. Even if these masters took the Heaven Opening Pill, it didn’t mean that they would necessarily break into the Xiantian realm.

Qin Ziya’s talent could already be considered heaven defying. He had started cultivating at 20 years of age, and at 45 he had reached the peak Houtian realm. Once, he too had been given a Heaven Opening Pill. After he took it he attempted to break through the Xiantian bottleneck. However, there was a problem that arose from within his Zither Heart, and he had failed just a step away!

Finally Qin Ziya had stopped a half-step into the Xiantian realm. These years he had been roaming the deep valleys and tempering his Zither Heart. Now, his Zither Heart had reached the Large Success stage. He would only need a Heaven Opening Pill to attack the Xiantian realm bottleneck once again!

Every three years during the martial gathering, two Heaven Opening Pills were rewarded. One to the core disciple, and one to the Martial House Master.

Only first place was rewarded!

Of course, a core disciple had to reach the peak Houtian realm before he could cash in on this reward.

If their cultivation was insufficient, then it would be a waste for them to take the Heaven Opening Pill.

To a core disciple, besides a Heaven Opening Pill, there were also many other rich rewards. For instance, high-grade human-step treasures, top-quality pills, core cultivation methods, and other such great items.

Qin Ziya of course wanted to obtain the Heaven Opening Pill, but he knew it was hopeless for Lin Ming to take the number one spot; that was simply too distant a dream. Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House was strong, but compared to those of Huoluo Nation or the Eastern Sun Country, they were still sorely lacking.

However, just because they couldn’t obtain first place this time didn’t mean they couldn’t next time. If they couldn’t next time, then they could try the time after that. Lin Ming was only 15 years old. He would be able to participate in a total of 3 martial gatherings.

Even if Lin Ming failed these three times, if he was able to make good progress, that could be considered as a merit of Qin Ziya.

But Qin Ziya hadn’t thought that when he had come back, Lin Ming would already have disappeared for one month, his location unknown.

…………………………

Southern Wilderness, Blackwater Swamp —

The chase between Lin Ming and the little flame boy had lasted for more than an hour!

In the time of this hour, the two of them had already fought several times, but neither had been able to gain an advantage.

Lin Ming only had about 30% of his true essence left within him. With the long time that he had been flying as well as the high-intensity combat he engaged in, even though his blood vitality was strong and he had the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ augmenting him, he wouldn’t be able to last much longer.

Like this, his true essence would be completely exhausted in one more hour!

In comparison, the little flame boy had no weakening or lack of true essence. The reason for this was because his cultivation was far more profound and deep than Lin Ming’s, and also because the little flame boy was not a human, but rather a Flame Essence. A Flame Essence grew forever, and wouldn’t be extinguished.

Lin Ming became increasingly anxious; he couldn’t keep on going like this!

If he stopped to fight, he still wouldn’t win. If he was delayed long enough, then the Fire Worm Shaman’s true self would catch up.

If he continued to run away, then he could last one more hour at most. Afterwards, once his true essence was all depleted, the Fire Worm Shaman’s true self wouldn’t even need to come; even the little flame boy could kill him!

It was as if he had already fallen into a dead end…

No, as long as he was alive he had a chance, he just hadn’t thought of it!

Calm down!

Lin Ming’s breathing became more even. His mind had entered into a state similar to the realm of the ethereal martial intent. He had to find a way to break out of this doom!

At this time, 600 miles away from Lin Ming, a middle-aged bald man in a black robe was sitting cross-legged on a Heavenly Wind Eagle with a cold expression. This person was the Fire Worm Shaman, Chi Yue.

He had already ridden the Heavenly Wind Eagle in pursuit for more than one hour while his Fire Essence avatar was diverting Lin Ming. Even so, he was still 600 miles away.

However Chi Yue didn’t worry. He was fine waiting for his prey to exhaust themselves and consume their true essence. As long as this continued for another hour, he would almost win by default.

But this prey’s strength was beyond his expectations. He was only at the peak Bone Forging stage, but his combat prowess actually matched a Houtian realm martial artist. Not only that, but he could also fly, and his endurance and sustained fighting ability were simply frightening!

“No matter what secrets you have on your body, they will all be mine!”

Chi Yue sneered. His goal was to conquer the Southern Wilderness. No one could block his path!

But at this moment, Chi Yue’s smile suddenly froze as he instantly paled!

“This… this is the Vermillion Bird!”

600 miles away, Lin Ming’s eyes were round as he stared at a large red bird flying in the sky. His mind was full of a disbelieving expression; was this the Vermillion Bird?

A legendary Saint Beast actually appeared in front of him?

Chapter 201 – Nest Cavern

The black-clothed martial artist ruefully smiled and said, “I want to, but I would have to have the strength for the job. This kind of treasure might not be protected by just two Thunder Lizards. It might even possibly be a small Thunder Lizard tribal group. If I do go, I fear I would already be dead before I even arrived.”

“Even if I arrive safely, and have the luck to not encounter any Thunder Lizards, the rare thunder-attribute treasure is not something that I can meddle with. It contains a very potent power of thunder. Let alone a valuable thunder attribute material, I can’t even pick 500 year old Thundergrass. If I accidently touch the leaves, then I would follow the same fate as my junior-apprentice brother.”

The black-clothed martial artist glanced at the Altering Muscle youth who was lying unconscious on the ground.

Lin Ming said, “Whether your guess is correct or not, the information you told me is very valuable. Speak up, what sort of reward do you want?”

The black-clothed martial artist was delighted; he had spoken up with this end goal in mind. If the other party eats the meat, it’s fine even if he was just given a little bit of soup. He hesitated and said truthfully, “I don’t know if there really is a treasure, so it’s a bit hasty to talk about rewards. It’s just…Senior; could you please save my junior-apprentice brother first? If he’s left in this state any longer, he might remain disabled for his entire life…”

The black-clothed martial artist spoke with some difficulty. Since he didn’t know how old Lin Ming was, or maybe even that Lin Ming was some old monster, he might have heard him and his junior-apprentice brother’s conversation. He could only hope that this mighty elder wasn’t someone who would keep such small things in his heart.

Sure enough, Lin Ming said, “No problem.”

Towards the trivial little guy lying on the floor, Lin Ming didn’t really bother to care about him.

He pulled out a vial of pills from his spatial ring and walked over to the twin girl’s side.

Over half of the youth’s body was charred. After he probed the youth with his soul force, Lin Ming discovered that there was still a very oppressive power of thunder that remained in his body. The reason the youth was so gravely wounded was because of the continued ravaging of this thunder.

Lin Ming grabbed onto the youth’s hand. Using his Thunder Soul, he was easily able to drain the power of thunder out from the youth, and absorb it all into the Thunder Soul.

Then, he took out a pill from the vial in his hand and shoved it into the youth’s mouth.

Although the twin sisters didn’t know what sort of medicine Lin Ming had fed their second senior-apprentice brother, they only had to see how the pill sparked with light while emitting a rich fragrance to guess that this pill was definitely an expensive miracle medicine.

It was said that a high-level miracle medicine was commonly worth thousands of gold taels. There were even pills that could directly enhance a martial artist’s cultivation that cost tens of thousands of gold taels.

If they could obtain such a pill, then the two sisters wouldn’t have to suffer such hardship in their struggle to reach the Altering Muscle stage. Thinking of this, the two sister’s eyes heated up with a little bit of envy.

The power of thunder had already been removed by Lin Ming. Together with the quick efficacy of the pill, the unconscious youth coughed and woke up. He looked around in a daze. The heavy attack he had received caused him to forget what had happened to him.

“Good,” Lin Ming stood up and said to the black-clothed martial artist, “Let’s go.”

“Mm. Thank you Senior.” The black-clothed martial artist wanted to leave the twin sisters behind to look after Second Junior-apprentice Brother, but, he was worried about letting them stay here by themselves, so he let them all to go together.

The black-clothed martial artist had done a great deal of research into tracking Thunder Lizards. He was able to follow their tracks and traces of activity to retrace their steps. Even if it was hard stone ground where the footsteps were scattered, he was still able to rely on smell and other clues to accurately continue.

Finally, he brought Lin Ming to the lair of the two Thunder Lizards.

“It’s there, behind that big stone.”

The black-clothed martial artist pointed to an extremely secluded and well-hidden cavern not too far away. The cavern was completely composed of magnetic ore, and it was pitch dark inside. It looked just like the mouth of a giant vicious beast.

Lin Ming investigated with his soul force and found that there was a very vibrant power of thunder that undulated from inside the cavern. It was right to come along.

He would also have to thank the black-clothed martial artist, otherwise he wouldn’t have found this place.

Lin Ming said, “It’s fine if you wait outside. I’ll go in.”

Once the big stone was removed, the cavern entrance was just a bit wider than ten feet; it was just enough for a Thunder Lizard to pass through. It seems that this stone was moved by the Thunder Lizard in order to hide the entrance to the cavern. It was just like a gate, every time someone went in or out they had to move the gate.

Lin Ming spread out his soul force and cautiously walked into the cavern. The atmosphere inside was dark and damp, but it didn’t affect Lin Ming’s perception.

He walked a few dozen feet in, when he suddenly saw a light in front of him. The inside of the cavern was actually a very large space. There were small little inlets flowing through the ground, and the sound of water dripping onto the ground clearly reverberated through the empty silence of the cavern.

‘The scenery here isn’t too bad,’ Lin Ming thought while maintaining a high degree of vigilance.

At this moment, he suddenly felt his heart go cold. A dark murderous intent had lock onto him, and a feeling of imminent danger rose from his heart. In the next second, a red light flashed and a thunder ball struck Lin Ming’s body!

‘Thunder Lizard.’

Lin Ming instantly took out the Heavy Profound Soft Spear. This Thunder Lizard was even stronger than the last two he had encountered, and the influx of red lightning that penetrated his body was much more oppressive. Even though Lin Ming had a Thunder Soul, he wasn’t able to immediately quench it.

At this moment, the Thunder Lizard that had been hiding in the shadows roared again. Red balls of thunder shot out one after another and seven or eight of them bombarded Lin Ming like a fierce storm.

Kacha! Kacha! Kacha!

The rocks around Lin Ming were split apart by the force of this attack. Lin Ming stood in the center of this thunder barrage, accepting every single strand of thunder. An intense and painful tingling sensation flooded into him. At first, Lin Ming was extremely uncomfortable, but as the vast power of thunder was gradually being absorbed by him, Lin Ming felt a faint hint of excitement.

‘Good heavens, this peak Pulse Condensation Period Thunder Lizard is no weaker than Chi Guda!’ Recognizing the strength of this Thunder Lizard, Lin Ming was thrilled. Without a doubt, the only reason that this lizard was able to evolve had to be because of some rare thunder-attribute treasure.

The Thunder Lizard found that the usually unstoppable power of its thunder barrage was having no effect whatsoever on Lin Ming. It snarled and dashed towards Lin Ming, wanting to slam him against the stone wall and squash him into a meat patty.

Lin Ming gave a loud shot. He stepped back with his left foot, pressing it against the rock. He lifted both his arms up and true essence erupted from his body. The Heavy Profound Soft Spear was like a mountain that fell from the sky!

Bang!

Lin Ming’s spear struck the top of the Thunder Lizards back. At the same time, his body took advantage of the inertia and sprang upwards. Right after, the Thunder Lizard collided against the rock wall, and the entire cavern shook like an earthquake had occurred as massive stones started cascading down.

The black-clothed martial artist and the twin sisters had been waiting outside the cave when they suddenly heard a raging roar and the sound of an intense impact ringing from inside. They immediately blanched.

The two sisters even considered leaving first. If that senior inside had an accident and the vicious beast ran out, then they would die with him.

“Senior-apprentice Brother, we aren’t….”

“It’s alright.” The black-clothed martial artist waved his hand in dismissal. Listening to the roar, he was able to judge the strength of the Thunder Lizard inside. It shouldn’t be a match for Lin Ming.

He thought that the male and female Thunder Lizard from before were spouses, but it seemed that they were actually mother and child. Currently inside the cavern was actually the fiercest grown-up male lizard!

Whiz!

The Thunder Lizard struck out with its tail. Lin Ming roared and Flow like Silk burst out. Without hesitation he lifted the spear and smashed down onto the tail.

Kacha!

There was the sound of stone cracking. Lin Ming’s Heavy Profound Soft Spear had bent into a crescent moon!

Even though the Heavy Profound Soft Spear was very elastic, it still couldn’t resist such a strong shock. Normal martial artists would already have their hands paralyzed and even broken their arms from such an impact.

However, after Lin Ming entered the Sorcerer Pagoda, his body’s physical strength had become fearsome. He was able to resist this impact, and instead, it was the Thunder Lizard’s spine that was injured by Flow like Silk.

“Die!”

Lin Ming didn’t waste any more time. He directly opened the Heretical God Force!

Thunderfire Annihilation!

In order to deal with a peak Pulse Condensation Period master, Lin Ming could only use his strongest move. At worst, he would just return to the cavern and wait until he was restored to peak condition before he exited again.

The power of thunder and fire intertwined together. The dark cave instantly bloomed with a dazzling brilliance, as if a sun had begun to rise from inside the cave!

The vivid blaze of light illuminated out from the cavern; even the black-clothed martial artist and the two twins couldn’t help but close their eyes. Following closely was an ear-shattering explosion; it was at least 10 times louder than the Thunder Lizard’s roar!

A visible shockwave rushed out from the dark cavern. The 10,000 jin large stone that had been used to block the cavern entrance was sent flying like a lightweight ball that had been kicked; it instantly flew across the air.

The entire cave trembled. Even the rocky ground underneath shook as a violent tremor passed through the entire cavern and countless stones fell from the ceiling. At that moment, the two twin girls suspected that the cavern was about to collapse.

……..

In the cave, waves of blood had already stained the ground crimson. Lin Ming was propping himself up with the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, panting for breath as he stared at the huge corpse of the Thunder Lizard.

Although Lin Ming’s strength had greatly increased after entering the Sorcerer Pagoda, the amount of true essence that Thunderfire Annihilation used had increased correspondingly.

In just one move, almost 40% of Lin Ming’s vast true essence reserves had been consumed. The cost was considerable.

Lin Ming crammed some pills into his mouth and pulled out a True Essence Stone as he continuously absorbed the true essence within. After he recovered a bit, Lin Ming stood up and continued to walk deeper into the cavern. He didn’t even bother taking the time to cut out the Thunder Pearl from the dead Thunder Lizard.

Lin Ming had already probed further into the cavern with his soul force, and didn’t sense any other enemies or threats within. At the end of the cave, he found a red bamboo rooted in a hard magnetic ore surface, stubbornly growing.

Red arcs of lightning twined around the bamboo branch as it crackled. The bamboo leaves were just like sharp swords.

A incomparably formidable power of thunder was steadily streaming out from this bamboo. Without a doubt, this bamboo was the reason for the cave’s rich power of thunder.

This bamboo was the thunder-attribute treasure that the black-clothed martial artist had mentioned.

Chapter 202 – Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo

Looking at this red thunder bamboo, Lin Ming was able to feel a formidable power emanating from it.

Feeling exuberant, he prepared to pick the bamboo. However, he immediately paused. Was there a taboo in picking this sort of valuable material?

He had never seen this thunder bamboo before, but maybe the black-clothed martial artist might have heard about it. With this thought, Lin Ming called out to the black-clothed martial artist to come in.

The black-clothed martial artist had been waiting patiently outside the cave, feeling a bit perturbed. He was afraid that he had guessed wrong and had aroused Lin Ming’s wrath because of that. Although Lin Ming had said it didn’t matter if he was right or wrong, no one could guarantee that Lin Ming wouldn’t turn hostile against them.

At this moment, he heard the voice of Lin Ming sound in his ear, speaking only a few words, “Enter the cave and check this for me.”

The black-clothed martial artist’s heart tightened. He grit his teeth and told the twin sisters and the Viscera Training stage youth, “Come in with me.”

The group cautiously entered on their tippy-toes. Due to the dim lighting in the cave, as the twin girls were walking deeper, they felt something bump against their feet. As soon as they peered downwards, they saw a massive Red Thunder Lizard lying dead on the floor. The twins almost fainted as they let out an alarming cry.

“It’s okay, it’s already dead,” The black-clothed martial artist assured.

As he saw the deep scarlet scales of the Thunder Lizard, the black-clothed martial artist was startled. This was a Thunder Lizard that was equal to a peak Pulse Condensation Period martial artist in strength! Even if it was his master who encountered this fellow, he would instantly be killed, yet now, this fearsome beast had been slaughtered.

As the group reached the end of the cave, the black-clothed martial artist finally arrived to where Lin Ming was at. The moment the black-clothed martial artist laid eyes on the crimson bamboo in front of Lin Ming, he let out a sigh of relief. He wasn’t wrong!

Lin Ming pointed at the red bamboo and asked, “You know what this is?”

The black-clothed martial artist shifted his vision to the red bamboo. He hadn’t taken a good look at it a moment ago, but now that he carefully reviewed hit, he was instantly awed. “This…this is probably Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo!”

“Mm? Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo?” Lin Ming looked at the red bamboo and the red lightning that twined around the bamboo. ‘Why wasn’t this called Red Electricity Spirit Bamboo instead?’

The black-clothed martial artist saw Lin Ming’s doubting expression and said, “This is because the bamboo hasn’t grown up yet. When Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo is 60 years old it’s’s shoots would be white. When it’s 900 years old it’s shoots would be red. And when its 9000 years old it’s shoots are purple.”

Lin Ming said, “This is only a young bamboo?”

“Mm.”

“This….” Lin Ming couldn’t help but be slightly disappointed. Even if it was a rare material, it was still only a young bamboo, so its inherent power was limited.

The black-clothed martial artist saw Lin Ming’s disappointment and consoled, “Senior, although it is only 900 year-old bamboo, it is still very precious and rare. Not only that, but since there is a young bamboo, then there should be a Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo too. Every 9000 years only one bamboo shoot will be born. The small bamboo shoot will drill through magnetic ore and live inside until it finds a good place to break out, where it will grow into white bamboo.”

“Oh?” Lin Ming mind’s stirred. “You mean to say that there is an adult Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo in Thundercrash Mountain?”

“Yes, if there isn’t a problem, then there should be. Moreover, that bamboo should already be 9,900 years old.”

A Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo would only breed a new bamboo shoot every 9000 years. Since this red bamboo shoot was already 900 years old, then the adult should be 9900 years old.

“9900 years old…..” Lin Ming furrowed his eyebrows. It was said that thunder had been striking Thundercrash Mountain for 10,000 years. That would mean that this bamboo was nearly as old as Thundercrash Mountain!

If Lin Ming wasn’t wrong, then this bamboo would definitely be at the summit of Thundercrash Mountain!

But with his current strength, if he met a Houtian realm Blue Thunder Lizard, he could only run for his life; how would he ever reach the summit?

And the legends even said that there was a Purple Thunder Lizard that was equal to a Xiantian realm martial artist!

In addition, he was afraid of the probability of there being more than one.

Even if Lin Ming was able to resist the lightning that the Purple Thunder Lizards spat out, there was no way that he could resist their physical assault.

The Thunder Lizards had the blood of a Flood Dragon flowing through their veins; they were not common vicious beasts.

Although he knew there was little hope, more so that there would be danger within danger, Lin Ming still decided to climb up Thundercrash Mountain. He would climb until he reached his limit; until he was no longer able to go even one more step higher, otherwise he would regret it forever.

Lin Ming asked the black-clothed martial artist, “Is there a taboo to picking the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo?”

The black-clothed martial artist answered, “It is hard to sever Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo with swords or spears; it can only be easily cut off with the power of thunder. But Senior, this sort of Spirit Bamboo doesn’t form easily, it comes from a combination of Thundercrash Mountains energy and the spiritual pulse of the land. If possible, I hope that Senior can leave the bamboo root so that in a few hundred or thousand years, a new Violet Electricity Bamboo can be born.”

“I understand.” Lin Ming nodded. It wasn’t admirable to destroy a valuable material’s origins; it was quite a dreadful thing. This sort of treasure only formed in extremely difficult conditions; it needs all sort of luck and special environments to form.

Normally, a martial artist would abide by this unwritten rule; it could be considered accumulating a bit of good karma.

Lin Ming pulled out his saber. It’s sharp blade was bright as snow, and it shimmered with a deadly cold gleam. This was the high-grade human-step treasure that was taken from Huo Gong, and it was also the saber he carried with him.

Let alone a high-grade human-step treasure, the twin sisters hadn’t even seen many low-grade human-step treasures. Only their master had a low-grade human-step treasure sword. The two twin sisters were, once again, filled with envy.

Lin Ming didn’t mind revealing his wealth. With his current strength, even if he wore a high-grade human-step treasure and it became public, he would still be able to protect it.

True essence poured into the Thunder Soul within the Heretical God Seed. The power of thunder steadily streamed out, and the snow white treasure sword began to sparkle with a faint purple light.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and aimed at the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo’s root. He slashed out!

Cha!

Lin Ming hadn’t imagined that it would be so tough. The crimson blood-coloured Spirit Bamboo was cut down, its edges smooth like a mirror.

When Lin Ming reached out to grab it. The black-clothed martial artist cried out in alarm. This Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo contained the violent power of thunder. A normal martial artist’s arm would be charred to ash. But, thinking of Lin Ming’s strength and the way he had been able to take on the Thunder Lizard’s thunder ball, he felt that it should be alright.

Sure enough, Lin Ming gripped the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo. Besides looking a little stiff, there wasn’t any difference. Even his clothes were alright.

‘What a strong power of thunder!’

Lin Ming praised the bamboo in his mind. If 900 year old red bamboo had such a potent force contained within, then what would 9000 purple bamboo be like? It was simply unimaginable.

Unfortunately, this bamboo was taken too early; it wasn’t able to grow into that.

Although he didn’t entertain much hope, Lin Ming still asked, “Is there any way to grow Violet Electricity Thunder Bamboo?”

The black-clothed martial artist said, “It’s impossible. Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo must grow in lands that are rich in the thunder element, such as Thundercrash Mountain. Not only that, but the bamboo has a proud character and won’t be raised.”

“Mm. I understand.”

Lin Ming placed the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo into his spatial ring and glanced at black-clothed martial artist’s party of four.

He looked at the two swords in the twin girls hands, and hesitated slightly. He said, “Take out your swords and let me have a look.”

“….Okay.” The two young girls obediently drew out their swords. The soft swords were forged from fine steel. To a mortal blacksmith, making this sword would not have been easy. But compared to a treasure sword made by a refining master, it was far weaker.

Lin Ming traced his finger on his spatial ring and three low-grade human-step treasure swords appeared in his hands.

Seeing the swords emit a snow bright light, the twin sister’s eyes widened….an idea caught in their mind that made their heartbeat accelerate and their mouths dry. Were these swords for them? Could they also have a treasure like this one day?

“For you.” Lin Ming casually tossed the swords and they pierced tip first into the magnetic ore. These swords were made by Huo Gong. Lin Ming had no use for the 30 low-grade human-step treasures that he had made; giving them away was just right. Of course, the low-grade human-step treasures that Huo Gong had made were very good; they were much better compared to a normal low-grade human-step treasure.

“For…for us?” The twin sisters mind reeled in surprise. They hadn’t dared to imagine that they would ever have a reward, and it would be the dream treasure they had longed for!

Lin Ming said, “You’d best be careful and put it somewhere safe, otherwise it will likely be taken. These three treasure can tempt even peak Bone Forging martial artists.”

“Yes, yes!” The two twin sisters hurriedly nodded, looking at Lin Ming with eyes filled with gratitude and hero worship.

At this moment, Lin Ming looked towards the black-clothed martial artist. The black-clothed martial artist felt his heartbeat rapidly rising. He had seen Lin Ming casually toss out three top low-grade human-step treasures without even batting an eye; it was as if he treated them like scrap iron! These three treasure swords were no less than 8 or 9 thousand gold taels!

What would he receive? The black-clothed martial artists had a giddy feeling of excitement, anticipation, and apprehension.

Lin Ming looked at the black-clothed martial artist and said, “Your weapon is a staff. It’s too bad, but I do not have a treasured staff. I do have a dark purple elastic iron spear, but because it was a weapon I once used, I cannot give it to you…”

Hearing Lin Ming say this, the black-clothed martial artist was slightly disappointed. But, Lin Ming’s following words caused his heart to be filled with a great joy.

Lin Ming stated, “Cultivation pills, 20,000 gold, cultivation method. You can choose one.”

Cultivation pills, 20,000 gold, and also a cultivation method?

The black-clothed martial artist mouth dried. If he wasn’t able to reach the Pulse Condensation Period, then he would never be able to earn 20,000 gold in his lifetime. As for the cultivation pills, those were dream treasures that martial artists longed for. And since these were pills given by this senior, they must be priceless.

The black-clothed martial artist went through a series of mental battles. He finally said, “I want the cultivation method!”

Compared to pills or gold, a cultivation method was the most important. This was the foundation of every martial artist!

“Good. But, I warn you. Do not reveal this cultivation method to the public, otherwise you may experience calamity.” Lin Ming flicked his hand and a jade slip appeared in his palm.

This was the medium-step human-grade cultivation method manual that he had taken from Huo Gong after his death. This set of cultivation methods did not belong to the Seven Profound Valleys, otherwise Lin Ming would not dare to hand it  over. If he was right, then this cultivation method should be taken from other martial artists that Huo Gong had killed. In short, it had a questionable background, and Lin Ming didn’t want to have it with him in order to avoid future trouble. Giving it to someone of the Southern Wilderness was a good choice.

The black-clothed martial artist received the jade slip and probed with his soul force. He was immediately overjoyed.

‘Medium-grade human-step cultivation method!’

Chapter 203 – Near The Summit

This medium-grade human-step cultivation method was absolutely worth more than 20,000 gold taels. Although Lin Ming had said that this cultivation method could give rise to a fatal calamity, the risk was nothing compared to the tremendous rewards that this cultivation method would bring.

The black-clothed martial artist thought increasingly more that telling Lin Ming about the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo was the best choice he had ever made. He didn’t have the ability to cut the spirit bamboo down, but even if he did, there was no way he could sell it. If he took this level of treasure out and showed it to others, he would be eaten to the bones.

“You can only take the Thunder Lizard’s blood away; I have no need for it.” Lin Ming said this because the Thunder Lizard had the bloodline of a Flood Dragon flowing in it, so their blood had a very great medicinal value. If it was placed in a bath, one could soak in blood and come out with a stronger and healthier body.

The black-clothed martial artist’s group of four nodded in joy. This was a great harvest of income. The blood of a Red Thunder Lizard that was on the same level as a peak Pulse Condensation Period martial artist could sell for at least one or two thousand taels of gold.

“Alright.  Then we shall part from here. About today’s events, I don’t want others to know about it. Otherwise… ”

Lin Ming didn’t say it out loud, but he let the clear meaning behind his words linger in the air. In fact, he wasn’t afraid if others knew, he just didn’t want to be troubled.

The black-clothed martial artist shrank backwards and hurriedly nodded. The only one that they could not conceal the truth from was their master. But, after he obtained this medium-grade human-step cultivation method, the black-clothed martial artist already planned to leave the school. If he went back and faced his master, would he still be able to keep the cultivation method jade slip treasure that he had obtained?

It wasn’t only the black-clothed martial artist, the twin girls also had similar thoughts. They had finally managed to obtain a treasure sword after so much difficulty. They didn’t want their master to take it away.

All in all, they had been in the school for such a long time, yet they hadn’t obtained any substantial benefits from their master there.

After Lin Ming departed, the black-clothed martial artist gathered the twin sisters and their young junior-apprentice brother to have a meeting. They decided that all of them would leave their school and establish their own gang. By relying on the medium-grade human-step cultivation method that Lin Ming had given them, they would make a name for themselves.

However, this was a story for another time.

…

After he had parted from the black-clothed martial artist’s group, Lin Ming looked for a safe place and started to absorb the power of thunder from the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo.

This red lightning was much more cruel and savage than all of the lightning that Lin Ming had absorbed so far.

But Lin Ming was not worried. First, he sat down in meditation. After he had completely recovered all the true essence he had lost, he entered the ethereal martial intent state, and adjusted his mental condition to consummate tranquility.

Then, he took the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo out from his spatial ring.

Gripping the Spirit Bamboo in both hands, Lin Ming began to guide the power of thunder in the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, allowing it to flow into his body.

After the crimson power of thunder entered Lin Ming’s meridians, it was just like a wild horse that was dashing around in defiance. If a normal martial artist at the Pulse Condensation realm or even the Houtian realm, had this tyrannically oppressive red thunder enter their organs, their meridians would be destroyed and they would be severely injured or even die.

But Lin Ming had the existence of a Thunder Soul in his body. No matter how overbearing the lightning was, once it encountered the Thunder Soul, it would slowly be absorbed.

In this way, the small Thunder Soul was just like a small silkworm. It continually nibbled on the power of thunder that was in the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, slowly eroding it. During this period, Lin Ming only felt a faint numb feeling; it wasn’t particularly painful.

After Lin Ming had sat in meditation for half an hour, he had managed to completely absorb the power of thunder. As he looked in at the Heretical God Seed, Lin Ming was pleasantly surprised. After absorbing the lightning from the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, the energy of his Thunder Soul had increased by 50%.

If just a 900 year old baby bamboo was able to increase the power of his Thunder Soul by 50%, what would a 9000 year old bamboo do to it?

Lin Ming was filled with anticipation. Unfortunately, there might not even be a sliver of hope in obtaining this bamboo.

After absorbing the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, Lin Ming continued climbing upwards.

The higher he went, the more Thunder Lizards there were.

These Thunder Lizards were superior vicious beasts that had the bloodline of a Flood Dragon. Although the Thunder Lizards at the base of Thundercrash Mountain had a very shallow bloodline, they still weren’t easy to deal with.

As Lin Ming approached the mountainside, he began to feel it becoming difficult.

Whiz!

The spear wind pierced the void. Lin Ming’s spear shot through the immense body of a Red Thunder Lizard and vibrating true essence erupted. This middle Pulse Condensation Period Red Thunder Lizard immediately died a terrible death.

After Lin Ming had fused with the reverse scale blood, his Flow like Silk continued to grow. Even if it entered the enemy’s body, it wouldn’t easily break down, and its power had also increased a bit. Otherwise, with just true essence attacks alone, Lin Ming would have found it exceedingly difficult to kill a middle Pulse Condensation Thunder Lizard. After all, the physical defense capabilities of a Thunder Lizard were much sturdier than those a human at the same level of cultivation.

Lin Ming let a breath loose as he cut the Thunder Lizards open and dug out the Thunder Pearl. With a though, he absorbed the power of thunder from the Thunder Pearl into his meridians. This was already the 20th Thunder Lizard that he had killed. Through the continuous absorption of the Thunder Pearls, the total increase in power of his Thunder Soul had already reached 60%.

He looked up at Thundercrash Mountain. From where he was now, there was still about 50,000 feet until he reached the summit. He was already able to clearly see the thick lightning that flashed at the summit. This lightning was true thunder. Even though Lin Ming had a Thunder Soul, he didn’t dare to attempt to go up there.

Lin Ming used his movement technique and rushed towards the summit. At this moment, a blue light flashed and a blue arc of lightning hit Lin Ming.

Zizizi!

A powerful numbing electric feeling made Lin Ming go stiff, almost causing him to fall. This was only because he had absorbed the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo a while ago and his Thunder Soul had become much stronger. Otherwise, Lin Ming suspected he really would have fallen.

“Blue Thunder Lizard!”

This was the first time that Lin Ming had seen a Thunder Lizard at the same level as a Houtian realm martial artist.

Without a single word, he launched his movement technique to flee. Although he could resist the thunder attack of a Blue Thunder Lizard, it was impossible for him to kill it. Even if he used Thunderfire Annihilation, he still wouldn’t be able to kill it.

In that case, Lin Ming didn’t want to waste any effort.

Thankfully, Lin Ming was much faster than the Blue Thunder Lizard. In a few jumps, he had already lost it.

In the mountainside region, there were mostly Red Thunder Lizards. Blue Thunder Lizards would only occasionally appear. Lin Ming went on a killing spree; he slaughtered for one day and one night!

After such a long rampage, Lin Ming’s fighting skill were becoming more and more refined, and the Thunder Soul in his body had finally achieved 70% increased power after absorbing a massive amount of thunder. But, as the power of this Thunder Soul increased, the effects of the nourishment from the Thunder Pearl were becoming less and less.

Lin Ming filled an empty pool with Thunder Lizard blood and soaked in it for a quarter of an hour. Afterwards, Lin Ming dried his body and took a new set of clothes out of his spatial ring. Thunder Lizard blood could to increase the health and fitness of the human body. Although it’s effect wasn’t too obvious on Lin Ming, he still didn’t want to waste it.

After eating a simple meal, Lin Ming leapt up on a several hundred feet tree and began to meditate. A Bone Forging martial artist could go for days without sleeping and still remain energetic and buoyant. But, in order for Lin Ming to maintain his peak condition, he had to rest for a couple hours. The next fights would be increasingly savage.

As he closed in on the summit, Lin Ming’s speed became slower. Before, it had taken him a few hours to reach the mountainside from the base of Thundercrash Mountain, but now the same distance took him an entire night.

Lin Ming finally arrived at an area blanketed in ice and snow. Every 1000 feet here took at least a few hours.

He needed to use his soul force to constantly assess his surroundings, and then slowly and cautiously, advance forwards. He didn’t want to accidently run into a Xiantian realm Purple Thunder Lizard. If that happened, there wasn’t much he could do.

Of course, Lin Ming could actually fly into the air and go straight into the sky. But in that case, there was no reason to come to Thundercrash Mountain. He would only be able to float around in the sky and look at the scenery. It would be impossible for him to obtain a shred of thunder power, and then, it would be even more impossible for him to obtain a Thunder Soul.

Cold winds blew everywhere, and snow filled the air. In the upper region of Thundercrash mountain, everywhere one looked there was the frost blue color of ice; crystal clear and incomparably pure.

This was true 10,000 year ice; hard as rock and beautiful like jade.

Clouds pooled at the ground. Leaning over, one was able to see an infinitely dense fog, surging seas of clouds reaching into the vast infinity; this truly was a fabled paradise.

What a pity that this beautiful land was entirely blanketed with a savage killing aura.

When Lin Ming saw a dark Blue Thunder Lizard near a patch of 10,000 year old ice, he knew that he had reached the end of his road. If he took even one step further, then he would be placed in a life-threatening situation.

This deep blue scaled Thunder Lizard was equal to a peak Houtian realm martial artist. Its scales were the exact color of the 10,000 year old ice, and it almost perfectly blended in. If one wasn’t carefully looking, it was simply impossible to find.

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming couldn’t help but exclaim. This Blue Thunder Lizard was a beautiful animal. Especially in this bitter cold land, it looked just like a fine ice sculpture.

But this beautiful ice sculpture could quickly kill him. The difference in its strength and Lin Mings was simply too great.

Prior to this, Lin Ming had encountered a middle Houtian realm Blue Thunder Lizard that had caused him some distress. Because it’s speed wasn’t slower than Lin Ming’s, Lin Ming had finally flew into the sky and only then was he able to escape unharmed.

Now that he faced a peak Houtian realm Thunder Lizard, the result could be imagined.

Lin Ming didn’t dare to go forwards any further. Who knew, maybe the Xiantian realm Thunder Lizard could fly. If it could, then he was dead.

Lin Ming was already prepared to run away, but at this moment, he noticed that the deep Blue Thunder Lizard’s eyes were filled a trace of confusion; it didn’t seem as if it were preparing to attack him.

“Mm? What is this fellow doing?” Lin Ming was filled with complete vigilance. He didn’t even taken the Heavy Profound Soft Spear out, because he knew that using a spear in this situation was useless. It was better to keep less weight on him so he could run faster.

The Thunder Lizard growled in bursts, its eyes revealing its confusion that gradually evolved into vigilance and fear. Its roar became louder, as if it were warning Lin Ming to leave its territory immediately.

Lin Ming had a puzzled look. “If I read this right, this Thunder Lizard seems to be afraid of me? What does it have to fear? I don’t even have a tenth of its strength.”

“This is the strongest Thunder Lizard that I’ve met so far, but this strongest one is actually scared of me. Why….?”

Chapter 209 – Injured Maiden

In a cave at the base of Thundercrash Mountain, Lin Ming was recovering from his injuries as he meditated. The residual flames of the Vermillion Bird had been difficult to deal with. Only after spending a great deal of effort was Lin Ming just able to suppress it forcefully.

After swallowing a medicinal pill, Lin Ming probed his body with his soul force; any hidden wounds were almost healed.

Lin Ming looked at the sky, the sun was setting over the horizon. Lin Ming intended to flee Thundercrash Mountain during the night and find a secret place to refine the thunder-attribute treasures he had picked up. It was a pity that he hadn’t succeeded in obtaining the Thunder Soul, this caused Lin Ming to feel a bit of regret.

As he carefully made his way out of the cave, Lin Ming launched his movement technique. He was like a sleek cheetah as he made his way through the forest with only the sounds of branches breaking beneath his feet. In an instant, Lin Ming had already rushed forwards several miles into the distance.

The sun disappeared over the horizon, and the dim forest became completely dark. But this had no impact on Lin Ming’s speed. After rushing several dozen more miles out, Lin Ming stopped in his footsteps. With his keen senses, he felt an overwhelmingly rich flame energy in the air.

Looking around, Lin Ming found that the surrounding ground was scorched black, and even the green leaves on the trees had been toasted into a withering yellow. They had apparently been roasted by a fiery air.

With all these signs of burned objects around him, Lin Ming was able to find obvious traces of flame, as if something flaming had gone deep into the forest.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment before following the traces of flames for several steps. His eyes suddenly narrowed, “Blood?”

On the ground, there were some dark red bloodstains. And the deadwood and leaves surrounding the bloodstains had been burnt to ashes.

Lin Ming had a faint guess of what had happened. He restrained the breath of his body  and sent out his soul force. Cautiously following the traces of flame, he only had to walk 2 or 3 miles before he suddenly froze in his steps.

In a clearing in the forest, a large red bird was sprawled on the ground, prostrate. This was the Vermillion Bird that Lin Ming had seen before.

This surprised Lin Ming. The Vermillion Bird’s wing was actually broken! Blood constantly dripped from the wound. The bloodstains that he had seen in the forest were left behind by this injured Vermillion Bird.

Looking at the ebbing appearance of the Vermillion Bird, it looked like it received extremely heavy injuries. The flames of its body weren’t as vibrant as they were before. Instead, they were like the flickering wicks of a candle flame just before it was extinguished.

Behind the Vermillion Bird, there was a woman in red leaning against a tree trunk. Her face was pale, her gorgeous eyes were closed shut and her long eyelashes were slightly trembling.

Her body was wrapped in fire and arcs of purple lightning. In the dark night, it was an especially dramatic image.

Obviously, she was also seriously injured.

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming’s eyes widened in stupefaction. The woman in red had been suppressing the Thunder Flood Dragon in their battle, so how did the situation reverse and she take such a heavy injury? If she couldn’t win, she could at least have fled. But even her Vermillion Bird mount had broken a wing. Did the Thunder Flood Dragon used an overwhelming final trump card? Or was there another awe-inspiring powerhouse that had arrived?

Lin Ming looked at the woman in red, and his expression changed several times, revealing his conflicting thoughts. He finally decided to return to where he came from. A powerhouse like this, even if severely injured, would still not find it difficult to kill him. Lin Ming didn’t want to place his own little life in the hands of others.

Of course, he also thought that if he could help the woman in red cure her injury, she would have to owe him a favor. The value of a favor from a Xiantian realm master could be imagined.

But if she was a Xiantian realm master, she most likely have several miracle medicines and elixirs  that she could casually bring out that were tantamount to his entire net worth. Why would she need his help in curing any injures?

Just as Lin Ming took a step back, the woman in red opened her eyes. Her jet black pupils stared forth. In the dark night, her eyes were just like shining stars.

Lin Ming stopped, standing where he was. He hesitated for a moment, before respectfully calling out. “Greetings, Senior!”

“It’s you.”

The woman in red had already felt someone nearby. It was only because their cultivation level was not high that she didn’t care too much.

But, it seemed that she had run across the boy from Thundercrash Mountain.

This was the third time they had met, this was truly destiny.

“Do you know if there is a large Southern Tribe nearby?” The woman in red asked. Her voice frail, but it still revealed an innate sense of prideful nobility.

“Yes, there is one 200 miles to the southwest.” Lin Ming said truthfully. He guessed that the during the time on the summit, the woman in red had been too busy to bother with such a weak and unimportant person like himself. There was no way that she knew that he had already looted the Thunder Flood Dragon’s cave, so he didn’t worry that she would covet anything on him.

“200 miles… ” The woman in red sighed, a sharp bitterness flashing across her face. She hadn’t imagined that one day, a dignified maiden of Divine Phoenix Island like herself would be stumped by a mere 200 miles.

Lin Ming became aware of the bitterness in the woman in red. He was surprised for a moment and then, he immediately understood. It was not only the Vermillion Bird whose wing was broken, but the woman in red was heavily injured too, to the point where even walking would be an painfully onerous task.

He was curious; how did this woman in red, who had been the one with the upper hand, suddenly suffer such a heavy injury? Of course, that was a question that he didn’t dare to ask.

Although it was unlikely, Lin Ming still politely asked, “Senior, is there any way that I can help you?”

The woman in red thought for a moment, and then asked, “This tribe that you mentioned, do they have any Heavenly Wind Eagles for sale?”

Lin Ming shook his head. “It’s only a small tribe, they wouldn’t have a mount like that. But, they do have horses….”

Lin Ming’s sentence trailed off as he glanced at the Vermillion Bird. Such a hefty bird, can a horse actually transport it?

The woman in red shook her head, her eyes flashing with disappointment.

She gently said, “Thank you.”

Then she stood up, and bent over to whisper into the Vermillion Bird’s ear. The Vermillion Bird opened both eyes and whined a few times, struggling to stand up.

The Vermillion Bird tried to uses its wings to prop itself up, but because its left wing was broken, it lost its balance and almost fell to the ground.

The woman in red couldn’t bear to watch such a pitiful scene. With a bit of deep regret, she stretched her jade-white hand out and placed it on the Vermillion Bird’s chest, continuously pouring fire true essence into the Vermillion Bird’s body.

As the woman in red’s true essence was poured into the Vermillion Bird, the Vermillion Bird’s healthy appearance was restored a bit. But, at the same time, the purple electric arcs of lightning on the woman in red’s body became wilder and more powerful. After more snaking arcs of lightning sprung up, the woman in red’s face became increasingly pale.

Lin Ming had been clearly watching everything from the side. The lightning was obviously left behind by the Thunder Flood Dragon’s attack, and the purple arcs of lightning were originating from within the woman in red’s body.

Before, the woman in red had been using her own true essence to suppress the lightning in her body, but she didn’t seemed to achieve any success. Now that she had poured a part of her true essence into the Vermillion Bird, the lightning around her became immediately fierce.

If it was a force of thunder that even the woman in red could not suppress, then maybe….

Lin Ming had a faint guess. This speculation caused him to pant, and his heart began to beat like a wild drum!

Seeing the woman in red take a pill and limp towards the Vermillion Bird, leading it towards the southwest, Lin Ming opened his mouth and said, “Senior, may I have a look at your injury?”

The woman in red turned her head, looking at Lin Ming with surprise. Although this youth in front of her seemed somewhat mystical, and his strength far surpassed his current cultivation, she didn’t think that there was any chance that he could possibly cure her injuries.

As the Thunder Flood Dragon went all out with his final strike, she could only use her thick true essence to barely suppress it. She had no other means to deal with it.

The woman in red had only wanted some of the Thunder Flood Dragon’s blood to help the Vermillion Bird complete its evolution. She had even brought sufficient treasures and terms to equally exchange with the Thunder Flood Dragon. She had never imaged that this matter, which could not have been regarded too seriously, had caused the Thunder Flood Dragon to bet everything it had against her.

As the woman in red held the upper hand and was suppressing the Thunder Flood Dragon, it didn’t even hesitate to use up the millennia Thunder Soul that it had been refining within itself for so long as its final strike.

If it was any common power of thunder, the woman in red would have been able to use her true essence to extinguish it. However, the Thunder Soul clung to life and refused to be smothered out. After entering her body, she had to transfer all of the true essence in her body to contain it. If she relaxed her guard just a bit, or used up any true essence, the Thunder Soul would immediately manifest, wantonly attacking the meridians in her body!

Because of this reason, she didn’t even have the ability to fly now.

If she wanted to eliminate the Thunder Soul from within her body, she could only do so at Divine Phoenix Island. But, Divine Phoenix Island was 500,000 miles from here. Thinking this, the woman in red’s heart was filled with bitterness. With her current condition, she would die before she ever walked the distance.

The Vermillion Bird rushed out of Thundercrash Mountain in order to salvage its life. It had also been seriously injured and it had barely managed to descend the mountain; its left wing had been completely destroyed.

One person and one bird would easily attract attention from high-level vicious beasts in this beastly forest. The woman in red could easily deal with them, however, the problem was if they came in great numbers. If they did, the woman in red would have to use up an excessive amount of true essence, aggravating her injuries.

The woman in red didn’t imagine that she would be placed in such a plight; it seemed that she had reached a dead end.

She said to Lin Ming, “Thank you, but no. You have no means to deal with my wound.”

She guessed that Lin Ming came from some great family in the mortal world, and he probably had some sort of expensive miracle medicine on his body. But, she had many of these pill and elixirs, and hers were even better. However, all her medicines were nothing in front of the Thunder Soul.

Lin Ming knew that the woman in red wouldn’t believe him. He said, “Senior, I would just like to take a look. If I can’t do anything, I will naturally give up. With Senior’s wound as they are now, does Senior actually plan on take the Vermillion Bird with a broken wing to the human tribe? Or does Senior plan on staying in this vicious beast forest? I fear that both these plans are a bit dangerous.”

“I said, there is nothing that you can do about my injury!” The woman in red said impatiently. She was someone who was used to being in the superior position and listened to; she wasn’t used to others questioning her, especially about such an obvious matter.

This was just like a little child telling an sage doctor that he would help take his pulse and see what illness he had. That doctor would absolutely think that the little child was just playing around and whiling his time away.

If it weren’t because the youth was so young, the woman in red would even suspect that he was having improper thoughts to take advantage of the situation.

Lin Ming saw the woman in red’s evident impatience and grumpiness. He did have an ulterior motive in asking to take a look at her wound. It was because he wanted to examine the possibility of the Thunder Soul. He patiently said, “I just want to take a look. If I can’t do anything, you have nothing to lose. You’re a great Xiantian master, why would you be afraid of a little Bone Forging boy like myself?”

Chapter 210 – Healing Wounds

The woman in red frowned at Lin Ming. She had been born with an inherent dignity and pride. Now, with her current cultivation and status, her noble manner had already integrated into her being. That didn’t mean she was arrogant,  this was only a normal response. It was just like the impossible prospect of a supreme Empress obeying the orders of a common peasant, not to mention that the peasant was speaking such unrealistic words.

Lin Ming saw that the woman in red was silent, so he tentatively took a few steps forward. “Senior, if I may, can I suggest using my soul force to examine your injury?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s inquiry, the woman in red expression became increasingly dark. Soul force was able to penetrate most objects, for instance, things like the human body, or clothes. If she lay down the true essence shielding her body, and let the other party scan her, it was no different than removing all her clothes. Everything would be visible.

How could she possibly agree to such a request? The woman in red coldly snorted, then turned around to walk away. With her identity and status, she would normally never come into contact with such a simple boy. They were people of completely separate worlds. If it weren’t for today’s special circumstances, these two would have never exchanged so many words.

Lin Ming saw the woman in red turn away. He rolled his eyes, and loudly said, “Senior, you were struck by the Thunder Flood Dragon’s Thunder Soul, right!?”

The woman in red stiffened. In surprise, she turned her head to look at Lin Ming. Although she had guessed this teenager in front of her was some extraordinary person in the mortal world, she didn’t think that he would have such good sight. Although he hadn’t used any soul force to examine her, he was still able to correctly guess what sort of injury she had.

“How did you know?”

“Just a guess.” Lin Ming shrugged. His speculation was the start, but the restlessness of the Thunder Soul in the Heretical God Seed let Lin Ming be confident in his guess.

Seeing the woman in red hesitate, Lin Ming continued, “How about it? In any case, you’ll find it difficult to suppress the Thunder Soul in your body any time soon. There’s no point in abandoning any hope. In desperate situations, you should try everything. If it doesn’t work, then there’s no loss for you.

Hearing ‘desperate situation’, the woman in red’s eyebrows slanted upwards. An invisible pressure suddenly rolled off from her body.

Lin Ming shrunk backwards. He knew that he had said something wrong, just like a peasant that had insulted an Empress. To say such words to an existence like her, his fate could be imagined. He hastily said, “I’m sorry, I spoke incorrectly.”

“Mm?” Seeing that Lin Ming did not feel distress under her pressure, the woman in red was somewhat surprised. She was a maiden of Divine Phoenix Island and the bloodline of the Vermillion Bird flowed through her. If she didn’t deliberately restrain her aura, those that came closer to her would usually feel a sense of discomfort.

This suppression originated from the depths of her special bloodline. Yet, this young body didn’t even have the least bit reaction, it was really weird. Was it possible that he also had some special bloodline?

“How old are you?” The woman in red asked.

Lin Ming hesitated, and then, he truthfully said, “I’m one month from 16.”

He thought that his cultivation being at the peak Bone Forging stage at this age would surprise the woman in red, but he didn’t think that the women in red‘s eyebrows would only prick up a bit, sizing Lin Ming up once more, not looking too impressed.

Lin Ming ruefully smiled; it seemed that he had thought to highly to himself. In the eyes of this woman in red, his cultivation was only considered good, not stunning. Of course, Qin Xingxuan was half a year younger than him, and she had already reached the early Bone Forging stage a month or two ago. If Qin Xingxuan was his age, it wouldn’t be strange for her to reach the peak Bone Forging stage.

The woman in red said, “Alright. I’ll let you look once. But, when you use your soul force, behave yourself!”

The woman in red’s tone was extremely harsh. To think that she, a master half-step into the Revolving Core realm, would actually agree to such ridiculous demands from a little boy and let him attempt to treat her. She really would be the laughing stock of everyone in the world.

“I understand.”

Lin Ming didn’t even have the courage to randomly scan her body with his soul force. Otherwise, this woman in red would start raging and probably kill him.

As Lin Ming walked over to the woman in red, he was able to clearly smell a delicate fragrance emanating from her body. Although this fragrance smelled very nice, Lin Ming didn’t dare to even breathe for fear that the woman in red would go crazy.

“Well… can you sit down first?”

The woman in red looked at Lin Ming, and then sat down. Although she felt that this young boy had some secrets on him, she had no hope that he would be able to help her.

When the Thunder Flood Dragon had used his final strike, he had poured his life essence and blood into the Thunder Soul. In addition to that, the Thunder Flood Dragon had nourished and refined the Thunder Soul in his body for many millennia. It could be said that the Thunder Soul contained the origin will of the Thunder Flood Dragon, and it was equal to an unthinking avatar of the Thunder Flood Dragon.

Not even a master with Xiantian realm cultivation and thunder-attribute would be able to absorb this Thunder Soul.

The Thunder Soul also had immortal characteristics that refused to be extinguished. If she wanted to extract it without harming herself, she could only ask a Revolving Core Elder of her sect!

Lin Ming wasn’t clear of the mysteries present; otherwise, he would hesitate to expose his secrets in order to risk the danger of absorbing the Thunder Soul. If he managed to arouse the interest of the woman in red, he would be finished if she decided to investigate him.

Lin Ming politely extended his soul force into the woman in red’s body, carefully avoiding any sensitive regions. Quickly, he was able to discern the source of the power of thunder. It was exactly at the woman in red’s heart. Without a doubt, this was where the Thunder Soul was hiding.

The heart was the weak point of a human. If the Thunder Soul was hiding in her heart, it would be extremely troublesome to deal with.

Lin Ming penetrated his soul force into her heart, and he saw a small purple Thunder Flood Dragon roaring and clawing as it made threatening gestures. It constantly generated purple arcs of electricity from its body that constantly seeped into the woman in red’s body.

“This is the Thunder Soul?”

Lin Ming could feel that his Heretical God Seed was becoming very excited; it wanted to devour this Thunder Soul!

“Mm? This Thunder Soul seems to contain a fiery soul… as if it is self-aware. Is this the Thunder Soul, or the Thunder Flood Dragon’s soul?”

Lin Ming hesitated. At this moment, he discovered that there was a faint cage of flames that surrounded the small purple Thunder Flood Dragon, firmly trapping it. The small purple Thunder Flood Dragon continuously attacked the flame cage, biting at the bars in an attempt to tear it open.

This flame cage was a true essence seal that the woman in red had put in place. If it weren’t for this seal, the small purple Thunder Flood Dragons spirit would have already broken into the woman in red’s body, destroying everything recklessly.

Retracting his soul force, Lin Ming moved behind the woman in red. He sat down and put his hand on her back.

This action caused the woman in red to suddenly stiffen. Not in all her years had a man dared to touch her like this. “What are you doing?!”

Lin Ming confidently said, “I’m sucking the Thunder Soul out. My true essence is a thunder-attribute, so I might be able to absorb the Thunder Soul.

The woman in red was disgruntled. “You want to absorb the Thunder Soul with your cultivation? Even an ordinary Thunder Soul would ruin your meridians! This Thunder Soul has the inherent origin will of the Thunder Flood Dragon. Even thunder-attribute masters would be helpless, and you think you are enough? Hurry up and leave, I don’t have time to play with you…”

The woman In red’s words trailed off. To her amazement, she felt that the power of thunder that the small purple Thunder Flood Dragon released was being pulled by an invisible strength towards her back, as if it were being sucked away by the youth’s palm.

The young boy’s hand became extremely hot on her back. With his palm touching her, it was a very strange feeling.

This is…

The woman in red was stunned. Although this was only the power of thunder that was released by the Thunder Soul, it shouldn’t have been easy to absorb. Just how was this young man doing this?

At this moment, something more startling occurred. The woman in red discovered that the small purple Thunder Flood Dragon in her heart was become violently restless, as if it feared something that was approaching. It no longer released the power of thunder. Instead, it put its full force into breaking the flame cage, wanting to escape immediately.

What was going on? What was the Thunder Flood Dragon afraid of?

The woman in red was shocked. Was it because of the youth behind her?

The small purple Thunder Flood Dragon was struggling with all its might, but there was an invisible force that had locked onto it. This force wasn’t too strong, but it contained an immense pressure.

This pressure not only suppressed the Thunder Flood Dragon’s soul, it also suppressed the Thunder Soul itself!

What was acting on the Thunder Flood Dragon’s soul was the blood of the True Dragon. This was bloodline suppression of the Thunder Flood Dragon!

As for what was acting on the Thunder Soul itself, it was the Heretical God Seed’s suppression!

Under this dual suppression, the Thunder Flood Dragon began to violently fear.

Lin Ming’s true essence was nothing compared to the Thunder Flood Dragon. But, this suppression had nothing to do with cultivation at all. This was akin to the law of suppression, not allowing any dissent or rebellion!

Chi chi chi!

The power of thunder was unceasingly siphoned from the small purple Thunder Flood Dragon’s body. The Thunder Flood Dragon grew increasingly anxious and frightened, madly slamming against the flame cage. This caused the woman in red to bite her lips, her complexion becoming increasingly pale. She had used almost all of her true essence to maintain the flame cage, and her body was extremely weak at the moment.

However, at this time, Lin Ming didn’t feel much better. Although the Heretical God Seed and the True Dragon’s blood were dually pressuring the Thunder Soul, Lin Ming’s cultivation was just too weak. This was like a little child that took two peerless treasure swords to deal with a wild tiger.

Lin Ming was able to absorb the power of thunder. This power of thunder was a trivial product of the Thunder Soul, but yet, it placed a huge pressure on Lin Ming. He was almost unable to suppress it.

“Hah!”

Lin Ming shut off his soul force and removed his right hand from the woman in red. He gasped for breath in great, heaving gulps. At this time, his right palm was completely covered in sweat.

The woman in red turned around, her beautiful pair of eyes blinking at Lin Ming. Her exquisite face was filled with a look of utter disbelief.

She hadn’t imagined that this little boy would actually have a way to move the Thunder Soul. It had even managed to frighten the origin will that the Thunder Flood Dragon had left in the Thunder Soul! Although this boy’s cultivation was only at the Bone Forging stage, it was the truth.

Of course, if the woman in red knew that during the battle on the summit of Thundercrash Mountain, the reason that the Thunder Flood Dragon had been suddenly distracted and allowed her to injure it was because this young boy had inexplicably gave out a fearsome True Dragon’s roar, she would be shocked speechless.

Chapter 216 – Controlling The Thunder Soul

Seeing such a powerful Thunder Soul delicacy appear in front of it, the Heretical God Seed began to make excited wuwu sounds.

Woosh!

The Heretical God Seed took the initiative to launch an attack for the first time. It swooped down, like an eagle swooping down towards its prey, towards the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder. It charged directly into the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder’s body.

The Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder began to shake, tumbling around in a frenzy as it roared. But no matter how much the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder struggled, it was unable to throw the Heretical God Seed off.

The power of thunder surged around like a turbulent tide that threatened to drown him. Lin Ming’s already severely wounded body once again suffered the baptism of wild and violent energy. But, with the aid of the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’ which he had cultivated for a long time to quench his meridians, and the perfectly circulating true essence from when he entered the ethereal martial intent state that moistened his meridians, he was able to get by with no damage to his meridians.

Clenching his teeth, Lin Ming held back the excruciating pain that came from his meridians. He forced the manic and rapid power of thunder into the Magnetic Birth Stone. If he didn’t have the Magnetic Birth Stone, his body might have already exploded by now.

In this war, Lin Ming’s advantages lay in the Heretical God Seed, which could hold the power of thunder, and the bloodline suppression of the True Dragon. He also had Mu Qianyu assisting him, as well as the Magnetic Birth Stone. But, the advantage of the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was that it had terrifying power. If it burst out with its full strength, Lin Ming’s body would be as fragile as a piece of paper in front of it!

All of Lin Ming’s muscles tensed. His clothes had already been burnt by the thunder fire and turned to ashes. The handsome symmetrical muscles of his body were oozing out large beads of sweat.

Mu Qianyu was waiting on the side, carefully watching Lin Ming. Once Lin Ming encountered a life threatening situation, she would immediately make her move. However, what caused her to be incomparably surprised was that Lin Ming was actually persisting through everything. From the beginning, because Lin Ming couldn’t withstand the sudden attacks of the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, his meridians had nearly been broken. But now, it was as if he slowly found a way to deal with the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, and the confrontation of energies in his body was beginning to stabilize.

“If he can sustain this state, he really might succeed…”  Mu Qianyu took a deep breath. It was the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, an existence that even a Xiantian powerhouse would be able to handle barely. Yet, he was only a little Bone Forging martial artist. If he actually managed to absorb it, what kind of concept would that be?

“What’s so special about his body?” Mu Qianyu muttered, as a surge of mixed emotions fluctuated through her heart. She remembered when Lin Ming had let out a low roar that had even caused her own bloodline to tremble in fear!

She had the bloodline of a Saint Beast, this wasn’t possible unless Lin Ming had the bloodline of a legendary God Beast.

“Impossible. It’s impossible for there to be a God Beast’s bloodline.” Mu Qianyu muttered as she denied this dreamy speculation. As a Saintess of Divine Phoenix Island, she had some knowledge of God Beasts. Such existences did not exist in the lower realms. Even in the upper realms, there was only a pitiful number of God Beast’s. There were even some species of God Beasts where only a single one of them existed.

However, no matter what she thought, there was something unusual about his body. His body must have undergone some sort of awakening…

“Is it the bloodline of a Flood Dragon?” If that’s the case… ” Mu Qianyu pursed her lips, she was perplexed.

Time passed second by second, minute by minute. Lin Ming was struggling to persist. Although the Heretical God Seed had locked the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder up, the power of thunder still escaped. In order for him to withstand it, his true essence was gradually being exhausted. Even if he opened the Heretical God Force, the situation wouldn’t change.

But at this moment, Lin Ming suddenly felt a cool feeling on his lips, as if something incomparably soft was touching him. He opened his eyes to see that Mu Qianyu had pinched a Bloodstone Pill with her slender fingers and was putting it in his mouth. That icy cold touch was Mu Qianyu’s finger’s moving along Lin Ming’s lips.

The Bloodstone Pill came at too prompt a time. Lin Ming swallowed it, and the Bloodstone Pill turned into a warm power that spread throughout his body, nourishing his meridians that were on their final legs.

In Lin Ming’s heart, the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was continuously being compressed, and the Heretical God Seed was becoming brighter and shinier. The Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was reduced to an inch in size, when suddenly, there was a long sound, and a scarlet dragon shot out of the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder’s body, angrily rushing towards Lin Ming’s heart.

“This is… the blood essence left behind in the Thunder Soul by the Thunder Flood Dragon?”

Lin Ming had just reacted, when the Magic Cube suddenly awoke from its slumber. An invisible force locked onto the blood essence, covering it, and dragged it directly into the Magic Cube.

The scarlet Flood Dragon crazily struggled to free itself, but in the face of this implacable force, its struggles were to no avail!

In a flash, the scarlet Flood Dragon was dragged into the Magic Cube, completely vanishing. There wasn’t even a single ripple to indicate anything was different.

Lin Ming was stunned. The Thunder Flood Dragon’s blood essence, which he had expected to expend a great deal of effort to control, was actually so easily and simply dealt with.

After the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder had lost the support of the Thunder Flood Dragon’s bloodline, it immediately calmed, becoming very sluggish. As for the Heretical God Seed, because it had devoured so much power of thunder from the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, it was actually much more active and robust than before.

Lin Ming’s mind moved, and he began to try controlling the rampaging violent purple thunder in his meridians. But, the purple thunder was simply too savage and fierce, it wouldn’t listen to his directions.

After failing to escape several times in a row, the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was finally and completely engulfed by the Heretical God Seed. Suddenly, the purple thunder instantly calmed down, and began to follow Lin Ming’s will, circling its way through his meridians.

He finally controlled the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder!

Lin Ming felt cheerful and ecstatic. At this moment, he discovered that dim purple lines had appeared on the surface of the steel needle Thunder Soul that was quietly suspended in the Heretical God Seed. On closer inspection, these small purple lines of light were actually the purple Flood Dragon, baring its teeth and claws!

This steel needle that was engraved with the Thunder Flood Dragon was the latest evolution of Lin Ming’s Thunder Soul!

He did it, he finally did it! After suffering through so much pain, his efforts hadn’t been in vain!

Lin Ming’s mind suddenly relaxed. He only felt a blinding dizziness in his mind, and then, he lost consciousness.

After an average person relaxed from such a high intensity state and deep psychological stress, they would find it easy to faint. Not to mention Lin Ming had experienced inhuman torture for such a long time. His soul force and true essence consumption had reached the limit; he was far too tired.

Mu Qianyu was sitting beside Lin Ming, and saw him faint. She put out a hand to grab hold of him, slowly laying him down on top of a straw mat.

She silently observed the young boy’s quiet and peaceful sleeping expression. She thought back to a day ago when he had been focused on cooking the barbecue and boiling the soup, and she remembered how he had used the barbecue to con the Vermillion Bird into exchanging a feather. Thinking this, the corners of her lips unconsciously formed into a beautiful smile.

What sort of person was he? There were simply too many mysteries and riddles contained in him.

First, he had climbed to the summit of Thundercrash Mountain by himself. Then, he had broken into the Flood Dragon’s cave and stole the Magnetic Birth Stone. With just his trivial Bone Forging cultivation, he had managed to help expel the Thunder Soul that was in her body. Now, he had absorbed a Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder that even Xiantian masters had to be careful of. At such a young age, he could control thunder.

These days, everything he did sound ridiculous and impossible. Even she, who had seen countless talents, geniuses, sages, hermits, and others, could not help but have a very intense curiosity towards Lin Ming.

If she didn’t have her own matters to deal with, she thought of quietly following Lin Ming back to his country, and having a good look at his parents and where he grew up.

“Mm? Why would I have such strange thoughts…?” Shaking her head, Mu Qianyu tossed this thought away. She took a red cloak out of her spatial ring and covered Lin Ming with it. Her movements were very light, in fear that she would disturb his rest.

“Now that he’s fallen asleep… I want to… explore his body to see what secrets he has…” Mu Qianyu was startled as this thought suddenly emerged in her heart.

To use soul force to penetrate someone’s body was an extremely uncouth and frivolously naughty behavior. Because soul force could penetrate clothing easily, it was no different than seeing someone naked and exposed.

Of course, if a martial artist was conscious, they could easily use true essence to form a barrier to shield their body and preventing others from peeping at them.

But now, Lin Ming was completely defenseless as he lay down on the straw mat. He had fallen into a deep sleep, and any barriers on his body had been lifted. Also, he was completely unconscious; he wouldn’t know if others were probing him.

“How could I have such a shameful idea? If he knew about this, I won’t have the face to appear in public anymore.”

Mu Qianyu’s gorgeous face blushed. To take advantage of someone being unconscious to snoop through them was absolutely despicable and contemptible behavior. It wasn’t anything that a regal and moderate woman like herself would ever, ever do.

But, an intense curiosity burned within her. It was like an enticing devil that lingered inside her heart; it wouldn’t go away until she did something.

“When he had expelled the Thunder Soul, he also investigated me with his soul force. This can be considered returning the favor… ” Mu Qianyu muttered as she grasped at a reason to console herself.

Finally, she could not resist the temptation. As she blushed, she extended her soul force into Lin Ming’s body.

Lin Ming had no guard up. Mu Qianyu first investigated Lin Ming’s heart. Except for the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder’s Thunder Soul, she didn’t notice anything strange except a strange mark on Lin Ming’s heart. But, this mark didn’t seem too special or different. After a fruitless probe, she continued forth.

She probed his viscera, and almost didn’t find anything too strange. As she considered whether or not to continue her search, at this moment, Lin Ming’s finger suddenly moved.

Mu Qianyu jumped up, startled. She quickly withdrew her soul force, and respectfully sat down.

“He woke up so fast?”

Mu Qianyu found that it was only Lin Ming’s finger that had moved. He hadn’t really woken up. She let out a breath of relief, and no longer dared to examine his body.

As she quietly waited, a day passed.

When Lin Ming woke up, it was dark.

Opening his eyes, he saw Mu Qianyu stirring up a fire. She was heating the leftover soup up from last night.

“You’re awake.”

Mu Qianyu smiled.

“Mm. How long have I been sleeping?” Lin Ming sat up. He examined his body, and he was suddenly filled with surprise. His meridians had been opened up, and they were completely connected!

The purple thunder that had flooded Lin Ming’s meridians and almost destroyed his body, had unexpectedly opened his meridians up.

The sign that a martial artist had stepped into the Pulse Condensation period was when their meridians were opened! But, to open up one’s meridians and connect them was an extremely difficult task. It was the bottleneck of the Bone Forging stage to the Pulse Condensation period. Because of this bottleneck, there were many martial artists that were trapped beneath for their entire lives!

But to Lin Ming, this bottleneck didn’t exist. As long as he poured enough true essence into his meridians, he could immediately break into the Pulse Condensation period.

Mu Qianyu also discovered the change in Lin Ming’s body. “You’ve broken through to the Pulse Condensation period?”

Chapter 220 – Suppression Of Absolute Power

“I haven’t done anything… other than use a Dreamland Pearl to lay down this illusionary world. It should give me enough time to play with you a bit. Don’t uselessly struggle; it’s pathetic. This enchantment can only be broken by a Xiantian realm master. All perception is isolated within. No matter what goes on in here, whether it be some earth-shaking power or wondrous ability, anyone looking in from the outside will only see a calm scene. If Mister Ouyang does not believe me, then feel free to try breaking the enchantment.”

Lin Ming slowly said as he crossed his arms across his chest. A cold smile flit across his features.

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, Ouyang Dihua’s heart sank. Only a Xiantian master could break through this enchantment? Was it really such a great treasure? Just where did he get this pearl from?

Such a pearl would be incomparably precious even within the Seven Profound Valleys!

Once again, Ouyang Dihua guessed that Lin Ming had an unknown yet fantastical background!

“What do you want?” Ouyang Dihua no longer doubted Lin Ming’s power. If he dared to come here today, then he must have had the absolute assurance to kill him.

“You ask what I want? Mister Ouyang, I can’t believe that you would ask such a silly question. Isn’t it obvious? I’m going to kill you. This illusionary world was laid down in order to avoid the attention of others, so that I can turn your corpse into ashes without a single trace.”

“Good! Very good! I want to see just how you will kill me!” Ouyang Dihua roared, true essence erupting from his body like a geyser. His body short forwards like an arrow, but what he aimed at was not Lin Ming, but the void of the illusionary world.

“Life Severing Dead Bone Blade!”

Ouyang Dihua’s entire body stirred with true essence. The long sword in his hand turned to a bone white color, and deep chilly wind ran out from it, followed by countless sad cries and mournful wails; it really made one feel a scalp-tingling creepiness!

This move had been used by Zhang Guanyu when he and Lin Ming had dueled each other. This was the most ruthless ability of the ‘Divine Acacia Powers’ first layer. But seeing it now, Zhang Guanyu’s version could not hold a candle to Ouyang Dihuas’.

“A wise move, unfortunately, useless.” Lin Ming hadn’t even moved. He simply watched as Ouyang Dihua’s sword struck against the edge of the illusionary world.

Zhi—!!!

A blinding white light sprung forth, and Ouyang Dihua’s sword emitted an ear-tingling grating sound, as if it were about to break. Ouyang Dihua gave a stuffy cough as his body trembled. The web between his fingers had cracked apart, dripping red with blood.

However, the invisible enchantment was motionless and intact, without even the least bit of damage.

It couldn’t be broken! It really couldn’t be broken!

Ouyang Dihua’s heart sank. Even though he felt as if a mountain had fallen upon him, the illusionary world wasn’t affected in the least! Perhaps what Lin Ming said was true, and only a Xiantian master could break apart this illusionary world!

“I already said that only a Xiantian master can break it. Otherwise, it is impossible to forcibly open this enchantment. Ouyang Dihua, accept your fate. Today is the day you die!”

Lin Ming touched his spatial ring, and the nine feet nine inch Heavy Profound Soft Spear appeared in his right hand, gripped horizontally. The silver-white spear edge gleamed a deadly radiance, overflowing with coldness!

Ouyang Dihua turned towards Lin Ming, his eyes glimmering with dark and decisive color. “Lin Ming, don’t force me! You think that you can win against me!? If I damage my cultivation to bring forth the Soul Severing Sword, don’t think that you will survive!

As Ouyang Dihua said this, his body suddenly shuddered. With a loud shout, all of his silk clothing was completely torn asunder, revealing a purple gold colored flexible armor. This was shockingly a high-grade human-step treasure armor!

As Ouyang Dihua flourished his sword, the blade began to resound with a mournful howls, as if countless grieving spirits were bitterly sealed within the sword.

Lin Ming chuckled and said, “You truly are worthy of being the nephew of a Seven Profound Valley’s Elder. You have a flexible armor protecting you, a long sword as a weapon, both of which are high-grade human-step treasures. Even I covet such treasures. That being the case, then I will kindly accept them.”

“You are reckless!” Ouyang Dihua’s feet pressed against the ground. He tread so hard that even the floor beneath him ruptured as he disappeared into a series of afterimages, his sword piercing straight towards Lin Ming’s throat!

“Fleeting Blade!”

Ouyang Dihua’s sword sliced through space, the air grated with a loud explosive sound. The momentum behind this strike was terrifying!

However, Lin Ming only laughed. Without using any martial skill, he gripped his spear in both hands and smashed down!

After absorbing the power of vitality in the Sorcerer Pagoda, in addition to the cultivation of ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ in his body, the strength behind his spear had reached a mind-boggling degree.

10,000 jins!!

Bang!

Ouyang Dihua felt as if a mountain had fallen onto him. As spear and sword crossed each other, a massive vibrating strength sent Ouyang Dihua flying backwards as he vomited blood. He felt as if his bones were about to fracture!

“Flow like Silk!” Lin Ming thrust out his spear, and 5000 vibrating true essence filaments formed a spiral that pierced towards Ouyang Dihua’s right shoulder. If this spear struck, then Ouyang Dihua’s right arm would be torn apart!

In this moment of life and death, Ouyang Dihua’s eyes flashed with a sinister color. He immediately drew backwards, and at the same time opened his mouth to spit out two beads towards Lin Ming’s eyes!

“Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead?”

Lin Ming sneered. The Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead that Zhang Guanyu had was given to him by Ouyang Dihua. Lin Ming had already guessed that Ouyang Dihua would secretly mix in Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads in his attacks, but he just didn’t think that the beads were hidden between his lips.

A Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead was best used in a surprise attack. Once the enemy was prepared for it, the effects would be greatly reduced.

“Concept of wind!”

Lin Ming waved his left hand, and a strong wind surged upwards, blowing away the Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads. At the same time, Lin Ming stepped forwards, his body shooting forth like an arrow as he stabbed his spear towards Ouyang Dihua’s belly!

Bang! Bang!

The Thunderbolt Devilfire Bead’s exploded in the sky, but they didn’t even have the slightest effect on the illusionary world enchantment. At this moment, Lin Ming’s long spear had already closed in, and was less than a hundred feet away! With Ouyang Dihua flying backwards in the air, there was no way for him to dodge!

“Lin Ming! I will bet my life against you! Soul Severing Blade!!!” Ouyang Dihua pounded his own chest, spitting out a mouthful of blood. This blood sprayed across the blade of his sword. After absorbing the blood, the originally gleaming silver blade transformed into a strange blood red color. There was a soul piercing scream as a massive red skull struggled out of the sword, as if it had emerged from a sea of crimson blood!

As soon as the skull appeared, it inflated like a balloon. In a short moment, it had already swelled to over ten feet wide. It faced Lin Ming and let loose a maddening howl. For a time, the entire sky was filled with a bone-freezing wind, as if all nearby human blood and flesh would be drained by this giant skull.

After he released this bloody skull, Ouyang Dihua immediately looked faint and lifeless; he could barely stand on his feet. This was the strongest skill in his repertoire – Soul Severing Sword. Once activated, he would lose 20% of his cultivation. He probably wouldn’t recover his vitality even in half a year.

Seeing this massive red skull appear, Lin Ming revealed an expression a surprise. Even though his own blood vitality billowed out into the sky, he still felt a chill from the depths of his soul when faced with this skull; it was as if he were stranded naked within an endless plain of snow in the middle of a great winter storm.

“Die, Lin Ming! Once this Soul Severing Blood Skeleton appears, it will never give up until it has sucked up all the blood essence of its enemies!” Ouyang Dihua hysterically raved. His entire face was a gloomy bright red, as if he had been possessed by a devil.

Seeing this bloody skull roaring towards him, Lin Ming put away the Heavy Profound Soft Spear. He flicked his right hand and a Coiling Dragon steel needle jumped out on his fingertips.

This small steel needle was only two inches long and on it engraved a Purple Flood Dragon. The Flood Dragon wound downwards, encircling the steel needle nine times, no more and no less. Although the Flood Dragon’s body was tiny, every subtle texture and detail contained the fierce and supremely tyrannical expression of the savage Flood Dragon; it was so vivid and vibrant that it appeared, not as an engraving, but instead a true Flood Dragon that had been pinned onto the steel needle.

The bloody skull rushed towards Lin Ming from the front, opening its jaws wide in an attempt to swallow Lin Ming whole! Lin Ming didn’t move; he simply aimed at the big mouth of the bloody skull and flicked his finger.

Whiz!

The Coiling Dragon steel needle transformed into a tiny purple line as it shot towards the blood skull. On one side was a massive blood-colored skull that was over ten feet wide, while on the other a small two-inch long steel needle. Their disproportionate sizes were simply too contrasting!

Puff!

The Coiling Dragon steel needle pierced straight through the bloody skull. A near infinite purple thunder erupted outwards, as a grid of lightning enveloped the entire blood skull.

The thick arcs of sizzling electricity flashed in the air, as the bloody skull let out piercingly shrill howls of pain. It’s body was like a cube of ice that had molten steel poured upon it, rapidly melting!

The greatest fear of ghosts was the power of thunder. If a ghost wished to ascend and attain a Pure Yang body, then they must pass heavenly tribulation. But under the divine judgement of heavenly tribulation, countless spirits and ghosts had been turned to ashes, completely annihilated forever!

Not only that, the Coiling Dragon steel needle in Lin Ming’s hand contained the illustrious Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder. While Ouyang Dihua had released a bloody skull, it wasn’t some amazingly desolate and evil power. Once the two forces collided, the results could be clearly predicted. In only a few shorts breaths, the bloody skull let out one final sorrowful wail, and then completely vanished into nothing!

The thick arcs of purple thunder still scintillated in the air. Lin Ming stretched out his hand, and the Coiling Dragon steel needle instantly returned to his palm, floating there as it slowly revolved. It was as if destroying the blood skull was easier than crushing an ant.

As Ouyang Dihua saw this scene, he was instantly stunned silly. Overcome with bewilderment, he had never dreamed that his ultimate move, which had taken 20% of his cultivation to use, had been so easily put out like a little candle by Lin Ming.

How was this possible!?

Ouyang Dihua’s heart surged with roiling despair and desperation. His hands trembled. The feeling of approaching doom had never been so close before!

“Did I surprise you? With your background as a nephew of a Seven Profound Valley‘s Elder, and also being older than me by 7 years, you are actually being toyed with in the palm of my hand. It really must be hard to accept….”

“In any case, you will not escape death today. Can you tell me who was disguised as Martial House Master Qin? In exchange, I will send you off with a sweet farewell.”

Lin Ming didn’t know if the one who had posed as Qin Ziya was Ouyang Dihua or someone else, so he could only ask him as a test.

Ouyang Dihua’s face twitched. His mouth turned into a scowl as he shouted, “You think I will tell you? Dream on!”

Lin Ming laughed. “Although I really do want to know what other enemies are hiding in the shadows, it doesn’t really matter anyhow. First, I will kill you, letting you suffer to death in the most painful and excruciating way possible.”

Lin Ming extracted the Heavy Profound Soft Spear as he said this. The spear point glimmered with electric light as 5000 vibrating true essence filaments were poured into it.

Ouyang Dihua’s eyes flashed with a ferocious color. “Since you won’t let me live, then die with me!”

Ouyang Dihua swiped his spatial ring, grabbing a handful of Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads.

“We shall perish together!”

Chapter 221 – Killing Ouyang Dihua

Lin Ming’s eyes condensed. He rapidly flicked his finger and the Coiling Dragon steel needle shot out with a whistling sound as it flew forwards like a bolt of lightning. The steel needle sliced through space and cut apart Ouyang Dihua’s hands with an unbelievable speed!

Puff!

Both Ouyang Dihua’s hands were torn to shreds; his wrists were broken in half, spurting blood. With both hands broken, he was sent flying into the sky with his pile of Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads.

“Ah ah ah ah!”

Ouyang Dihua screamed in anguish. Lin Ming coldly snorted and waved his hand. A tornado formed in the air and collected all the Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads.

The swirling wind held the Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads in air; there were at least 20 beads rolling around. As for Ouyang Dihua, he was painfully moaning as he tumbled to the ground.

Both his arms were completely crippled from the elbow down, and his upper arms still flashed with sparks of lightning; they were completely charred black!

Zhang Fengxian felt as the last fires of his hope were died down like fading embers. He was used to wonderful and magnificent scenes, but now, his legs were shaking. Zhang Fengxian had held the position of the Allied Trade Association’s President for many years; he didn’t even remember how many people he had put to death. But now, when faced with his own mortality, he trembled with abject fear.

Often times, the more high-ranking a person was, the more they feared death. Zhang Fengxian was like this. He had held absolute power within his grasp for decades, and his status was one that was venerated and worshipped. He had enjoyed countless wealth, treasure, and beauties. All of these caused him to have an enormous love for life, and an enormous fear of death.

That youth that was floating in air was simply a devil incarnate. He was too powerful. Powerful to the point where he could easily play with them; everything was in the palm of his hands, just like a game of cat and mouse. In front of him, any and all resistance was meaningless.

Lin Ming released his soul force had swept up all the Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads. He faintly smiled, and kindly accepted all of them.

“I already knew you had Thunderbolt Devilfire Beads. Why would I give you the chance to use them?”

Ouyang Dihua was lying prostrate on the ground like a dead dog. With both his arms broken, he could only prop his head on the ground, blood continuously flowing from his mouth. He viciously said, “You….you wait for my uncle’s revenge…..he will make you beg for death!”

Lin Ming slowly landed in front of Ouyang Dihua. He sneered, “Your uncle? Once I erase all evidence, how will he know I killed you? You, a middle Pulse Condensation master, with four bodyguards protecting you. You’ve been drinking in the Headquarters of the Allied Trade Association too. In this case, you will quietly die and disappear forever. Do you still think that your uncle will even suspect me at all? He might even think that this was done by a Xiantian master! Haha!”

The reason that he dared to kill Ouyang Dihua was because he had calculated that no one would ever suspect him.

“I had recorded at the Martial House Registration Office that I would be going adventuring for two months. Now, it’s only been a month and a half. After I kill you, I will wait another half month before I appear again. Who will even think to suspect me? People know that you and I are hostile to each other, but who would know that our conflict has already escalated to the point of killing the other?”

Lin Ming prodded Ouyang Dihua with his spear point. Ouyang Dihua’s face was covered in blood, at this point, he didn’t even look human anymore. Lin Ming calmly took off Ouyang Dihua’s spatial ring and swept it with his soul force. He cheerfully praised, “You truly are worthy of being a nephew of a Seven Profound Valley Elder, your collection is very rich. Thank you, I just happened to be a bit low on funds at the moment.”

As Li Ming said this, he was waving Ouyang Dihua’s own spatial ring in front of his face.

Pah!

Ouyang Dihua seethed in rage as his anger reached a tipping point and he suddenly vomited a mouthful of blood. Most of his body’s meridians were already broken. This wasn’t because he was beaten up, but because he was angered by Lin Ming.

Anger was part of the so called ‘spirit’. As long as one’s spirit was calm and soothed, and their thoughts enjoyable, their cultivation would be double the result with half the effort. On the other hand, if they became angry enough to the point of suffering psychological damage, then this spirit could even damage their meridians!

The more arrogant a person was, the easier it was to use anger to cause them to lose their minds. In ancient times, there were stories of genius advisers that vomited blood and died from anger. Although Ouyang Dihua was still alive, his meridians had been damaged, and this was because of how much he hated Lin Ming.

Looking at Ouyang Dihua’s state, Lin Ming shook his head. It was unlikely that he would get him to say who the one that disguised themselves as Qin Ziya and tried to kill him was. But at this moment, Zhang Fengxian who was hiding in the distance suddenly said, “Young Hero Lin, I know who it was that disguised themselves as Martial House Master Qin to trick you!”

“Mm?” Lin Ming turned around to look at Zhang Fengxian, “You know who?”

The deep murderous aura that emanated from Lin Ming’s eyes was no different from a sharp knife. As soon as Zhang Fengxian was touched by Lin Ming’s sight, his heart shrank and stepped backwards. He gulped, trembling as he said, “I don’t know, but I can make a very close guess.”

“Tell me.”

“I….I can tell you, but I would like to request Young Hero Lin to let me leave!” Zhang Fengxian plopped down with his knees to the ground as he said this. With his status, even when he saw the Emperor of Sky Fortune Kingdom, all he would need to do was bend a bit in a bow. Now, he was compelled by Ouyang Dihua’s miserable state to kneel down. Even the nephew of a Seven Profound Valley Elder had ended up like this, much less him.

It had to be said when a person was pushed up to the wall, their desire to live was terrible; what sort of things wouldn’t they do? How many people were there that were able to face death without fear? Most people, when facing their impending doom, bet everything they had to fight for even the slimmest chance of survival. At that time, things like dignity, honor, and ethics all became a joke.

“Oh? You think that you have the qualifications to speak to me about conditions?” Lin Ming’s voice suddenly dipped into sub-zero temperatures.

Zhang Fengxian hurriedly shook his head. “I do not dare. As long as Young Hero Lin lets me leave alive, then I can give Young Hero Lin one hundred million gold taels! I will force the entire Allied Trade Association to serve Young Hero! As long as Young Hero desires to search for any rare materials, maids, concubines, precious pills, herbs, anything can be made available through my Allied Trade Association! I dare guarantee that my Allied Trade Association has the broadest information network in Sky Fortune Kingdom, not even the Imperial Family can compare!”

One hundred million gold taels?

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. The entire tax revenue of Sky Fortune Kingdom in a year was 20 or 30 million gold taels. This Allied Trade Association was simply obscenely wealthy.

Zhang Fengxian feared that Lin Ming wouldn’t agree. He continued to say, “Young Hero, if you find me untrustworthy, then you keep me hidden somewhere else. With Young Hero’s talent, breaking through to the Xiantian realm is only a matter of time. As soon as Young Hero reaches the Xiantian realm, then my life will be completely within Young Hero’s grasp; I will absolutely never dare to betray you!”

Although Zhang Fengxian’s conditions were very persuasive, letting him leave was simply too great a danger. Lin Ming didn’t want to take such a needless risk. He said, “Don’t talk to me about these things. First, who do you think had disguised themselves as Martial House Master Qin?”

Zhang Fengxian tentatively asked, “Young Hero won’t kill me?”

Lin Ming confidently said, “I won’t kill you.”

Zhang Fengxian’s eyes narrowed. He wanted to have Lin Ming take an oath on his heart of martial arts, but at this time, Lin Ming gave a cold humph and suddenly turned, hitting Ouyang Dihua’s chest with his palm.

Pulse Cutting Palm!

Pah!

Ouyang Dihua’s briefly shook for a moment, and then all of the true essence in his body dissipated like a deflating rubber ball. In a blink of the eye, he had lost all of his martial arts.

Ouyang Dihua weakly fell to the ground, his eyes losing all focus. At this point, he was no different than a corpse.

Lin Ming retracted his palm and coldly said, “Don’t think that you will be able to commit suicide by abandoning your meridians.”

Zhang Fengxian was gripped with fear as he watched from the side. With just a hand, Lin Ming had crippled all of Ouyang Dihua’s martial arts so that he couldn’t even commit suicide. This Lin Ming was simply a demon.

“Well, have you thought it over yet?”

“I’ll talk….I’ll talk.” Zhang Fengxian no longer dared to mention anything concerning Lin Ming making an oath on his heart of martial arts. He was afraid that it would displace Lin Ming, and he would be placed in a position where he wouldn’t even be able to die if he wanted too. “I suspect that the one who disguised himself as Martial House Master Qin is the Seven Profound Martial House Deputy House Master, Bi Luo. He originates from the Mirage Faction and is the best at illusion techniques. Moreover, he has a very good personal friendship with Ouyang Dihua and dislikes Martial House Master Qin. So, it is likely that he was the one who tricked you.”

As the President of the Allied Trade Association, Zhang Fengxian knew a great deal of information; a normal martial artist wouldn’t know who Bi Luo was.

“Bi Luo? I see, so that’s how it was. What’s his cultivation?”

“Probably….middle Houtian realm.”

“Mm…thank you. Now, give me your spatial ring.”

“O…okay.” Zhang Fengxian trembled as he took off his spatial ring. As he handed the ring over to Lin Ming, he suddenly froze. His eyes opened wide open as he looked into Lin Ming’s eyes.

At this time, Lin Ming’s eyes had already become two swirling black vortexes, slowly spinning. They seemed to contain an endless darkness within them, as if they were but an infinite void.

Zhang Fengxian felt as if his own soul was being sucked out; a myriad of chaotic scenes and images emerged from his mind. He saw countless visions of his life. He saw when he was young, he saw when he was old. He saw when he became all-powerful, and when he became a beggar on the streets.

After experiencing countless manifold lives, these countless lives turned into never-ending fragments. All of this revolved within his mind, setting off a violent storm within the world of his spiritual sea. Zhang Fengxian fiercely trembled, and his spirit was shattered into shards. His eyes dilated as if he had lost all reasoning. He had already become an idiot.

But, Lin Ming didn’t stop. He continued to display the Samsara martial intent until Zhang Fengxian’s spiritual sea could no longer be broken down any further; there wasn’t even a hint of a complete thought left in his mind.

Poh!

Zhang Fengxian fell to the ground, his eyes wide as he stared at the sky. The corners of his eyes were bleeding, and he no longer had any pupils; all that was left over were the whites.

Lin Ming’s eyes returned to normal. “If I said that I won’t kill you, then I won’t kill you. I will let you keep your life. You can lie peacefully in bed for the rest of your days.”

He turned to look at Ouyang Dihua. Lin Ming flexed his finger and the Coiling Dragon steel needle jumped onto his fingertips. “Do you have any last words?”

Ouyang Dihua didn’t hear him. He lay down on the ground, motionless.

“Then die.”

The Coiling Dragon steel needle flew forth and penetrated Ouyang Dihua’s body. Soon, there was nothing left of him but ashes.

Lin Ming waved his hand and a cool breeze blew away all the ashes. He carefully absorbed the remaining power of thunder in the air, and put away the two spatial rings and the Dreamland Pearl.

After the Dreamland Pearl was put away, the illusionary world was still able to maintain itself for a bit. This gave Lin Ming enough time to leave.

Large snowflakes fluttered in the winter sky. Lin Ming had already reached the realm of returning to his true self, so he was able to restrain all of the breath within his body. Only a Xiantian realm master would be able to discover his existence.

He easily left the Allied Trade Association’s Headquarters without raising a single alarm.

“Middle Houtian realm, Seven Profound Martial House Deputy House Master Bi Luo….” Lin Ming sneered. In his heart he had already judged Bi Luo.

His sentence was death.

Total Faction Martial Meeting

Chapter 224 – Lin Ming’s Return

Lin Ming’s plan proceeded as he thought. After Ouyang Dihua died, Ouyang Boyan arrived, and the entire Sky Fortune City was overturned, every nook and cranny searched. However, everyone already had a preconceived idea that the one who killed Ouyang Dihua was a Xiantian realm master; Lin Ming was never considered as a suspect.

Even Bi Luo, who knew that there was hostility between Lin Ming and Ouyang Dihua, had never suspected him in the least. After all, Bi Luo knew that even if it were himself who had set up countless various illusions, he would never be able to silently kill Ouyang Dihua.

Thus, Ouyang Dihua’s death became a lingering mystery. Ouyang Boyan searched day and night, but no matter what he did he wasn’t able to find a single clue.

After ten days passed, the Seven Profound Martial House’s Total Faction Assembly Tournament had already begun….

…………..

Heavy snow had been falling on and off in Sky Fortune City for more these last ten days. The large fluffy snowflakes were just like tufts of cotton, thickly sprinkling down and layering upon the floor.

The entire city was blanketed in endless white. Every morning, the government laborers would take to the streets and sweep them clear of snow, but the next day, they would have to begin again, perpetually sweeping.

At the Seven Profound Martial House, the Registration Office deacon, Sun Liang, was buckled down as he fixated on reading a novel. Although it was freezing outside, the room was lit brightly with a brass basin fire. Thick cotton curtains hung on the front door, and the windows were pasted with heavy paper. The entire room was comfortable and warm.

Outside was snow and ice, but inside was just like a warm spring evening. This great atmosphere and comfy feeling was the best environment to read in.

But at this moment, the front door suddenly opened, and a cold wind blew inside. Sun Liang’s interest was disturbed. He looked up, unhappy, and was immediately shocked by what he saw.

This person who came was Lin Ming!

“Junior-apprentice brother Lin? You came back?” Sun Liang quickly placed down his novel, and greeted him with a smile. Sun Liang knew that everyone had a heart, and liked to be flattered.

“Mm. I just finished my adventuring. It’s been almost two months now, so I specifically came to the Registration Office to cancel my record.”

“Junior-apprentice brother Lin is too kind, there was no need to be so polite and especially visit; you could have found someone to pass on a message to me. Junior-apprentice brother Lin came back just in time. You may not know, but the Seven Profound Valley’s Total Faction Assembly Tournament has already begun. These past days, Martial House Master Qin has already begun to select candidates to participate.” As Sun Liang quickly spoke these words, he warmly greeted Lin Ming and graciously poured him a cup of hot tea.

“Mm?” Lin Ming was slightly surprised. As a quasi-core disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House, he naturally knew about the Total Faction Assembly Tournament.

The Seven Profound Valleys set up Seven Profound Martial Houses in the various countries under their control. The first reason was to better control these countries, and the second was to develop talents, and thus increase the overall strength of the Seven Profound Valleys. Every three years, the Total Faction would send out for the most talented Martial House disciples and hold a Martial Meeting.

The Martial Meeting was for all the core disciples of the Martial Houses. Of course, non-core disciples could also participate, as long as they were outstanding talents.

During the Martial Meeting, the core disciples of all the Martial Houses, the talented disciples of the various martial cultivation families, and the geniuses of Seven Profound Valley’s Total Faction would gather to test their mettle in combat.

If they achieved good results, not only would those core disciples be rewarded, but the Martial House Master as well.

The Heaven Opening Pill was an absolute treasure for those peak Houtian realm masters who were trying to attack the Xiantian bottleneck. The materials for the Heaven Opening Pill were difficult to find; the Seven Profound Valleys could only refine a batch every 3 years, and they would only end up with 20 or 30 pills.

Qin Ziya, who had amazing talent and had been with the Seven Profound Martial House for so long, had only obtained one Heaven Opening Pill so far. However, after he took the Heaven Opening Pill, he found that his Zither Heart hadn’t yet reached an exquisite state, so he had failed to make the Xiantian breakthrough.

These past years, Qin Ziya had been roaming the valleys and undergoing deep introspection. Because of this, his Zither Heart had reached the large success stage. Now, he urgently needed a Heaven Opening Pill in order to attempt to break through the Xiantian realm bottleneck.

But the Heaven Opening Pill was only awarded to the first place winner of the Martial Meeting!

Taking first place was easier said than done. The Seven Profound Valleys ruled over 36 countries. In addition to these 36 countries, there were also ancient martial cultivation families, as well as the gifted geniuses of the Total Factions.

However, even if one could not obtain first place, as long as they achieved a good ranking, they would be able to raise their status and gain face; their merits would also be recorded for posterity. Therefore, all the countries’ Martial House Masters would also attend this Martial Meeting, as they all attached a great importance to it.

“I didn’t think the Total Faction Assembly Tournament would begin so soon….”

Lin Ming was thinking about this, when Sun Liang suddenly cried out in surprise, “Junior-apprentice brother Lin…you…your cultivation has already reached the peak of Bone Forging?”

As soon as Sun Liang discovered Lin Ming’s cultivation, his hands trembled and he nearly dropped his teacup. He remembered that the last time Lin Ming had walked in here, he was only at the Altering Muscle stage. Now, after coming back so soon, he had unexpectedly already reached the peak of Bone Forging! This cultivation speed was simply too terrifyingly fast!

Originally, Sun Liang wasn’t very optimistic about Lin Ming going out for an adventure. In his opinion, the experiences he could gain from going adventuring could not compare to the resources that the Seven Profound Martial House provided. But, he had never imagined that after Lin Ming came back, his cultivation had actually increased by a realm and a half!

“Mm. I broke through by luck.” Lin Ming was reluctant to speak more about this issue. He knew that in front of Qin Ziya, he would not be able to conceal his cultivation. Also, it was best not to reveal the fact that he had reached the realm of returning to his origin, otherwise he would find it difficult to explain.

Lucky? How come I don’t have this kind of luck?”

Sun Liang listened to Lin Ming casually toss out an answer, and he had a sudden urge to strangle him. From Altering Muscle to Bone Forging, he had passed a realm and half in less than two months. This luck was really abnormal; it really made one irritated.

“That’s right, when the Seven Profound Decree was handed down, didn’t it state that as long as Junior-apprentice Brother Lin reached the peak of Altering Muscle before 16 years of age, then you will be able to become a core disciple?  Won’t Junior-apprentice Brother Lin already be regarded as a core disciple right now? Sun Liang remembered the uproar that the Seven Profound Decree had caused, and his two eyes began to shine.

“Mm. I should be.”

Sun Liang froze for a moment, not knowing how to respond. Although he knew that it was only a matter of time before Lin Ming became a core disciple, he had actually done so today. To Sun Liang, it felt a bit like being in a dream. Lin Ming was so young and he already achieved such incredible results. Before, he thought it was a bit of an exaggeration when others said Lin Ming would become a Seven Profound Envoy. But now it seemed that this was more than likely!

If he broke through to the Xiantian realm, then he would become a Seven Profound Valley Elder.

Sun Liang took a deep breath. He didn’t dare to imagine any further. His respect towards Lin Ming only increased, and he handed Lin Ming a teacup with both hands stretched. “Junior-apprentice Brother Lin’s cultivation speed is beyond amazing. Maybe this time in the Total Faction Martial Meeting, you will be able to enter the top 50.”

Sun Liang wasn’t underestimating Lin Ming when he mentioned the top 50. The truth was, most of the disciples that participated in the Total Faction Martial Meeting were in their late teens or even 20 years old. Their cultivation levels were almost all at the Pulse Condensation period or above. For the 15 year old Lin Ming, this was just too great a deficit. Facing against martial artists like them, he really suffered a loss.

Moreover, there were simply too many disciples participating in the Total Faction Martial Meeting. The Seven Profound Valleys ruled over 36 countries, and there were also over a dozen ancient martial cultivation families, as well as the most gifted disciples of the Total Factions. Altogether, there were around 5 or 6 hundred people. To stand out within such a crowd of genius talents was not easy.

Lin Ming smiled, not denying anything. He took a sip of hot tea and asked, “You said that Martial House Master Qin had begun selecting people, who has he chosen so far?”

Sun Liang said, “Two days ago, Martial House Master Qin and Martial House Master Sun had already convened all the core disciples together to battle in a great qualifying competition. The competition is already more than halfway over, and three people have qualified to enter the Martial Meeting. The last two candidate spots will be decided after the competition’s results are concluded.

“Oh? Which three people were selected?”

“The three disciples that have been chosen are Qin Xingxuan, Zhou Yu, and Liang Long. The other remaining undecideds are Ling Sen, Ta Ku, Zhao Jifeng, and Jiang Bin.”

“Mm? Ling Sen hasn’t been selected in the first group of people?” Lin Ming was somewhat surprised. Although Ling Sen wasn’t a core disciple, his strength had already reached that of Pulse Condensation period martial artists. Even Qin Xingxuan wasn’t necessarily Ling Sen’s match, so how come he wasn’t chosen?

Sun Liang said, “Martial House Master Qin first chose from the five core disciples, and then he began to consider Ling Sen, and Ta Ku.”

So that’s how it was. Lin Ming finally understood. The Seven Profound Valleys Total Faction Assembly Tournament was focused on the core disciples. Normally non-core disciples wouldn’t be allowed to participate. However, these five core disciples probably weren’t up to Qin Ziya’s standards, so he had pulled in Ling Sen and Ta Ku.

Sun Liang proceeded to say, “Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, since you’ve come back you should hurry and see Martial House Mater Qin. He’s currently at the Martial House’s Profound Martial Palace.”

……………………

To the Seven Profound Martial House Masters of every country, the Total Faction Martial Meeting that occurred every three years was a very important event. Qin Ziya also took this tournament in complete earnest. He had lent Lin Ming his assistance and helped him so much because he hoped that Lin Ming would be able to shine at the Total Faction Martial Meeting. Of course, now, he didn’t hold much hope this time. After all, Lin Ming was too young, and his cultivation was only at the Altering Muscle stage. No matter how great his talent, it was impossible for him to match against those Pulse Condensation period talents that seemed blessed by the will of the heavens.

The age limit for martial artists to participate in the Total Faction Martial Meeting was 22 years old. Since Lin Ming could participate in two more tournaments, Qin Ziya believed that, with Lin Ming’s talent, he would definitely be able to shine in all his radiant glory at the latter Martial Meetings.

But, before Qin Ziya had the time to carry out his plan, Lin Ming had gone missing.

Qin Ziya suspected the one behind this was Ouyang Dihua, but he had no proof to back his suspicions. However, he had never imagined that Ouyang Dihua would perish half a month ago. Not only did he meet his maker, he had also been killed in a very strange manner; he had actually died within the Headquarters of the Allied Trade association, and the several bodyguards close to him hadn’t even noticed anything strange.

As soon as Ouyang Dihua passed away, Ouyang Boyan had rushed to Sky Fortune City. Now, the whole Sky Fortune City was a complete mess; there was chaos and disorder everywhere, and Qin Ziya was constantly miserable.

At this critical junction, the Total Faction Assembly Tournament was about to begin. Because Sky Fortune Kingdom was a second-grade country, they were able to send out five participants.

The Seven Profound Martial House had altogether 5 core disciples.

However, Qin Ziya was unsatisfied and discontent with the strength of these 5 core disciples. Of those five, only Qin Xingxuan had shown some promise. But, her age was simply too young. He feared that she wouldn’t even reach the top 200.

Therefore, his only option had been to also let Ling Sen and Ta Ku participate. The truth was Qin Ziya did not wish to do this, because if he did, the other countries would laugh at his Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House and say that they didn’t have anyone decent. They would ridicule the fact that outer disciples had been chosen to participate in the Total Faction Martial Meeting and claim that they did so only to fill in numbers.

Although Qin Ziya had an easy going temperament and was usually indifferent, that didn’t mean that he didn’t care about anything. Since he became the Martial House Master, he also shouldered the burden of being a Martial House Master. He didn’t wish to see his Martial House being looked down upon by others.

Chapter 225 – Start Of The Qualifiers

Qin Ziya sighed, “This time we really are short on personnel. The last time, Mu Yin was able to enter the top 100, but now he has already passed 22 years of age, and was accepted into the Total Faction. Qin Xingxuan is still too young; she won’t achieve good results. From here on we can only rely on Ling Sen to fill the gap….”

“Mm. What a pity. If Lin Ming were here, then his current strength might have even surpassed Ta Ku.” The man who spoke to Qin Ziya wore blue-clothes, his white-hair tied up in a bun. He looked like a priest, and he was one of the two Deputy House Masters of the Seven Profound Martial House, Sun Youdao.

Sun Youdao was 45 years old when he stepped into the Houtian realm. Presently, he had already been stuck at the Houtian realm for 70 years. Although his cultivation had reached the peak of Houtian realm, Sun Youdao knew that with his talent, there was no way the Total Faction would bestow upon him a Heaven Opening Pill. In any case, the truth was that giving a Heaven Opening Pill to him would simply be a waste. A Heaven Opening Pill wouldn’t even be enough for him to reach the Xiantian realm.

Because he had already accepted the reality of his life, Sun Youdao had always maintained an upbeat and good mentality of things. He was proper, safe, and after becoming Deputy House Master, never engaged in any needless battles. He also maintained a good relationship with Qin Ziya.

Qin Ziya nodded and said, “It’s likely, but unfortunately, Lin Ming is still missing at this time.”

“If he had really gone out adventuring, then I fear that….” Sun Youdao trailed off. He wasn’t really convinced that Lin Ming had gone out adventuring; it simply made no sense. Not to mention all the enemies that he had managed to make, but even if he had no enemies, the experience of being out adventuring in the world wasn’t necessarily that much better than being in the Seven Profound Martial House, where he could have unlimited use of the seven major killing arrays.

Qin Ziya remained silent.

Sun Youdao sighed and said, “Lin Ming was indeed a good seed. If he had continued to grow, then even  though he might not achieve outstanding results at this Total Faction Martial Meeting, he definitely would have been able to get good results. He might not be able to reach the top ten, but he could still have his hopeful aspirations!”

Sun Youdao had just finished speaking, when a sound transmitting talisman burst into flames in the room. Qin Ziya heard the message in the sound transmitting talisman, and instantly shot up.

“What’s going on?” Sun Youdao rarely saw Qin Ziya lose his composure.

“The Martial House Registration Office just sent some news; Lin Ming has come back.”

“Mm?” Sun Youdao was shocked. “This boy, did he really go out adventuring?”

Sun Youdao had just voiced this out when Lin Ming called out from outside the Profound Martial Palace: “Disciple Lin Ming seeks an audience with Martial House Master Qin.”

“Come in!”

The doors of the palace were shoved open, and Lin Ming walked forward, bowing. “Martial House Master Qin, Martial House Master Sun.”

This was the blue-clothed old man that Lin Ming had met several months ago; he was the one that had given him the Heavy Profound Soft Spear.

Qin Ziya began giving Lin Ming a once over, examining him from head to toe. His facial expression even changed a few times, eyes widening and blinking, mouth closing and opening. Qin Ziya was usually calm, but this time he was stunned out of his indifferent and tranquil appearance. “Lin Ming, you reached the peak Bone Forging stage!?”

“Yes, a few days ago I encountered a lucky opportunity and made a breakthrough.

Lin Ming said this lightly, but Qin Ziya’s heart was surging with marvel and wonder. When a martial artist found a fortuitous encounter, it was usually followed by danger. The greater the opportunity, the greater the danger. Just what had Lin Ming experienced in his two months outside? Every martial artist had their own secrets, so Qin Ziya didn’t press this issue.

The blue-clothed old man was also stunned, almost to the point of his beard popping up. When Lin Ming was at the Altering Muscle stage, he was able to defeat the Bone Forging stage Zhang Guanyu. Now he was at the Bone Forging stage, a truly terrifying state! He might even reach the top 50 of the Total Faction Assembly Tournament, or if he did well, even the top 30!

Qin Ziya asked, “Lin Ming, did you really go out adventuring these past two months?”

Lin Ming nodded. Naturally, he did not mention the issue of Ouyang Dihua.

Qin Ziya hesitated, and didn’t ask again. He always thought that something seemed off about this. Lin Ming had suddenly gone out adventuring, and then there was the death of Ouyang Dihua….if Lin Ming’s cultivation weren’t so low where it would be impossible to kill Ouyang Dihua, then Qin Ziya might even suspect that he was related to the incident.

“I may have over thought some things.” Since Lin Ming had answered, Qin Ziya didn’t question him any further. What he wanted to know now was the extent of Lin Ming’s strength.

“Lin Ming, according to the Seven Profound Decree, you are now officially a core disciple of my Seven Profound Martial House. Do you know about this Total Faction Martial Meeting?”

Lin Ming nodded in affirmation, “This disciple knows.”

“Good. For this Total Faction Martial Meeting, we are actually short of two people. We originally decided to select from Ling Sen, Ta Ku, Zhao Jifeng, and Jiang Bin. Now, with you, that makes five people from which we can choose two! You rest well tonight. Tomorrow in the morning, the qualifying martial arts contest will begin. This is a good time for you to duel with Ling Sen and Ta Ku, we’ll have you match against those two. If you win, then the Blue Miracle Pill and Body Spiritual Ichor that was promised previously will also be given to you. Incidentally, Ling Sen had also broken through to the Bone Forging stage half a month ago; you should come prepared.”

Although he knew that Lin Ming would definitely take one of the two spots, Qin Ziya still wanted him to participate in the matches. The first reason was to convince the public, and the second reason was because he wanted to know just how strong Lin Ming had become.

“Oh, I know.” Lin Ming knew that this was no accident. Ling Sen had already paused at the peak Altering Muscle stage for a very long time; it was about time that he made a breakthrough.

Lin Ming was looking forward to this match against Ling Sen. Originally Ling Sen was the goal which Lin Ming had been whole-heartedly pursuing with all his passion. But now, that was all in the past.

…………………………

When news of Lin Ming’s return spread, it was as if it had grown wings, steadily spreading throughout the entire Sky Fortune City.

Most people didn’t have an inkling about anything untoward that happened. They only thought that Lin Ming had really gone out adventuring. There were only a few influential individuals who felt that this was unusual.

Of course, the most shocked one of all had been Bi Luo; Lin Ming was actually still alive!

“This little beast really has the best luck ever!” Bi Luo’s face sank. Because his lasting impression so far was that Ouyang Dihua had died in the hands of a Xiantian master, he did not suspect Lin Ming at all.

“Would he know that other than Ouyang Dihua trying to kill him, there was also me?” As Bi Luo thought this, he became very uneasy. Lin Ming’s rate of growth was simply too quick. In a few years, he might even be able to threaten him.

Bi Luo had thought of telling Ouyang Boyan of the hostility between Ouyang Dihua and Lin Ming, and how they had tried to murder him, but he feared that Ouyang Boyan would fly into a rage and take out his anger on him. As it was, Bi Luo was placed in a dilemma, as if he were walking on eggshells.

……………

The Total Faction Martial Meeting’s qualifying contest was a grand occasion that occurred every three years at the Seven Profound Martial House. The qualifying contest was open to some of the public. As long as one was an aristocrat, had status, or was a disciple of the Seven Profound Martial House, then they could come to observe.

When the first round of core disciples had been chosen, because of the cold weather, the audience was younger and smaller than it was in the past. But this time was different. Now, the entire field was packed with people. Out of them, 90% had come because they heard Lin Ming had returned, and wanted to watch the decisive showdown between Lin Ming and Ling Sen.

In Sky Fortune Kingdom, the two most well-known individuals of the younger generation were Ling Sen and Lin Ming. As for Zhou Yu and Liang Long, they were core disciples of the Martial House, and not many people knew of them. These two originated from the four great martial cultivation families that lived at the edge of Sky Fortune Kingdom. Because they were not people of Sky Fortune Kingdom, most people didn’t care whether they were strong or weak.

Snow was still falling from the sky, but it had greatly lessened from before. The entire Seven Profound Martial House martial stage had been swept clean of snow, and a snow cover was put up to prevent snow from falling around.

Those martial artists with cultivation had no need to fear the cold. But as for those physically weak aristocrats, they wore warm mink silk clothing, drank hot tea on one side and had a burning brazier on the other, so they weren’t feeling the chill either.

Liang Long and Zhou Yu, who had passed the qualifying contest early, were also sitting in the audience as they waited for the start of the matches.

“You think Ling Sen will win or will it be Lin Ming?” Liang Long casually mumbled as he ate pine nuts. In his opinion, the main event of the qualifiers was the showdown between Lin Ming and Ling Sen. As for Zhao Jifeng, Jiang Bin, and Ta Ku, they were a bit less exciting.

Zhou Yu laughed and said, “This is hard to say. When Ling Sen was at the peak of Altering Muscle, he was comparable to a Pulse Condensation period martial artist. As for Lin Ming, when he was at the early Altering Muscle stage, he was able to defeat Zhang Guanyu. Now that both their strengths have increased, this will truly be an absolutely savage and fierce struggle between the two.”

The news of Lin Ming reaching the peak Bone Forging stage hadn’t yet spread. But Zhou Yan had already been informed in advance. Lin Ming was now an official core disciple.

“Jiang Bin and Zhao Jifeng are truly much worse. I’d like to go up on stage and test myself against Lin Ming’s ability.” Liang Long said with a confident grin. He didn’t think his strength was any worse than that of Ling Sen and Lin Ming.

“Mm? The Martial House Master has arrived.” Liang Long put down his pine nuts. At the entrance of the martial stage, a line of people filed in. The one at the front wearing white was Qin Ziya. As the snowflakes fluttered down, none of them touched his body; they simply flew away before getting too close.

Behind Qin Ziya was Martial House Master Sun, and behind him was Lin Ming, Ling Sen, and the rest of the five participants.

Seeing Lin Ming appear, the atmosphere of the entire field began to suddenly boil over. A few months ago, Lin Ming had managed to create miracles over and over again. His accumulated popularity even surpassed that of Qin Xingxuan. To martial artists with commoner backgrounds, his male fans, and his female Linmaniacs, Lin Ming was their absolute idol. He was their rising sun, dazzlingly splendid.

There were many young aristocrat girls who dropped all sense of modesty and bawdily waved at Lin Ming with their handkerchiefs. Due to Lin Ming reappearing after two months of silence, this caused a feeling of intense and infinite anticipation among all the Linmaniacs, like a roiling storm beneath a calm sea.

As the hour approached, more and more people began to arrive on the viewing grounds. Among them was even Bai Jingyun, who had recently left the confines of her home. This had even caused Murong Zi to be surprised. “Big Sister Jingyun, you finally came out! If you stayed in your room any longer then you might start molding.”

Bai Jingyun smiled and said nothing. She inadvertently glanced at the audience, her eyes stopping on Lin Ming for a moment before moving past him.

Bai Jingyun naturally knew of the feud between Ouyang Dihua and Lin Ming. But, common logic and reasoning told her that Ouyang Dihua’s death was committed by a mysterious Xiantian realm master, and had nothing at all to do with Lin Ming. However, she didn’t know why, but somehow she had subconsciously associated Lin Ming with her mysterious Xiantian savior.

“Big Sister Jingyun, who are you looking for?” Murong Zi asked on the side with an impish smile.

“Nothing, I’m just looking around.” Bai Jingyun shook her head and lightly smiled. But, the truth was, her heart wasn’t calm at all.

With a quarter of an hour left until the start of the qualifiers, Crown Prince Yang Lin also appeared. Today, Yang Lin had put on a gown emblazoned with a Kirin. He wore snow boots and straddled a Snow Dragon Horse. He could be described as being in very high-spirits.

When the Crown Prince arrived, there wasn’t an announcement. This was because among those present today, there were many important people; too many to count. There were the heads and elders of large and small aristocratic families, the nobility, marquis, counts, and even two of the Ten Great Generals.

With such a scene, his mere status of a Prince wasn’t as high-profile.

Chapter 230 – Martial Intent Showdown

“I too have long been awaiting this showdown. Ever since you defeated Zhang Cang, I thought I would have to wait several years, but I never imagined this fated day would arrive so soon!”

The first time Ling Sen had begun to pay attention to Lin Ming was when he saw Lin Ming’s duel against Zhang Cang. He had arrived at the scene together with Ta Ku, causing no small stir.

Lin Ming had only entered the Seven Profound Martial House for a trivial month, and yet he was able to defeat the Earth Hall master, Zhang Cang. At that time, Ling Sen had a premonition that he would eventually face Lin Ming one day. To him, this was already a very high evaluation of Lin Ming’s skills. But now looking back, it seemed that he had underestimated Lin Ming by far.

For a quarter of an hour, Lin Ming sat down in meditation, adjusting his condition to the peak even though he hadn’t consumed any of his strength.

With his thoughts completely relaxed, he entered into the ethereal state, waiting for this anticipated match.

The audience was already fidgeting with expectation. This long-awaited battle was a matchup between the fiercest top two young talents of Sky Fortune Kingdom!

This was a rarely seen once in a lifetime grand event. As far as a martial artist was concerned, what could possibly be more exciting?

Although snow was falling from the sky, the burning enthusiasm of the audience seemed hot enough to melt the winter ice.

“Who will win?”

“Who do you think will win?”

“I wonder who will be the number one martial artist among our Sky Fortune Kingdom’s younger generation?”

……

Almost the entire audience was discussing this issue. They each began to express their own views and opinions of the match. There were even some discerning ‘experts’ that were deducing how the fight would progress, even though the match hadn’t even started. Ling Sen and Lin Ming hadn’t yet fought, but already there were a good number of possible versions and outcomes that had been imagined, each of them narrated with a vivid intensity.

These stories were so vibrant and imaginative that if people didn’t know, they might even think that these spittle splashing martial artists had already seen the outcome of Lin Ming and Ling Sen’s match.

This fight would determine who was at the pinnacle of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s younger generation. But, Ling Sen actually thought that his chances of winning weren’t high. Even if he won, he also wouldn’t take the position of the number one youth talent. He was already 21 years old, while Lin Ming was almost 16. This 5 year age gap between them was an insurmountable divide.

These 5 years were the most important and essential years of a martial artist’s life. Five years later, Lin Ming would definitely become a Houtian master.

But at that time, Ling Sen would have only broken through to the Pulse Condensation period.

A quarter hour passed quickly.

Ling Sen was the first to walk onto the martial stage. His pace was steady, calm, and his entire being exuded a murderous aura. The snow that fell towards him was blown away by this aura; not a single snowflake landed on his body.

Lin Ming took out his Heavy Profound Soft Spear. His spear and Ling Sen’s sword were both medium-grade human-step treasures; the weapons were fair and equal.

The two stood 100 feet apart, silently gazing at the other. The surrounding airflow around them was disturbed by their presence, as if an invisible vortex had been summoned. Billowing snow recklessly covered the sky.

“The rules will not be repeated. Match, begin!”

After the referee Elder announced the start of the match, the two of them on stage hadn’t even moved. Lin Ming’s right hand gripped the Heavy Profound Soft Spear outwards, the spear tip slanted towards the ground. Ling Sen had his heavy sword in both hands, the hilt pressed against his chest.

Although they hadn’t moved, the two of them were slowly beginning to gather their momentum.

Ling Sen’s murderous aura was formed from his countless beheadings and massacre of the Ashura Devils within his Ashura martial intent. If a weaker martial artist were to directly confront Ling Sen’s murderous aura, it would be the same as if an average man were standing stark naked in a frozen world of snow and ice. They would only be able to use half of their strength, and those whose minds weren’t as aware, might even be directly struck by dread and forced into defeat without having done anything.

But Lin Ming was the opposite. His imposing and majestic aura was formed by the power of his vitality. The force of his powerful spirit was like a billowing flame that reached the clouds. An ordinary person might not feel anything strange, but if a martial artist that cultivated dark arts of technique involving the usage of evil spirits approached, then they would feel as if they were in a blazing inferno. Any ghosts or demons that drew near would be immediately returned to nothingness.

Ling Sen’s icy cold murderous aura and Lin Ming’s power of vitality engaged in an airborne battle. One was freezing cold and the other was burning hot. As these two forces met, they would battle. Ice would not coexist with fire!

But eventually, Lin Ming’s billowing vitality overcame Ling Sen’s Yin chill. Ling Sen could evenly clearly hear his murderous aura being chipped apart by Lin Ming’s power of vitality.

‘I never thought that someone would be able to suppress my Ashura murderous intent with just the strength of their blood vitality!’

His speed was like a phantom, his body strength was formidable, his true essence was pure and thick, and he also had the support of an overwhelming blood vitality; his endurance was without a doubt terrifying. This Lin Ming was simply versatile in all aspects!

Ling Sen’s expression became more dignified. He instantly converged all of his murderous aura, condensing that murderous essence onto the surface of his body in conjunction with his heavy sword. At that moment, he was like an insurmountable existence in the eyes of all present.

Even the two Great Generals in the audience, who had reached the middle and late Pulse Condensation period, were unable to help but wonder if they could win against Ling Sen if they fought.

For a middle Pulse Condensation period martial artist to not be able to defeat an early Bone Forging stage martial artist. that was simply an unimaginable fantasy.

“Meet my sword!”

As the word ‘sword’ was said, the murderous aura that was concentrated on Ling Sen’s body began to flow into the black heavy sword. This five foot long heavy sword began to emit a piercing cry!

Cha!

It was as if space itself was torn asunder. A peerless sword wind shot forwards like a dark rainbow, piercing towards Lin Ming’s chest.

The entire area was swept up by the aftermath of the sword wind; even the tiles cracked and exploded under the pressure. Countless broken stones that were crushed by true essence was thrown into the wind. From afar, Ling Sen’s blade was like a missile that left the ground shattered in its path; it was simply unstoppable.

“Flood Dragon Goes to Sea!”

Lin Ming gave a loud shout and 5000 vibrating true essence filaments erupted outwards. Towards the surging tide of true essence that rolled towards him, the Heavy Profound Soft Spear was like a silver Flood Dragon, thrusting forwards with a grandiose momentum!

Bang!

The powerful impact formed a shockwave that was visible to the naked eye. The loose floor tiles were all sent flying backwards, and all the snow in a radius of a hundred meters was swept clean. The savage true essence continued to flood outwards. Being met with this rush of true essence, even a Flesh Training or Viscera Training martial artist felt as if they were mere leaves in a storm; they could be blown away at any moment!

Fortunately, the important personages in the audience had master bodyguards protecting them. A true essence shield was put up, guarding them from the aftermath of the true essence collision.

Peng peng peng peng peng peng!

After Ling Sen made his first move, he no longer stopped; following up his first strike with a series of attacks. The heavy sword carried an epic majesty as thick true essence congealed into each sword strike. Every strike contained an immense potential, as if a mountain were crashing down!

Lin Ming unhurriedly and calmly revolved the True Primal Chaos Formula to the limit. He steadily blocked each strike, slowly retreating backwards. But no matter how calm his expression was, every time he took a blow the stage behind him would explode, sending everyone watching into alarm!

Lin Ming took a step back after every strike and every time he stepped backwards, the stage tiles would explode into pieces. Then, Ling Sen’s sword wind would lift up all these fragments, before throwing them off the stage. In just a few moments of time, the entire stage had become very unseemly.

“This is too terrifying. Just the true essence that is scattered from their strikes already carried such destructive power. If one were to face them head-on in a fight, how could anyone possibly resist?” There were some martial artists, that believed they were strong, watching the battle on stage. As they saw the match unfold, they were gradually filled with abject depression. They had been cultivating for several dozens of years, but yet there was such a big difference between them and the two youths on stage.

“Ling Sen’s strength is at least equal to a normal middle Pulse Condensation period martial artist. He might even be able to compete with the late Pulse Condensation period!” After the masters present made some comparisons, they couldn’t help but draw this conclusion.

For someone with an early Bone Forging cultivation to cross over an entire realm and surpass someone at the middle Pulse Condensation period was simply incredible.

Bai Jingyun listened to the arguments occurring around her and silently gazed at Lin Ming’s figure, her expression complex.

Lin Ming, what cards do you hold in your hands? Just what is the limit of your power?

The battle on stage was becoming increasingly intense. True essence collided in the air causing deafening explosions, as if they were in the middle of a roiling spring thunderstorm.

However, during the fight, Lin Ming’s face wasn’t flushed; his heartbeat was normal. His blood vitality was vigorous, and his breath was long, he inhaled like a snake and exhaled like bellows. In such a calm state, a single breath was enough to let him fight for an incense stick of time.

But Ling Sen had slightly less stamina.

“Slaughter Aura!”

Ling Sen gave a loud shout, and his Slaughter Domain broke forth. This was a specialized domain attack that he developed using the Ashura martial intent! When he had faced Zhao Jifeng, Ling Sen’s sword hadn’t even touched his opponent’s body. This was because he had used the Slaughter Domain to defeat his enemy!

Huooo!

In that moment, Lin Ming’s surroundings instantly changed. The audience vanished, all became quiet, and the stage under his feet disappeared; he arrived in a completely new and strange world.

The world was cast in a dim bleak gray. The sky overhead was coloured in a dull beige tones. Endless rocky outcroppings dotted the world, and behind these rocks were hiding countless Ashura Devils.

Between the giant rocks, there were bottomless pits that seemed to lead into an abyss, exuding a limitless yin cold. Ghosts constantly crawled out from this abyss. Their expressions were ferocious, and they hungrily gazed at Lin Ming with their empty eyes, trembling with greed and desire for human life.

This extremely cold feeling was like a freezing wind that could drill its way into a person’s soul. Even though Lin Ming had exuberant blood vitality, in such an environment, he still felt as if he were being pushed down upon.

Ashura?

So this is the Ashura martial intent attack!

A martial intent wasn’t only used in cultivation; some could also be used offensively. It all depended on a martial artist’s utilization and comprehension, but also the inherent quality of the martial intent.

This Ashura martial intent was a martial intent that cultivated battle!

From this aspect, it was superior to even Lin Ming’s ethereal martial intent.

However, Lin Ming didn’t only possess the ethereal martial intent.

Lin Ming gave a cold snort, and both of his eyes turned into swirling black vortexes. Two rotating storms appeared. With Lin Ming’s eyes as the center, they indiscriminately swept out!

Wu wu wu wu wu!

The countless devils emitted heart piercing screams. However, they were unable to resist the pulling force of the tornado and were swept inside the vortex, shredded into fragments!

The gray rocks they hid behind disintegrated under the power of the vortexes; even space itself began to crack under the immense pressure.

“These are only Ashura Devils formed by a martial intent; how can it be equal the hell found within the life and death smelting trial?”

Lin Ming let loose a resonant roar.

Peng!

With a bang, the dark world collapsed!

The countless illusionary fragments were all swept into the giant swirling black vortex and completely vanished into oblivion.

Lin Ming’s Samsara martial intent was comprehended after experiencing the world of 100 Samsaras. In terms of illusion attacks, how could Ling Sen possibly compare!?

Lin Ming appeared back on the familiar martial stage. Across him, Ling Sen  gave a stuff cough and kneeled down onto the stage, supporting himself with his heavy sword, his face pale.

The audience was baffled. They only saw Lin Ming pause for a moment, and then Ling Sen fell to his knees as if he had been heavily struck. In this period of time, Lin Ming’s spear hadn’t even touched Ling Sen.

Just what was going on?

Chapter 233 – Earth-Step Treasure

Liang Long thought that Lin Ming and Ling Sen were freakish enough. Even if they couldn’t obtain first place, he assumed that it would still be a piece of cake for them to reach the top 20 or 30. For himself, making the top 100 was already a great honor he could return home with. But now it looked like out of all these hundreds of people, he was one of the worst.

If he ranked lower than 400 or 500, it would be a deep shame. How could he explain it once he returned home?

Liang Long hadn’t even spoken again when the next words of Qin Ziya caused his heart to sink to the bottom of the ocean. Qin Ziya said, “The Total Faction’s Martial Meeting will be held at the Seven Profound Valleys’ Profound Sky Mountain Range. Before the Martial Meeting starts, there will be a checkpoint barrier; at least 60% of participants will be eliminated. Only those that pass through will have the qualifications to enter the Profound Sky Mountains.”

“60%?” Liang Long’s mouth fell open. Did that mean he wouldn’t even have the chance to pass through the mountain gate?

If he went to the Total Faction Martial Meeting and couldn’t even pass through the door, then that would be an absolute family shame that even his grandma would feel!

If this news spread throughout the family, then where would he have face to see anyone? Wouldn’t he just become the family joke? Liang Long was known as the future head of the Liang Family, there were many people who were jealous of his position. If he became a joke, then all sorts of baseless rumors would be spread!

As he turned around to look at Zhou Yu, he saw that Zhou Yu was also forcing a smile. Even Zhou Yu was worrying about whether or not he would pass through the gate.

The family head always said that there was a heaven above the heavens, and there were always people that stood above others. Now he finally understood that let alone him, there were even monsters that were stronger than Qin Xingxuan.

“Martial House Master, this…”

“What’s the matter?”

Liang Long wanted to say the he wished to abstain from the meeting. Since he couldn’t even pass through the gate, there was no point in going just to shame himself. But seeing Qin Ziya’s eyes sweep past him, Liang Long felt his mind numb and his body go cold. He could only gulp and change his words. “When do we leave?”

“We will go early tomorrow morning. You will go back and prepare. Tomorrow, we will take the Heavenly Wind Eagles to get there. Do you have any other questions?”

Lin Ming was silent for a moment, and then he said, “Martial House Master Qin, I have a question.”

“Mm? Ask.”

“What is the prize?”

As soon as this question was asked, Liang Long and Zhou Yu both shrank their necks. They had both been worrying about how to pass through the mountain gate and not lose face after returning to their family in shame, but Lin Ming had actually opened his big mouth and asked what the prize would be. This was really the difference in their positions, their thoughts were just too different.

Qin Ziya gave Lin Ming an appreciative look and said, “The reward for first place is a Heaven Opening Pill! However, you won’t immediately receive this Heaven Opening Pill. First you must officially join the Seven Profound Valleys and then reach the peak Houtian realm. Afterwards it will be given to you. I won’t go into unnecessary details about how valuable the Heaven Opening Pill is.”

“Besides the Heaven Opening Pill, there are also some low-grade Earth-step treasures. There are offensive treasures and defensive treasures of all sorts. Second through fifth place will not receive a Heaven Opening Pill, but they will be rewarded with a low-grade Earth-step treasure. Sixth through tenth place will receive a Sky Spirit Pill, which is also a top-quality medicinal pill. As for eleventh through thirtieth place, they will receive a high-grade human-step treasure and an Earth Spirit Pill…”

Lin Ming’s mind stirred as soon as he heard ‘Earth-step treasure’. “They have many different types of treasure? Do they have a spear?”

Qin Ziya smiled and said, “Your weapon simply takes advantages of others. A spear’s value is several times that of other weapons of the same step. Still, you can rest assured that the Seven Profound Valleys has been established for many years, and they have a deep heritage; naturally, they will have a spear!

Earth-step treasure…

Lin Ming clenched his fists.

Qin Ziya saw Lin Ming’s enthusiastic look and couldn’t help musing to himself. This boy won’t make first place. Although Lin Ming is strong, reaching first place is just too distant a goal. There are many middle Pulse Condensation, late Pulse Condensation, and even peak Pulse Condensation masters. How could a peak Bone Forging martial artist ever take first place?

What Qin Ziya didn’t know was that ever since Lin Ming had met Mu Qianyu, in Lin Ming’s eyes, these so called ‘talents’ of the Seven Profound Valleys weren’t even worth mentioning.

Mu Qianyu reached Pulse Condensation at 15, Houtian at 17, Xiantian at 22, extreme Xiantian at 26, and now at 27 she was a half-step into the Revolving Dan realm.

At 22 years of age, talents of the Seven Profound Valleys were just beginning to attempt their breakthrough to the Houtian Realm, but Mu Qianyu had already stepped into the Xiantian realm!

This difference was simply like cloud and mud!

If he couldn’t defeat these professed talent of the Seven Profound Valleys, then what was the point in reaching for the peak of martial arts?

………………………..

Seven hundred thousand miles away, Seven Profound Valleys.

The tens of thousands of miles of the Profound Sky Mountains were just like a towering black dragon. In the center of the Seven Profound territory of the Profound Sky Mountains was the Absolute Sword Peak. This mountain peak was 60,000 feet high and incredibly steep. The cliffs in all directions were almost vertical; it was as if the entire Absolute Sword Peak was made of 60,000 feet high sharp swords, piercing the heavens!

This Absolute Sword Peak was the center of the Seven Profound Valleys’ Sword Faction. With the Absolute Sword Peak as the center, there were also 12 surrounding smaller peaks that circled around like a constellation.

In the thick high clouds there was a majestic and grand main hall. The outside of the main hall was layered with hundreds of feet of blue stone tiles. In the middle of these tiles was a massive 200 foot sword that stabbed the ground.

Although this giant sword was just a carved statue, it was entirely made of darksteel and weighed hundreds of thousands of jins. If there really was a giant capable of pulling this sword up from the ground, it could truly be used for slaughtering one’s enemies.

Under this great sword, the Sword Faction Sovereign stood there with his hands crossed behind his back. He was looking at an 18 or 19 year old youth in front of him. His eyebrows were slanted up like scimitars and his aura was impressive.

“During the last Martial Meeting, you were defeated by the Acacia Faction’s Ouyang Ming. Now, after three years, Ouyang Ming has already reached the peak of Pulse Condensation. He will be your greatest opponent.”

The youth was silent for a moment, then he said, “Ouyang Ming is not my greatest opponent.”

“Mm? Then who will you take as your opponent?”

“My greatest opponent is only myself!” As the young man said this, his eyes shone with brilliance, “If during this Martial Meeting I can’t even defeat the talents of a third-grade sect, what is the point of me thinking of climbing to the peak of swordsmanship?”

Though he and Lin Ming were separated by several hundred thousand miles, words similar to those that were said by Lin Ming slowly came from this young man’s lips.

“Haha! Well said! You are truly my son! Then during this Martial Meeting I will only have one expectation – you will win first place!”

“Yes, Father!”

………………….

At the same time, just a hundred miles away at the main peak of the Acacia Faction, there was another young man around 20 years old that was looking down on the cloudy mountains, as if he was disdaining everything beneath him.

This young man was the one mentioned by the Sword Faction youth, Ouyang Ming.

“Ming’er, you are the most splendidly talented disciple that has come from the Acacia Faction in the last 100 years. This is the last Martial Meeting you can participate in before you are too old. I hope that you will be able to attain first place!”

“Yes, Mother.”

Behind Ouyang Ming was a beautiful woman. This elegant lady was none other than Ouyang Ming’s mother. Although she was already over 50 years old, her appearance was no different to a young girl in her twenties.

“This time I am destined to be first place. I had actually hoped that Su Ran hadn’t surpassed the age limit; I was hoping to have a match against him. This is such a pity!”

The age limit for the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction disciples to participate in the Martial Meeting was 20 years, two years less than the disciples from outside. This was the last time that Ouyang Ming would be able to participate in the Total Faction Martial Meeting.

“Achieving first place is good enough. As for the battle between you and Su Ran, you must win, otherwise it will frustrate your spirit.”

“I understand, Mother.”

“Also, do not lower your guard and underestimate others. The Zither Faction’s Qin Wuxin’s cultivation has reached the peak of Pulse Condensation. Although the Zither Faction doesn’t have many disciples, their skills and abilities are the most difficult to handle. There is also the Refiner Faction’s Han Yanluo. The Refiner Faction Sovereign has paid a great price in order to force a Flame Essence into Han Yanluo’s body using a special method. This man cannot be looked down upon!”

“I know, Mother.”

Although the Seven Factions of the Seven Profound Valleys were united together due to common interests, there was still infighting among them. They constantly struggled for power, treasure, resources, talent, pills, manuals, and other things…

Sometimes there were conflicts that escalated to the point of fighting. In regards to this, even the Seven Profound Valleys’ Valley Master couldn’t do anything. If it wasn’t for the fact that the Valley Master had excellent cultivation and also the backing of the Ancestor, then there would be no one that even cared about him.

The Seven Profound Valleys had many worries, and these things weren’t necessarily unsolvable, they just had to be changed to a certain extent. For instance, the assignment of resources in the Seven Profound Valleys must have a method to distribute resources.

200 years ago, the old Valley Master decreed that every three years there would be a Total Faction Martial Meeting. The overall assignment of resources would be given out according to results of the disciples, then, nobody could oppose it.

Therefore the Seven Factions consumed a massive amount of resources and took great care in order to raise the ultimate direct disciple and use them to aim for the first place of the Total Faction Martial Meeting.

The direct disciple was chosen from the most talented individuals of the younger generation, and then unlimited resources were poured into them. The Sovereign would personally aid in their cultivation, and they would receive any sort of core cultivation method or ability they desired.

For the last 200 years, almost all of the first place titles of the Total Faction Martial Meeting were taken by a direct disciple of the Seven Factions. There were only a few exceptions, but those were also caused by other disciples of the Total Faction.

As for disciples outside of the Seven Profound Valleys, they had never achieved first place. Let alone first place, they hadn’t even reached the top 10. To the disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys, those so-called talents that came from the 36 countries and second-grade martial families were nothing more than country bumpkins. At most they would be slightly stronger than a janitor who swept the floor.

The direct disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys had only ever considered each other as their opponents. They hadn’t even deigned to consider the disciples that were from the outside.

……………………..

Sky Fortune Kingdom was 200,000 miles away from the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction. It would take over a dozen days to get there, even riding a Heavenly Wind Eagle.

Qin Ziya led a line of people to the Seven Profound Martial House’s departure station. There were already a row of Heavenly Wind Eagles waiting there, and not only that, but they were of the finest quality. Their flying speed would be much quicker than an ordinary Heavenly Wind Eagle.

“Let’s go.”

As soon as Qin Ziya waved his hand, Lin Ming leapt onto a Heavenly Wind Eagle. With a keening screech, the Heavenly Wind Eagle shot into the sky, a billowing cloud of snow following in its wake.

The cold wind whistled in one’s ears. In a few breaths, the Heavenly Wind Eagles had already risen a thousand feet into the sky. If one leaned over to look, they could see the endless earth carpeted by a pure white blanket. This snowy-white extended all the way to the ends of the horizon. The touching scene gave birth to a desolate heroic feeling in one’s heart.

Because the Heavenly Wind Eagle was so fast, the snowflakes that struck the face were just like blades. Lin Ming put up a shield of true essence around himself, blocking the wind and snow.

The Heavenly Wind Eagle flew faster and faster, a clarion cry sounded out like a joyous song, echoing between the ends of heaven and earth…

Chapter 234 – Profound Sky City

The Seven Profound Valleys Total Faction was located within the Profound Sky Mountain Range. The Profound Sky Mountain Range didn’t belong to any country; it had a very special status within the 36 countries in the Seven Profound territory.

The Profound Sky Mountain Range’s tallest peak was 60,000 feet high. The mountain itself contained a massive amount of profound iron ore, so the entire mountain was a deep black iron color all over. The mountain had sparse vegetation, was rocky, and had extremely dangerous and steep cliffs. It was unknown why, but the entire mountain exuded a thick a baleful aura that caused those watching to feel unease. An average person climbing the mountain would feel very suppressed, and even if a martial artist were to pass by this place, they would attempt to take a winding detour around.

At the foot of the Profound Sky Mountain Range was a giant city. The walls of the city were 50 feet high and stretched for hundreds of miles.

This city was named Profound Sky City, and this was where the Total Faction Martial Meeting was held every three years.

There was a city-wide flying ban for hundreds of miles around Profound Sky City. Lin Ming saw this magnificent city rising from afar as a line of people swooped down from their Heavenly Wind Eagles and walked towards Profound Sky City on foot.

Along the way there were many fellow martial artists coming and going. Most of the martial artists’ cultivations were at the Altering Muscle stage or above; with their movement abilities, they were able to cover the hundred miles in only a quarter of an hour.

Outside the city gate of Profound Sky City was a team of guards that kept watch. Seeing the cultivation of these guards, Lin Ming let out a breath, they were actually all Bone Forging martial artists. The captain of that group of guards was impressively at the peak of Bone Forging.

The Seven Profound Valleys was truly worthy of being called a large sect. if a peak Bone Forging martial artist went to the Sky Fortune Kingdom, they could become a well-known and respected commander in the army. But in the Seven profound Valleys, these Bone Forging martial artists were only gate guards.

Many martial artists rushed to the Seven Profound Valleys because of their esteemed reputation. The Profound Sky Mountains contained an incomparably rich and thick heaven and earth origin energy. This was the reason the guards would rather live here. For instance, some people would rather live in the capital city and work hard labor as opposed to living in the countryside and finding a wife and having children. As long as they stayed in the capital city, they would have the hope of breaking through. But if they lived in a small country, then they might live their entire lives as a mere commander and never enter into the Pulse Condensation period.

The Profound Sky City’s gate was gigantic, but there were too many people trying to enter the city, it seemed very crowded. Particularly because the Total Faction Martial Meeting was occurring, there were many people that accompanied the core disciples.

To enter the city cost 10 gold taels. This high entry fee caused many of the low-level martial artists and common folk to shrink back, discouraged by the price.

Once Lin Ming paid the gold fee to enter the city, he discovered that over 90% of the residents of Profound Sky City were martial artists. Even the random peddler who hawked his wares on the street, or the waiters serving outside restaurants were martial artists. Although their cultivation was only at the first or second stage of Body Transformation, these people, if they went to Sky Fortune City, could live as a well-to-do servant or retainer in a respected family, while also having a high income and good reputation.

As the group walked by, Lin Ming saw all sorts of various treasures being sold. There was a pill shop and inscription symbol shops everywhere. If these shops were casually placed in Sky Fortune City, they would be on the scale of the Hundred Treasures Pavilions. What they sold would be considered incredibly valuable items that a common martial artist would never be able to afford even if they added up all of their savings.

All of this caused Lin Ming to sigh with emotion. If one lived at a different location, then their experience was also different. If he didn’t reach his current strength, then he would never have come to Profound Sky City in his entire life and seen such scenes.

Zhou Yu and Liang Long also noticed these shops. They drooled over many of the items inside; there were many treasures that were difficult to purchase in Sky Fortune Kingdom, or might not even be sold.

Qin Ziya sensed what was on everyone’s mind. He waited until they reached the inn, and then he told everyone, “You can go anywhere you want now. Come back to the inn before it’s dark, and try not to cause a ruckus anywhere.”

“Okay.” Zhou Yu and Liang Long were very happy at this news. They left first together, there were many shops that they wanted to go check out.

Lin Ming had wanted to stay in the inn and calmly cultivate, but Qin Xingxuan suddenly tugged on his sleeve and said, “Lin Ming, don’t you want to take a stroll around? This is my first time coming to Profound Sky City, I want to have a look around…”

This was considered an implicit invitation from Qin Xingxuan. Lin Ming naturally wouldn’t decline such an invitation. He laughed and said with a smile, “This is also good. How about we go together?”

“Okay!” As soon as she heard this, Qin Xingxuan’s features lit up with a smile; it was otherworldly and enchanting, the epitome of beauty and elegance.

After the two of them walked away, Sun Youdao sighed and said, “Ahh, it’s nice to be young. Those two cute little kids are just a match made in heaven. I really hope they end up together.”

Qin Ziya heard Sun Youdao’s thoughts and only smiled, not saying anything. If these two were content with the current status quo, then ending up together would be very easy. But, if they both had the determination and resolve to pursue the peak of martial arts, then he was afraid that they would have to separate in the future.

………………………….

The two youths freely strolled around the city. Qin Xingxuan bought many things. She bought jewelery, some precious fabrics to weave into beautiful dresses, unique souvenirs, hand crafted items, and other little trinkets and things like this.

The merchandise of Profound Sky City was valuable, there were even some items that required true essence stones to buy. For instance, Qin Xingxuan bought a dress, but because there was Sky Worm Silk woven into the fabric, giving it protection against fire and water, the price was a true essence stone.

Luckily, Qin Xingxuan was the daughter of a rich family. If it were a normal martial artist, they would never be willing to buy a piece of clothing for 1000 gold taels. This was half the price of a treasure.

As they walked around, they suddenly saw a restaurant with a pleasant atmosphere. This restaurant was called Desert Flower Hall. There was a signboard in front of the restaurant that listed out some signature dishes which caught Lin Ming’s eye.

The recipes here actually contained the meat of fourth-level vicious beasts.

It had to be known that a fourth-level vicious beast was equal to a Houtian realm master. In the Sky Fortune Kingdom, this power was considered the pinnacle. Even if Lin Ming were to encounter a fourth-level vicious beast, he would usually run away.

A fourth-level vicious beast’s body was simply a treasure. There were many parts that could be used to refine pills and elixirs. But placed here, it was actually food that was prepared in a restaurant. If this was so, then just how outrageously expensive would the food be?

“We’ve been in a hurry for the last few days, so all we’ve eaten is dry food and cured meats. Since we came here, let’s take a look inside.” Lin Ming said.  Since he had grown up in a restaurant, he had special feelings towards them. Since he came to Profound Sky City, he definitely needed to sample the best restaurant here.

Qin Xingxuan read the signboard. She hesitated and said, “Here… is very expensive…”

If in the past Lin Ming had heard that Qin Xingxuan would feel timid about going into a restaurant due to price, then he would think it was simply a joke. But looking at this restaurant, it wouldn’t be strange if the food it prepared with fourth-level vicious beasts cost around 20 or 30 pure true essence stones. 20 or 30 true essence stones was equal to 20 to 30 thousand gold taels. That was a price equivalent to a medium-grade human-step treasure; even Qin Xingxuan would feel a bit distressed by this cost.

After Lin Ming had looted Ouyang Dihua and Zhang Fengxian, he could be said to be filthy rich; he naturally didn’t care about costs like this. He smiled and said, “During my adventure, I found a small treasure site and gained some true essence stones. Let me treat you.”

“But……”

Before Qin Xingxuan could say any more, Lin Ming had already pulled her hand and entered into Desert Flower Hall.

When they found a tasteful corner of the restaurant to sit down in, the waiter took out two menus and handed them to them. Qin Xingxuan glanced over the prices and was secretly mind-boggled. Every dish on the menu was priced in true essence stones. The cheapest dish cost 2 true essence stones.

“If I eat the food here can I become immortal?” Qin Xingxuan excoriated in her heart. Coming here, she had brought 80,000 gold taels. This money was meant to buy pills and treasures. If she spend a quarter of it on food, then that would be hilarious.

“What are your specialties here?” Lin Ming asked after he glanced over the menu. If he was eating at a famous restaurant, then he naturally must eat the best and most well-known dishes.

The water’s smiling face blossomed at hearing this. He said, “We have many specialties. For instance, we have keel soup made from the marrow of a fourth-level vicious beast with a Horned Dragon’s bloodline, and also brewed with several dozen different sorts of precious herbs. The taste is mellow and the soup is smooth. After drinking, it can help consolidate true essence and positively affect the body. The keel soup is 25 true essence stones.

25 true essence stones? 25,000 gold? This was simply robbery!

Qin Xingxuan let out a breath. Although she didn’t feel like it was worth the price, she didn’t display any different expression in front of the waiter.

The waiter smiled and said, “Young master, young lady, I can see with just a glance that you are talented juniors of a large aristocratic martial family. If a martial artist cultivates every day, it is easy to overtax one’s body. If one doesn’t supplement their body with food, then later it will be very difficult to reach the Xiantian realm.

A mere waiter with a cultivation at the Third Stage of Body Transformation opened his mouth and spoke about breaking through to the Xiantian realm. This sort of vision could be considered pretty grand. Desert Flower Hall probably didn’t often entertain many true Xiantian realm masters.

“Then I’ll take a pot of the keel soup, and a few side dishes, two bowls of spirit valley rice, and a pot of green tea.”

Even if Lin Ming was rich, he would only occasionally partake in such a luxurious feast. If he ate like this too often, even he wouldn’t be able to afford it.

The dishes soon came. The keel soup was a lustrous pearl-white, and was as thick as milk. Just looking at it made one’s appetite rise.

As Qin Xingxuan saw this keel soup arrive, she first served Lin Ming a big bowl, and then scooped one for herself. The creamy thick soup within the crystal jade bowl appeared just like a work of art.

Looking at this small bowl of soup, Qin Xingxuan self-deprecatingly said, “This small bowl is two or three true essence stones. It’s enough for me to spend for half a month. I’ll have to thoroughly taste it and see if it’s any different.”

Qin Xingxuan picked up the clear jade bowl and took a small sip. After feeling the soup slide past her lips, it quickly turned into a warm stream that flowed into her stomach. There seemed to be a faint trace of origin energy that flowed into her meridians, slowly and gently tempering the meridians within her body.

Although this origin energy was very weak, it was incomparably pure!

Pills had pill toxins. If one ate them, they could increase one’s cultivation. But, it would cause their true essence to become impure and they would need to expend energy in order to refine it out. But this keel soup, although it contained traces of origin energy, was very smooth and gentle. If one drank this long-term, it would consolidate one’s true essence and give a miraculous strengthening effect on the meridians. And the best part was that there were no side effects.

Qin Xingxuan was shocked. There might not be any effect with just one or two bowls, but what if one were to drink it all the time, would it accumulate?

After she tasted the spirit valley rice, she found that it had equally good effects. Even the pot of green tea contained a rich wood-based origin energy, and was extremely refreshing. After drinking it, the soul force within her spiritual sea seemed to have been subtly supplemented.

“How is it?” Lin Ming asked Qin Xingxuan as he put down his chopsticks.

Qin Xingxuan’s beautiful eyebrows furrowed for a bit as she pondered the aftertaste. She sighed and said, “No wonder their food is more expensive than our treasure. If you ate this every day then even without practice you could still break through to the Pulse Condensation period…”

Chapter 238 – Jiang Lanjian

“That kid may be considered invincible underneath the Pulse Condensation period, but once he meets a true Pulse Condensation talent, anything he does will be useless.” The black-clothed martial artist casually said. His name was Jiang Lanjian, and he was a direct descendent of the Sword Faction Founder Jiang Yu. In addition, he was also the second genius direct disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys’ Sword Faction, just underneath Jiang Baoyun.

Jiang Lanjian’s cultivation was already at the peak Pulse Condensation period. With such strength, he was considered among the best disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys.

“My sword wind has already reached the higher echelons; there is nothing that I cannot cut to nihility. Whether it is obsession, life, heart demons, which also includes soul attacks, or even the power of thunder, there is nothing my sword cannot pierce. Even if that boy was at the same cultivation level as me, he still wouldn’t be my match!

“After all, soul attacks simply aren’t the correct path. At first you will have wonderful results and your strength will rapidly grow, but once you reach a higher realm, they simply become weak. If you put in too much effort, it will instead be a limiter placed on your future strength and potential.”

Jiang Lanjian calmly commented as he quietly drank his wine, pointing out the details to the purple-clothed person. The purple-clothed person laughed. He knew that Jiang Lanjian had an extremely broad vision of the world, and there was nothing wrong with his review of abilities, styles, cultivations and so on. Even the Sword Faction Sovereign praised his judgement.

“How can the disciples of the 36 countries possibly compare with you? Even if they advance to the top 100, that can already be considered their greatest glory. If they luck their way into the top 50, that can be considered the highest praise to their ancestors. As for soul attacks, they certainly aren’t the proper path, but it is still better than those unorthodox methods.”

Jiang Lanjian no longer spoke. Towards the 36 countries, if they had a decent ability, it was better than nothing – even if it didn’t follow the proper path.

“Let’s go, the Acacia Faction hates being shown up the most. Now that Ouyang Ziyun has suffered so much this time, his big brother Ouyang Zifeng will surely take revenge for him. This young boy has gotten himself into no small amount of trouble.”

………..

While Lin Ming was fighting Ouyang Ziyun, Long Yun had already drank up some Bloodstone Milk to recover his blood vitality. He had recovered just in time to see Lin Ming defeating Ouyang Ziyun.

After finding out that Lin Ming came from Sky Fortune Kingdom, Long Yun was filled with emotion. The 16 martial cultivation families had also had a certain conceit and arrogance, because they had abundant resources and their own independent heritage. As for Long Yun, he was an outstanding genius of the Long Family, yet today, he had actually fallen far behind a young talent from the Sky Fortune Kingdom. Not only that, but what Long Yun was most unable to accept was that Lin Ming’s cultivation was lower than his.

“Thank you. I am Long Yun, a disciple of the 31st generation of the Long Family.” Long Yun stepped forwards, cupping his fists together in thanks.

The ancient martial cultivation families would often introduce themselves by stating which generation they stemmed from. This was also a way for these martial families to show off their heritage. For many martial artists, in order to not delay their cultivation, they would marry and have children at 30 or 40 years of age. If a family could have 31 generations of disciples, that meant they had to at least have a millennium of history.

“I am Lin Ming from Sky Fortune Kingdom.” Lin Ming politely stated his own name, then went to sit back in his own seat. Qin Xingxuan was waiting there and kindly handed Lin Ming a big bowl of keel soup. To her, Lin Ming’s victory was a natural matter. Not counting Lin Ming, even Ling Sen would have easily defeated that Ouyang Ziyun.

Long Yun also noticed that Qin Xingxuan was at the middle Bone Forging stage. This cultivation – in contrast with her young and incomparably beautiful appearance – immediately took him by surprise.

This young girl was obviously 15 or 16 years old, and yet she had such a high cultivation. Did she also have a high talent?

If she didn’t have some fortuitous encounter, then she was probably a sixth-grade martial talent.

Was she also from the Sky Fortune Kingdom? When did the Sky Fortune kingdom have so many talents?

The several people behind Long Yun also noticed Qin Xingxuan. For the past few months that Lin Ming had wandered in the Southern Wilderness, he had already grown up. His skin had tanned, his features became sharper, and his presence contained a dark edge. It wouldn’t be too much even if someone thought he was 17 years old. But as for Qin Xingxuan, she had a very sweet and young appearance. When they were the same age as Qin Xingxuan, their cultivations were only at the Altering Muscle stage.

Especially the young girl behind Long Yun. After she saw Qin Xingxuan, a deep feeling of inferiority and unworthiness emerged in her heart. After all, when two girls met, they compared not just their strength and talent, but even their looks.

Having lost in every aspect, the young girl could only give a heavy sigh. If she knew earlier, then she wouldn’t have come.

Long Yun hid his shock and sent a friendly smile towards Qin Xingxuan. Perhaps in five years, this young girl would become infamous throughout all 36 countries.

Seeing Long Yun smile at her, Qin Xingxuan only politely nodded her head.

Since Long Yun had no intention of staying, he quickly bid farewell.

“Brother Lin, if you go to Huoluo Nation, you can come visit my Long Family. My Long Family lives at the edge of Huoluo Nation, at Flower Spirit Mountain. Well then, goodbye.”

“Farewell.”

……………………………

Several hours later, Seven Profound Valleys Acacia Faction –

The mountain peak where the Acacia Faction was stationed was lush with perennial flowers and plants, as if it were a glorious spring morning. This was because the founder of the Acacia Faction, Ouyang Xun, had paid a steep price in order to set up a massive array formation at the peak of the Acacia Faction and prevent the cold mountain air from entering. Because of this, the entire mountain peak was green all year round.

Of course, because of this array formation, over 10,000 pure true essence stones were consumed every year. In a small country, this amount would already have been enough to bankrupt a great family.

As one walked up to the peak of the Acacia Faction, not only did they see gorgeous flowers, but there were also superb and exquisite women roaming around. This sight was simply beautiful to behold.

The faction within the Seven Profound Valleys with the most women was not the Zither Faction, who primarily took in female disciples, but the Acacia Faction.

For every male disciple of the Acacia Faction, there would be three or four female companions.

Some of these women were coerced, but most of them had voluntarily come. The cultivation method of the Acacia Faction had a greater benefit for the men, but if applied properly, would also benefit the women. Because of this, there were some fourth-grade talents who hadn’t been able to join the Seven Profound Valleys as disciples, who would rather enter the Acacia Faction and cultivate the ‘Divine Acacia Power’. With the assistance of the Acacia Faction, they hoped they would step into the Pulse Condensation period, or even the Houtian realm, before their looks began to wither from age.

If they could do this, they would have dozens of extra years of life, and they would be able to remain at the most beautiful point of their lives. To those beautiful women, this was a fatal temptation. Among them there were even many women who came from distinguished families of the 36 countries; their statuses weren’t much different compared to Bai Jingyun or Murong Zi’s positions in Sky Fortune Kingdom. If Bai Jingyun hadn’t preferred to die rather than join Ouyang Dihua, she would have entered here and also have become a companion in these halls.

At a gathering in the mountains, there was a group of female cultivators that had come together. They were celebrating the fact that they had just stepped into the Pulse Condensation period and attained several dozen years of youth. Most of them were in their mid-twenties; this was the time in a woman’s life when they were at their most mesmerizing and enchanting. Because they had good maintenance of their looks, and took a variety of pills, their skin was tender and moist like water. They looked no different from a young girl in her teens.

But as they were celebrating, they were surprised to see several Acacia Faction disciples hurriedly carrying someone up the mountain. This person was pale and his whole body was twitching, just as if he were an epileptic.

“That twitching person is probably… is that Ouyang Ziyun?” A woman recognized Ouyang Ziyun. There were a handful of promising future disciples that the female cultivators gave special attention towards. After all, if they cultivated with these geniuses, they would obtain more resources. If they took care of them, they might even obtain miracle medicines that would help them break through to the Pulse Condensation period. To these women, pill toxins were something that never entered their thoughts. As long as they entered the Pulse Condensation period, they had no problem, even if their combat prowess was horrible.

“It’s really Ouyang Ziyun. Heavens, how did he come to look like that?” Another woman covered up her mouth. Recently things seemed to have been occurring at the Acacia Faction. Just a while ago an Elder’s nephew, Ouyang Dihua, had been killed. And now, Ouyang Ziyun had become like this.

As they spoke, a middle-aged man and a youth came soaring down from the mountain. Apparently they had received a message in advance and had come down to receive them.

As soon as the middle-aged man saw Ouyang Ziyun’s pitiful appearance, his soul force swept out and he immediately understood his condition. After he reluctantly summoned the Purple Flame Bone Lance, he was attacked. The following backlash from the attack had turned him into this. It would take him at least half a month to recover.

Like this, he could not participate in the Total Faction Martial Meeting. This would be a large blow to Ouyang Ziyun. The middle-aged man frowned and asked, “What happened?”

This middle-aged man was Ouyang Ziyun’s father, Ouyang Wenzong. He was a Xiantian elder of the Acacia Faction. In the Acacia Faction, around 70% of the elders had the surname of Ouyang. This was because they were the descendants of the Acacia Faction Founder, Ouyang Xun. As they had a solid foundation already established, they were able to obtain more resources. Also, because their inherited talent was better than other disciples, the chances of them breaking into the Xiantian realm were quite high.

The several low-level Acacia Faction disciples were compelled by Ouyang Wenzong’s forceful aura, and immediately felt a heavy sense of pressure. They didn’t dare to say anything false, and reported what had happened with quivering lips.

As the middle-aged man heard the several people tell their story, his eyes flashed. “An expert soul attack user, but also has some ability to control thunder. He is able to instantly defeat any martial artist at his cultivation, and is invincible under the Pulse Condensation period?”

The three Acacia Faction disciples were only trying to shift the blame onto someone else, thus they had branded Lin Ming as brilliant and mysterious, giving him the title of ‘invincible under the Pulse Condensation period’. In their opinion, Ouyang Ziyun was already someone with only a rare rival underneath the Pulse Condensation period. If Lin Ming could defeat Ouyang Ziyun in an instant, then saying invincible underneath the Pulse Condensation period wasn’t an exaggeration.

“Humph. This world is so big, and yet he dares to call himself invincible underneath the Pulse Condensation period?” The youth snorted, obviously thinking otherwise. This youth was Ouyang Ziyun’s older brother, Ouyang Zifeng, and his cultivation was at the late Pulse Condensation period.

“Those martial artists that can use soul attacks are completely worthless against martial artists that are stronger. I will defeat him on the Martial Meeting stage, and make him pay a great price for what he’s done.”

“Mm. But only as far as the rules allow, don’t try to be provocative.” Ouyang Wenzong also wanted to have Ouyang Zifeng give some payback for his youngest son, otherwise it would frustrate Ouyang Ziyun’s heart and affect his future cultivation.

“Father, don’t worry. I understand.”

………………………..

On the fifth day since Qin Ziya and his team arrived at Profound Sky City, the Total Faction Martial Meeting began. The 520 disciples of the 36 countries within the Seven Profound territory, the 16 martial cultivation families, as well as the Seven Profound Valleys Total Faction, converged at the Profound Sky Mountain Range and waited to enter the entrance.

With so many young talents gathered, Lin Ming was inconspicuous in the crowd. Although he had aroused a lot of interest in Desert Flower Hall a few days ago, compared to the middle Pulse Condensation or late Pulse Condensation talents, he was only a little genius worth paying attention to, unworthy of being the cause of widespread discussion amongst everyone.

Chapter 246 – Hope

“Instructor, what sort of news is worth 36 true essence stones to send? Is it a combat report from the frontline battlefield?” The youth who asked came from a military family. In his opinion, only a combat report of Sky Fortune Kingdom was worth spending 36 true essence stones on. After all, victory or defeat in war was related to the destiny of a nation.”

The middle-aged instructor shook his head and said, “A frontline combat report wouldn’t use a sound transmission array. Our Seven Profound Martial House isn’t a messenger for Sky Fortune Kingdom.”

A sound transmission array formation that could pass a message through several hundred thousand miles wasn’t something that could simply be created on a whim. Not even Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Imperial Palace could hope to ever construct something like this.

“Then what sort of news is being sent?” The young boys and girls eyes were filled with curiosity. They were at the age where they were intensely inquisitive into all things.

“This transmission array will send a victory report from the Total Faction Martial Meeting. It will be sent tonight,” The middle-aged instructor replied.

“Mm….Total Faction Martial Meeting?” Most disciples face were filled with befuddlement; none of them knew what that was. After all, the common person was rarely exposed to such a high-level existence. Even the Seven Profound Valleys that stood behind the Seven Profound Martial House was an incomparably vague concept. They simply didn’t know just how strong the Seven Profound Valleys actually were.

“The Seven Profound Valleys set up a Total Faction Martial Meeting and gathered the talents of all the countries together to compare their strengths.” Although the middle-aged instructor knew that this wouldn’t make much sense to these new disciples nor did it matter to them, he still patiently explained it.

“Oh? The geniuses of all the countries gather together?” As a youth heard this, his eyes suddenly shone. He was the first place candidate of this time’s entrance examination – the freshman disciple named Huayu. Huayu also came from a large, respected family, and at 15 years old, his cultivation was at the Viscera Training stage; his strength as quite alright. When the middle-aged teacher had said that the talents of all the countries would gather together, Huayu felt incomparably enthusiastic, burning with fighting spirit. He said, “Instructor, when can I participate? What rank would I be able to get?”

The middle-aged instructor didn’t know whether to laugh or to cry. He said, “You can’t go….”

“Why?” Huayu felt as if he had been slapped. He was the number one candidate in the Seven Profound Martial House entrance examination. He could be considered the most talented young martial artist of Sky Fortune Kingdom within the last half year. With such a proud and worthy title, how could he not even participate?

The middle-aged instructor sighed with poignancy. This youth was merely a superior fourth-grade talent. Only if he was an inestimable surprise like Ling Sen or Lin Ming would he ever be able to reach the level needed to contact the Total Faction.

He didn’t want to ruin to the youths self-confidence, so he tried a different tactic. “Do you see that well-dressed man in the robe near the transmission array?”

“Mm? I see.” Huayu turned his head and saw in man in a brocaded robe. He was sitting in a mahogany chair near the altar and was looking a bit anxious at the moment.

“He is the current dynasty’s Crown Prince. News from the Total Faction Martial Meeting will only arrive during the evening, yet it is only noon and he’s waiting here. Do you know what this means?”

“What? Crown Prince!?”

“His Highness the Crown Prince!? He is the current dynasty’s Crown Prince!?”

All of the youths gasped in complete and utter surprise, their eyes wide with incredulity as if they couldn’t believe their eyes. To the common people, the Crown Prince was a legendary figure they had only ever heard about.

The Crown Prince was waiting here even though the news came in the evening. Not only that, but the price of the transmission array was 36 pure true essence stones. All of these implied just how important this news was!

This also meant that this unknown Total Faction Martial Meeting had an extraordinary significance!

The middle-aged instructor let out a sigh. He didn’t envy these heavenly favored talents when there was the grand stage where countless talents that were above them reigned; that was the true world. Casually choosing any one of these talents was like taking a small rock front a giant mountain of stones.

“Do you understand now? This Total Faction Martial Meeting is grander than you can imagine. All of the talents, geniuses and young heroes from all the countries and numerous martial families will gather in the Seven Profound Valley’s Total Faction. It is simply impossible for you to stand on that stage! Let alone you, even the core disciples of the Martial House cannot. There are many inferior fifth-grade talents and medium fifth-grade talents that have no hope of going.”

“Not even a medium fifth-grade talent has a chance?” Huayu was shocked. To say it more directly, he was only a superior fourth-grade talent. A fifth-grade talent was only born once a decade in the entire Sky Fortune Kingdom. In his opinion, this kind of existence would simply be a son of god.

“But….since this tournament is so important, then how come we’ve never heard of it?” Huayu asked the question that all the other new disciples were wondering. If this Martial Meeting were truly so grand, how come no one had ever heard of it before?

The middle-aged instructor explained, “That is because, in all these years, this Martial Meeting had held no significance for our Sky Fortune Kingdom. Every three years, the Seven Profound Martial House will send out 5 disciples to participate in this tournament. However, usually four out of the five sent would come from the four martial families that live on the edge of Sky Fortune Kingdom. Every so often, even all five of them would come from the four martial families, and our Sky Fortune Kingdom would have no share in participating.”

“I had said that even a medium fifth-grade talent may not necessarily participate in the Martial Meeting. It’s the same for the other countries and martial families too. Our Sky Fortune Kingdom only produces a fifth-grade talent every 10 years. They do have a large chance of participating, but….”

The middle-aged instructor paused here, and shook his head before continuing, “That is only in terms of filling the quota of people that we send. Actually, there is a mountain gate trial that most cannot even pass, and they are eliminated from the Martial Meeting. A few years ago, the four martial families produced a disciple named Mu Yinzhou who managed to reach the top 100. That was the most joyous and proud moment for our Seven Profound Martial House. However, that was only the pride of the Martial House and the pride of the four great martial families. It had nothing to do with our Sky Fortune Kingdom.

A martial family wouldn’t necessarily only have a single last name. A child would follow their father’s last name, and if a daughter were to marry someone else, her children would follow her husband’s last name. Mu Yinzhou was talented because he had the bloodline of his father, a wandering martial artist that roamed the world and wasn’t a Sky Fortune citizen.

An outer disciple inevitably could not compare to someone in the martial family that shared the main lineage. Even Mu Yinzhou couldn’t be considered a true member of the four great martial families.

“Proud to reach the top 100? Our Sky Fortune Kingdom has so many talents, how can they not reach the top 100? How many countries participate in the Total Faction martial Meeting?”

“It’s not a question of how many countries participate. It’s that our Sky Fortune Kingdom has simply too wide a gap compared to those ancient and glorious martial families and sects. When the disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys are at your age, it’s only considered extremely ordinary to have a cultivation at the peak of Altering Muscle.

“Eh….” Huayu stared with wide eyes. He hadn’t yet reached 16 years old and his cultivation was at middle Viscera Training stage. This was already considered very good, good enough that even the Family Head had praised him. But….peak Altering Muscle at 15 years of age? What sort of concept was that? And that was only ordinary? Was this some sort of joke? Was he lying?

The middle-aged instructor sighed, “It’s shameful to say this, but the last time someone born from the Sky Fortune Kingdom had reached the top 100 rankings was 50 or 60 years ago. Even having someone pass the mountain gate trial was 15 years ago. This was truly shameful for our Sky Fortune Kingdom, and also for our Seven Profound Martial House! I am an instructor of the Martial House who was born in Sky Fortune Kingdom, and even I feel disgraced just mentioning this subject. That is why I didn’t wish to speak of the Total Faction Martial Meeting.”

While conversing, they had finally arrived before the Ranking Stone. Gazing up, they could view the numerous names engraved upon the large Ranking Stone. These were the talents of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House.

The higher one’s ranking, the larger their name would be. The first row only had one name – Lin Ming.

Following closely behind Lin Ming were Ling Sen and Ta Ku. In another half month, these three names would be removed from this Ranking Stone. Ling Sen and Ta Ku would graduate, and Lin Ming would become a core disciple.

Thinking this, the middle-aged instructor felt very melancholic. Lin Ming was once his student. Although he had only taught him for a few days, Lin Ming was the most outstanding and wonderful student that he had ever taught in his entire life; it had left a deep and profound impression on him.

“Lin Ming! It’s Lin Ming!

“Wow, I’m so excited! I can actually see the name of my idol in first place!”

“That’s right, Instructor Hong, did Mister Lin Ming participate in this year’s Total Faction Martial Meeting?”

The name of Lin Ming resounded like thunder in the ears of these young martial artists. He was without a doubt the utter and complete inspiration of those in every youthful martial arts circle. These young boys and girls couldn’t help but ask this question.

“He participated! Of course he participated!”

Hong Xi took a deep breath, and his somewhat disconsolate eyes began to suddenly shine with a flashing and glorious brilliance, like a sleeping lion that had woken up.

“Can Lin Ming reach the top 100?” A young girl whispered.

“Of course he can, he definitely will! Not only will he reach the top 100, but he will reach the top 50, even the top 30!” Hong Xi subconsciously gripped his fists, his emotions surging like the tide. It was like the one participating in the Total Faction Martial Meeting wasn’t Lin Ming, but himself. In Lin Ming, he had placed all his hopes.

His eyes shifted towards the direction of the Seven Profound Valleys. Across all those endless miles and rivers and valleys, Lin Ming and his group of three had enormous hopes placed upon them. This wasn’t only the hope of the instructors within the Seven Profound Martial House, but was also the hope of all the generations of martial artists within Sky Fortune Kingdom……

……………………………………..

When the third round began, Lin Ming met with three forfeits. It was not only him, but also Jiang Lanjian and Bi Tinghua who had opponents admitting defeat as the match started. In the group stages, one only had to be in the top ten to advance; there was no need to fight in every match.

Then, it was time for lunch.

Lin Ming, five matches, five victories.

Ling Sen, five matches, five victories.

Qin Xingxuan’s luck was quite bad. She had already lost three matches. Her chances of qualifying for the next stage were becoming increasingly precarious.

Although she had long expected this result, and knew that the main reason she lost was not because of her talent but because of her age, Qin Xingxuan still felt a bit disappointed. During this Martial Meeting, her journey would most likely end at the group stages. But three years from now, this would become her stage.

After five matches, Lin Ming had already gained some fame. As for Ling Sen, the matches he had met were a bit weaker, so his fame was also correspondingly smaller.

There were some people trying to take advantage of the situation and were beginning to estimate the future rankings; they had even opened up gambling houses.

The Seven Profound Valleys would not interfere in this. In fact, the ones that opened these gambling houses were usually the children of the Elders; their backgrounds weren’t small. For them, the gambling house was merely a pleasurable pastime. It was difficult to judge the strength of a participant in the group stages, so the gambling house wouldn’t necessarily make any profit.

During lunch time, Qin Xingxuan smiled at Lin Ming and praised, “Lin Ming, you’re chosen as one of the seeded players in the gambling house. Your odds aren’t too bad.”

“Oh? What are my odds of winning the whole thing?” Lin Ming casually asked. If the compensation rate was good, he might consider placing a bet on himself.

“Uh, well….you have….um, no odds of winning the championship….” Qin Xingxuan didn’t think that the first question Lin Ming would ask was what his rates were for winning the entire Martial Meeting. Even her, who had utter faith in Lin Ming, wasn’t very optimistic in Lin Ming’s chances of winning the championship.

   r]

Chapter 248 – The Second Round Begins

The snow fluttered in the falling light and the icy wind was chilling to the bone. Crown Prince Yang Lin had a thick golden-purple cloak draped over his body, he was waiting patiently on a thick wooden chair.

The truth was that Yang Lin didn’t have to stay here to listen to the message as it came. As long as the Total Faction Martial Meeting victory report arrived, thousands of sound transmitting talismans would instantly light up and the report would be sent to important figures of all the great power players. Tomorrow, the national newspaper of Sky Fortune City would publish the results.

The reason that Yang Lin personally insisted on waiting here was besides Qin Ziya, there was no one else that was more concerned about Lin Ming’s results than him.

His destiny had already been tightly bound together with Lin Ming. Now that Ouyang Dihua was dead, as long as Lin Ming’s influence increased just a little bit, his chances of winning the throne were that much higher.

Outside the temple, there were many disciples of the Seven Profound Martial House waiting, many of them being the new disciples that had entered the Seven Profound Martial House through the entrance exam. The words that Instructor Hong Xi had said to them had left a very deep and shocking impression on their young minds, and they had braved the chilling cold to stand here because they believed that they would be able to witness a historic moment.

The results from the Total Faction Martial Meeting wasn’t only related to the glory of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Martial House, it also had a very important political significance and it represented the power of the country’s martial artists. The dazzling successes of the young martial artists was a manifestation of the nation’s strength. If they could reach a result that was up to the standards of the Seven Profound Valleys, the Seven Profound Valleys would also increase the resources allotted to Sky Fortune Kingdom.

Although the Seven Profound Valleys was a blood sucking vampire, they weren’t completely merciless or without foresight. If a country could prove its value, then the Seven Profound Valleys would be willing to help elevate it. For instance, Huoluo Nation, Grace Venerate Nation, and some of the 16 martial cultivation families like the Zhang Family were like this.

In summary, the Seven Profound Valleys would use their resources in a way to maximize efficiency. It would not waste any resources on the weak and the wasted.

In the sunset of early winter, the clouds were thick in the sky, and the dark night fell sooner. There were some maids near the altar that had lit candle lamps under the shade. In such cold weather, these maids that had no martial cultivation could not stay warm, no matter how much they wore.

Even though there was shelter, the light was erratic and the snow sporadically fell, turning into small droplets of water that wet the lamp paper.

Just when everyone was beginning to become anxious, the sound transmission array suddenly activated, and the 36 true essence stones began to light up one at a time.

Yang Lin immediately stood up, looking unblinkingly towards the sound transmission array, his ears at full attention.

A sound transmission array was different from a sound transmission talisman, everyone around it would be able to hear the message. As the light of the transmission array began to reach a peak, the sound of Qin Ziya’s voice was emitted.

“Qin Xingxuan was off by two necessary wins. She can go no further in the group stages.”

“Ling Sen won 12 and lost 3. His results in group six qualify him to take part in the next stages.  He has entered the top 100.“

“Lin Ming… all matches were complete victories. He is first in the qualifying group and he has entered the top 100!”

Even though Qin Ziya was usually tranquil, his voice still trembled as he said Lin Ming’s results.

All matches were complete victories!

This was a glory that had never happened ever since Sky Fortune Kingdom was founded!

For the countries ranked in the middle of the 36 countries, it was already a cause worth rejoicing if they had a talent that could pass the mountain gate trial every 2 or 3 Total Faction Martial Meetings. A local talent of Sky Fortune Kingdom hadn’t passed the mountain gate trial in the last 15 years!

But now, the three disciples, Lin Ming, Ling Sen, and Qin Xingxuan, had all crossed the mountain gate trial. Not only that, but Lin Ming and Ling Sen had both passed the first group stage.

What was even more riveting was that Lin Ming had passed by having a complete victory!

What kind of glory was this? Even Huoluo Nation had never achieved something like this!

“All matches, complete victory? If it really is a complete victory, then Lin Ming has just created a Sky Fortune Kingdom record!” The Heavenly Abode Elder Sun Sifan gleefully laughed. He was probably the Elder in the Seven Profound Martial House that had the best relations with Lin Ming. He had supported the newbie Lin Ming during the time of the entrance examination when he had achieved first place. Now, Sun Sifan believed that this was the wisest decision he had made in his entire life.

Compared to the laughing Sun Sifan, Yang Lin sank back into his chair. His hands were trembling as they gripped the armrest. This revealed his inner excitement and roiling emotions.

Yang Lin was absolutely the most overjoyed person here. Someone like Lin Ming with such a strong and pure heart of martial arts would never be ungrateful and renege on a promise that he had made. As long as there wasn’t an accident, Yang Lin would be able to smoothly inherit the throne.

Yang Lin had already been waiting too long for this day. Although everybody looked up to him as the Crown Prince and they were in awe of what a great position he had, no one actually understood the pain, doubt, and fear that pierced Yang Lin’s deepest feelings. Once the struggle for the throne began, there was no turning back. Once he walked down that harsh path, there was no redemption if he fell. Even his own mother’s and sister’s life were tied together with his.

It was as if he were walking on a tightrope every day and living in abject fear of the future’s possibilities. But now that he finally saw the dawning sun, how could he not be excited?

The new Seven Profound Martial House disciples also cheered as they heard the news. They had braved this cold wind in order to stand here because they were part of the Linmaniacs that had taken Lin Ming as their idol. To them, they would never envy Lin Ming’s glory, they would only admire and respect him.

Hu! Hu! Hu!

Several dozens of sound transmitting talismans simultaneously lit up at once, rapidly circulating the joyous news.

Because of the distances, series of sound transmitting talismans were used. These ordinary sound transmitting talismans could only work in a hundred mile range. A large sect could use high-grade sound transmitting talismans that could send messages tens of thousands of miles, but Sky Fortune Kingdom naturally wouldn’t have this sort of sound transmitting talisman.

As one batch of sound transmitting talismans burned out, the second batch was lit!

In the dark night, the dancing flames of the sound transmitting talismans became increasingly brilliant and gorgeous.

Yang Lin took a deep breath. Watching these burning flames, he suddenly thought that this sight was extremely beautiful…

…………………………………………

Next day, Profound Sky Mountains –

It was a new day and a new martial stage. There were less matches today, but the matches were much more intense.

The matches were still arranged without drawing lots, the referee was the one who organized the brackets. This was to arrange the various participants based on their strength, and so that the extremely formidable seeded participants wouldn’t meet ahead of time.

Lin Ming had been placed in the seventh group, and this group also had ten people.

Within these ten was actually a direct disciple of the Array Faction, Fang Qi.

In addition, there was also the Mirage Faction’s Bi Tinghua.

In this group of 10, every disciple had to fight in 8 matches, there would only be one person they wouldn’t battle. The match between Lin Ming and Bi Tinghua was said to be inevitable.

Even though two strong participants like Lin Ming and Bi Tinghua would meet, this would be replicated across many martial stages. Out of each group, the participants would be divided again based on their final result. The top three would enter the first tier, the next three would enter the second tier, and the remaining four would enter the third tier.

With ten groups, there would be a total of 30 people in the first tier. Although these 30 people weren’t considered to be the top 30, there wouldn’t be much difference. When the time came for the round robin tournament, the final result would be decided by points. In that case, the first place participant in the first tier would become the champion of the Total Faction Martial Meeting.

The second tier would also carry out a round robin tournament. The top ten rankerd of the second tier would earn the qualifications to challenge the rankings of the first tier disciples. If they won, they might be able to advance into the top 30. But, it would basically be impossible for them to reach the top 20.

The third tier was the same except they could earn the qualifications to compare to the second tier.

In short, this current group stage was extremely critical, it would directly decide the final result of a contestant.

Whether a carp fish could become a dragon would all be decided here!

If one wanted to struggle for the top 20, they would have to at least reach the first tier!

This time, unless one was a talent on par with a direct disciple, there was no way that they would be able to hide the extent of their strength. The first tier of each group only had three people. After deducting a spot for the seeded player, there were in fact only two spots that the disciples could struggle for.

With nine people competing for 2 spots, and not only that, but with these 9 disciples being top-tier geniuses that had passed through layers and layers of screening, the intensity of the competition could be imagined.

“First match! Jing Chanyu against Zi Ling!

With the referee’s announcement, a woman activated her movement technique and jumped onto the stage, her clothes fluttering in the wind just like a heavenly fairy maiden that was riding the surging waves. The woman’s face was covered with a thin light gauze veil, but it was still possible to faintly make out the image of her face. Although she wasn’t considered to be a heavenly beauty, there was actually something mysterious about her that was extremely fascinating.

Qin Xingxuan was slightly stunned. She said to Lin Ming in a low voice, “That’s Jing Chanyu from Grace Venerate Nation. She’s the sister of the brother sister pair from Huoluo Nation, the two of them are called the Jingchan Duo, and they are more famous than you right now.”

Grace Veneration Nation was an extremely mysterious country. It wouldn’t be wrong to say that they were the strongest country within the 36 countries. The whole population of Grace Venerate Nation believed in a goddess named Chan. In Grace Venerate Nation, the theocracy was above the imperial throne. If the Emperor ascended the throne, he also needed to be crowned by the leader of their church.

Lin Ming guessed that this ‘goddess’ named Chan had a very high possibility of being someone like the Southern Wilderness’s Sorcerer. She might have been a Supreme Being that had appeared in ancient times and left behind some inheritances and legacies after flying towards the Realm of the Gods. With her good fortunes and lucks that she left behind, this would have been the reason for the power of Grace Venerate Nation.

The Jingchan Duo’s compensation rate for becoming the top champions of the 36 countries was 1:2. As for Lin Ming, his odds had been 1:6. After he handily defeated the Refiner Faction’s Sun Dong, his compensation rate had dropped to 1:3. Although his odds were good, he was still overshadowed by the Jingchan Duo.

This caused Lin Ming to have a wondering curiosity about these twins. What was exactly so great about them?

Seeing Jing Chanyu step on stage, the audience was stirred into a furor. Especially the male disciples, their interest towards Jing Chanyu far surpassed everyone else. The obsessive light from their eyes was nearly visible.

“I heard that she is only 18 years old and this is her first time participating in the Total Faction Marital Meeting. I wonder what rank she’ll reach in her first time!”

“She might be the next Zhang Yanzhao!”

“Up until now there hasn’t been an opponent that has disturbed her calm, no one has even managed to take her veil off, it really is indescribable. Such a beautiful girl, it’s a pity she’s wearing a veil… ”

As the people hollered in excitement, all of their eyes were focuses in Jing Chanyu. Suddenly, the referee announced, “Match, start!” Everyone hesitated. Mm? An opponent hadn’t appeared on stage yet, where was Zi Ling?

“How come there’s only Jing Chanyu on stage?” Qin Xingxuan asked, also puzzled. She looked at the martial stage in confusion.

Lin Ming smiled at her and said, “Zi Ling is already on stage. It’s just that she went on earlier and she’s hiding in distorted light so she can’t be seen so easily.”

“What? How is that possible?” Qin Xingxuan was shocked. Isn’t this just invisibility? The path of martial arts truly diverged and converged into endless profound paths, any strange and wonderful phenomenon could occur.

At this moment, an indifferent voice could be heard from behind them, “Zi Ling is a talented disciple of the Mirage Faction. She is able to manipulate light to deceive the eye. During the last Total Faction Martial Meeting, she attained a 56th ranking. Now after three years, it looks quite promising that she’ll reach the top 30.”

Chapter 251 – One Willing To Fight, One Willing To Endure

In the endless illusionary dreamland, the Samsara martial intent rolled out like a tide, frantically swelling as it rushed over Bi Tinghua. Because of that split second of fearful hesitation, a glimmer of a flaw was produced within Bi Tinghua’s mind. Lin Ming seized this opportunity and struck back.

Bang!

Countless phantoms and images flowed into Bi Tinghua’s mind, the endless lives of 100 Samsaras drowning him like a chaotic whirlpool.

A showdown between soul forces was constantly evolving. A dangerous move, a wrong move, and everything could be lost. Fortunately, Bi Tinghua was much more proficient than Lin Ming in terms of utilizing his soul force. Although that flaw in his mind had placed him in a passive situation of defending, his soul force defensive skills were able to barely hold off the attacks on his spiritual sea.

The battle between the two became increasingly ruthless and savage. Lin Ming was relying on the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder in his spiritual sea to launch an all-out offensive. With the power of thunder to protect his spiritual sea, he was in a nearly impregnable position.

As for Bi Tinghua, he was surrounded by danger on all sides. While Bi Tinghua had the cultivation methods of the Mirage Faction, towards Lin Ming’s Samsara martial intent that he had comprehended in the Sorcerer Holy Land after experiencing 100 lives of Samsara, they were on completely different levels in comparison.

With Bi Tinghua’s many years of cultivation and foundation within the Mirage Faction accumulated together, he was barely able to endure this attack.

With the dramatic and massive consumption of soul force, Bi Tinghua’s true body that was still standing on stage immediately paled, without a single trace of red in his cheeks.

“This damn boy, his soul force was actually so strong!”

Bi Tinghua was a disciple of the Mirage Faction, so he specialized in extremely precise use of soul force. But compared to Lin Ming, he was still inferior. It had to be known that Bi Tinghua’s cultivation was almost an entire realm above Lin Ming’s.

“Lucky for me this boy has only a single way to attack, and a complete lack of soul force skills. Every time he attacks, he wastes too much!” Bi Tinghua’s thoughts raced. As he was resisting Lin Ming’s attack, he was also thinking of possibilities to win.

“I can only defend and not attack. Although this Lin Ming has an extremely formidable soul force, he doesn’t know any techniques to use with it. Every time he attacks me he wastes a massive amount of soul force. Plus, since I am the one defending, I have to put in less effort to maintain this. His soul force consumption rate has to be at least three times my own! If this continues, he will definitely lose! As long as I can resist this round of continuous onslaught, my victory will be decided once he exhausts his soul force and can no longer maintain that purple lightning that covers his spiritual sea.”

Thinking this, Bi Tinghua’s lips curved up in a devilish grin. In the end, this country bumpkin martial artist who came from a hick village could only rely on brute force and had no skills. He was doomed to lose by his own hands!

Bi Tinghua had no way of knowing that this situation was exactly what Lin Ming was hoping for. Ever since Lin Ming had begun to use his Samsara martial intent, he had been trying to further his comprehension of the Samsara martial intent. It seemed as if his and Bi Tinghua’s soul force strength were comparable, in addition, this Bi Tinghua was quite skilled in soul force techniques. To come across such a good opponent and moreover, in an endurance match, it could only be considered serendipity.

To Lin Ming, Bi Tinghua was an exceptionally good grindstone to hone his abilities.

The dreamland around them began to morph over and over again. From a prairie to black lands. From black lands to a prairie. From black lands to a desert. From a desert to a bloody hell.

Devils and dark spirits and nagas danced around Bi Tinghua, twisting around his body. These monsters were summoned by Bi Tinghua in order to protect his own spiritual sea. But in front of Lin Ming’s never-ending brutal onslaught, everything was eventually torn apart by the swirling black vortex!

As soon as the match began, it lasted for an incense stick, then two incense sticks, then three incense sticks…..to half an hour.  During this entire time, the two youths on the martial stage were still standing there, completely motionless!

Bi Tinghua’s face was already paler than bleached paper! With half an hour of intense soul force consumption, it wasn’t something that the average person could endure. If it weren’t for Bi Tinghua’s high soul talent and thick foundation, he would have already fallen flat on the ground.

“How is this possible!? Is this fellow really a human!?”

Bi Tinghua couldn’t imagine that his opponent could still persist until this moment even though his soul force consumption rate was three times his own. If their positions were reversed, he would have already been done in!

“If I hold on for a bit longer, he won’t be able to last much longer! I will be the one to finally win!

Indeed, it was just as Bi Tinghua had said. Lin Ming truly couldn’t persist much longer. Since he was on the offensive, his soul force consumption was tremendous!

Lin Ming had been depending on the ‘Overbearing Soul Tactic’ that was left behind from the Supreme Elder from the Realm of the Gods. He had already accumulated a great deal of experience with this soul law formula by practicing his inscription technique. Although this soul law formula couldn’t be considered the best within the Realm of the Gods, if placed in the Sky Spill Continent, it was actually a top quality technique among all top quality techniques.

However, even though he had this, he still was unable to withstand a soul force consumption that was three times Bi Tinghua’s. His complexion wasn’t much better than Bi Tinghua’s!

Lin Ming had clenched his teeth and persisted in his attacks until now because in this high intensity soul force battle, he had obtained substantial benefits and had also increased his understanding of soul force techniques. Secondly, this was a unsurpassed great chance to further his comprehension of his Samsara martial intent. If he missed this opportunity to fight against someone like Bi Tinghua whose soul force strength was close to his own and was also experienced, then it would be truly been a pity.

In one breath, the two people had been standing on the martial stage for an entire half hour. The eyes of the audience had already glazed over in a dull and dazed look.

The disciples of the Mirage Faction were more fortunate, after all, they were already long used to this type of scene. Not only that, but the outcome of this match concerned the reputation of the Mirage Faction. Naturally, they would be patiently watching.

As for everyone else, they had already lost their patience. Some people had left this stage, and some people had just fallen asleep in their seats.

“Lin Ming probably can’t persist much longer.”

In a duel between soul force and illusion techniques, it was absolutely difficult for outsiders to determine who had the upper hand in the duel. They simply weren’t able to see what sorts of moves and abilities were used. They could only distinguish a general situation of the duel by looking at the external appearance of the participants. At this moment, Bi Tinghua looked a bit better than Lin Ming.

“Mm. It’s just really inconceivable that a martial artist from the 36 countries could reach his point. To compel Senior-apprentice Brother Bi into this appearance, this Lin Ming truly is a worthy talent. But this is as far as he goes. Finally, we barely manage to preserve the face of our Mirage Faction.”

As the two Mirage Faction disciples discussed the match, Lin Ming’s body was shaking a bit. As for Bi Tinghua, although his face was as white as paper, he was barely able to stabilize himself from falling.

“He’s going to win.”

“At last!”

The Mirage Faction disciples present sighed a breath of relief. Although this match had been won with difficulty and they had lost a great deal of face, in the end, for better or worse, they had still won.

This soul force contest was completely a contest of endurance and willpower.

After several dozen breaths of time, Lin Ming’s soul force was reaching a state of near depletion. If he really ran out of soul force, then Lin Ming would lose his ability to control his true essence. At that time, he would surely lose.

‘Looks like I have to stop here.’ Lin Ming thought it was a bit of a pity; he had wanted to persist a bit longer and gain some more insights. However, now it seemed that he could only end this soul force showdown and use his Heavy Profound Soft Spear to finish off Bi Tinghua and conclude this match.

As he was considering withdrawing the leftovers of his depleted soul force, suddenly an incomparably pure and vibrant soul energy welled up from within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, making his soul shake with excitement!

‘Mm? What is this?’

This pure soul force had suddenly swelled up from the underneath the depths of his spiritual sea; it was just as if it were buried there, and had been waiting for a chance to be unearthed.

‘This is probably…I remember!’

“This is the soul force that I absorbed from Hungry Ghosts in the Sorcerer Pagoda!”

Lin Ming suddenly realized what was happening. Back when he had entered the life and death smelting trial of the Sorcerer Pagoda, he had passed all seven trials in a single go!

The first trial had been a hellish world that was able to enhance his blood vitality. The second trial had comprised Hungry Ghosts that could supplement his soul force. The third trial consisted of beasts that increased his physical body strength. The fourth trial had the Witch Slave which enhanced the defensive power of his body. The fifth trial – mortal martial artists who were able to directly increase his cultivation. The sixth trial held no reward. As for the seventh trial, that was the World of the Sorcerer, in which Lin Ming had comprehended his Samsara martial intent.

During the second Hungry Ghost trial, Lin Ming had used the power of thunder to kill many Hungry Ghosts as well as decapitated a massive beautiful woman who had been the King of Hungry Ghosts. These dead lingering spirits had transformed into a pure spiritual force that nourished Lin Ming’s soul.

But because there was simply too much soul force and Lin Ming’s cultivation was limited, he had, at most, managed to absorb a fraction of it; the rest had been stored within his body.

The excess blood vitality that had been absorbed from the Blood Devils was also temporarily stored within his body.

And today, under this lucky coincidence, that pure soul force had been unexpectedly awakened, constantly injecting itself into his spiritual sea, nourishing his soul.

Of course, it wasn’t possible to instantly take all of it in in one go; it was a very long process. But once this pure soul force was released, it wouldn’t stop. It could be said that for a very long time in the future, Lin Ming’s soul would constantly be strengthening itself even when he’s eating or sleeping!

‘What a pleasant surprise!’

After he accidently connected to that pure soul force that had been buried beneath his spiritual sea, Lin Ming flushed red with excitement. Now that he had Bi Tinghua’s ‘help’ to absorb this, he wasn’t willing to let this opportunity go. Under the support of the pure soul force, the ferocity of Lin Ming’s soul attack became increasingly savage.

“This….how is this possible, he still has the strength to make another round of attacks!???”

Bi Tinghua thought he was going insane. Lin Ming’s soul force consumption rate was three times his own, but he had lasted until now and actually had the strength to launch a new salvo of attacks. But as for him, he was already stretched to his limit, completely overwhelmed!

“Impossible! This is impossible! Even Huan Xiaodie is not such an abnormal freak!”

Huan Xiaodie was the direct disciple of the Mirage Faction. In the Seven Profound Valleys, the disciples of the Mirage Faction and Zither Faction were mostly girls. In terms of strength, Huan Xiaodie was far superior to Bi Tinghua.

“He must have reached his limit; this must be his final effort before he completely collapses!”

Bi Tinghua was confident in his assumption. Lin Ming must have reached the limit of his power. Now, with this new unexpected round of even more violent attacks, this must be the side effect of some secret skill that he used on himself.

Most martial artists that specialized in soul force techniques understood several secret skills that they could use in order to insure their survival in a critical moment.

For instance, there were many secret skills that used a form of self-hypnosis in order to stimulate the full potential of the soul. However, the human soul was very fragile; once it was hurt, it was extremely difficult to heal. Therefore, this sort of secret skill tended to have extreme side effects.

Of course, the Seven Profound Valley’s Mirage Faction had their own sets of secret skills. Relatively speaking, the side effects of these secret skills were much milder.

“Humph! You’re not the only one with a secret skill. You think that just because you use it, I won’t dare to do the same!?”

Bi Tinghua’s eyes were colored red anger; he was raging to the point of almost vomiting blood. This had originally been a simple friendly martial arts match, and yet his opponent had used a secret skill without regards to his own well-being. However, he had already spoken so much trash talk before this match. If he lost now, then he would absolutely become a complete laughingstock within the Seven Profound Valleys!

Sh*t!

Not only that, but there were only three spots in the first tier. Fang Qi was such a freak of nature; Bi Tinghua had to admit that he was definitely not his match. As for Jing Chanyu, he wasn’t completely confident in being able to defeat her. If he lost to Lin Ming now, then he would truly be placed in a precarious position.

If one of the top three disciples of the Mirage Faction couldn’t enter into the first tier, then he wouldn’t have the face to look anyone in the eye ever again.

Thinking this, Bi Tinghua clenched his teeth.

‘This father will fight with you!’

Blood Sacrifice Soul Alacrity Law!

Chapter 252 – Blood Sacrifice Soul Alacrity Law

“My Seven Profound Valley’s Soul Alacrity Law definitely has less backlash than yours! We’ll see just who can hold out longer!”

Bi Tinghua was also ready to make any sacrifice necessary; this was a battle he couldn’t afford to lose.

Once his soul was damaged, at worst he would have to spend several months recovering in bed. He could just spend some of his sect points and use his connections to obtain a few bottles of the best soul recovery pills, and he’d be back in no time.

But if he lost this match, not only would he lose all his face, his spirit would be so frustrated that it would negatively affect all of his future cultivation.

Like this, the battle between Lin Ming and Bi Tinghua suddenly became extremely bitter and violent. Lin Ming’s Samsara martial intent was just like the ocean tide that never stopped; Bi Tinghua’s monsters and ghosts, even after being shattered, were endlessly birthed from their remains!

“I defend, you attack, and you consume three times the soul force that I do. Coupled with the side effects from the secret soul skill you are using, I don’t believe that your soul is made of iron! Let’s see how many lives you have to handle this!”

In Bi Tinghua’s opinion, Lin Ming was using some sort of forbidden soul technique, and the side effects of that technique would certainly be more dangerous than the one he was using. After all, Lin Ming was just some small country side bumpkin martial artist, there was no way he had adequate or decent training in understanding the consequences of soul damage. If he can’t get medicine in the future, his cultivation might even decline!

Thinking this, Bi Tinghua was suddenly in an jubilant mood. He had originally been depressed after having been forced to use the Blood Sacrifice Soul Alacrity Law, but now he was finally seeing the light at the end of the tunnel.

Now, it didn’t matter how miserable he would be. What was more important was how miserable his opponent would be!

If a man faced death alone, then he would feel extreme terror. But if faced with the end of the world together, then there wasn’t anything to fear.

At this moment, Bi Tinghua’s expression changed. In the dreamland world, the massive black vortex that had been giving him a headache suddenly disappeared. In its place a mass of Hungry Ghosts swelled up, thin bones protruding all over. These Hungry Ghosts had distorted limbs as if they were emaciated, and their heads were incomparably massive. Their mouths were twisted sideways, and sharp teeth glinted in the dark. Their blood-red tongue drooped downwards, constantly leaking saliva.

“Could this fellow actually have figured out the concept of using illusions to attack?” Bi Tinghua’s face darkened. Up until now, Lin Ming had only been using that massive black vortex to attack. But now he had summoned a horde of Hungry Ghosts; he thought that these Hungry Ghosts stemmed from the wilds of Lin Ming’s imagination.

“Ashura King!”

After Bi Tinghua used the Blood Sacrifice Soul Alacrity Law, Bi Tinghua’s soul force had experienced an increase in strength. He was able to directly summon that Ashura King that was usually difficult to call down!

Bang!

The Ashura King smashed into the piles of Hungry Ghosts. The Hungry Ghosts threw themselves on the Ashura King, frenziedly biting its body. Then, Bi Tinghua’s face became extremely ugly. The Ashura King managed to resist for a while, before being slowly chewed apart…..

………………………………

After the first half an hour, another quarter of an hour passed!!!!

The two were still standing on stage, a winner not yet decided!

At this point, the Mirage Faction disciples that were watching began to feel anxious and doubtful; if the match had reached this point, it could only mean that the situation in their soul battle was extremely dangerous!

A physical injury would only take a few days to heal. Something like a fracture would take a few months. But if the soul was damaged, it might possibly take several years or even a lifetime to recover from.

Even with the support of top quality pills and medicines, it would still take several months to recover.

The two individuals had been standing on stage for almost an hour, and yet there was no victor yet. Had they two of them gone all out against each other?

“Senior-apprentice Brother Bi has probably used the Blood Sacrifice Soul Alacrity Law; if you look at his eyes you can see they are completely bloodshot. He’s already reached his absolute limit! If he continues any longer, there’s a chance his soul would be extremely hurt!

“Let’s wait for another incense stick of time. If the match still isn’t settled, then we will ask the referee to force it to an end; even a draw would be fine. But I don’t think that the Lin boy will be able to last another incense stick of time. You can tell from his red face that something’s not right with him.”

“Mm. I felt his soul force suddenly shoot up a moment ago. He definitely used some sort of secret soul skill to boost his power, and its strength is much greater than the Blood Sacrifice Soul Alacrity Law. Normally speaking, the more potent a secret skill is, the greater its backlash will be.”

After Lin Ming galvanized the pure soul force that had been buried beneath his spiritual sea, it had caused the blood flow within his body to accelerate and thus his face had become flush red with blood. To a Mirage Faction disciple, it was just like the deathly redness that occurred after using a soul enhancing secret skill.

“Half an incense stick has passed, how can Lin Ming still persist?” A Mirage Faction disciple commented as he furrowed his brows.

“Something’s wrong….”

The Mirage Faction disciple felt something fishy was happening. Lin Ming had simply been able to last for too long a time. Moreover, his soul force power had suddenly experienced a great increase. Besides a soul enhancing secret skill, there was no other explanation as to how that could have happened. Did Lin Ming have a secret skill that somehow didn’t have any negative side effects?

This was absolutely impossible.

He immediately rejected this incredulous idea. If there really was a secret skill like this, then wouldn’t a martial artist’s soul force be all-powerful and endless?

At this a moment, a girl that was standing next to him raised a trembling finger and pointed towards the stage. She whispered, “Senior-apprentice Brother Bi….his….nose is bleeding….”

“Mm?”

The disciple turned around and saw that two streams of blood were flowing down Bi Tinghua’s nose, leaking past his mouth and unceasingly dripping down his chin.

“This is bad!”

“Stop the match! This other man is a crazy madman!”

At this moment, Bi Tinghua’s body trembled, and then he slumped face down on the ground…..

“Lin Ming, victory!”

With the referee’s announcement, most of the audience only had a tepid reaction. This silly little stupid match was finally over. From the beginning to end, the two of them had only stood on stage staring at each other for almost an hour! What could be more boring than this match?

Several disciples of the Mirage Faction rushed on stage. Bi Tinghua’s face was pallid, his eyes were bloodshot, and his nose was bloody. He had long lost consciousness.

“Let’s carry him off.”

The 20 year-old female disciple waved her hand, ordering everyone. She only had unpleasant feelings towards someone like Bi Tinghua, but for better or for worse, he was still one of the three top core disciples of the Mirage Faction’s younger generation.

She looked at Lin Ming deeply, wanting to find some consequence he suffered from using a secret soul technique. However, she was disappointed as she found nothing.

She didn’t believe that there was a secret soul technique that didn’t have any side effects. In that case, there could only be one possible explanation, and that was that Lin Ming had an extraordinarily overwhelming soul force capacity. He must have only prepared to be a weak soul force user, and then lured Bi Tinghua into a battle of attrition with him.

The woman’s voice was icy as she said, “You could already have won earlier, and yet you still deliberately led Bi Tinghua into fighting with you like this?”

Lin Ming had been walking off the stage, but hearing the woman’s question he stopped in his tracks and glanced backwards. He didn’t deny anything. After all, it would impossible for him to clearly explain about the pure soul force that had been slumbering deep beneath his spiritual sea.

He pointed at Bi Tinghua who was lying on the ground and said, “Believe whatever you want, but if I was the one lying on the ground right now, I believe that your Junior-apprentice Brother would have been very happy to see me in a miserable state. I hadn’t even used my full strength against him, and yet he turned out like this. Did he use some sort of forbidden secret skill? It’s only a friendly martial arts contest, there was no need to push through a secret skill with side effects in order to deal with me. Does he have that great a hatred with me?”

The woman was stunned, speechless. She couldn’t find the words to refute Lin Ming.

“I didn’t force him to use any secret skill, this was something that he brought down upon himself, and yet you are actually blaming me for harming him. Is this the logical reasoning of your Seven Profound Valleys Mirage Faction? Only you can bully others? Others cannot resist?”

The woman grit her teeth and said, “You obviously had ulterior motives and lured Bi Tinghua into this state! Your sly words and arguments are meaningless here. After entering the finals, you will encounter the Mirage Faction’s direct disciple, Huan Xiaodie. When that time comes, I hope you can fight like a man, and not immediately give up!”

“Naturally, that isn’t something you need worry about.” Lin Ming finished his sentence and then turned around to walk off stage.

The audience made room for Lin Ming to leave. In fact, to most people, Lin Ming’s battle wasn’t worthy of anything special.

The match had lasted for almost a whole hour, and though he had defeated Bi Tinghua, it seemed that he had only done so reluctantly. His face had whitened, and then it had flushed red. Obviously, this fight had been extremely difficult for him.

Lin Ming’s strength was recognized as a bit higher than Bi Tinghua’s. But how could this strength compare to someone like Jing Chanyu?

The odds of the gambling house had changed. Now Jing Chanyu’s odds were 1:1.8, Jing Chanshi’s odds were 1:2, and Lin Ming’s odds were 1:4.

Because of the match between Bi Tinghua and Lin Ming, Jing Chanyu’s odds had gone up whereas Lin Ming’s odds had gone down. But the odds still favored Jing Chanyu.

Throughout every single match so far, Jing Chanyu had maintained her calm. There hadn’t even been an opponent who had managed to force her into taking a single step; no one knew just how much of her strength she had used to defeat Zi Ling.

As for Lin Ming, he had already approached his limit in facing Bi Tinghua. Unless he had cards still hidden in his sleeve, then his chances of defeating Jing Chanyu weren’t looking good.

After the five total victory contestants in the seventh group finished their matches, the remaining matches weren’t so interesting. Although everyone that had managed to pass the first group stage could be considered a master, there was simply too great a difference compared to the first few matches.

Like this, the group stage advanced to the second round.

Fang Qi was the first one to go on stage, and his opponent was Zi Ling. As for who his opponent was: Zhou Yan or Zi Ling, there was simply no difference to him.

A single move, instant defeat!

“Fang Qi, victory!”

As the referee announced this, Zi Ling let out a sad, low-spirited sigh. She had been hoping to enter the first tier, but now that she had lost two straight matches, unless there was an accident, she would definitely lose to that Lin Ming fellow!

“Second round….second match….” The referee intentionally paused here, and all of the contestants pricked their ears up in attention. Because the matches were arranged completely according to the referees’ wishes, none of the contestants knew who would be the next one called up.

“Second match, Lin Ming against Jing Chanyu!”

With this sentence, the entire audience rose in an uproar. Lin Ming against Jing Chanyu was absolutely the most anticipated match of the entire seventh group!

The unbeatably Zi Ling and Bi Tinghua who both had complete victories in the first group stage had already been defeated. Now, there were only three people who were still undefeated, and two of those were Jing Chanyu and Lin Ming. As for Fang Qi against Jing Chanyu and Fang Qi against Lin Ming, truth be told, there wasn’t much interest in those matches. In everyone’s opinion, Fang Qi’s victory was inevitable; a direct disciple was simply too strong. With his peak Pulse Condensation period cultivation, his strength was already equal to a middle Houtian master’s; his position was simply unshakeable.

Thus, the most anticipated and the most suspenseful match was Jing Chanyu against Lin Ming!

The majority’s opinion was that as things stood, Jing Chanyu had a 70% chance of winning, and Lin Ming had a 30% chance of winning.

But how true this was, it could only be found out through a true battle.

Jing Chanyu’s clothes fluttered in the wind as she landed in the center of the martial stage.

Jing Chanyu greeted, “Grace Venerate Nation’s disciple, Jing Chanyu.”

She still had her thin gauze veil on; her voice someone unreal and nebulous.

Lin Ming cupped fists together in respect, “Lin Ming. Please advise.”

Chapter 254 – Digging For Talent?

If Lin Ming had released a supremely formidable martial skill that was able to shatter her defense, she would not have been surprised. But it had only been a punch; it was simply impossible to condense enough energy onto that fist. That casual blow he sent out wasn’t even with a weapon!

Or maybe he had always been a fist fighting martial artist?

The current situation had already gone beyond any of Jing Chanyu’s calculations, she was extremely startled. After Lin Ming broke apart her absolute defense, he grasped towards her jade-like neck!

Jing Chanyu shook as if an earthquake passed through her, and her face turned incomparably white. At such a close range, it was impossible to use any martial skills, but could she use speed to dodge him? Jing Chanyu had never excelled at speed, but even if she did, could she compare to someone like Lin Ming? He was some abnormal freak that had managed to continuously avoid her Halcyon Reflection 1000 Shaded Hands; Jing Chanyu did not believe for a second that she could accomplish something similar.

At this critical juncture, Jing Chanyu formed her hand into a saber, and chopped down at Lin Ming’s wrist.

Although Jing Chanyu seemed like a delicate and gossamer lady, anyone who assumed she would be weak because of her physical charms was sorely mistaken. Jing Chanyu had reached a medium sixth-grade fusion with her Earth-attribute true essence; she had already achieved the stage of using her elemental origin energy to temper her body. Usually if she didn’t use true essence, her body would seem soft and liquid-like, but once she imbued her body with true essence, her body would be as strong as a treasure weapon!

Therefore Jing Chanyu didn’t need to use a weapon, because her body was in itself a marvelous natural weapon!

Jing Chanyu had wanted to force Lin Ming to retreat with her hand saber, but hadn’t thought that not only would Lin Ming not react, he would keep rushing towards her.

This fellow!

Jing Chanyu was finally angry. She clenched her beautiful jade teeth tight, and her left hand chopped down. If a normal martial artist were struck by this, they would suffer the fate of having their bones fractured.

Peng!

Her hand cut down on Lin Ming’s wrist, but Jing Chanyu’s face drained of blood right after. She felt as if her hand saber had cut down on darksteel. Not only was Lin Ming’s hand not affected in the least, but she felt her own arm lose feeling from the backlash reverberations.

Was his body made of iron or something?

She only had enough time to think this single thought. In the next moment, Lin Ming’s hand already wrapped around her tender neck and his five fingers gripped tightly against her throat and carotid artery. As long as Lin Ming put in just a bit of strength, he could have immediately killed Jing Chanyu!

Jing Chanyu’s veil had originally covered down to her neck, but in that fierce impact when Lin Ming had grabbed onto her, the veil that was the symbol of her tranquility was pulled down, revealing Jing Chanyu’s beautiful and mysterious face.

“You…!” Jing Chanyu’s eyes flashed with a sullen anger.

“Well fought!” Lin Ming withdrew his hand, bowed in a gesture of respect and then turned to leave the stage. If it hadn’t been his hand a moment ago but instead his spear, then Jing Chanyu’s throat would have been nothing but a bloody hole. The outcome of this battle had already been decided.

“Lin Ming, victory!”

As the referee announced the victor, the audience was stunned by the sudden turn in events.

What had just happened a moment ago? Lin Ming used his fist?”

And he had shattered Jing Chanyu’s absolute defense with a single punch! There wasn’t even true essence condensed onto his fist!

This match between Lin Ming and Jing Chanyu had already undergone all sorts of analysis in the minds of the audience, still, no one thought that the end result would turn out like this. It was just as when Jing Chanyu had defeated Zi Ling: it only took several breaths of time for Lin Ming to defeat Jing Chanyu.

Not only that, but he didn’t use the soul force attacks that he was known for. Instead, he had used his fist.

“Isn’t Lin Ming a soul force attack expert? How come he used his fist?”

The path of martial arts was limitless and profound. For someone so young like Lin Ming, it was already excellent that they were skilled in a single aspect. A soul force attack was already an extremely obscure and esoteric method of fighting. To be able to achieve good success in this ability, one had to invest a great amount of time within it. Naturally, other aspects of their training would lag behind.

But now it looked like Lin Ming didn’t know just soul attacks. If Lin Ming knew some swordsmanship, then the audience wouldn’t have been too surprised. But a fist…

This sort of attack method was simply too different from a soul attack, it was just too difficult to link the two together.

“You’ve done well.” Qin Ziya praised as Lin Ming walked off stage.

Although Qin Ziya sounded calm, his mind was actually surging with an overwhelming tide of feelings and emotions. At first, he had estimated that Lin Ming had high hopes of entering the top 20 ranks, but after he had arrived at the Seven Profound Valleys’ Total Faction and seen such geniuses like Zhang Yanzhao, the Jingchan Duo, and others emerge from the shadows one at a time, Qin Ziya’s confidence had been somewhat shaken.

But now it seemed as if he had underestimated Lin Ming by far. Lin Ming reached the first tier, which also meant he had entered into the top 30 ranks. And yet he still hadn’t used his spear!

Did this mean that there was a chance Lin Ming would enter into the top 10 ranks during his first Total Faction Martial Meeting?

Thinking this, Qin Ziya felt a giddiness surge within him. Although the top 10 and top 20 sounded close, the truth was, there was a massive difference between them!

The top 10 rankings were nearly completely dominated by direct disciples! There were some large factions like the Sword Faction and the Acacia Faction that had bountiful resources and numerous disciples. The resources that the second ranked disciple received wouldn’t be that much different from the direct disciple.

In other words, these top-level direct disciples already filled the top 10. If a disciple wished to enter into the top 10, then they would have to struggle against these direct disciples!

Ever since the Seven Profound Valleys Total Faction Martial Meeting had begun, the 36 countries and 16 martial families had produced a number of amazing talents that were able to enter into the top 20 rankings, such as Zhang Yanzhao.

There were many talents that had entered into the top 20. But to enter into the top 10? There had only been a few!

If Lin Ming was able to enter the top 10 of the Total Faction Meeting during his first time, then what about his second time? Or third time? Lin Ming had only just reached 16 years of age – he still had two more Total Faction Martial Meetings he could attend!

Qin Ziya didn’t dare to imagine what could happen. Lin Ming’s growth was simply too terrifying. He guessed that after this Martial Meeting, Lin Ming might even be selected to enter the Total Faction ahead of time!

With the support of the Total Faction’s resources and cultivation methods, then Lin Ming might even become the champion of the next Martial Meeting! Compared to his own hopes, that would have been three years early!

Of course, even if Lin Ming entered into the Total Faction, his achievements would partially be attributed to Qin Ziya. But thinking that just as his Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House had raised a genius like this with so much difficulty, they had to instantly send him away, Qin Ziya felt a bit melancholic.

……………………………………

In the Grand Hall of the Seven Profound Valleys, Mu Qinghong had been following Lin Ming’s match from beginning to end.

“Haha, Fairy Maiden Qinghong seems to have some interest in that young boy. This is a talent that my Seven Profound Valleys has cultivated with care; he is a good seedling!”

At the side of Mu Qinghong, Seven Profound Valley Master Shi Zongtian was laughing with a big smile as he spoke.

Mu Qinghong was still quietly observing Lin Ming with her soul force, looking indifferent to the situation. Shi Zongtian had no idea what sort of thoughts Mu Qinghong was thinking, he only thought that maybe she had been drawn in by Lin Ming’s exemplary performance.

Lin Ming had also caught Shi Zongtian’s attention. To have such strength at the peak Bone Forging stage was just too eye-catching, it was hard not to notice.

However, although Shi Zongtian kept note of Lin Ming, he hadn’t investigated any information on Lin Ming’s background.

Lin Ming had been revealed to be a soul talent genius, but, soul attacks just weren’t the right way to do things. Once he tried to attack the Xiantian realm, he would experience an insurmountable bottleneck. To Shi Zongtian, this meant that Lin Ming wasn’t worth caring about. But now it seemed that Lin Ming wasn’t just a simple soul force master after all!

Mu Qinghong looked at Shi Zongtian and chuckled in her heart. According to the data she had obtained from Mu Qianyu, although Lin Ming was technically a disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys, he hadn’t been ‘cultivated with care’ as Shi Zongtian had claimed. He wasn’t even a disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys Total Faction, but just someone who had been hanging around at a Seven Profound Martial House.

She smiled and said, “He truly is a good seedling. With such strength at his age, his future will be bright and limitless. Valley Master Shi’s ability to find talents like this is praiseworthy.”

Hearing such high appraisal coming from the lofty Mu Qinghong, Shi Zongtian felt his own mood soar to the sky. Before a top-tier fourth-grade sect, Shi Zongtian was naturally happy to show off the strength of his sect. “I didn’t really think that such a genius would emerge at this Total Faction Martial Meeting… it looks like I need to recruit him into the Martial House ahead of time. Such a good seedling is just wasted within the 36 countries… mm? 36 countries?”

Shi Zongtian suddenly realized something. He send out a true essence sound transmission to a servant and said, “Look up which country Lin Ming from the seventh group came from.”

Shi Zongtian suddenly felt a foreboding omen creeping up. This Lin Ming couldn’t possibly come from Sky Fortune Kingdom…

An answer soon arrived back, and that unlucky feeling in Shi Zongtian’s heart came true. Lin Ming really was from Sky Fortune Kingdom!

He turned his head to glance at Mu Qinghong, and his expression became somewhat ugly. He remembered that just when the Martial Meeting had started, Mu Qinghong had asked which stage the participants of Sky Fortune Kingdom were at.

At first, Shi Zongtian had thought it was strange that Mu Qinghong of all people would ask something like this. But now, it seemed as if the reason was because of Lin Ming!

If he hadn’t guessed wrong, then the reason Mu Qinghong came to the Seven Profound Valleys to specifically observe the Total Faction Martial Meeting was to look for Lin Ming!

A dignified and haughty Fairy Maiden of Divine Phoenix Island with an extreme Xiantian cultivation would actually travel all this way to look for a little boy from Sky Fortune Kingdom with a peak Bone Forging stage cultivation. This was just too ridiculous!

“How old is Lin Ming?” Shi Zongtian asked a servant again with true essence sound transmission.

“Reporting to the Valley Master, Lin Ming has just reached 16 years of age!”

To have reached a cultivation at the peak Bone Forging stage at only 16 years of age, he must have at least a sixth-grade martial talent!

Within the Seven Profound Valleys, a sixth-grade talent was already at the top. But placed within Divine Phoenix Island, a sixth-grade talent was only so-so. It wasn’t a reason for someone like Mu Qinghong to personally come to the Seven Profound Valleys.

That meant that there were other aspects of Lin Ming that were worth Mu Qinghong’s attention, but he still didn’t know what these were!

Realizing this point, Shi Zongtian’s complexion became increasingly ugly. The fourth-grade sect Divine Phoenix Island would actually come to his little corner of land in order to search for talent? Although they were a fourth-grade sect and the Seven Profound Valleys was only a third-grade sect, and the difference in their strength was too great, they still couldn’t bully them like such!

“Is there a problem, Valley Master Shi?” Mu  Qinghong saw that Shi Zongtian was looking awful at the moment, so she smiled as she asked him. She noticed that Shi Zongtian’s servant had left for a bit a moment ago, and was able to vaguely guess what had just happened.

Shi Zongtian forced a smile and said with a low voice, “Is Fairy Maiden Qinghong old acquaintances with my sect’s disciple Lin Ming?”

“No. It’s just because of some coincidence that Little Brother Lin knows my family’s Young Mistress.”

Young Mistress!

Shi Zongtian almost wanted to jump out of his seat. The ‘Young Mistress’ of Mu Qinghong could only be a single person – the Saintess of Divine Phoenix Island, Mu Qianyu!

Lin Ming actually was personally acquainted with Mu Qianyu?

What was happening? How could Lin Ming possibly know the Saintess of Divine Phoenix Island? An existence like her would have a high status even if placed in the entire South Horizon Region of Sky Spill Continent! Even he had to bow if he saw her!

Chapter 256 – The Final Competition Begins

“Are you not convinced by what I’m saying?” Fang Qi faintly smiled as he noticed Lin Ming’s somewhat disinterested expression.

“It’s already a fantastic result for a disciple of the 36 countries to have the qualifications to reach the top 10 ranks in their first Total Faction Martial Meeting. Although your natural talent is shocking, it’s a pity that your cultivation is too low.”

Fang Qi waggled his fingers as he shook his head, “Wait until your strength reaches the middle Pulse Condensation period and maintain your ability to fight above your cultivation. If you can do so, then you will have the qualifications that make you worthy to be my match. But as for some other people, that might not be enough!”

Lin Ming was stunned. The core disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys were just too arrogant. Fang Qi was naturally a proud person, but from his words it seemed that even he admitted he was inferior to some others.

This ‘other people’ that he mentioned could only be extremely abnormal.

Fang Qi didn’t intend to speak anymore, and he jumped onstage, stretching out his fingers as he faced Jing Chanyu. “This match will be decided in five breaths of time!” Lin Ming had used 15 breaths of time in order to defeat Jing Chanyu; Fang Qi would settle this in five, which was one third of Lin Ming’s time. This was to deliberately show those young geniuses of the Seven Profound Valleys that the martial artists from the 36 countries were inferior to them.

“Fang Qi, you can do it!”

“Destroy her in one second, destroy her!”

As Fang Qi’s voice fell, the audience burst into cheers. This was the home of the Seven Profound Valleys, and there were also many Array Faction disciples in the audience, and they had a good impression of their faction’s direct disciple, Fang Qi. Naturally, he also had an extremely high popularity. In particular, there were many people that had lost a great deal of money because of Lin Ming and Jing Chanyu, and they wanted to vent their feelings.

At this time, Jing Chanyu was using a new veil. She didn’t have any reaction, even seeing the overwhelming one-sided support towards her opponent. She had the same absolute defense that surrounded her when she fought Lin Ming, except this time it was much thicker. She intended to thoroughly frustrate Fang Qi for looking down on her so much.

She knew that she was inferior to Fang Qi, but she wouldn’t let him easily end this match in five breaths of time.

“Match, begin!”

As the referee announced the beginning of the match, Fang Qi’s ten fingers quickly linked together at a terrifying speed as he formed golden symbol after golden symbol. The speed at which he formed his seals was a blur, and in just a breath of time, 100 symbols flew out of Fang Qi’s hand and soared towards Jing Chanyu.

In the second breath of time, all of these golden symbols completely surrounded Jing Chanyu. In the midst of this dangerous energy, Jing Chanyu could only grit her teeth and supplement the shield that was guarding her with everything she had. She was a martial artist of the 36 countries. Facing a disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys who looked down on her with nothing but contempt, she could only suppress the anger in her heart.

At this time, Jing Chanyu only had one thought on her mind, and that was to never let Fang Qi easily win. She would fight for the honor of the 36 countries!

“Golden Octagon Lock!”

Fang Qi clasped his hands together, and those hundreds of golden symbols that surrounded Jing Chanyu congealed together into eight formation arrays that struck Jing Chanyu’s protection!

Kacha!

That protective eggshell was tightened by an invisible chain, severely distorting!

Jing Chanyu paled, and true essence surged within her body. In that split second, her protection had almost burst open!

“Mm?” Fang Qi lightly sneered. It seemed that his opponent’s protective barrier had exceeded his imagination.

“Heaven and Earth Sword Formation!”

Fang Qi thrust out his hand! 36 blades of light flew out from his body and landed near Jing Chanyu.

The sword light seemed to undulate, as if the air itself was being cut apart by the swords. The sharp sword energy pierced Jing Chanyu’s protective defense!

Chi chi chi chi chi chi!

In that moment, the 36 blades of light had punctured Jing Chanyu’s protection like a porcupine!

It had only been three breaths of time!

Jing Chanyu clenched her teeth; she didn’t think of attack, everything she had was placed into her defense. She galvanized the true essence within her body to the extreme! Her determination would not waver, she would bet everything she had to last past the fifth breath!

The protective eggshell severely deformed, and the sword energy seemed to slow down. Still, in the blink of an eye, Jing Chanyu had already been pressed to her limit. When Zi Ling had used the 36 light blades to strike her, her move had been melted away by Jing Chanyu’s protection. But now, it was the opposite! Fang Qi’s sword energy was too strong, in just a breath of time his swords had pierced through her protection!

Pah pah pah!

Although the protective eggshell shield hadn’t broken, the 36 light blades had already pierced through, pointing at Jing Chanyu from all directions. With just a thought from Fang Qi, Jing Chanyu would be cut to pieces!

“Fang Qi, victory!”

With the referee’s announcement, just five breaths of time had passed.

“Only five breaths!”

“Haha, he truly is the direct disciple of the Array Faction. Senior-apprentice Brother Fang is too amazing!”

The audience resounded with thunderous cheers, especially from those disciples of the array faction. Many of the female disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys even dropped their modesty and let out clear screams. Obviously, they had long held a liking towards Fang Qi.

In fact, of the Seven Profound Valleys’ seven direct disciples, except for the strange and weird Puppet Faction direct disciple, all the other six direct disciples were greatly welcomed and popular among girls. Even Ouyang Ming of the Acacia Faction who was known as a player was no different. There were many girls that dreamed of one day being able to marry them; even being a concubine would be nice, as that would greatly increase the resources they would have.

Jing Changyu removed her protective shield and walked down the stage. Under the barrage of endless boos from the enemy audience, her sense of desolation and disorientation was indescribable.

As a proud woman who had grown up under the halo of being a heavenly genius, she was representing the 36 countries on behalf of their honor. And yet, the outcome of this match was… the opponent had said he would end the match in five breaths, and he really had ended it in five breaths. No matter how hard she had tried, she was unable to change this. She hadn’t even been able to force him to use his full strength, was the difference in their power truly so great?

As she inadvertently looked up, she saw Lin Ming standing on the side, his hands folded behind his back. His expression was someone plain and casual.

Lin Ming…

After seeing Fang Qi’s formidable strength with his own eyes, how could he maintain such a calm expression? What sort of cards did he have in his hands? Would he be able to defeat Fang Qi?

Jing Chanyu couldn’t believe that was possible. Maybe Lin Ming was only a person who was unwilling to admit defeat. He might reach the top, but if he did, he would inevitably clash with the direct disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys!

“Are you okay?” Lin Ming could imagine what Jing Chanyu was feeling at this time. She had desperately gone all out, and yet she had still suffered so miserably. As a proud woman of Grace Venerate Nation, the damage to Jing Chanyu’s self-esteem could be imagined.

Jing Chanyu stubbornly nodded her head.

Lin Ming smiled and turned to leave. He only came to express his polite condolences to someone who was once his opponent.

At this moment, Jing Chanyu suddenly said, “Lin Ming!”

“Mm? What’s the matter?” Lin Ming turned his head. To his surprise, he could hear that Jing Chanyu sounded somewhat excited.

Jing Chanyu hesitated, nipped her red lips and asked, “You… can you win?”

Lin Ming was slightly stunned. Suddenly, he brilliantly smiled and nodded, “I can!”

He hadn’t even asked who he needed to win against.

“I meant to ask if you could defeat Fang Qi.”

“It’s all the same!”

Jing Chanyu was shocked speechless. Even she didn’t expect such an absurd dialogue between them. If they were heard by the disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys, they would probably laugh until they were rolling on the ground.

She had asked if Lin Ming could win, not if he could defeat Fang Qi.

Yet Lin Ming hadn’t even asked any questions. Even after she pointed out Fang Qi, his reply had still been – “It’s all the same!”

This answer was filled with a complete and absolute confidence. It implied that Fang Qi was merely one of the opponents that he would defeat, and that he would be ‘first’!

What did Lin Ming want to do? Did he not want to struggle for the top five, but the top three?

Thinking this, Jing Chanyu gasped. She didn’t know why, but she had a gut instinct that trusted in Lin Ming. Perhaps it was because of his confidence, or maybe it was because of Jing Chanyu’s own sentinel emotions, but regardless of whatever the reason was, Lin Ming was now the only contestant of the 36 countries who remained undefeated.

Grace Venerate Nation could only come so far, Jing Chanyu’s older brother had also lost. Jing Chanyu guessed that she and her twin would end up in the final rankings between 20 and 40. The only one that could go on to represent the 36 countries was one person, Lin Ming!

“Lin Ming, you have to win!” Jing Chanyu slowly said, stressing every syllable.

“Mm. At the very least, I will defeat Fang Qi.”

Lin Ming wasn’t blindly arrogant, rampant, or stupid. If even someone as proud as Fang Qi admitted that the other seven direct disciples were superior to him, that meant that the disparity between them was very big.

Facing opponents like them, he feared that his matches would not be so easy!

After he parted ways with Jing Chanyu, it was already time for lunch. Now that every other group stage match had been basically settled, the only ones to enter into the first tier from the 36 countries were Jing Chanyu and Lin Ming.

Jing Chanyu’s older brother Jing Chanshi was off by one point, and barely missed making the first tier.

As for Ling Sen, in his eight matches he had won two and lost six. He finally entered into the third tier.

Besides Ling Sen, Huoluo Nation’s Wang Mu and Easter Sun Country’s Zhao Yang also entered the third tier.

Thus, out of all the disciples of the 36 countries, six of them were able to enter into the top 100 rankings of the Total Faction Martial Meeting. Of those, Sky Fortune Kingdom had two disciples, and Lin Ming was ranked first among the 36 countries.

This was an event that had never shown up in the history of Sky Fortune Kingdom.

Qin Xingxuan was also thrilled to receive 120 true essence stones as a reward. She had bet 20 true essence stones on Lin Ming to win when his compensation rate had been 1:6. With Lin Ming’s victory, she had gained a net total of 100. 100 true essence stones was equal to 100,000 gold taels! This was a great sum of money even to someone like Qin Xingxuan.

……………………….

The second round of the group matches had finished by the afternoon. At that time, all the contestants were able to rest for the night. On the next day, the final tournament would begin!

The first tier had 30 people, of which 20 were still undefeated. Of these 20 people, seven of them were direct disciples. Before the final showdown, these seven disciples wouldn’t normally meet in a match.

Besides the direct disciples, there were three or four top core disciples of the Seven Factions. These individuals were only inferior to the direct disciples. For instance, Jiang Lanjian was one of them. There were many disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys that had already subconsciously placed Jiang Lanjian as a master equal to the seven direct disciples.

Of the remaining people, several of them were great figures within their factions. As long as they had enough resources, they were hopeful in breaking through to the Xiantian realm!

There were seven direct disciples, three to four top core disciples, and several other influential core disciples. Altogether, this was 18 people in total.

The 19th person was Zhang Yanzhao. He came from the Zhang Family, one of the 16 martial cultivation families. The Zhang Family had a staggering history that reached back 3000 years; it was said that the first Head of the Zhang Family who created his family foundation with his own hands was a Revolving Core master! But regardless of their past, the Zhang Family had greatly declined since their heydays. Still, they maintained their deep heritage and legacy. The Zhang Family had two Xiantian realm masters that led their family, even the Seven Profound Valleys had to give some respect to the Zhang Family.

Chapter 263 – Genius Of The Spear Path

“Lin Ming, victory!”

As the referee declared the result, the audience was completely blown away by this unbelievable conclusion. Fang Qi said he would allow Lin Ming three moves, and in the end, he was defeated in three moves…

Especially the disciples of the Array Faction, they looked like overripe eggplants that had been trampled on. Their complexions were simply beyond ugly. They had been counting on Fang Qi to maliciously stomp on Lin Ming, and let these toads known as the country hick martial artists that they would never be able to eat swan meat. They wanted Fang Qi to show them just what true disparity was. They simply never imagined this result, they could hardly accept it.

Fang Qi had been so completely defeated. If it were them, they would no doubt be in an even worse position!

As Lin Ming arrived at the contestant waiting area, he saw a yellow-clothed girl waiting there for him. This girl was Jing Chanyu.

“Thank you.” Jing Chanyu said in a hushed tone.

“Fang Qi is someone that I would have to defeat sooner or later. You don’t have to thank me.”

“Mm, I know…” Jing Chanyu was silent for a moment, not knowing a topic of conversation to bring up. When Lin Ming had unleashed the Flood Dragon shade behind him, and pierced through Fang Qi’s defensive barriers with a single spear thrust, it had left a deep impression on her.

He was simply like a handsome, peerless god of war, shattering all barriers. Unstoppable!

At this moment, Jiang Lanjian walked over. He and Lin Ming barely knew each other.

“Lin Ming!”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Jiang.” Lin Ming cupped his fists together and bowed. Lin Ming had a good impression of Jiang Lanjian. Jiang Lanjian was a swordsman who pursued the path of the blade with all of his heart and soul. With such a person, there was no need to be reserved or guarded.

In many cases, one could determine the basic character of someone from the cultivation method that they practiced. The Seven Profound Valleys contained both good and evil, but no kind and righteous person would cultivate the dark and wicked legacies of the Acacia Faction. But the disciples of the Sword Faction and Zither Faction were mostly conscientious and virtuous people, they could be considered good people. At least, they weren’t the type that would stab you behind the back. Even if they thirsted for your blood, they would be honest. Otherwise, if their heart was not right, then their Sword Heart or Zither Heart would never reach the stage of Perfection.

“Lin Ming, you just turned 16 years old?” Although he had just heard this news from Jiang Baoyun’s own mouth, Jiang Lanjian had to personally confirm it. This new information had simply been too shocking.

Hearing this question and seeing Lin Ming not answer, Jing Chanyu was suddenly startled. He had just reached 16 years of age!? She unconsciously covered her small mouth with her tender hands, her large eyes blinking as she stared disbelievingly at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming didn’t hesitate, he directly nodded to acknowledge the claim. After all, this was something that he couldn’t conceal. As long as the Seven Profound Valleys wanted to check up on him, they could investigate all the generations of his family with ease.

Although his age was a bit too suspicious, Lin Ming didn’t worry. The more outstanding one’s talent was, the more valuable they would be to the Seven Profound Valleys, and the more resources they could earn.

Looking at a broader view, even if he exposed too many of his powers and some people began to have dark intentions towards him, he could still stand behind Divine Phoenix Island. If he did, these people who harbored evil intentions could do nothing at all.

Lin Ming believed that Mu Qianyu might not necessarily care about him, but he believed that she would help him if he was in a time of dire trouble.

Seeing Lin Ming nod in affirmation, Jing Chanyu gasped.

She was already considered young within all the martial artists that entered the Total Faction Martial Meeting. But she was still two months from reaching 18 years of age. She thought that Lin Ming was similar to her, at most a few months or half a year younger, but she never thought that he would actually only be 16 years old!

A 16 year old boy had participated in the Total Faction Martial Meeting, and also defeated the direct disciple Fang Qi in three moves.

What sort of terrifying result was that?

Even if it were a direct disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys like Jiang Baoyun or Ouyang Ming, they still wouldn’t have such strength at 16 years of age!

Jing Chanyu thought the more she knew of Lin Ming, the less she understood him. Lin Ming was like a massive iceberg, one could only see the tip from the sky. You would only see that insignificant portion of him, without realizing the truly terrifying ability that lay beneath.

Jiang Lanjian took a deep breath, then earnestly and seriously looked at Lin Ming. He recalled the time when he had judged Lin Ming in Desert Flower Hall, saying that if he and Lin Ming were the same level, then there was no way that Lin Ming could be his match… he had never imagined that with just a peak Bone Forging cultivation, Lin Ming was already strong enough to threaten him!

But most importantly, Lin Ming was just too young. Even Jiang Lanjian who had reached Large Success of the Sword Heart began to feel helpless. How many years had Lin Ming practiced the spear? He hadn’t even practicing the spear for the entire time, and yet his spearmanship had already surpassed his own swordsmanship.

“Lin Ming, I’m looking forward to our match!” Jiang Lanjian vigorously exclaimed.

Lin Ming smiled, “We’ll fight soon enough.”

Jiang Lanjian turned around and left, leaving behind a slack-jawed Jing Chanyu.

Jing Chanyu didn’t know what to say at this time. She clearly knew that in the future, Lin Ming would at least become a direct disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys. If the trend of his growth continued, he would easily reach the Xiantian stage, and he might even have an extremely high chance to aim for the Revolving Core realm!

It had to be known that there was only a single Revolving Core master in the entire Seven Profound Valleys. Not only that, but this master was only at the early Revolving Core realm.

If Lin Ming was able to reach the Revolving Core realm, then he most likely wouldn’t be some ordinary Revolving Core master. He was likely to be the most powerful being within the entire Seven Profound territory, he might even become the Elder Ancestor of the Seven Profound Valleys!

As Jing Chanyu thought this, her heartbeat began to rise. Was she actually standing next to someone who would control the fate of the entire Seven Profound territory in the future?

Although Jing Chanyu knew she would have endless benefits and advantages if she befriended someone like Lin Ming, she had never done this type of thing before and approached someone unfamiliar on her own initiative. She didn’t know how she should proceed from this point.

In fact, putting national interests aside, Jing Chanyu quite wanted to know Lin Ming on a more personal, intimate level. But how should she even begin?

At this moment, Qin Xingxuan and Qin Ziya walked over to Lin Ming.

When Lin Ming had heroically defeated Fang Qi on the martial stage, Qin Xingxuan had felt a precocious jolt within her young heart. Especially when Lin Ming had struck out that last spear and continuously shattered all five Nine Revolutions of Blue Light Arrays, sending Fang Qi soaring backwards and spitting blood. At this moment, just remembering that scene, Qin Xingxuan felt goosebumps rise on her arms and her mind surge with emotion.

“Lin Ming, did you consume too much energy?” Qin Ziya asked as he took out a small jade bottle. “This is an Essence Fusing Pill, it’s able to help restore your strength and improve your condition.”

Qin Ziya feared that Lin Ming’s second round would be affected, so he didn’t hesitate in taking out an Essence Fusing pill that cost several true essence stones. This was a restorative pill and therefore didn’t contain pill toxins, one could eat them as they liked.

Lin Ming nodded, he really did need to supplement his own energy reserves. The Heretical God Force had already been used up, and he needed time to compress true essence again. Although the current restoration rate of the Heretical God Force was very quick, he would also need to hurry as fast as he could if he wanted to be able to fully utilize the Heretical God Force during the next round.

Lin Ming immediately took the pills, sat down cross-legged on a cushion, and entered the ethereal martial state to recover.

Suddenly, there was only Qin Ziya, Qin Xingxuan, and Jing Chanyu left.

Qin Xingxuan revealed a well-mannered smiled towards Jing Chanyu, politely saying, “Miss Jing, this is our first time meeting. My name is Qin Xingxuan, I am Lin Ming’s friend.”

Jing Chanyu forced a courtesy smile in return, somewhat embarrassed. She saw that Qin Xingxuan seemed to be around 15 or 16 years old, and was most likely Lin Ming’s girlfriend. Jing Chanyu didn’t want Qin Xingxuan to misunderstand; she only wanted to get to know Lin Ming, there was no other motive.

“I see, so it’s Miss Qin. It’s very nice to meet you.” Jing Chanyu bowed. Although she was someone who focused on cultivation, Jing Chanyu was a young girl in the end, and also had the thoughts of a young girl. Seeing Qin Xingxuan, she unconsciously compared herself to her.

Jing Chanyu thought that her looks weren’t any less than Qin Xingxuan’s. Both of them had different good points in their temperament. Her talent wasn’t inferior to Qin Xingxuan, or at least, there was no clear winner between them, but… Qin Xingxuan was much younger than her. This was something that she couldn’t change…

Jing Chanyu sighed, somewhat defeated. She said, “Chanyu bids farewell.”

“Mm. Miss Jing, please take care.” Qin Xingxuan bowed back and watched Jing Chanyu leave.

Qin Ziya smiled as he watched this interaction, shaking his head. “Xingxuan, let’s go. This is the contestant waiting area, it’s not appropriate for us to stay here too long.”

“Mm, okay.” Qin Xingxuan nodded.

As she was leaving, she couldn’t help but glance back at Lin Ming one more time. At this moment, Lin Ming had already completely entered into the ethereal martial intent state, and wasn’t aware of anything happening around him. During this state, Lin Ming’s consciousness was in meditation. Unless there was imminent danger, he wouldn’t feel anything at all.

……………………….

In the Grand Hall of the Seven Profound Valleys, Mu Qinghong smiled as she watched Lin Ming meditate in the contestant waiting area. This was the ethereal martial intent that Qianyu had informed her about. If she hadn’t been told ahead of time, then she really wouldn’t have been able to detect anything out of place.

“He’s used the power of thunder, and now he’s even used his spear. This little boy still has the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder in his hand, I simply have no idea what could force him to use it.

“Qianyu’s judgement is too good. Not to mention Lin Ming’s high-grade thunder origin energy fusion compatibility or the skill at which he can use his soul force, just the momentum of his spear is far beyond any martial artist of the same level. His spear force is like a mountain, his spear might is like a dragon; it’s just unbelievable that someone so young could reach this point. This is simply an overwhelmingly monstrous perception! That Jiang Baoyun also isn’t too bad, but the results of his swordsmanship just cannot surpass Lin Ming. Jiang Baoyun is someone who cultivates the sword path with all his heart, but he’s also older than Lin Ming by several years. In this aspect, the disparity between them is too great.”

Everyone, including Mu Qianyu, thought that Lin Ming was a once in a millennia rare and gifted spear genius and soul force genius, his perception was just ridiculously high to the point of being preposterous.

What they didn’t know was that Lin Ming’s soul force attacks all relied on his Samsara martial intent.

As for his spear force like mountain, that was because of his extreme Yang and extreme light ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, which also contained the power of the rivers and mountains.

As for his spear might like dragon, that was even simpler. Not only did Lin Ming absorb the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, but his body also contained the blood of a True Dragon. If he could not achieve spear might like dragon, then there might not be anyone else in this world who could.

Mu Qinghong shot a glance at Shi Zongtian by her side. She saw that Shi Zongtian seemed calm, but his eyes shined with light. It was unknown what he was thinking.

Mu Qinghong smirked, she was more or less able to deduce Shi Zongtian’s thoughts. His Seven Profound Valleys had suddenly produced a monstrous talent of the highest level, and yet this talent was suddenly being eyed by her Divine Phoenix Island.

Shi Zongtian was swayed by his own feelings and desires for his sect, and the advantages and disadvantages. He was simply unable to calm down. He even feared that his own prior promises were useless.

Mu Qinghong expected that Shi Zongtian would quickly circulate this news to the Seven Profound Valleys’ Elder Ancestor. A genius of this level was already enough to be brought to the Elder Ancestor’s attention.

Of course, Mu Qinghong did not care about this old fossil who had half a leg in the grave. That old man may be the ultimate dominating force in the Seven Profound territory, but in Divine Phoenix Island he was only an ordinary elder, and not only that, but one that was relegated to the second-tier.

Chapter 266 – Blood King’s Triple Murder

Bang!

A wave of blood soared to the heavens, and even the clouds in the skies parted. The rich true essence surged in the air like ripples in water, visible to even the naked eye. This true essence dispersed, struck the stage protection barrier, and then bounced back.

To the audience, it was as if the entire martial stage had been covered with a faint red tint; it seemed as if blood was floating everywhere in the sky.

“Blood King’s First Murder – Endless Waves!!”

Zhang Yanzhao gave a loud shout, and the treasure sword in his hand turned a brilliant blood red. A rich blood energy suddenly erupted forwards, it was as if countless surges of blood waves were rushing through the air.

As Zhang Yanzhao cut out with his knife, it was like the entire world had been covered by his saber energy; he could cut anything he wanted!

As Lin Ming faced this sword energy that seemed like massive waves of blood that blotted out the sky, Lin Ming also became incomparably serious. True essence poured into the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, and Flow like Silk broke out. At the same time, countless flashes of thunder arched around Lin Ming’s body, spear prestige transformed into a dragon!

A spear thrust out with an unstoppable momentum. 5000 filaments of vibrating true essence pounded wave after bloody wave.

Peng!

Under the vibrating true essence, the waves of blood turned into a shower of blood. It seemed as if crimson lotuses were blooming in the sky. As the waves of blood were torn apart, Lin Ming’s spear and Zhang Yanzhao’s saber collided in midair!

A blood red light flashed, and Lin Ming’s spear pierced the curtain of blood, unstoppable!

Zhang Yanzhao was shocked in his heart. This spear of Lin Ming’s looked simple, but there were profound principles and esoteric truths contained within!

The majestic strength of the world, the power of the strange vibrations, and the wildly savage purple thunder; all three of these powers perfectly fused together, creating an implacable force!

At this moment, he realized Lin Ming’s strength. It wasn’t that Fang Qi was weak, it was only that Mugu Buyu and Lin Ming were too strong. That was the only reason that Fang Qi had been so thoroughly and completely defeated!

The long spear was like a dragon; after breaking through the mist of blood, it pierced towards Zhang Yanzhao’s chest!

At this critical moment, Zhang Yanzhao used his palm as a saber and cut down on the Heavy Profound Soft Spear.

Clang!

The intense impact caused the Heavy Profound Soft Spear to instantly bend like a crescent moon. Zhang Yanzhao grit his teeth as he retreated backwards, his right hand was already stained red with blood!

“What? A spear broke through Zhang Yanzhao’s Blood King’s First Murder, and he was also injured?”

“This is too weird. Didn’t Lin Ming not use a martial skill during that spear strike? Can there be such strength without a martial skill? How terrifying would it be if he did use a martial skill!!?”

To most of the audience, whether it was Zhang Yanzhao or Lin Ming, both of them gave them an unfathomable feeling. During the last Martial Meeting, he had reached the top 20. Now, during this Martial Meeting, he had defeated Liu Yan with just a single saber strike. Liu Yan’s strength probably wasn’t in the top ten, but he could still be around rank 12 or 13; he was definitely not some weak nobody.

There was no need to mention anything about Lin Ming. Against Fang Qi, he had defeated him as if he were just chopping a melon!

However, these matches were not enough to fully explain the level of these two people. Everyone knew that before now, neither of them had used their full strength to fight. This would be a truly powerful battle!

They had thought that the difference in strength between Lin Ming and Zhang Yanzhao wasn’t too great, but they never thought that Zhang Yanzhao would be the first one injured, and so quickly too.

“Second Elder, Zhang Yanzhao seems to be in danger. That Lin Ming had only used a casual spear thrust without any martial skill or technique, and he was able to break through Zhang Yanzhao’s Blood King’s First Murder!” Since Zhang Yanzhao was competing, then naturally people from the Zhang Family would also have come. The group leader was the Second Elder of the Zhang Family.

“No martial skill? Heh, you’re wrong. Lin Ming’s spear skill has fused many unknown principles within – every move he makes is the same as a martial skill!” As the Second Elder gazed at the two people onstage, his pair of deep eyes shined brightly. “Don’t worry, that casual spear thrust is powerful, and it wouldn’t be strange if he had other cards in his hand, but that Blood King’s First Murder that Yanzhao just used was the weakest saber. The second saber will be three times as strong. And the third saber will be three times stronger than the second. Breaking through the first saber doesn’t mean anything at all!

On the martial stage, Zhang Yanzhao’s eyes were brilliant. “Lin Ming, your strength astonishes even me! But you’re wrong if you think you’ll defeat me so easily!”

As Zhang Yanzhao said this, the saber in his hand began to shine. The tiles under Zhang Yanzhao’s feet began to be pulverized by waves of violent air.

“Blood King’s Second Murder – Extermination of Gods and Ghosts!!!”

“Haaah–!”

The blood energy in the air seemed to incinerate, and a crimson vortex appeared on Zhang Yanzhao’s saber, instantly absorbing all of the blood energy everywhere, wiping even the sky clean! Suddenly, the energy condensed onto the saber was several times stronger than before!

Lin Ming was startled. Mm? Once the blood energy from the first saber was fused into the second, the power actually increased so much!

“This is at least three times as strong!” Lin Ming frowned. It wasn’t as if he couldn’t block this saber – he could. The problem was if the second saber’s power had already increased by so much, then what would the third saber be like?

Bang!

Burning waves of blood surged towards Lin Ming. The saber energy was just like a massive river that had suddenly been unleashed from a dam, resulting in an unstoppable flood!

Facing a saber energy that even covered the sky, Lin Ming instantly activated Golden Roc Shattering the Void, his body like a shadow as it retreated. At the same time, the Heavy Profound Soft Spear struck out like a serpent!

Flowers in the Storm!

Puff puff puff puff puff puff!

In that moment, Lin Ming pierced out with hundreds of spear strikes. Each spear contained the power of thunder fused with vibrating true essence.

In this continuous onslaught, the massive wave of blood continued for hundreds of feet, pushing Lin Ming to the edge of the stage before finally dissipating.

The audience hadn’t yet been able to respond to such a quick reversal of fortune. Just awhile ago Lin Ming had broken through Zhang Yanzhao’s first saber, and had even injured him. Now, Lin Ming had been pushed back so far by Zhang Yanzhao’s second saber.

There could only be one explanation, and that was that Zhang Yanzhao’s Blood King’s Triple Murder became increasingly powerful with each saber. Not only that, but the disparity between each strike was gargantuan. If so, then just how strong would the third saber be? How would Lin Ming deal with it?

The disciples of the 36 countries couldn’t help but feel nervous for Lin Ming, their faces dripping with anxious sweat.

“Haha, good!”

A Zhang Family elder laughed. In all of Lin Ming’s matches so far, no one had been able to push him back. Now, he was actually forced back hundreds of feet by Zhang Yanzhao’s saber.

Moreover, this was only the second saber of the Blood King’s Triple Murder. The third saber would be three times stronger than even the second saber. The Zhang Family elder wanted to see just how Lin Ming would be able to block that.

“Yanzhao has already won half the battle. Now, even if Lin Ming has a hidden card in his hand, it still might not be enough to block the third saber!”

“Mm. If Yanzhao can defeat Lin Ming here, then that would be a great advantage to my Zhang Family’s momentum. This match is just too important!” The Second Elder confidently spoke this as he stroked his beard.

The Zhang Family had been hiding their strength for the last several hundred years. Now, it was finally time to begin their revival; there was just no significance in blindly and constantly hiding their family’s resources. On the contrary, what they had to do was expand their family’s influence. The more influence they had, the more powerhouses they could hire to join their family.

“There is still the last saber. Lin Ming, I want to see how you’ll block this!” As Zhang Yanzhao said this, his entire body erupted with a surge of true essence. He lifted the Blood Wave Saber high above his head, and the entire saber began to blaze with a brilliant light. The true essence of his body was just like a flood that was being held back by the treasure sword in his hands.

Lin Ming could clearly feel that the true essence reserves in Zhang Yanzhao’s body were rapidly depleting!

“This is truly worthy of being called an Earth-step treasure sword; it can actually store so much true essence!”

When Lin Ming used Thunderfire Annihilation, he would instantly consume 40% of his true essence, and that was because he had to suffuse his true essence into the Heretical God Seed. The Heretical God Seed was simply a bottomless pit. But if Lin Ming tried to pour his true essence into the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, it wouldn’t take much true essence before the Heavy Profound Soft Spear reached its limit. Looking at it from this aspect, the disparity between a medium-grade human-step treasure and an earth-step treasure was simply like clouds and mud!

“No wonder it is said that the Blood King’s Triple Murder needs the Earth-step treasure Blood Wave Saber in order to display its power, it was for this reason. A human-step treasure simply cannot contain that much true essence.

Within a breath of time, Zhang Yanzhao had already poured over 50% of his true essence into the Blood Wave Saber. In addition to the consumption of the last two sabers, Zhang Yanzhao didn’t even have 30% of his total true essence remaining.

He was staking everything on this, a single saber to decide victory or defeat!

“This is my strongest ability! Blood King’s Absolute Murder – Heaven and Earth Collapse!”

Zhang Yanzhao loudly bellowed, and he suddenly rose several hundreds of feet into the air;  everything under his feet had become meaningless!

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. The power of Zhang Yanzhao’s saber was actually three times stronger than the last! It kept rising by three times every time! In comparison to the first saber, Zhang Yanzhao’s third saber was nine times stronger!

Even if Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force and increased his power by 60%, he still wouldn’t be able to block this saber. If he wished to confront his opponent head-on, he either had to use the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder or Thunderfire Annihilation.

However, Lin Ming didn’t want to use these two trump cards against Zhang Yanzhao.

That was because he still had another card in his hand – reverse scale blood!

With the fusion of the True Dragon Energy’s azure true essence, it would continually grow, endlessly!

Not only was this kind of true essence all-conquering, able to break through any defense, it was tenacious and difficult to destroy. Although it wasn’t eternal like a Flame Essence, if one wished to destroy it, they needed multiple times the true essence in order to wear it down.

This was the everlasting concept that existed forever within the True Dragon – eternal and immortal power!

As for the present Lin Ming, he could not achieve true immortality. That was because his cultivation was limited and he wasn’t able to display the full might of the reverse scale blood.

Even so, this endless true essence was not so easy to destroy.

“Roar!”

With the resonant and majestic cry of a dragon, Lin Ming’s aura shot into the clouds, piercing the heavens, and the reverse scale blood completely fused into his true essence.

At that moment, Mu Qinghong, who had been sitting in the Grand Hall, was shocked in her heart, her beautiful face suddenly changing color!

This… this is…

Mu Qinghong had lived in Divine Phoenix Island for many years, and she had the bloodline of the Vermillion Bird injected within her body. As she heard that loud dragon’s cry a moment ago, she felt the bloodline within her body tremble in fear!

“Could this… could this be the strange Flood Dragon bloodline that Qianyu had mentioned?”

She helplessly watched as the shade of a Flood Dragon appeared behind Li Ming once again. Compared to before, this time it was even more real. The more she looked at it, the less it seemed like a Flood Dragon. It was as if… as if… True Dragon!?!?

Long spear manifesting dragon!

It was a true blue, genuine long spear manifesting dragon! Heavens! How old was he again!?

A spear genius of this level was unprecedented from ancient times until now!

Bang!

The vibrating true essence that contained the energy of the True Dragon intensely impacted against the Blood King’s Absolute Murder! Lin Ming’s true essence had transformed into a deep azure color, standing out in stark contrast to the deep dark red that stained everywhere; it was an incomparably gorgeous and dazzling sight!

It was as if space was torn apart. Intense red shockwaves violently impacted everywhere, alarmingly dire waves of blood frothing forth. But in the midst of these crazy and turbulent waves, a bright azure colored spear light pierced through, thrusting straight towards Zhang Yanzhao’s chest!

Zhang Yanzhao’s triumphant expression instantly froze.

Puff!

It was like his chest had been struck by a mountain. Zhang Yanzhao spat out a mouthful of blood, and he flew backwards like a broken ragdoll.

Chapter 270 – Concept Showdown

Lin Ming had already comprehended the Concept of Wind a long time ago. The basis for his comprehension of the Concept of Wind was the top movement skill from the Realm of the Gods, ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’.

‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ was created by a senior Supreme Elder who had watched the cataclysmic battle between a Golden-winged Roc and a True Dragon. Afterwards, he had gone into closed seclusion for 60 years to meditate and comprehend the deep mysteries behind it. It could be said that the wind-attribute God Beast, the Golden-winged Roc, was the original ancestor of all wind. If the Concept of Wind was comprehended from its movements, the lofty heights of its boundary could be imagined!

Lin Ming’s perception wasn’t amazingly high, but it was by no means low. After a very long time, he had been able to trace upon the most basic superficial knowledge of ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’. Still, this little bit wasn’t something that a normal martial artist of the Sky Spill Continent could ever compare to. Even a wind-attribute martial artist who thoroughly studied wind true essence for their entire life would not be able to achieve something like this.

This could be called different starting points between their comprehensions of the Concept of Wind. Lin Ming’s starting point was simply much, much higher, it wasn’t something that a disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys could catch up to if they diligently trained for their entire life. It was just like how a common martial artist had a completely different starting point compared to a disciple of a great sect.

Although Lin Ming had understood a very high boundary of the Concept of Wind, it terms of utilizing its abilities, he could only find out through his own experiences. Lin Ming understood how to use the Concept of Wind for movement, but he didn’t know that the Concept of Wind could also be used in attacking.

‘I have to see just how the Concept of Wind can be used offensively, this is just a wonderful inspiration!’ Lin Ming activated his soul force, tracing each and every action of Jiang Lanjian’s movements with his perception.

Jiang Lanjian’s sword seemed to be fused into the air. One couldn’t even see the blade, they only saw brilliantly flashing sword lights.

Hu hu hu hu!

All of the surrounding wind was attracted by Jiang Lanjian’s sword energy, creating a massive cyclone.

…….

“It’s getting windy here!” Everyone in the audience felt a sudden change with the wind in the air, as if every single air current was converging onto the center of the stage.

“How is this possible? The martial stage has protective array formations, Jiang Lanjian’s true essence shouldn’t be able to break through it!”

Many of the disciples expressed surprise and wonder. At this moment, a Sword Faction disciple stuck out his chest and proudly said, “Heh, what do you know? A Concept is a power of Laws! Senior-apprentice Brother Jiang has already firmly grasped the power of a Law; it’s just as if he were overlooking us from the top of the highest cliff. How could this power that comes from the origin of all existence be stopped by a Houtian level protection array!?”

The Power of Laws… it didn’t even need to break through, but could still penetrate a Houtian level array formation? Regardless of whether it was a disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys, 36 countries, or 16 martial families, all of them were beyond startled. This was simply too abnormal!

“If one can comprehend a Concept, they can ignore an array formation? Then can an Array Faction disciple who has comprehended a Concept fight against someone who has also comprehended a Concept?” A martial artist from the 36 countries humbly asked.

The Sword Faction disciple looked at that disciple with disdain, “Humph, you think that it’s so easy to comprehend a Concept? Its power is just too remote for the likes of you. Let alone your 36 countries, even in the entire younger generation of our Seven Profound Valleys, the number of people who have managed to comprehend a Concept can be counted on a single hand!”

“It’s not difficult to use an array formation to suppress a Concept, it just needs an array master to also have comprehended that Concept and then add that Concept into the array formation!

Can be counted on a single hand?

Hearing this number, many of the disciples present gasped. When this disciple mentioned younger generation, that meant all disciples that were 26 or younger. That included not just the geniuses of this Total Faction Martial Meeting, but even the disciples of the last Martial Meeting, and the Martial meeting before that.

With all of these talents added together, the number of people who have managed to comprehend a Concept still could be counted on a single hand?

If this number was true, then Jiang Lanjian’s perception was absolutely monstrous. If it wasn’t for the even more abnormal Jiang Baoyun, then Jiang Lanjian would certainly have been the Sword Faction’s direct disciple.

On the martial stage, the wind was blowing faster and faster, the air currents gathering to an extreme. Jiang Lanjian moved, his body suddenly blurring.

“Absolute Murder Breeze Blade!”

In that instant, all the wind in the air seemed to come to a standstill. Jiang Lanjian thrust out his sword, and 72 fierce sword energies molded into wind blades that pierced towards Lin Ming’s side.

However, Jiang Lanjian’s sword had vanished into the wind; the wind of the world was his sword!

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with a bright light. True essence poured into the wind, and the sword melted into the wind. Using the wind as a sword, this was another way to utilize the Concept of Wind?

The long spear in Lin Ming’s hand began to tremble, the vibrating true essence within howling into the air, responding to Lin Ming’s desire to block Jiang Lanjian’s sword energy.

But at this moment, his pupils suddenly contracted.

Lin Ming hadn’t imagined that the first thing he would see coming at him was not the sword energy that Jiang Lanjian had released, but the hardened eyes of Jiang Lanjian!

Mm!?

Lin Ming was shocked, his movement speed was actually quicker than the sword energy!?!

Cha!

The longsword drew out an arc. Jiang Lanjian was actually a step faster than his own sword energy, he arrived in front of Lin Ming first, his sword stabbing out!

At such a close distance and with the fast sword fused with the Concept of Wind, it was impossible for Lin Ming to dodge, and he didn’t have time to lift his spear! At this critical moment, Lin Ming’s palm formed a saber, and he slapped down on Jiang Lanjian’s sword!

Keeping off a saber with his hand!?

This was madness, utter madness!

The minds of everyone in the audience flashed with this thought. A sword and a spear were different. It was possible to keep off a spear by pushing down on the spear shaft, but a sword had two bladed sides, and this sword also contained an incomparably keen sword energy. Not only that, but the sword wielder was the sword talent Jiang Lanjian!

Even darksteel would be cut apart by Jiang Lanjian’s sword!

Did Lin Ming not want this hand anymore!?

In that flash of light, the audience simply didn’t have time to reflect on what was happening. Lin Ming’s hand had already slapped down on top of the sword!

A turbulent azure true essence raged out!

The vibrating true essence was just like the tide of the ocean as it rushed the sword blade.

Chi chi chi!

Jiang Lanjian’s blade was severely sharp, it endlessly sliced open true essence, but the azure true essence was simply endless; it could not be cut apart!

Jiang Lanjian was greatly surprised, he tried to arouse the true essence in his body to break apart Lin Ming’s azure true essence, but at this moment, he felt his own sword violently shake. Lin Ming’s true essence had penetrated through to his sword, scattering his sword energy.

“What!?”

Jiang Lanjian was shocked, he immediately pulled back his sword and withdrew like a storm. But in the moment that he retreated, the 72 sword energies that he had released earlier rushed around him, piercing towards Lin Ming!

This was the sword energy that he had previously sent forth. He had fused them completely into the wind. From the start until now, there had been no gap in this all-out attack, it was simply overwhelming!

Lin Ming had just blocked Jiang Lanjian’s attack, and hadn’t yet fully recovered from it. He was just unable to resist this blow!

Lin Ming shouted out and flew backwards. At the same time, the azure light protecting him suddenly rose like a deep sea sun!

Heretical God Force – open!

The azure true essence poured out without reservation, torrent upon torrent of blazing blue light!

Puff puff puff puff puff puff puff!

Although he had just managed to barely force away most of the sword energy, part of the sharp sword energy that contained the Concept of Wind managed to pierce through the true essence protecting Lin Ming. Even though he had opened the Heretical God Force, that sword energy had still made its way through and cut into his flesh!

However, Lin Ming’s bodily defense had transformed after his experience in the Sorcerer Pagoda, and his body was tough to an abnormal degree!

As blood oozed from his wounds, Lin Ming was forced back dozens of feet until he stopped. He had been injured by 13 sword strokes!

After the azure true essence that protected his body weakened, the sword energy also weakened. As it cut into Lin Ming’s tough flesh, it only cut less than an inch deep. To a martial artist with true essence at the Altering Muscle or Bone Forging stage, this could only be considered a light superficial wound!

Seeing Lin Ming stand on the martial stage as if nothing had happened, the audience all gaped at him.

This… was Lin Ming’s body made from iron? Even iron would have been reduced to pieces!

He had kept off the sword with his hand. The hand was fine, and the sword had been forced away!

He had used his body to directly withstand the sword energy, and he had only received a light wound!

This defensive power was just an anomaly!

It had to be said that the sword and sword energy were sent out by Jiang Lanjian! And he had also fused the Concept of Wind into his strikes!

The offensive attack power of the Sword Faction was number one within the entire Seven Profound Valleys! And Jiang Lanjian was the second ranked talent of the Sword Faction’s younger generation. His sword energy could easily slice apart darksteel!

In the contestant waiting area, Zhang Yanzhao was surging with emotions, his skin crawling with goosebumps. He imagined that if he had exchanged places with Lin Ming and had to face Jiang Lanjian who could use the Concept of Wind, then he would be defeated without a doubt! This…was simply too depressing a thought.

Let alone the late 72 sword energies, Zhang Yanzhao wouldn’t even be able to keep off that first sword strike of Jiang Lanjian’s. It was simply too fast!

There was no way he could keep off a sword with just his hands. When he had fought Lin Ming, he had used his own hand to stop Lin Ming’s spear shaft, and his hand had almost shattered. If he tried to keep off Jiang Lanjian’s sword, then he might as well cut off his own hand.

“This is the trump card that Jiang Lanjian has? He actually comprehended the Concept of Wind! If Jiang Lanjian hadn’t encountered Lin Ming this time, then how many people would have been able to block his sword skill? This Lin Ming is just too abnormal. If a sword skill like that cannot defeat him, then exactly what can?”

…………….

On the martial stage, Lin Ming was holding his spear as he stood, staring at Jiang Lanjian. ‘The Concept of Wind is truly endless and crafty in its usage. It is simply traceless! Jiang Lanjian is truly a genius; he managed to simultaneously fuse the Concept of Wind into his own attack and movements and create his own sword technique. If it wasn’t for my fortuitous encounters in the Sorcerer Pagoda, I would have been defeated by this sword! If just Jiang Lanjian is this powerful, then what degree will Jiang Baoyun have arrived at? It seems I mistakenly underestimated the geniuses of the Seven Profound Valleys, after all, they are 3 or 4 years older than me!’

Jiang Lanjian’s eyes shined brightly. ‘The sword energy was useless against him? That azure true essence that protects Lin Ming is too strong. Not only that, but his body’s defensive capabilities are astonishing. I really do not know what is so peculiar about his body, or how he managed to cultivate that azure true essence!’

‘If sword energy is useless, then I can only directly attack with my sword!’

As Jiang Lanjian took a step forwards, the Concept of Wind rose up again!

“Seven Swords Absolute Summit!”

The sword light entered into the wind. This time, Jiang Lanjian chose to directly attack with his sword.

Without the strange sword energy, Jiang Lanjian’s attack was much clearer. Lin Ming stimulated his azure vibrating true essence, and dispersed Jiang Lanjian’s attack with a single spear strike!

However, although the attack was repulsed, the sword energy stayed. The sword energy had fused with the Concept of Wind – it could not be scattered. Whether it was a saber, sword, spear, or any other weapon, none of them were able to cut the wind!

As the two youths fought, their battle became fiercer and faster, but Lin Ming’s heart was becoming increasingly clear.

‘This wind will never disperse, so the sword energy will also not disperse. This way of attacking with the Concept of Wind… I understand it!’

‘Then I’ll just have to experience for myself how to fuse the Concept of Wind into the spear!’

In a split-second when Jiang Lanjian’s sword was drawn back, Lin Ming’s spear suddenly turned into countless phantom mirages…

“Flowers in the Storm!”

Out of all the moves in the ‘Foundation Spear Technique’, none of them were more suitable to display the Concept of Wind than Flowers in the Storm!

The spear light fused into the wind, with no shadow and no form. True essence suddenly swelled forth, and the wind on the stage suddenly turned into countless sharp blades that pierced towards Jiang Lanjian!

This sudden turn of events caused Jiang Lanjian to cry out in surprise. With a stuffy cough, he anxiously retreated. As he tried to suppress the roiling blood in his body, he cast an incredulous look towards Lin Ming.

“This… this is…”

“Concept of Wind!?!??”

This is impossible!

Impossible!

Chapter 271 – Stealing From A Master

Jiang Lanjian’s face flashed with bewilderment. Lin Ming had obviously used the Concept of Wind a moment ago. Not only that, but he was able to faintly feel that Lin Ming’s Concept of Wind boundary was even higher than his own! It was as if he had touched upon the origin of all wind!

How was this possible?

There was complete silence in the entire area for several breaths of time. Suddenly, the noisy sound of discussion broke the quiet.

“Lin Ming actually comprehended the Concept of Wind? How did that happen?”

The Sword Faction disciple that had been so haughtily explaining the difficulty in comprehending the Concept of Wind to everyone around him that would listen, suddenly found himself unable to accept this new reality. In the entire Seven Profound Valleys’ younger generation, the number of people that could understand a Concept could be counted on a single hand, and they had all did so in their later years when they had reached 19 or 20 years of age.

But as for Lin Ming, he was a mere 16 years old, and he also came from the pitiful background of the 36 countries. Who had taught him how to comprehend the Concept of Wind? Had he learnt it himself?

“Haha! You just said that we 36 countries’ disciples couldn’t comprehend the Concept of Wind, and look at that! Now what, huh!?” All of the 36 countries’ disciples that heard the bragging of the Sword Faction disciple suddenly felt extremely proud and glorious. Before, they had been talked down to like little country bumpkins who had wandered into a bustling major city, and their hearts had already lit with a simmering fire. Before, they didn’t know what a Concept of Wind was, nor that Lin Ming had also managed to understand it, so they could only shut up as others boasted around them.

Now, they could finally come back.

“Haha, a little pitiful Concept of Wind, even if the Seven Profound Valleys doesn’t have over 5 people that can comprehend it, it’s not anything to someone as cool and awesome as Lin Ming.”

“Maybe Lin Ming hadn’t even understood the Concept of Wind, but comprehended it after watching Jiang Lanjian display it. Comprehending this sort of small fry stuff would probably only take Lin Ming half an incense stick of time.”

“Right, right, right! Or else why would Lin Ming drag this fight out for so long? The reason is because he was meditating on the Concept of Wind from Jiang Lanjian’s blade!

This disciple’s wonderful fantasies were immediately approved and welcomed by everyone. In their minds, the Concept of Wind sounded very powerful, but to the omnipotent Lin Ming, it should be enough just tossing it a few thoughts, it was just absolutely nothing.

Hearing this idea spread through the crowd, the Seven Profound Valleys’ Sword Faction disciple could only force a smile, he was disinclined to argue with them. Did they think that the Concept of Wind was some cabbage that they could eat whenever they wanted?

In the Grand Hall of the Seven Profound Valleys, several Great Elders had the feeling that this was something they couldn’t immediately accept, even if placed in front of them; they had simply never seen a genius of this level before.

If he could actually comprehended a Concept, then there was probably nothing else that Lin Ming couldn’t!

A Sword Faction Great Elder lamentably shook his head and said, “Lin Ming not only comprehended the Concept of Wind, but the boundary at which he’s done so is very high. Unfortunately, Lanjian’s Concept of Wind was his final trump card, but it’s too bad he’s only showing off his meager skill in front of a true expert.”

Shi Zongtian was silent. Jiang Lanjian was already considered a talent among talents, and the Concept of Wind was sufficiently powerful to be called one’s secret card.

What a pity it was that Jiang Lanjian’s match was against Lin Ming.

As Mu Qinghong looked at the amazing expressions on these old elders’ faces, the smile that crossed hers was growing more and more. She felt that Lin Ming was simply an endless trove of treasure, he always brought new and wonderful surprises.

Something like the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder could be said to be obtained by luck or fortune. Individual cultivation could be enhanced by valuable materials or other rare medicines and treasure. But as for Lin Ming’s comprehension of the Concept of Wind, spear skills, and martial intent, all of those depended on his own heart of martial arts and monstrous perception. There was no fortuitous encounter that could ever help him with that.

Spear path, Concept, martial intent, soul force; Lin Ming had made startling progress in all four of these major aspects. Not only that, but his cultivation could also be considered at the pinnacle of his age, and he also had a high thunder origin energy fusion compatibility. With his mere Bone Forging cultivation, he had managed to absorb the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, and his body seemed to contain the bloodline of some ancient beast.

Lin Ming’s existence had already exceeded the limits of common sense.

Mu Qinghong secretly thought, “Even Qianyu hadn’t completely understood Lin Ming, he is even more wonderful than she had imagined! My Divine Phoenix Island will never let go of a talent like this.”

On the martial stage, Jiang Lanjian heaved a heavy sigh. “Lin Ming, I, Jiang Lanjian have never witnessed someone of your talent in my life. I might have already lost this match, but until the final moment, I will not put down my sword!”

Jiang Lanjian brought his sword in front of him, directed straight at Lin Ming.

“Good, I also want to enjoy a satisfying battle with you.” Lin Ming brightly laughed and then smiled at Jiang Lanjian. Jiang Lanjian’s words were just what he had hoped for, he also wanted to continue dueling with Jiang Lanjian and attain more inspirations about the Concept of Wind.

“Graceful Sword!”

Jiang Lanjian thrust his sword out again, and a strong wind howled around him. Lin Ming’s spear had also fused into the wind, and under the blessing of the Concept of Wind, his spear speed had reached a terrifying degree. One could listen to the sharp cries as the long spear broke through the wind; it seemed as if spear shadows covered the sky!

If there was a weakness in Lin Ming’s spearmanship, that would be that his attack speed was too slow!

But in truth, this really could not be considered a shortcoming. A spear was originally a heavy weapon meant to be used against armies. It emphasized oppressing and overwhelming all opposition by brute strength; it was simply impossible for it to display such an extreme speed like a sword.

Therefore, when Lin Ming had been facing Jiang Lanjian’s sword light that seemed everywhere, he was only able to rely on his vibrating true essence to fend it off.

But now, with the Concept of Wind behind his back, his spear wasn’t actually much slower than Jiang Lanjian’s sword!

Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding!

In a few breathes of time, it was unknown how many times Lin Ming and Jiang Lanjian’s spear and sword had exchanged blows. Lin Ming’s speed hadn’t fallen at all!

Even the surrounding wind began to fall under Lin Ming’s sway, condensing into sharp wind blades that attacked Jiang Lanjian!

The elders in the Seven Profound Valleys’ Grand Hall were becoming more and more flabbergasted as they watched the match go on. They had thought that Lin Ming’s comprehension of the Concept of Wind was at a very high state, but they realized that even they had  underestimated him. As this match progressed, Lin Ming was becoming increasingly deft with the Concept of Wind; it was already far beyond anything Jiang Lanjian could hope to compare with.

“I can’t imagine how he managed to contemplate this!” The Sword Faction’s Great Elder sighed with emotion. To have a 1200 jin Heavy Profound Soft Spear keep up with the speed of a longsword, Lin Ming’s comprehension of the Concept of Wind was simply inconceivable.

“I feel like… as Lin Ming continues to progress in this match, it seems that Lin Ming is imitating Lanjian’s moves!”

“Mm!?”

As an elder casually spoke his thoughts, all of them became startled!

Jiang Lanjian’s Graceful Sword was able to hide the sword blade in the wind. When he did so, Lin Ming also hid his spear in the wind!

When Jiang Lanjian condensed blades of wind to attack, so did Lin Ming.

When Jiang Lanjian fused the sword energy into the wind so that the wind would not disperse and the sword energy would not disperse, Lin Ming also fused his spear light into the wind – it was almost the exact same process!

“He is studying Lanjian’s styles.”

“Heavens… did he not comprehend the Concept of Wind before this, and suddenly comprehended it during this fight against Lanjian?”

“That’s impossible, no talent can be like such. He must have comprehended it a long time ago, but didn’t have a master to teach him. He was only able to rely on his heaven defying perception to comprehend the Concept of Wind, but didn’t understand just how to use it to attack. Now, he’s found inspiration in Lanjian’s sword, and his self-taught Concept of Wind has already surpassed Lanjian by many degrees. This young boy its just too terrifying!”

On the martial stage, the outcome was already clear to all. Over 90% of the power of wind was sent by Lin Ming. As for Jiang Lanjian, he wasn’t even able to muster 10% of the power of wind.

Bang!

As Jiang Lanjian met Lin Ming’s attack, he was forced backwards dozens of feet. He wiped off the blood from the corners of his mouth and put away the longsword in his hand, “I admit defeat.”

“Thank you!”

Lin Ming cupped his hands together in respect. He did not say the more formal and polite ‘well fought’, but instead thanked him. This was naturally because in this fight, Jiang Lanjian had taught him much about how to use the Concept of Wind to attack.

The memories of the Realm of the Gods’ Supreme Elder was incomparably fragmented, there were very few complete memories. Although Lin Ming was able to comprehend the Concept of Wind, the memories of the methods of utilization were lost. If it wasn’t for Jiang Lanjian, then it would have been a long time before he was able to utilize the Concept of Wind in different ways.

“Lin Ming, victory!”

With the announcement from the referee elder, many of the Seven Profound Valleys’ disciples gasped together.

Jiang Lanjian had also been defeated!

Qin Wuxin who had mastered Large Success of her Zither Heart, or Huo Yanluo who controlled a Flame Essence, could either of them stop Lin Ming’s winning streak?

Lin Ming turned around to spot Jiang Baoyun watching him in the midst of the crowd. Jiang Baoyun’s two eyes pierced him like twin sword lights, it was impossible not to notice.

Jiang Baoyun faintly smiled. Lin Ming also politely returned a smile, but his heart was feeling quite cold.

Although Lin Ming had defeated Jiang Lanjian, he didn’t feel relaxed at all. In this match, he had already used all of his cards besides Thunderfire Annihilation and the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder.

He had already shown the azure true essence, Concept of Wind, Heretical God Force, and Flow like Silk.

All these abilities had been used, and yet he had still been injured!

Jiang Lanjian’s Absolute Murder Breeze Blade was too strong. It was not that Lin Ming didn’t want to dodge, but that he couldn’t.

It could be said that if Lin Ming hadn’t ‘stolen’ the method to utilize the Concept of Wind in attacks and deprived Jiang Lanjian of his control over the wind, then it would have been extremely difficult for him to win the match!

Now seeing Jiang Baoyun’s smile, Lin Ming suddenly remembered that from the start until now, he had never seen an expression of panic, surprise, or astonishment on Jiang Baoyun’s face.

Maybe this was because Jiang Baoyun had reached Large Success of his Sword Heart, but it was most likely because he had absolute belief in his own ability!

Regardless of whether it was Mugu Buyu’s Essence Integration, Lin Ming’s own hidden cards coming out one after another, or even Huo Yanluo’s shocking Flame Essence, Jiang Baoyun had maintained a tranquil expression through all of it, just like a light spring afternoon.

The feeling he gave off was as if everything was in the grasp of his palm.

Then… what were Jiang Baoyun’s own hidden cards? What did he rely on to be so confident in himself?

If Jiang Lanjian, the second ranked disciple of the Sword Faction was already so formidable, then how strong was the direct disciple, Jiang Baoyun? Just what were the limits of his strength?

Lin Ming let out a long breath. He realized that his own chances of defeating Jiang Baoyun were not high at all!

The Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was without a doubt an attack with a monstrous attack power. But a battle didn’t look at whose attack power was stronger, but rather who could win.

In terms of attack power, Jiang Lanjian was still inferior to Zhang Yanzhao.

But Zhang Yanzhao could not win against Jiang Lanjian!

This was because he would have already lost before he used the Blood King’s Triple Murder!

Like this, could he defeat Jiang Baoyun using the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder?

The Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was amazingly strong, but if it could not strike Jiang Baoyun, then it was completely useless.

Would Jiang Baoyun’s sword be slower than the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder? Could he dodge it?

Lin Ming surmised the outcome of the future match in his heart, and realized that as long as Jiang Baoyun’s sword speed had reached a certain level, and he comprehended another Concept besides the Concept of Wind, then he would definitely lose!

Besides the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, Lin Ming also had Thunderfire Annihilation. But, because the Flame Essence was much weaker and thus imbalanced, Thunderfire Annihilation wouldn’t be much stronger than the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder. Not only that, but the consumption of energy was tremendous and it took a long period of time to wind up. The Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder was currently a much more practical move.

‘It looks like I underestimated the Seven Profound Valleys’ direct disciples. With Jiang Baoyun’s talent, he would also be fantastic if placed within a fourth-grade sect. Not only that, but he is older than me by three years!’

Chapter 277 – Against The Fire Dragon

The Refiner Faction disciples spoke with great enthusiasm. At their side, a young Zither Faction girl was not happy. “What do you mean? If our Senior-apprentice Sister hadn’t encountered some abnormal fellow, then she would absolutely still have complete victories now. Are you saying that our Senior-apprentice Sister is weaker than your Huo Yanluo?”

“Hehe, we’re not saying that.” The several Refiner Faction disciples lewdly smiled, their eyes involuntarily scanning up and down the body of the young Zither Faction girl’s body.

The Refiner Faction disciples were almost all men. It was because in the mortal world, their refining occupation would be equivalent to a blacksmith. There were very few women that were willing to withstand striking iron for hours on end and endure the harsh conditions. These young men almost never saw women, and now they witnessed rows upon rows of beautiful Zither Faction girls here, it was simply an intense visual shock. They couldn’t help but salivate and continue gulping over and over.

The Zither Faction girl was disgusted as she saw these vulgar young men. She icily said, “Just you wait. Sooner or later your Senior-apprentice Brother Huo will have to battle with our Senior-apprentice Sister Qin. Then you’ll be able to see just how fierce the Profound Wind Eight Melodies is.”

“Haha, the Profound Wind Eight Melodies only sounds scary. This morning, wasn’t it that bumpkin Lin Ming from the 36 countries that broke through that technique in a single attempt? Our Senior-apprentice Brother Huo has a medium-grade human-step Flame Essence in his control, who can break something like that? Let alone Lin Ming, even if it were Jiang Baoyun or Mugu Buyu, if they ran into our Senior-apprentice Brother’s Flame Essence, they would still have to retreat!”

“Aren’t you afraid of the wind cutting your worthlessly flapping tongue? According to your own words, do you actually think your Senior-apprentice Brother Huo can  take first place?”

“I didn’t say for sure that he will take number one, I only said that no one can block Senior-apprentice Brother’s Flame Essence. At most, they can only evade it. A medium-grade human-step Flame Essence is a power that a Pulse Condensation martial artist just can’t resist.” The Refiner Faction disciple’s words were thick with a refined sense of superiority.

He condescendingly waved and continued, “You’re not a Refiner Faction disciple so you have no idea what significance a Flame Essence has! Your Senior-apprentice Sister Qin losing to Lin Ming is a undeniable fact, and our Senior-apprentice Brother Huo keeping his winning streak is also an undeniable fact. Even if he meets Ouyang Ming or Lin Ming, Senior-apprentice Brother Huo can still fight! Once he takes out the Flame Essence, he has at least a 50-50 chance of winning! If he went up against your Senior-apprentice Sister Qin, then… hehe, I’m afraid that all of her clothes would be burnt off by fire!”

“You… shameless hooligan!” The Zither Faction girl glared angrily at the Refiner Faction boys.

“Hehe, us brothers are good enough, would you like to try us?”

The disciples of both sides argued, their dispute growing more and more fierce. The Refiner Faction disciples had extremely salacious expressions. Although they couldn’t eat these beautiful women in front of them, they could at least take liberties and sexually harass them. As for the young girl of the Zither Faction, her face was filled with utter loathing.

At this moment, the referee announced, “Eleventh round, first match. Lin Ming against Huo Yanluo!”

Hearing this, the Refiner Faction disciple seemed a bit muddled. The Zither Faction girl’s eyes immediately brightened. She had been hoping that Huo Yanluo would hurry up and fight with Qin Wuxin so that she could show this Refiner Faction disciple just who was better. But although it wasn’t Qin Wuxin, going up against Lin Ming was also good.

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, you can do it! I’m cheering for you!”

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, kill that bastard Huo in a second!”

“Junior-apprentice Brother Lin, we love you!”

In the audience, the young female disciples of the Zither Faction were cheering for Lin Ming, their sweet voices crisp and clear. Maybe because it was the influence of their well-groomed temperament, but their cheering began to find an identical rhythm, and soon their cheers were loud enough to shock everyone around them, and attract the attention of the entire audience.

Lin Ming was also flabbergasted. He looked at that crowd of extremely beautiful girls that were cheering for him, and his expression turned a little strange as he traced his nose.

“I don’t think I know them…”

Lin Ming had already been in many matches. Because this was the home stage of the Seven Profound Valleys, the so-called ‘cheers’ that Lin Ming had received so far were jeers and heckling from the crowd. But now, for the first time, there were actually people unexpectedly cheering for him. Not only that, but it was a rabid mass of frantic young girls, this caused Lin Ming to not really be able to enjoy his first fans here.

In the audience, Qin Xingxuan looked at the crowd of young Zither Faction girls with a bit of confusion and puzzlement. But then, this puzzlement immediately switched to a wary vigilance.

Although Qin Xingxuan’s natural temperament was tranquil and calm, she was still a young girl and had the sensitivities of a young girl. She quickly realized that at the end of this tournament, Lin Ming was destined to join the Seven Profound Valleys. But as for herself, she might need to wait several years before she could join. Thinking of the beautiful girls of the Zither Faction and Mirage Faction, Qin Xingxuan felt a sudden sinking sense of crisis in her heart. If such a group of Linmaniacs had developed in only several days, then she had no idea what would happen in the future.

As the young girls of the Zither Faction cheered for Lin Ming, the Refiner Faction disciples naturally wouldn’t let themselves be outdone.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Huo, we believe in you!”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Huo, wreck him!”

The two sides’ cheers were in sharp opposition of each other. On the martial stage, Huo Yanluo didn’t have complete assurance that he would win, Lin Ming’s strength had been evident for anyone to see. But as long as he had the Flame Essence in his hand, Huo Yanluo also had faith he could fight on even terms.

“You are very strong. Before this Martial Meeting began, I never would have imagined you would come this far. You defeated Fang Qi, Jiang Lanjian, and Qin Wuxin one after another. But don’t think that defeating them means that you’ve defeated me! The way that I fight is completely different!” As Huo Yanluo said this, he took out an exaggeratedly large red sword from his spatial ring. He hadn’t even poured true essence into it, and yet a scorching heat wave blew out, as if he were holding onto a burning red-hot iron rod.

“Words are meaningless, let’s fight!” Lin Ming took out his Heavy Profound Soft Spear, and a surge of momentum flowed out with it.

“Match, start!”

With the referee’s announcement, Huo Yanluo stimulated all of the true essence in his body. The high-grade human-step treasure sword in his hand kindled with brilliant Abyssal Flames!

This treasure sword was called the Abyss Blade. It was crafted after Huo Yanluo had obtained a Flame Essence, and personally tailored towards his strengths by a Refiner Faction elder. A massive amount of precious and rare materials had been used in its production, so much that its soaring cost equaled that of a normal earth-step treasure. It was only because there had been excessive care in trying to increase the power of fire origin energy within the blade that caused a minor impact on its quality so that it ultimately failed to become an earth-step treasure. However, it was still a top-ranked treasure among all high-grade human-step treasures.

With the Abyss Blade in hand, the Abyssal Flames burned even brighter. Layers of heat waves spread out, and soon even the tiles on the stage began to melt away.

“Ardent Flames Burning City!”

Huo Yanluo gave a loud cry, and the red Abyss Blade transformed into a roaring dragon. It rushed straight towards Lin Ming with a nearly unstoppable momentum!

As the Flame Essence was displayed on stage, the disciples of the Refiner Faction cheered out with all their strength. With the Flame Essence in his control and combined with the Abyss Blade’s increased fire power, even Mugu Buyu or Ouyang Ming had to dodge this attack of Huo Yanluo!

Lin Ming saw this fire dragon rushing towards him and slightly hesitated. With this slight hesitation, the fire dragon had already come directly in front of Lin Ming!

Lin Ming revolved the true essence within his body and poured azure true essence into his long spear, he stabbed out at the Abyssal Flames!

10,000 vibrating true essence filaments howled into the fire dragon. Everyone that saw this scene was shocked beyond measure!

He took it head-on?

Nobody believed that Huo Yanluo could become the champion, and very few believed he would even reach the top three. But nobody doubted the power of the Flame Essence, especially under the increased range of strength from the Abyss Blade!

Even darksteel would instantly melt under this high temperature. If a normal treasure lost its true essence protection, it would be reduced to slag under the Abyssal Flame!

To most people, even if Jiang Baoyun was facing Huo Yanluo, he would still have to avoid the Abyssal Flames and use his quick speed and sword to attack Huo Yanluo, winning with a single strike.

And yet Lin Ming actually met this attack head-on?

The young girl from the Zither Faction covered her mouth in alarm. As for the Refiner Faction disciple, his expression was filled with excitement, waiting for Lin Ming to lose.

In that split-second, it was too late for anyone in the audience to respond. Lin Ming’s spear had already inserted itself into the flame dragon’s gaping maw; azure true essence thundered forth!

Huo Yanluo’s lips curved up in a fierce grin. The reason he hadn’t had confidence he could defeat Lin Ming was because of his erratic and evasive movements, and that spear of his that contained the Concept of Wind. He feared that Lin Ming would simply avoid his Abyssal Flames and attack him directly.

But in terms of a head-to-head attack, Huo Yanluo had complete faith in his abilities. He galvanized all of the true essence in his body, and the power of blazing hot fire poured out into the Heavy Profound Soft Spear, shooting towards Lin Ming along the spear shaft!

The power of fire was tyrannical and cruel, once it impacted into Lin Ming, it would ruin his meridians.

But at this time, Lin Ming’s entire body erupted with an immense amount of true essence. The Heretical God Seed began to let out cries of excitement. An enormous coercive power came crashing down, imprisoning the power of fire that had broken into Lin Ming’s body!

Then, an irresistible suction force gushed out of the Heretical God Seed, directly pulling in the power of fire, using it to nourish the weak Flame Essence that hid within the Heretical God Seed.

In terms of grade, Lin Ming’s own Flame Essence was barely enough to be called the lowest and weakest of all low-grade human-step Flame Essences. And this was only achieved after absorbing Huo Gong’s Hollow Flame Essence.

But Huo Yanluo’s own bodily Flame Essence was a true medium-grade human-step Abyssal Flame. Generally speaking, the flames that a Flame Essence released were a single grade higher than the Flame Essence itself. For instance, Huo Yanluo’s Abyssal Flame released flames that were at the high-grade human-step level. In addition to the increased range of power from Abyss Blade, the strength of this flame had already reached the top-tier among all high-grade human-step flames.

This top-tier high-grade human-step flame was without a doubt great nourishment for the Flame Essence within the Heretical God Seed!

The tiny Flame Essence within the Heretical God Seed began to greedily devour the power of fire, slowly growing.

As the audience watched the scene on stage, all of them were dumbfounded. Lin Ming stood there in a lunging stance, his Heavy Profound Soft Spear thrust straight into the thick pillar of flame that was the fire dragon’s maw. No matter how much Huo Yanluo urged his flames to grow and burn, Lin Ming hadn’t even drawn back a single step!

Under the smoldering flames, even the tiles under Lin Ming’s feet began to melt. An azure true essence protective shield guarded Lin Ming’s body. No matter how much the snakes of fire raged throughout the barrier of azure true essence, that barrier showed not even a single sign of melting.

This scene was just like a mighty sea god stabbing a trident into a fiery dragon! No matter how much the fiery dragon struggled, it couldn’t escape from the control of the sea god!

This aura caused everyone’s hearts to quiver!

“Impossible, this is impossible!! How is this possible!?”

No one was more shocked than the disciples of the Refiner Faction. The Abyssal Flame was a medium-grade human-step Flame Essence – it was something that only a peak Houtian realm master could absorb! And now that the Flame Essence had the support of the Abyss Blade, if one wished to resist it, they could only do so with a higher cultivation. They would at least need to be at the extreme Houtian realm!

Although all of these geniuses were truly formidable, no one thought that their strength could reach the extreme Houtian realm, not even Jiang Baoyun!

Most of these so-called geniuses could at best compare with a middle Houtian master, and that was only the weakest middle Houtian master of the 36 countries.

Chapter 280 – Soaring Strength

Up until now, Ouyang Ming hadn’t encountered many top masters. He had only faced off against Fang Qi, Mugu Jirong, and Huan Xiaodie. Of these three matches, he had emerged victorious through overwhelming superiority; he hadn’t been forced to show any of his true strength.

However, no one doubted Ouyang Ming’s power. In the last Total Faction Martial Meeting, he had defeated Jiang Baoyun for the first time. He was once considered as the one with the highest chances of becoming the next Martial Meeting champion, but he never imagined that Jiang Baoyun would recover from his loss and become a terrifying presence that occupied the spotlight and suppressed Ouyang Ming.

In comparison to Ouyang Ming who hadn’t faced any great obstacles on his way to a string of complete victories, Lin Ming could be said to have had to overcome one great hardship after another. Now, Lin Ming’s fame was only inferior to Jiang Baoyun and Mugu Buyu, and was tied with Ouyang Ming.

As the referee announced the start of the match, the arena began to buzz with excitement. The crowd was neatly divided in half for those who favored Lin Ming and those who favored Ouyang Ming.

Many of the Acacia Faction disciples were screaming out cheers for Ouyang Ming. In comparison, the cheers for the visiting Lin Ming were much weaker. Besides the martial artists of the 36 countries cheering for him, there were the young girls of the Zither Faction who had good impressions of him.

On the martial stage, Ouyang Ming was dressed in complete white, and he held an iron folding fan in his hand. His long black hair was tied back with a silk ribbon, and he looked just like a handsome royal son. From his head to his toes, he had the makings of a jade tree facing the gentle wind.

As a disciple of the Acacia Faction, Ouyang Ming naturally had hordes of cawing girls by his side, and groups of wives and concubines. Even so, there were still many young and beautiful girls that threw themselves at him of their own initiative. One reason was because Ouyang Ming’s looks were simply outstanding like a heavenly prince, and the second reason was because of Ouyang Ming’s status as a core disciple. If they could follow by his side, they would be able to obtain more resources and break through to the Pulse Condensation period more easily.

200 feet away from Ouyang Ming, Lin Ming was standing straight, holding a long silver spear in his hand. His posture was upright and steady. Because Lin Ming had been practicing a Body Transformation cultivation method of the highest rank for the past six months, his body had been maturing at a very high rate. Although he was only 16 years old now, he wasn’t much shorter than the tall and handsome Ouyang Ming.

“This boy, I don’t know what the limit of his strength is…” As Ouyang Ming faced Lin Ming, he had a faint feeling in his heart that he wouldn’t be able to win. It was the same feeling as if he was looking at Mugu Buyu.

Before this point, he never imagined that he would be pressured so much by a disciple from the 36 countries.

Lin Ming was a well-rounded fighter, he was simply versatile in all aspects of combat. Such a person was a very rare existence. Most geniuses had a particular advantage that served as their point of superiority, but they also had a corresponding weakness to go with it. For instance, Qin Wuxin’s attacks were invisible and formless and they were difficult to avoid; but once one was able to close in on her and engage in close-range battle, one would basically have won.

As for Huo Yanluo and Zhang Yanzhao, those two had an incomparably overwhelming offensive attack power, but their true combat prowess was limited. Once one dodged their attacks, they would easily lose. Even if it was someone like Jiang Lanjian who seemed to be a versatile fighter, he still had weaknesses in his insufficient attack momentum and his weak defensive power.

Because of the different strengths and weaknesses of geniuses, they would usually serve to restrain each other. As long as they had the same strength and the same talent, victory would be settled by which skills held advantages over others.

But as for Lin Ming, he was simply an all-around combat king. His aura was formidable, and his spear was fierce and sharp. His attacks contained the Concept of Wind, making them incomparably swift. There wasn’t even need to mention his defensive capabilities. He had been able to take Jiang Lanjian’s full attack strike head-on and come out with only a few scratches! In terms of movement speed, his agility was simply like gods and ghosts – there was almost no weakness to him!

Against a master who didn’t seem to have any weaknesses at all, Ouyang Ming just didn’t know what he could do to win.

As the match officially started, Ouyang Ming didn’t bother saying any useless words. He unfolded the iron fan in his hands.

“Absolute Life Purple Flame!”

With a ‘chi chi’ sound, a massive purple flame burst out from his iron fan, blazing in the air like an inferno. This purple fire was a much deeper color than the Purple Flame Bone Lance that had been used by Ouyang Zifeng.

Fuu!

The purple inferno fired towards Lin Ming, and a bone chilling energy rolled off in front it. This freezing cold flame was incomparably strange.

Azure true essence erupted forth. Lin Ming took a step forwards and thrust out with his spear. 10,000 vibrating true essence filaments savagely ran out.

Bang!

The purple flames immediately disintegrated; they had been scattered by Flow like Silk.

After reaching the early Pulse Condensation period, combined with the power of the Flow like Silk breakthrough, the strength of Lin Ming’s past vibrating true essence could not compare to its current incarnation.

Ouyang Ming’s expression suddenly changed for the worse. Although he hadn’t held on to any hope that the purple flames would be able to defeat Lin Ming, he hadn’t thought that Lin Ming would so easily destroy his flames.

“Purple Flame Bone Lance!”

“Scythe of the Death God!”

Ouyang Ming gave a loud shout, and a purple bone lance made of fire appeared by his side. Compared to Ouyang Zifeng, it was as if Ouyang Ming’s bone lance instantly appeared by his side, shooting forwards without even needing any time to condense his true essence. Not only that, but as he flourished his fan, a purple scythe appeared, flying forwards to cut off Lin Ming’s head!

Facing this roaring attack, Lin Ming maintained a completely indifferent expression. His feet moved and his speed instantly achieved the limit.

Ka!

A shadow blurred, and Lin Ming broke through a narrow gap between the Purple Flame Bone Lance and Scythe of the Death God. His spear was wreathed in arcs of lightning; it contained the Concept of Wind and power of thunder, thrusting straight towards Ouyang Ming’s side!

Ouyang Ming’s heart went cold and he instantly drew back. At the same time, he waved his fan back and forth, and clouds of purple flame seemed to blossom in front of him, forming layers of defensive fire that protected his body!

Bang!

10,000 filaments of vibrating azure true essence rampaged out. The thick coils of thunder were just like massive purple snakes that twisted in a frenzy. The purple barriers of flame were only able to resist for a split second before being torn apart by the spear!

Seeing the cold spearpoint come towards him, Ouyang Ming’s pupils contracted. He hadn’t imagined that a casual spear thrust of Lin Ming’s had achieved such a terrifying degree of strength. It had even broken through three of his purple flame cloud shields!

He instantly realized that if he was struck even once by this spear, he would lose without a doubt. When Lin Ming had faced Fang Qi, a single spear of his had broken through five continuous Nine Circles of Blue Light Arrays. Ouyang Ming was confident, but he didn’t believe that the true essence that protected his body was any stronger than five layers of Nine Circles of Blue Light Arrays.

This Lin Ming, his attack power was too abnormal!

“Butterflies Dance on 100 Flowers!”

Ouyang Ming’s body instantly turned into a series of shadows, evading the spear by dancing on the edge of destruction.

“Movement martial skill?” Lin Ming watched as Ouyang Ming flitted around like a butterfly hovering over flowers, his form drifting from end to end. This was obviously an extremely gorgeous and sublime avoidance movement skill. There were over a dozen images that seemed real and fake at the same time; it was impossible for a normal martial artist to distinguish just where Ouyang Ming’s true self was. It was futile to attack, one could only passively leave themselves vulnerable to attack. Not only that, but it was futile to guess just where Ouyang Ming’s attack came from.

However, to Lin Ming, none of this was a problem. He simply closed his eyes and let his soul force fuse into the Concept of Wind. Suddenly, Lin Ming’s figure disappeared!

“Total Annihilation!”

Lin Ming used the same constant Foundation Spear Technique and swept out into space. But in the moment that Lin Ming swept out with his spear, Ouyang Ming appeared just under the spearhead as if he had ran into it.

Ouyang Ming’s instantly paled. His Butterflies Dance on 100 Flowers had been seen through in a single try!!??

At this time Ouyang Ming could not evade, collision was inevitable. He had to take this attack head-on!

Pa!

The iron fan opened, and Ouyang Ming cried out, pushing all of the true essence within his body to the limit. A bluish purple evil flame shrieked as it ran out of the iron fan, directly cleaving towards the spearpoint.

Bang!

The bluish purple evil flame smashed against the purple thunder, the power of thunderbolts exploded out!

In the moment that the iron fan struck the spearpoint, Ouyang Ming felt as if he had chopped against a mountain. 10,000 vibrating true essence filaments cascaded forth and an incomparably vast peerless vibration directly cracked apart Ouyang Ming’s grip, causing his right arm to lose all feeling.

“This is…!”

Ouyang Ming felt as if his chest had been hit by a massive hammer. There was a tangy copper taste in the back of his throat, and Ouyang Ming spat out a mouthful of blood as he flew backwards and struck the martial stage’s protective barrier.

This unexpected result caused the entire audience to pause, slack-jawed. Even Jiang Lanjian who usually highly respected Lin Ming’s abilities was looking at this scene, an extremely incredulous expression coloring his face.

Ouyang Ming, who had ranked third place during the last Total Faction Martial Meeting was defeated so easily?

The truth was that Jiang Lanjian had expected that Lin Ming would win. However, he thought that the two contestants would have a fierce dogfight where each one would use hidden card after hidden card, finally ending with Lin Ming as victor through a small advantage. He hadn’t expected that Lin Ming would prevail in less than 20 moves.

“How did Ouyang Ming lose so easily? Doesn’t he have any more cards in his hands?” Jiang Lanjian just couldn’t believe this. He had also lost to Ouyang Ming during the last Total Faction Martial Meeting, and this time, he didn’t have much confidence that he would be able to defeat Ouyang Ming. However, Lin Ming had actually defeated Ouyang Ming so easily!

Jiang Baoyun slowly said, “Ouyang Ming already used the cards in his hands, and that was his Perfect fifth stage of the ‘Divine Acacia Power’. Absolute Life Purple Flame and Scythe of the Death God are both moves that can only be used after reaching the fifth layer of the ‘Divine Acacia Power’. It’s just that they were easily broken by Lin Ming. Many people didn’t see just how strong Ouyang Ming’s attacks were… it’s not that Ouyang Ming is weak, but that Lin Ming is too strong. After breaking through to the Pulse Condensation period, his strength has soared past what it once was!”

Jiang Baoyun took a deep breath. Normally when a martial artist broke through to the Pulse Condensation period from the peak Bone Forging stage, their strength wouldn’t increase too much.

However, Lin Ming wasn’t a normal martial artist. The method in which he reached Pulse Condensation was through a perfect breakthrough, and his foundation was extremely solid. Not only that, but the cultivation method he practiced was the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’. After breaking through each stage, his true essence would grow incomparably thicker and purer than a martial artist at the same stage.

Also, Lin Ming’s azure true essence, Flow like Silk, and Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder were absurdly abnormal and overpowered abilities. If his true essence was twice as strong, then his attack power would be three times, four times, or even five times greater!

So from the peak Bone Forging stage to the Pulse Condensation period, Lin Ming had experienced a great leap in strength!

“Ouyang Ming was defeated! Now there are only three people left that still have a flawless winning streak!”

“Besides Mugu Buyu and Jiang Baoyun, Lin Ming has already fought with most of the other masters, except for Huan Xiaodie and Mugu Jirong. However, those two are not his match. Even if Lin Ming lost to Mugu Buyu and Jiang Baoyun, he would still reach the top three!”

The audience discussed the situation of the tournament and the possible outcomes. This dark horse known as Lin Ming was simply too dark. A disciple of the 36 countries had entered the Total Faction Martial Meeting for the first time and had already reached the top three rankings. Moreover, he had just reached 16 years of age. This was simply too shocking for anyone to comprehend.

After Lin Ming walked offstage, he saw Mugu Buyu staring at him. Mugu Buyu’s skinny mummy face still had his trademark tricky smile. But as he looked at Lin Ming’s eyes, his eyes no longer held the previous teasing banter and contempt. Instead, there was a solemn, dignified expression.

Clearly, Mugu Buyu finally felt threatened by Lin Ming.

Chapter 288 – The Peak Of All Battles

The referee team was keenly interested in the final match of Lin Ming and Jiang Baoyun. They decided to let the two of them adjust and restore their conditions to the peak. Before the final match began, the tournament was placed on hold for three hours until lunchtime was finished.

In fact, by this point many people weren’t even in the mood for lunch. They remained in their seats, fervently anticipating the upcoming match and discussing amongst themselves.

The common disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys had limited vision on what would truly happen. However, they had an outstanding capacity to fantasize how the match would play out, brainstorming countless ways that Lin Ming and Jiang Baoyun would fight. Even Jiang Baoyun’s Black Crystal Sword had had its function and characteristics thoroughly ‘researched’. Especially for the disciples of the Refiner Faction, although they were not so good at combat, this was a prime opportunity for them to display their specialized skillsets. They analyzed Jiang Baoyun’s Black Crystal Sword from multiple angles and deduced its attributes. If one wasn’t aware of the situation, then they would have even thought that these Refiner disciples were the ones who personally hand crafted the sword.

The afternoon sun in the winter was gentle and hazy. After noon had passed, the last match of the Total Faction Martial Meeting would begin. This was the showdown between the top talents within the several hundred thousand miles of the Seven Profound territory; this would decide who was the number one of the younger generation!

As the fateful moment approached, the cheers of the arena became thunderous, drowning out every other sound for hundreds of miles. By this time, no one dared to mock or look down on Lin Ming, not even the Seven Profound Valleys’ disciples. Everyone just wanted to see this showdown between these two geniuses that stood at the apex of talent. This was an opportunity that only came around once every several hundred years. It could be said that this sort of chance could only occur through the fickle fortunes of fate. It had to be known that if a martial artist didn’t step into the Xiantian realm, they would live at most around 200 years. For them, this battle would only happen once in their lifetimes! By just that point alone, it was enough to excite them to the point of frothing at the mouth!

On the martial stage, Lin Ming and Jiang Baoyun stood 200 feet apart. Jiang Baoyun opened the sword case he carried on his back, and took out the vivid blue longsword.

With this sword in hand, the momentum that Jiang Baoyun had already gathered around him suddenly shifted. His eyes sharpened as if they contained a limitless sword light, piercing the heart of anyone he glanced at.

If Jiang Baoyun had been a calm man with a gentle temperament, then now he had the qualities of the finest sword. He was sharp, ice-cold, and filled with murderous intent!

Jiang Baoyun pointed sword fingers at Lin Ming and said, “Before this Martial Meeting began, my Sovereign once told me that Ouyang Ming, who I lost to three years ago at the last Martial Meeting, had reached the peak Pulse Condensation period and would be my greatest match. He cautioned me to take be careful, but I told him that Ouyang Ming was not my greatest rival; my greatest rival is only myself! If I cannot continuously defeat talents of a third-grade sect, then what qualifications do I have to even speak of pursuing the end of the sword path

“But now, those words…” Jiang Baoyun took a deep breath, his eyes flashing with a dazzling light as if they were bright stars shining in the inky black night.

“I cannot help but acknowledge that your talent far exceeds mine. When you and I were the same age, I did not have your strength. But more than that, I am even more enthusiastic. A peerless powerhouse needs a grand stage to grow. This small Seven Profound territory does not qualify for such a stage, and even being the number one hero of the Seven Profound territory holds no meaning for me. Even worse, my eyes might be clouded by this title, and I might become complacent, weak! Therefore when I was 18 years old, I began to challenge to talents of all other third-grade sects, including even Peacock Mountain. At the start, I lost many and won only a few times. But after that, I won many times, and lost only a few! And now this year, I challenged four geniuses, and was defeated not even once!

“Therefore, I once again became confused, thinking that I would lose my way. And then you appeared! You are the rival of my destiny. Once I defeat you, I will become a hero of this era. The greater your talent, the higher my spirit burns with passion!

“Lin Ming, do not let me down!”

Lin Ming looked at Jiang Baoyun with surprise, he hadn’t imagined he would have such a broad view of the world.

In one year, he had challenged four other geniuses from different sects, and defeated them all. One had to know that this was an extraordinary achievement. After all, the Seven Profound Valleys couldn’t be considered the highest of the third-grade sects.

No wonder. Although Jiang Baoyun had lost to Ouyang Ming in the last Total Faction Marital Meeting, his power and influence now far exceeded Ouyang Ming’s, and he held an unshakable position in the heart of every disciple of the Seven Profound Valleys. All of this was accomplished by his own sword!

Lin Ming also understood why Jiang Baoyun had kindly invited him to join the Sword Faction. This was because he was not afraid of a challenge. On the contrary, he longed for a true opponent to test himself. The desire to challenge himself… this was his heart of martial arts, this was the heart of martial arts that a genuine master should have!

Lin Ming slowly said, “From the moment I began to walk the path of martial arts, I had heard the great name of the Seven Profound Valleys. To the me of that time, the Seven Profound Valleys was like a forbidden temple that loomed high in the heavens, impossible for us ordinary commoners to even see. After I stepped into the hallowed halls of Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Seven Profound Martial House, I became increasingly aware of just how terrifying the Seven Profound Valleys was. Because of your existence, there are many martial artists like me, common, ordinary ones, who have forever lost their chance to practice martial arts. This is the fate that has been engraved within their very bones since birth! Since that moment, I had resolved to someday bring my spear here and break through that fate of imprisonment, to fight for what belongs to me, and take control of my own destiny!

“Now, what I will say is that if you wish to take me as the rival of your destiny, then I will tell you that I will not disappoint you. However, whether or not you can keep up with my pace will all depend on yourself!”

As Lin Ming said these words, the entire audience was startled.

This was just crazy talk, a martial artist from the 36 countries had actually said such insolent words. If it were just a few days ago, then these Seven Profound Valleys’ disciples would have been laughing until they rolled on the floor, but now, no one dared to laugh. This was because Lin Ming had the ability to say so!

“Good!” Jiang Baoyun laughed, “Lin Ming, take out your spear!”

These words filled with a surging fighting spirit were just like a thunderclap that rolled throughout the entire Profound Sky Mountains.

“Take out your spear!”

“Take out your spear!”

“Take out your spear!”

The echo impacted into the sky, reverberating between the heavens and earth!

At this moment, the entire atmosphere of the arena lit up in a glorious frenzy. This time, the cheers were not for Jiang Baoyun – nor were they for Lin Ming. They were only for this match that would decide the top master of the younger generation!

Lin Ming turned his wrist, and the Heavy Profound Soft Spear appeared in his hand. His aura immediately erupted; he was just like an implacable mountain!

At this moment, Jiang Baoyun also moved. He began to slowly walk towards Lin Ming. However, his footsteps had an unapproachable feeling, as if the ground he walked on could not be violated. After a few steps, the unbelievable occurred. As Jiang Baoyun moved forwards, he left behind a phantom that was identical to his shadow!

This phantom was also wearing black clothes and holding the Blue Peak treasure sword in his hand. It was almost impossible to discern any difference between it and Jiang Baoyun.

Phantom?

Lin Ming’s brows furrowed, and his soul force swept out; he was actually able to feel a chilling murderous intent emitting from that phantom body!

It wasn’t just a ghost, but a true phantom that could attack. Its own attack power was no weaker than the true Jiang Baoyun!

Lin Ming drew in a breath of cold air, there was actually such a cultivation method in this world?

As two Jiang Baoyuns appeared, the audience was stunned.

Jiang Baoyun said, “From your expression, it seems that you’ve already deduced the truth. You’re right, the phantom behind me is not a just a ghost, it is a true swordsman. It has the same speed and attack power as I do – it is my Sword Spirit Avatar. Right now, it could be said that you are fighting two of me.”

“What? Simultaneously fighting two Jiang Baoyuns!?”

Many people were frightened silly. Jiang Baoyun was already an abnormal freak, and his skill with the sword was at the highest peak. His attacks were sharp, swift, and incomparably fierce. And now Lin Ming had to fight two Jiang Baoyuns at once, what kind of concept was this?

Everyone knew just how terrifying Jiang Baoyun was. In one year, he had challenged four top talents of third-grade sects, and had achieved victory against all of them. But because Jiang Baoyun had fought in distant lands, his moves were unknown, and no one knew just what the limits of his strength were.

In the audience, Qin Xingxuan was nervously wringing her hands together, her palms already wet with sweat. Could Lin Ming defend against this? And Jiang Baoyun still had that Black Crystal Sword!

“Sword Spirit Avatar?”

Lin Ming could be considered opened minded. There were countless varieties of martial artist, and too many that he didn’t understand. There were some he had never heard of, and even some that he could never have imagined.

Almost all of these abilities and skills were either mediocre or of an unorthodox origin. Because there were just too many, there had to be some cultivation methods that were considered wonderful treasures even in the Realm of the Gods, waiting for him to find.

“Graceful Sword!”

Jiang Baoyun gave a loud shot, and there was only a flash of blue. That flash of blue was too quick, it was just like a flicker of color that suddenly appeared in front of Lin Ming!

Lin Ming’s pupils contracted.

Golden Roc Shattering the Void!

Ka!

The sword light directly pierced through Lin Ming, Jiang Baoyun and his blade had cleanly sliced through Lin Ming’s body. But it soon became clear that he was only an afterimage!

Jiang Baoyun hadn’t even looked back when his Sword Spirit Avatar shot forwards with the same speed, unstoppable!

The blue sword flickered, thrusting straight towards Lin Ming’s throat. At this time, Lin Ming was in the air – he could not evade!

“Ah!” The audience didn’t even have time to cry out in alarm. Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with flight, Concept of Wind!

Ka!

Another afterimage was cut apart. Lin Ming fell to the ground with his spear, a foot-long cut in his plain clothes.

“Good speed!”

Lin Ming was shocked. The truth was that Lin Ming’s speed wasn’t slow. The Concept of Wind was fused into his attacks and into his movements. Whether it was movement speed or attack speed, he far exceeded a martial artist of the same level!

However, he had been completely unable to catch up to Jiang Baoyun’s speed. It could only be said that Jiang Baoyun’s speed was completely abnormal!

How was this possible?

Lin Ming found this hard to believe; was this really a speed that a Pulse Condensation period martial artist could achieve?

‘I see… so Jiang Baoyun has already comprehended his own Sword Step.’

In the Seven Profound Valleys’ Grand Hall, Shi Zongtian was watching Jiang Baoyun, finding it difficult to remain calm. This so-called Sword Step was when one’s own movement fused into one’s sword intent. When a person’s movement achieved the boundary of becoming one with the sword, the sword would move as the person did, and the person would move as the sword did. Because of this, Jiang Baoyun was able to reach a truly terrifying speed.

To walk the sword path, one not only needed a deep cultivation, but also an extremely high perception. Jiang Baoyun was able to reach this Sword Step boundary because of his own indispensable talent and perception!

It wasn’t only Shi Zongtian. Several other faction elders were startled. Lin Ming’s speed was truly praiseworthy, but Jiang Baoyun’s speed was even quicker! He had a natural inborn Sword Spirit, and he had managed to comprehend his own Sword Step at the young age of 19. Such a terrifying swordsman had never been seen in the Seven Profound territories within the last millennium!

The Refiner Faction Sovereign Huo Xuan couldn’t help but ask, “Elder Jiang, just what realm has Jiang Baoyun reached? Just a year ago I had seen him in action, and he is completely incomparable with his current self.”

Chapter 299 – Heaven Opening Pill In Hand

The reason why Zhang Shaoshan was so madly envious of Lin Ming wasn’t just the additional resources that were available to him, but because of the attitude that Mu Qianyu had towards Lin Ming. Even Zhang Shaoshan clearly knew that whether now or in the future, Mu Qianyu would have absolutely no relation to him. This caused his antipathy to rise to the skies!

Those who went against their true nature would damage their heart of martial arts. Every person’s true nature was decided by their conscience. For instance, those righteous individuals like Jiang Baoyun and Qin Wuxin followed the noble and virtuous path. If they did something evil, such as plotting against others, treachery, betrayal, or other malicious actions, this would go against their nature, inevitably ruining their heart of martial arts.

But as for those like the Acacia Faction and the South Sea Demon Region, these kinds of martial artists followed the immoral, wicked path. They placed emphasis on indulging in their most basic desires and fulfilling all of their dark ideas. If they were to behave and be goodly like some holy monk, then that also would go against their nature.

Zhang Shaoshan was an individual who had a very heavy and proud heart, and was also narrow-minded with a low tolerance level. He loved to step on others, but if someday he were to be disgraced and stepped on by someone else, this would frustrate his spirit and thoughts, blocking his cultivation.

As of now, Zhang Shaoshan was in this situation. In front of everyone, he had been repeatedly stepped on. Although the person who had done this was Mugu Buyu, Zhang Shaoshan had also counted Lin Ming as one of his heart’s thorns. He had even linked in Jiang Baoyun, bearing a deep grudge against all three of them.

‘Just you wait, I will have you pay the price for shaming me!’

Zhang Shaoshan clenched his teeth, and was finally carried away.

………….

“Lin Ming, this is for you.” Mu Qianyu turned her hands, and a sparkling, translucent pill bottle and a ring appeared in her hands. The pill bottle was made from exquisite jade, and was beautiful just like the whitest crystal. As for the ring, it was very plain, looking no different to a copper or steel ring.

But Lin Ming was able to recognize that this ring was actually a high-grade human-step spatial ring.

It wasn’t an easy task to forge a spatial ring. Because of this, a spatial ring was often much more expensive than a treasure of the same grade. This spatial ring might not be as valuable as a weak earth-step treasure, but it wasn’t too different.

Mu Qianyu smiled and said, “The true essence stones inside the ring are yours. There are 240 of them, I’m giving you these resources ahead of time so you can cultivate.”

Hearing the number 240, Lin Ming was overjoyed. These true essence stones that Mu Qianyu had passed to him were naturally medium-grade true essence stones. A single medium-grade true essence stone was worth 100 normal true essence stones, meaning that these 240 medium-grade true essence stones were worth 24,000 ordinary pure true essence stones! Also, it wasn’t easy to trade for medium-grade true essence stones; the true value of them was probably much higher than he thought.

To use medium-grade true essence stones to cultivate was a luxury that not even the core disciples of the Seven Profound Valleys could enjoy.

“I’ll use these 240 medium-grade true essence stones to cultivate. As for those other true essence stones that I won through the gambling house, I’ll use those as currency to buy items.”

Lin Ming planned to use the true essence stones with this intention. But,the true essence stones seemed to have become a bit heavier. If he only used medium-grade true essence stones to cultivate, 240 wouldn’t be enough. As for the ordinary true essence stones, those would quickly be spent if he wished to purchase some top quality materials.

“Thank you, Saintess Your Highness.”

Because Shi Zongtian was also present, Lin Ming didn’t show any surprise or knowledge of what he knew was in Mu Qianyu’s hands, and respectfully received the pill bottle and spatial ring.

“This spatial ring is also for you. I see that your spatial ring is some low-grade treasure, it’s best to change it.” Mu Qianyu casually said. Lin Ming hesitated for a moment but didn’t decline. After all, this was part of the ceremony.

Previously, he had taken three medium-grade human-step spatial rings from the bodies of Huo Gong, Ouyang Dihua, and the Allied Trade Association’s President Zhang Fengxian. But he never showed these rings to the light of day or wore them on his hand.

With this high-grade human-step spatial ring, he would be able to destroy those three spatial rings he got from killing others.

A high-grade human-step spatial ring had an inner dimensional capacity that was larger than all of Lin Ming’s total rings combined. Not only that, but it was much more stable and could last for thousands of years without collapsing.

After Mu Qianyu handed over the Heaven Opening Pill, Shi Zongtian also took out a vivid red pill box. After opening it, there was a crystal clear emerald pill inside, the size of a longan. It shined with an incomparably pure origin energy – this was also a Heaven Opening Pill.

This was the reward for being the champion of this year’s Total Faction Martial Meeting. Shi Zongtian had already promised to deliver the prize to Lin Ming ahead of time; this was the most convenient time to settle this matter.

Lin Ming took a deep breath. Out of nowhere, he had suddenly obtained two Heaven Opening Pills. This was simply an unthinkable dream to most martial artists. For instance, Qin Ziya had paid such a great price and so much time for a Heaven Opening Pill. With this alone, one could imagine how precious they were.

Lin Ming’s heart stirred and he asked, “Valley Master Shi, if I take a Heaven Opening Pill whilst at the Pulse Condensation period, will there be any side effects?”

Shi Zongtian’s mouth twitched. Was this boy actually thinking of eating a Heaven Opening Pill during the Pulse Condensation period? This was just a waste of such a precious treasure!

As far as most martial artists were concerned, taking a Heaven Opening Pill was their life’s grandest and most solemn event. There were even those who prepared for decades for this! They would cultivate until their cultivation couldn’t rise even a tiny bit more, and they would wait until their Zither Heart or Sword Heart or whatever else had reached its own bottleneck. Finally, they would go into seclusion and swallow the Heaven Opening Pill. Earlier, if Qin Ziya hadn’t been worried about failing to break through to the Xiantian realm due to his 50 years of age and low chance of ever receiving another Heaven Opening Pill, causing a problem with his Zither Heart, then he would most likely have broken through.

Most martial artists would hold a series of rituals before they took the Heaven Opening Pill. They would choose an auspicious date and bathe in incense. Afterwards, they might even stay in seclusion for over a year to refine all of the medicine and not let a single bit go to waste.

But Lin Ming, he was actually thinking of taking a Heaven Opening Pill with his Pulse Condensation period cultivation, treating these treasures like candy.

If those peak Houtian realm masters who could never step into the Xiantian realm because they lacked a Heaven Opening Pill heard this, they would probably go mad with rage and spit out several liters of blood.

Shi Zongtian coughed and said, “Lin Ming, although there aren’t any side effects from taking the Heaven Opening Pill during the Pulse Condensation period, you won’t be able to avoid wasting much of the efficacy due to your cultivation. You should consider reaching the Houtian realm before taking it, its effects will be better then.”

“I understand.” Lin Ming only heard Shi Zongtian say that there wouldn’t be side effects. As for wasting efficacy of the medicine, that simply wasn’t even in his consideration. What he wanted to attack first wasn’t the Houtian realm or even the Xiantian realm, but the Tempering Marrow boundary!

If he could open the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, he would be far superior to anyone else in the Xiantian realm or Revolving Core realm!

‘Of these two Heaven Opening Pills, it should be fine for me to take one now. Then I can see if the Heaven Opening Pill is enough to satisfy the lowest requirements of the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ to help reach the Pulse Condensation Tempering Marrow boundary!

‘If eating one doesn’t work so well, then I will spend a massive amount of energy to draw up a medicinal inscription symbol so that I can inscribe onto the Heaven Opening Pill! If I add a medicinal inscription symbol to the Heaven Opening Pill and take it again, it should be good!’

As Lin Ming’s cultivation and power increased by bounds and leaps, his own inscription technique had fallen behind too much.

Practicing inscription technique required a great deal of time and energy. When Lin Ming had been poor and had no resources, he had no choice but to invest a massive amount of time in practicing inscription techniques, and use those inscription symbols he drew up to trade for cultivation resources. But as his status grew higher and higher, he no longer had to waste his time to trade for resources, but was able to invest all of his time into cultivating.

The most recent time that Lin Ming had used inscription techniques was when he was exchanging the symbols he drew for materials for his body inscription symbol. At that time, Lin Ming had drawn up inscription symbols for Sky Fortune Kingdom’s Pulse Condensation and Houtian masters for their medium-grade human-step weapons.

Since he was only able to draw up inscription symbols for medium-grade human-step treasures, Lin Ming could only be considered a medium-grade human-step inscription master.

But the Heaven Opening Pill rank was about equal to an earth-step pill; it was a sudden rise of two grades in difficulty. If Lin Ming wanted to draw up a medicinal inscription symbol that could pair up with the Heaven Opening Pill, he would need to at least achieve a low-grade earth-step ability in inscription technique. This would again take a massive amount of time and energy.

But, if this method could really help him enter into the Tempering Marrow boundary, then it was all worth it.

At this time, Shi Zongtian asked, “Lin Ming, have you chosen what earth-step treasure you would like?”

Lin Ming shook his head, “Not yet.”

“Mm? Liu Xuan hasn’t brought you to the Treasure Pavilion?”

“He did, it’s just that the spears within the Treasure Pavilion do not suit me.” Lin Ming tactfully said, carefully considering the words and expressions to use so as not to be rude.

“Ha!” Shi Zongtian laughed. If nothing was suitable, that just meant Lin Ming didn’t take a fancy to any of his Seven Profound Valleys’ earth-step treasure spears.

Shi Zongtian glanced at Liu Xuan who was responsible for the Treasure Pavilion. After Liu Xuan had brought Lin Ming here, he had gone to stand at a corner in the square. Shi Zongtian smiled and used a true essence sound transmission to beckon him over.

“Liu Xuan, what’s wrong, your Refiner Faction’s Treasure Pavilion doesn’t even have a single decent spear?”

Liu Xuan forced a smiled. He was still a Xiantian master and had a very acute sense of hearing. Shi Zongtian hadn’t bothered to conceal the conversation he had with Lin Ming, Liu Xuan had heard every bit of it. It was just that the Seven Profound Valleys didn’t have any masters who forged spears, so where would a high quality earth-step treasure spear come from?

Liu Xuan honestly said, “Apprentice Nephew Lin wishes for a flexible spear. However, our Treasure Pavilion only has three earth-step spears, all of which are hard spears. Not only that, but they are of quite ordinary quality. However, Apprentice Nephew Lin has said that he can provide spear crafting materials if we can forge it for him.”

As Liu Xuan said this, he cast a somewhat doubtful look towards Lin Ming. In Liu Xuan’s opinion, with Lin Ming’s common mortal background and young age, it was unlikely for him to understand how difficult it was to refine treasures, especially earth-step treasures. He probably had some low-quality common materials that he thought could be used to refine an earth-step treasure.

However, this wasn’t related to him. Since Shi Zongtian had asked, he had truthfully spoken.

The fact was, Liu Xuan was a tiny bit annoyed by Lin Ming. After all, the Treasure Pavilion could be said to be equivalent to his Refining Faction. There were many disciples who vainly dreamed and hoped to one day enter and choose a treasure. But Lin Ming hadn’t taken a liking to any of the treasures inside. It had to be known that there were many martial artists, that from the very first time they cultivated martial artists to the point when they reached the Xiantian realm, would never have had a chance to touch an earth-step treasure!

“Oh?” Shi Zongtian’s eyes picked up. Lin Ming actually had materials to make a flexible spear? But the materials that were qualified to craft an earth-step flexible spear were rare and exceedingly difficult to find. “What sort of materials do you have?”

“It’s only the spear shaft material. As for the spearhead material, I do not have any.”

“The spear shaft is enough. When making a flexible spear, the spear shaft is the most important part. Also, the materials to craft an earth-step flexible spear’s shaft are very rare. Lin Ming, do you really have any something?” Shi Zongtian actually did believe Lin Ming to an extent. After all, he was certain that Lin Ming had experienced some great fortuitous opportunity.

“It’s a piece of bamboo…” Lin Ming said, and then pulled the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo from his spatial ring. The nine foot nine inch Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo was a deep vivid color, and it sparkled with electric flashes.

Liu Xuan was directly befuddled, just what was this?

Chapter 300 – Spear Refining Grandmaster

The truth was that even though Liu Xuan only had a very shallow experience of these materials, Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo was simply an exceedingly rare treasure. It could only been formed at special locations which had experienced powerful thunder for 10,000 years. The commoners who lived around Thundercrash Mountain in the Southern Wilderness had a much broader knowledge of the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, as they were more closely intertwined with that environment.

In addition, Liu Xuan was a refining master whose specialty was forging swords and sabers. He understood almost every kind of top quality metal, but as for bamboo and other types of wood like materials, he almost never used them.

However, even though Liu Xuan didn’t know much about the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, that didn’t stop him from being able to see the terrifying power of thunder that was emitting from this piece of bamboo.

As the bamboo appeared, an incomparably rich power of thunder flooded outwards. The flashes of electricity were even enough to force Liu Xuan to subconsciously step backwards, and make all of the hairs on his body stand. This bamboo was still able to cause this effect, even though Liu Xuan was protected by his powerful true essence; obviously the thunder created a very formidable electricity field.

And what startled Liu Xuan was that he was able to see that the power of thunder origin energy of the world was flowing into this stick of bamboo, forming an invisible whirlpool of origin energy.

‘It can independently absorb thunder origin energy?’

This was simply incredible. If a thunder-attribute martial artist had this stick of bamboo, then he could continuously absorb thunder origin energy from the world during a battle in order to supplement his own reserves. Not only would his moves be more powerful, but he would have greater endurance in combat.

Realizing this, Liu Xuan gulped, his throat twitching. This bamboo was absolutely a treasure material that all thunder-attribute martial artists longed for in their dreams!

Among the three present, the one who best understood Thundercrash Mountain was Mu Qianyu. With just a glance, she was able to recognize this piece of Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, and was also able to discern just where Lin Ming got it from.

‘I didn’t think that the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo that has been bred in Thundercrash Mountain for 10,000 years was actually obtained by him. It seems that his little sojourn into the Flood Dragon Cave really had a rich harvest.’ Thinking this, Mu Qianyu grinned as she shook her head. The wealth that the Thunder Flood Dragon had accumulated was actually all plucked away by Lin Ming.

Shi Zongtian’s experience couldn’t compare to Mu Qianyu’s. After he saw this Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, he pondered for a moment before suddenly remembering that long ago, he had read about this sort of spiritual bamboo in the ancient texts.

“This is Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo?” Shi Zongtian asked.

Lin Ming nodded.

“Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo grows one inch every 100 years. This piece is nearly 10 feet tall. Is it 10,000 year old Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo?”

“Nine feet nine inches, it is 9900 year old Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo. It also birthed a 900 year old young bamboo shoot that is in my possession.” Lin Ming said, not bothering to conceal anything.

Nine feet nine inches was the same length as the Heavy Profound Soft Spear. However, the Heavy Profound Soft Spear’s length also included the spear head.

If one were to forge a spear with the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, it would also have another foot long spearhead. Its final length would be more than 10 feet long. In truth, this was a bit too long.

After hearing Lin Ming’s affirmation, Shi Zongtian sucked in a deep breath of air. This young boy had actually managed to obtain this sort of rare material. Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo could only be found in lands of thunder. As for lands of thunder, the only place nearby would be Thundercrash Mountain!

It was said that a Thunder Flood Dragon lived at the summit of Thundercrash Mountain, with a profoundly deep cultivation. Not only that, but it had the bloodline of a Saint Beast. Its strength was unfathomable. Coupled with the help of the countless Thunder Lizards that lived on Thundercrash Mountain, even the highest elder of the Seven Profound Valleys wouldn’t be able to return unscathed. And Lin Ming was actually able to obtain this Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo from Thundercrash Mountain?

Shi Zongtian found this impossible to imagine. He subconsciously glanced at Mu Qianyu. Did Mu Qianyu help Lin Ming? If so, then Mu Qianyu was simply too good to Lin Ming. Shi Zongtian thought for a moment, and then began to reevaluate the relationship between Mu Qianyu and Lin Ming. Maybe their relationship wasn’t as simple as he had imagined…

Even that Thunder Soul might have only been absorbed with help from Mu Qianyu. Otherwise, how could a young boy who didn’t even have a Pulse Condensation cultivation possibly absorb a low-grade earth-step Thunder Soul?

As Shi Zongtian thought more and more, he realized that the Seven Profound Valleys wouldn’t be able to retain a talent like Lin Ming. He was simply a dragon with a deep pool, and the waters of the Seven Profound Valleys were too shallow – a True Dragon could not swim in their waters.

Also, Lin Ming didn’t have an average connection to Mu Qianyu. Him joining Divine Phoenix Island was only a matter of time…

Thinking this, Shi Zongtian let out a long breath. Before, he had struggled with his thoughts and decisions. Lin Ming had never been his, and couldn’t be considered as a Seven Profound Valleys disciple from the start.

In that case, drawing back and looking at things, befriending such a master was also good.

“I would like to use this Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo to forge a spear!”

Lin Ming solemnly said as he held out the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo.

Liu Xuan’s eyes jumped as he heard this. Make a spear shaft with this bamboo? This… this was just too shocking an idea. If one could create an earth-step treasure spear, with the added quality from the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo of being able to absorb and strengthen the power of thunder, then that spear would be a highest quality weapon for any thunder-attribute martial artist!

‘Yes! Wasn’t Lin Ming a thunder-attribute martial artist?’ Liu Xuan slapped his forehead, cursing himself for being so stupid. He had actually forgotten that Lin Ming was a thunder-attribute martial artist with an absurdly high thunder origin energy fusion compatibility!

As Liu Xuan thought this, his mind began to shiver. This was incredible! Lin Ming was already disgustingly strong to such a degree, but if he also had a top quality thunder spear, he would be even more powerful. With his power unleashed, who among the younger generation could hope to stop him?

No wonder Lin Ming didn’t even spare a glance at the treasures of the Refiner Faction. In comparison to a top quality thunder spear that was made from Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, those weapons within the Treasure Pavilion were nothing more than scrap iron!

Shi Zongtian’s eyes also jumped. Lin Ming’s strength was just becoming increasingly terrifying. Perhaps in one year, even Peacock Mountain’s Lin Ping might not be his match… it might even be less than a year!

He turned and looked at Liu Xuan, saying, “Liu Xuan, who within the Refiner Faction is best at forging spears?”

As Liu Xuan heard this question, he suddenly flushed red, looking helpless. Although there really were a few elders within the Refiner Faction who could forge spears, the best they could make were high-grade human-step treasure spears. To let them use the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo would simply be a waste.

Liu Xuan still remembered that he had just suspected Lin Ming of not understanding how difficult refining was, and not having any materials to craft an earth-step treasure. But now, Lin Ming had actually put out a more than adequate material, but there wasn’t anyone who could use it. Liu Xuan could only ruefully smile.

Liu Xuan helplessly shook his head, looking somewhat embarrassed. He said, “Our Refiner Faction simply cannot forge an earth-step treasure spear… the most we can craft is an earth-step treasure spearhead. For instance, a Cold Star Iron spearhead…

Cold Star Iron was a top quality metal material used to make earth-step treasures. The use of Cold Star Iron to create treasures was a very arduous and complicated process, and was also one of the legacy techniques of the Seven Profound Valleys’ Refiner Faction. It was a strictly confidential technique that was absolutely forbidden for outsiders. However, it was also the process they were most proud and confident in, thus Liu Xuan had suggested this.

But, Liu Xuan didn’t think that Mu Qianyu would shake her head and say, “Cold Star Iron can only create up to a low-grade earth-step treasure, and 10,000 year old Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo is far beyond that. A spearhead made from Cold Star Iron does not match well with Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo. Not only that, but if the spearhead is created separately from the spear shaft, then the spear will be unable to merge into one natural whole, and the quality of the end product would suffer greatly.”

Mu Qianyu calmly spoke a statement of facts. As Liu Xuan heard this, he immediately reddened. He had actually suggested one of his Refiner Faction’s most precious legacy secret techniques, but yet in just a few demeaning words from Mu Qianyu, it had become worthless within her eyes…

He opened his mouth to speak, but couldn’t find the words to refute her. In the end, he didn’t say anything, there was simply nothing he could use as a rebuttal. This was the gap in their sects’ heritages. A dignified top fourth-grade sect would of course look down on their so-called secret technique.

Mu Qianyu said, “Lin Ming, I actually know a spear refining master whose cultivation is at the middle Revolving Core realm. If he can be found, then the full power of the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo can be displayed. Of course, this is only if you can afford the other materials that can match the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo in order to craft the spearhead.”

A middle Revolving Core realm spear refining master?

As Lin Ming heard Mu Qianyu, his heart rate suddenly increased. The Sovereign of the Seven Profound Valleys’ Refiner Faction only had cultivation at the late Xiantian realm. Just from cultivation only, one could imagine how much stronger a spear made by this spear refining master would be.

However, thinking that Mu Qianyu also said that he needed to provide materials that matched the Violet Electricity Spirit Bamboo, Lin Ming was somewhat depressed. The value of these materials could be imagined. Even if he put forth all of his possessions, he would not be able to afford it.

Unless, he reached out his beggar hand towards Mu Qianyu.

If Mu Qianyu was willing to pay the price, then she could of course obtain these materials. But, there was no reason that Mu Qianyu would help him for no return.

Even if he was a genius, he still hadn’t fully matured. There was no reason for Mu Qianyu to repeatedly give out such precious resources to him.

No one could say what would happen in the future. Also, he wasn’t even a Divine Phoenix Island disciple.

Mu Qianyu saw Lin Ming’s somewhat despondent expression and was able to imagine what he was thinking about. She faintly smiled and asked, “Lin Ming, don’t you want to see this spear refining master?”

“I would like to, but…”

“Then come with me.” As Mu Qianyu said this, she clapped her hands, and a strange fluctuation of  fire true essence spread from her palms. Soon, a faint phoenix cry resounded, and a giant bird with a 70 foot long wingspan flew down towards the Grand Hall, landing in front of the square.

The bird had the head of a golden pheasant, a long neck like a snake, and feathers that burned like brilliant flames of the sun. This was Mu Qianyu’s life’s Vermillion Bird, Little Flame.

Little Flame landed on the ground, and an incomparably scorching wave of heat burned the atmosphere. Lin Ming – and even the early Xiantian realm Liu Xuan – couldn’t help but take several steps back.

Lin Ming stimulated the Heretical God Seed within his body, finally able to stand firm against the burning heat waves that emanated from Little Flame. This fellow had evolved?

Lin Ming remembered that when he first saw Little Flame, Little Flame only had a wingspan of 50 feet. Now, it already had a wingspan of 70 feet, and the fire true essence that percolated around its body seemed much more formidable.

At this point, Little Flame proudly stretched back its wings, preening as it raised its phoenix beak in a self-satisfied gesture, demonstrating its noble and elegant bearing. Obviously, it was quite happy seeing the shock in Lin Ming’s eyes.

Little Flame was naturally able to recognize Lin Ming. Or, it was more accurate to say that Little Flame was able to recognize the barbecue boy.

“Let’s go.” Mu Qianyu lightly tapped her toes, jumping into the air and falling gently onto Little Flame’s back like a feather. She motioned for Lin Ming to follow her.

Lin Ming paused, he could sit on Little Flame’s back? Would Little Flame let him?

Shi Zongtian and Liu Xuan were also incomparably startled. How arrogant and proud was a Saint Beast? Not everyone was qualified to sit on its back.

Sure enough, Little Flame let out a few discontented chirps. But, it was only a few chirps, it still allowed Lin Ming to climb up.

This was mainly because it was Mu Qianyu’s order. But Lin Ming’s status as the barbecue boy also played a major role.

Lin Ming tapped his feet, soaring into the air and steadily falling onto Little Flame’s back. Liu Xuan couldn’t help but swallow a mouthful of saliva as he saw this. As a disciple of the Refining Faction, he was also a fire-attribute martial artist. Seeing Lin Ming being able to ride such a majestic fire-attribute Saint Beast, he could only feel extreme envy in his heart.

Chapter 307 – Medicine Strength Washing Marrow

Although the Tempering Marrow boundary lay above the Pulse Condensation period, one didn’t actually need to slowly reach the peak Pulse Condensation period before making a breakthrough to Tempering Marrow. To the contrary, to reach the Tempering Marrow boundary, it didn’t matter whether one was at the early Pulse Condensation period or even the late Pulse Condensation period.

In other words, Tempering Marrow and Pulse Condensation were belonged to two completely different cultivation systems.

Tempering Marrow belonged to the Realm of the Gods’ Body Transformation cultivation method.

As for the Pulse Condensation, Houtian, Xiantian, and Revolving Core realms, those belonged to the essence gathering cultivation system.

When a martial artist went from Strength Training to Flesh Training to Viscera Training to Altering Muscle and finally to Bone Forging, the true essence of one’s body permeated deeper within, becoming more and more thorough. Afterwards, once true essence penetrated the marrow, that was Tempering Marrow.

Otherwise, true essence would flood through the body’s meridians – this was called the Pulse Condensation period.

After Pulse Condensation, true essence would converge within the dantian by following along the meridians, and one would enter Houtian, Xiantian. Then, when that true essence became a core within the dantian, that would be the Revolving Core realm.

That is, the Tempering Marrow boundary ran parallel to the Pulse Condensation period.

Tempering Marrow laid the foundation for one to enter the Eight Inner Hidden Gates; this was Body Transformation.

But, once Pulse Condensation true essence penetrated through the meridians and converged into the dantian, this was laying the foundation for the essence gathering system.

However, reaching Pulse Condensation was easy, whereas Tempering Marrow was incomparably difficult. That was why normally one would reach the Pulse Condensation period first and then go onwards to the Tempering Marrow boundary.

This was what Lin Ming was doing now.

He followed the methods and principles found within the Tempering Marrow portion of the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ in order to forcefully control the medicinal efficacy and slowly penetrate it into the bone, bit by bit.

The Heaven Opening Pill’s medicinal power was extremely savage and violent. If a normal martial artist consumed the Heaven Opening Pill, they could only ease the way and slowly refine it. But if someone did the same as Lin Ming and tried to bind the Heaven Opening Pill’s medicinal efficacy with their true essence and force it into the marrow, it would provoke a strong counterattack from the medicinal strength!

Lin Ming felt as if his blood had been replaced by burning lava; wherever it went, there would be a bone-biting pain!

“Lin Ming, are you alright…” As Mu Qianyu watched Lin Ming’s appearance that seemed like he was in deep suffering, she was somewhat worried. If one’s strength was insufficient, they might even die upon eating the Heaven Opening Pill. Since the ancient times, there had been Pulse Condensation period martial artists who wished to rush forwards, and after swallowing the Heaven Opening Pill they would suffer a horribly violent death because they could not fully digest the medicine’s potency.

However, Mu Qianyu hadn’t worried that this would happen to Lin Ming. After all, Lin Ming’s strength was far above that. If he were placed within a small country, his strength would be equivalent to a late Houtian martial artist and above.

But now seeing Lin Ming’s pained appearance, Mu Qianyu’s heart stopped for a moment. Lin Ming’s reaction was just too intense, it was beyond what she had imagined.

In absorbing the Heaven Opening Pill, it was useless for others to try to help. Mu Qianyu could only take a handkerchief and wipe away the sweat from Lin Ming’s forehead.

In this touch, Mu Qianyu found that Lin Ming’s forehead was burning with a raging heat.

“What’s going on?” Mu Qianyu’s eyebrows furrowed together. Was there an accident when he was trying to absorb the Heaven Opening Pill medicinal efficacy?

For a moment Mu Qianyu hesitated, thinking about whether she should use her own deep cultivation in order to forcefully compel the medicine out of Lin Ming’s body. At this moment, Lin Ming waved his hand with some difficulty, clenched his teeth and said, “I… I’m alright…”

When he opened his mouth, Mu Qianyu saw that his teeth were stained red with blood.

It wasn’t that Lin Ming couldn’t withstand the medicinal efficacy of the Heaven Opening Pill, it was only that forcing true essence to enter the marrow was simply too difficult.

Lin Ming felt like his bones were an impregnable bastion. He stiffly forced a wisp of the Heaven Opening Pill’s medicinal efficacy a bit at a time, but every time was as if his bones were being drilled into!

At first, Lin Ming had been stuck and at the peak Bone Forging stage for a long time. Finally, his true essence had naturally overflowed, resulting in a perfect breakthrough!

This course of action laid a solid foundation. But his bones had been hardened by the prolonged forging of true essence, and they were nearly perfect in density, without a single flaw.

But the more solid the skeleton was, the more difficult it was to penetrate the drug efficacy into the bone!

However, Lin Ming did not regret this a single bit.

The more difficult it was to break through, the more thorough and complete Tempering Marrow would be!

Only when the medicinal efficacy of the Heaven Opening Pill underwent purification through the dense bone would it achieve the best effect towards Tempering Marrow.

Lin Ming’s philosophy was…

In order to lay a foundation, it must be laid in the most complete and solid manner.

In order to break through a boundary, it must be go through a perfect breakthrough!

After a quarter of an hour, Lin Ming’s entire body was soaked in sweat. At this time, within his body, in his marrow, there was just the slightest tint of gold that was impossibly difficult to see!

Marrow like golden soup, that was the symbol of Tempering Marrow!

However, Lin Ming didn’t even feel the slightest bit of joy, he only felt very depressed. This was because it was an incomparably small amount!

He had used up one fifth of the Heaven Opening Pill’s medicinal efficacy, but he only managed to create such a tiny trace of Tempering Marrow that could hardly be seen. If he wanted to fully complete the process, he feared that he would need to repeat this whole process 10 or 20 thousand times. Could it be that in order to fully complete the Tempering Marrow boundary, he needed several thousand Heaven Opening Pills!?!?

Heavens!

Even if the rich and resourceful Divine Phoenix Island were to supply him with several thousand Heaven Opening Pills, he would probably die from stuffing himself with that many!

It had to be known that the Seven Profound Valleys only made between 20 and 30 Heaven Opening Pills every three years. On average, they had eight or nine Heaven Opening Pills every year. As for Divine Phoenix Island, they could make several dozen Heaven Opening Pills in one year. With this speed, it would still take Divine Phoenix Island over a hundred years to gather several thousand Heaven Opening Pills!

No matter how talented Lin Ming was, or how much of a monstrous genius he was, it would be impossible for Divine Phoenix Island to perform such an impossibly difficult feat for him and save up every single one of their Heaven Opening Pills for the next 100 years.

Not only that, but even if Divine Phoenix Island were willing, Lin Ming would not wait.

Was he destined not to fully complete the Tempering Marrow boundary?

Thinking about the Eight Inner Hidden Gates and Nine Stars of the Dao Palace recorded within the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, and the images of his feet cracking the earth, and his fist shattering stars, Lin Ming was unwilling to let this go. In any event, he would not give up on the Tempering Marrow boundary. As long as he had just a bit of hope, he would still manage to find a way.

He would do it bit by bit, slowly, and inexorably!

After shoring up his resolve, Lin Ming clenched his teeth and continued to absorb the leftover efficacy of the Heaven Opening Pill.

If Lin Ming used the Heaven Opening Pill on his entire body, there might not be any effect from the Tempering Marrow.

Although Lin Ming was rich, he wasn’t wealthy to the point of gobbling up Heaven Opening Pills like candy. He couldn’t accept eating up such a rare and precious Heaven Opening Pill and not gaining even the tiniest bit of growth in his strength.

Thinking this, Lin Ming used the techniques found within the ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’, revolving all of the true essence in his body and forcing every bit of drug efficacy into his right hand.

Since there wasn’t any effect in tempering the entire body, then he might as well focus on tempering just a single spot!

Lin Ming chose his right hand. Whether it was the Body Tearing Bone Shattering Fist or using his spear, the right hand was the most critical part.

First he would temper his right hand, and then reconsider his options.

The medicinal efficacy rushed to his right hand like a tide. Under the oppression the medicine, Lin Ming’s right hand felt as if a saber was being twisted into it. If it wasn’t for the many body transformations that he had undergone within the Sorcerer Pagoda that made his body incomparably tough, his hand might have already exploded into bloody bits.

Then Lin Ming forced the medicinal efficacy into his right hand, it was truly difficult.

His entire right hand bulged red like a bag of blood, and the blue veins on his hand throbbed like massive earthworms, fiercely wriggling. Lin Ming fell over, pressing his right hand against his body as he barely held against the pain of the medicinal efficacy tempering his marrow. Beads of sweat tumbled down his hair, flowing to the ground.

Time passed slowly, and finally an hour passed. Lin Ming had finally refined most of the Heaven Opening Pill. At this time, he felt as if he were a weak newborn baby.

His true essence consumption had been too great. Lin Ming rolled over flat on the stone altar, taking great, heaving gasps.

Fortunately, this location was unique. With every breath, a great amount of fire origin energy entered his body, quickly being absorbed into the Heretical God Seed and moistening Lin Ming’s dried meridians.

As he looked at his right hand, there was only the thinnest layer of pale gold that just skimmed over the surface of the bone marrow. Although this was far from achieving the boundary of marrow like golden soup, Lin Ming could still feel that this tiny part of his marrow was filled with an overwhelming blood vitality!

“Only a little marrow of my hand has the faintest hint of pale gold. Although there isn’t any change in my forearm, it seems to be much redder…”

Lin Ming was speaking to himself. A human had two types of marrow: the first was a yellow marrow, and the second was a red marrow. Only the red marrow could create blood.

When a baby was just born, its entire body was filled with red marrow that could create blood. But as one slowly aged, the bone cavity that held the red marrow gradually filled with fat, turning the red marrow into yellow marrow that could no longer produce blood.

The older a person was, the higher the proportion of yellow marrow would be, causing a person’s blood vitality to be insufficient. That was why a baby’s blood vitality was so much more vigorous and potent that the elderly’s.

Lin Ming’s right forearm had already changed into pure red bone marrow. If his entire body’s marrow could change to pure red bone marrow, then the power of blood vitality would be much more robust, and whether it was endurance or resilience, all would be much more formidable!

“Lin Ming, are you alright?” Seeing that Lin Ming had finally regained consciousness, Mu Qianyu let out a breath of relief, handing over her handkerchief to him. She hadn’t thought that Lin Ming would have such a brutal reaction after swallowing the Heaven Opening Pill.

“I’m alright.” Lin Ming waved his hand and took the handkerchief that Mu Qianyu handed over. He found that this piece of cloth that contained a faint heavenly fragrance had already become dirty; obviously, this was because of him.

Lin Ming awkwardly smiled, abashed. He looked down and saw that his entire body was covered in a thick layer of greasy black oil. The Heaven Opening Pill was able to wash the marrows and muscles, a miracle cure that was able to remove the foul Houtian air. After eating one, one would naturally discharge impurities.

Lin Ming couldn’t stand the sticky feeling of laying down in this grease. He said to Mu Qianyu, “I’m going to take a bath.”

“Mm, go ahead.”

At the back of Ancestor Chi Yan’s cave was a deep pool that had been excavated. Lin Ming hurried there with long steps, and when he reached it, he didn’t actually start removing his clothes to take a bath, but instead looked to see that no one was there, and then took a low-grade human-step treasure sword from his spatial ring.

Looking at the shining tip of the treasure sword, Lin Ming suddenly stretched out his right and grabbed the sword edge. He didn’t use any true essence protection but just depended on the bare flesh of his palm, firmly digging his fingers into the treasure sword, kneading and twisting.

Zhi zhi zhi –

In the silence of the bathing pool, there was only the clear screeching sound of deforming metal. Lin Ming felt some slight pain in his hand, but his hand actually wasn’t cut at all by the sword edge.

After several breaths, the low-grade human-step treasure sword was completely bent out of shape by Lin Ming. The blade had been twisted into a mess. This was a treasure sword that Huo Gong had made, and could also be considered among the top of all low-grade human-step treasures.

In other words, the toughness of Lin Ming’s right had had actually surpassed that of a low-grade human-step treasure!

Lin Ming had once depended on using Flow like Silk to ‘meet a bare blade with an empty palm’. But now, he could actually twist a treasure sword without any true essence protection.

The dynamic strength of Lin Ming’s right hand’s flesh had actually reached such a degree. If he used it with his true essence, his defensive power would truly reach a terrifying level!

Not only that, but the stronger his bodily strength was, the stronger his attack strength would be. With a single punch, he would be able to crack rocks. It could be said that when that happened, Lin Ming’s own body would become a treasure weapon.

Chapter 308 – Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle

The ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ had stated that after going through Strength Training, Flesh Training, Viscera Training, Altering Muscle, and Bone Forging by tempering the body with true essence, the biggest impediment after that would be the human marrow. If the marrow is not tempered, it cannot be shocked, and it would be vulnerable to injury. This was the greatest weakness to Body Transformation martial artists.

But after the tempering of the marrow had been fully completed, not only would it eliminate this vulnerability, but it would also enhance the fusion of true essence and the body, within and without, true essence would be seamlessly unified from all directions. Only when this was achieved could one attain the most stable and perfect stage.

Lin Ming stood near the deep pool and continued to revolve the ‘True Primal Chaos Formula’, feeling the Tempering Marrow boundary. After this change in his hand, the true essence really did unify, and had experienced a qualitative leap.

The ‘Chaotic Virtues Combat Meridians’ was right, but as Lin Ming thought of the exceedingly harsh conditions necessary to fully complete Tempering Marrow, he felt a headache creeping up.  If things continued like this, he would probably have to reach the Revolving Core realm before he had the strength to collect the pills he needed to finish Tempering Marrow.

Although Tempering Marrow belonged to a completely different cultivation system from the essence gathering system, it was still better to break through sooner. At least, the best outcome would be if he could do so before he turned 20.

But no matter how heaven defying a talent one was, it was impossible to reach the Revolving Core realm before 20 years of age. After, it would still take an unknown amount of time to collect the materials he needed. If he missed the best time to temper his marrow, then his marrow would age, and it would become much more difficult to fully complete Tempering Marrow.

Just how should he proceed?

Lin Ming quickly took a bath, taking a spare set of clothes from his spatial ring, and then returned to the cultivation chamber.

Mu Qianyu saw Lin Ming come back, his hair slicked back and wet, a new set of clean clothes on, and looking quite refreshed and gallant. She finally breathed a sigh of relief. “Lin Ming, did you take the Heaven Opening Pill to wash your marrow and muscles? I think that you released a very small amount of impurities.”

The Heaven Opening Pill had an extremely dominant power to wash the marrow and muscle, especially when used by earthly martial artists. They would often discharge thick layers of gray sludge, but Lin Ming only discharged a bit of the foul Houtian air. This was why Mu Qianyu had asked.

“Mm… I ate it.” Lin Ming awkwardly nodded. When he had taken the Heaven Opening Pill, 90% of the medicinal efficacy had been used by him for Tempering Marrow; the little bit left behind was in his meridians. He hadn’t used any to wash his marrow and muscles.

Mu Qianyu’s eyes swept Lin Ming from head to toe, and finally gave a satisfied nod, saying, “I don’t think your cultivation rose by much. Probably, the medicinal efficacy is hiding somewhere in your body. But you don’t need to worry about that. After you take the Heaven Opening Pill, you only need to go into seclusion for a period to slowly pull out and absorb the power of the medicine. After that, your strength should be able to break through to the middle Pulse Condensation period, or maybe even the late Pulse Condensation period. But this type of cultivation doesn’t come from practice, so it’s best if you also spend a good period of time consolidating in order to have the best result. If you eat another Heaven Opening Pill before you reach the Houtian realm, it probably won’t do you much good. It’s simply not worth it.”

“Uh… I, um, I understand.” Lin Ming half-heartedly smiled. After such a lie, he also had to use more lies to conceal his last lies. Where was there any leftover medicinal efficacy in his body? All of it had already been cleanly sucked out. His cultivation hadn’t risen by much, and he was still quite far from reaching the middle Pulse Condensation period.

Mu Qianyu beckoned Lin Ming over and said, “Lin Ming, sit down over here, I want to test your fire origin energy fusion compatibility.”

Lin Ming hesitated, and then nodded. He sat cross-legged in front of Mu Qianyu. He didn’t know just what the standards were for Sky Spill Continent or what grade of fire origin energy fusion compatibility he had.

“Relax your body. Don’t try to purposely control the way your body absorbs fire origin energy.”

Mu Qianyu took hold of Lin Ming’s hand and then closed her eyes. Then, Lin Ming felt a strange fluctuation of fire origin energy in his body, as true essence entered into him. He absorbed the true essence, letting it judge just what grade his fusion compatibility with fire was.

Maybe it was because the fire origin energy in the room was too rich, but when Mu Qianyu sat on the altar, she slightly perspired, releasing an extremely delightful and alluring fragrance. Since Lin Ming was so close to Mu Qianyu and they were facing each other, he was somewhat distracted.

A moment later, Mu Qianyu opened her eyes, a bit of disappointment on her face. “You are maybe an inferior sixth-grade fusion compatibility…”

A martial artist that had this degree of fusion compatibility with any element was already heaven defying, much less Lin Ming who was a double-attribute. His thunder origin energy fusion compatibility was definitely higher.

But Mu Qianyu was still a bit dissatisfied. Divine Phoenix Island’s cultivation method had extremely harsh requirements of fire origin energy fusion compatibility. For instance, Mu Qianyu’s fire origin energy fusion compatibility was a superior seventh-grade that absolutely defied the will of the heavens!

A sixth-grade fusion compatibility was just at the barest standard to study the core cultivation methods. However, if Lin Ming wanted to achieve the highest levels of this cultivation method, it would probably be impossible.

Mu Qianyu felt a great deal of regret. Besides his fire attribute, Mu Qianyu didn’t have much in common with Lin Ming’s other strengths. The only thing that could strengthen the bond between her and Lin Ming were the cultivation methods of Divine Phoenix Island.

“Inferior sixth-grade?” Lin Ming wasn’t surprised. Although the Heretical God Seed was amazing, all of the other strengths of his body had no connection to the fire attribute, so of course he wouldn’t have a fire origin energy fusion compatibility that defied the heavens.

‘I wonder what will happen when I take that super valuable spear that Ancestor Chi Yan is refining, and then go to the Southern Wilderness to eliminate the Fire Worm Shaman. After I absorb the Eternal Flame Flame Essence, just what degree of fusion compatibility will my fire attribute reach?’

The greatest and most distinct feature that the Heretical God Force had in comparison to normal martial artists was that it had the capabilities to evolve and grow. Because Lin Ming had absorbed the Purple Flood Dragon Divine Thunder, his thunder origin energy fusion compatibility absolutely surpassed a mere inferior sixth-grade.

This was the strange and unbelievable power of the Heretical God Force. Lin Ming sighed. The Heretical God Force was too powerful. It was no wonder that the Supreme Elder from the Realm of the Gods had taken this secret skill as the most precious one he had ever obtained in his lifetime, even above the ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’.

Not only that, but even though the ‘Golden Roc Shattering the Void’ was extremely rare and precious, there were still some other people who knew about it in the Realm of the Gods. But the Heretical God Force was actually unique; this secret skill was obtained in some ancient ruins, and was probably created by some archaic Evil God.

When that Supreme Elder had discovered the Heretical God Force, it had already been sealed for a countless number of years. Afterwards, the Supreme Elder had carefully kept this secret skill hidden without leaking any details of it. This made it even more precious.

Unfortunately, that Supreme Elder of the Realm of the Gods hadn’t been able to thoroughly study and research the Heretical God Force in detail. He had only practiced it to the third layer, and then he followed Tian Mingzi to the Verdant Feather Holy Lands to steal the Divine Crystal Magic Cube, finally dying with his soul shattered.

Now, discovering any new information on the Heretical God Force depended on Lin Ming’s own luck and ability. He stumbled onto the fact that it responded to thunder and fire attribute origin energy, but as for the other types such as earth, ice, wood, water, or anything else, he had no idea how to utilize those different types of origin energy.

Mu Qianyu looked at Lin Ming then hesitated, saying, “Lin Ming, would you be willing to study Divine Phoenix Island’s fire attribute cultivation methods?”

Lin Ming nodded, “I’d like to try.”

The cultivation methods of Divine Phoenix Island were naturally far inferior to the cultivation methods that the Supreme Elder knew in the Realm of the Gods. However, although the Supreme Elder’s cultivation methods were amazing, they didn’t suit him. At best, there were just a few cultivation methods in the memories, and he couldn’t choose a specific direction that he wanted to go in.

In the past, Lin Ming had wanted to study a thunder attribute cultivation method in order to make up for his lack of speed. But, to find a high-grade thunder attribute cultivation method manual within the Sky Spill Continent was much easier said than done. On the other hand, Divine Phoenix Island’s cultivation methods were already considered to be at the top.

“Lin Ming, your true essence is far thicker and purer than that of a martial artist at the same level, and your body also has several special places within it. I think that you have already studied some sort of top quality cultivation method from your master. Although I don’t know what sort of cultivation method it is, I have to say that the amazing cultivation methods of Divine Phoenix Island won’t lose out to any other fire attribute cultivation method.” These days, Mu Qianyu had spent a great deal of time with Lin Ming. With her cultivation and great eyesight, she was able to see that there were many unusual aspects about Lin Ming’s body. However, she didn’t ask about these, as every powerhouse had their own secrets to keep.

“But, since you haven’t formally joined Divine Phoenix Island, the most I can pass on to you is the first few layers. Before I pass this onto you, you must swear that you will not leak these cultivation methods.” Mu Qianyu looked at Lin Ming with a very serious and solemn expression in her eyes, her each and every syllable pronounced clearly and loudly.

“I swear upon my heart of martial arts, that if I do not have Divine Phoenix Island’s permission, I will not divulge anything.” Lin Ming took an oath without hesitating. Every sect had their own inheritances and legacies that were equivalent to their lifeblood. These inheritances and legacies were the fundamental basis for every sect.

“Good. Then, this cultivation method is called the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. It originates from the ancient Phoenix Clan. Unfortunately… this cultivation method has a flaw, otherwise, even the few Holy Lands of Sky Spill Continent might covet it.”

As Mu Qianyu spoke, she heaved a great sigh. The ancient Phoenix Clan had the bloodline of a Phoenix – that was a true God Beast. It wasn’t an existence that a Vermillion Bird or any other Saint Beast could compare with. Since they had left behind a cultivation method, the terrifying fearsomeness of its power could be imagined.

“The two great core cultivation methods of Divine Phoenix Island are the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and the ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’. More than half has been lost, otherwise Divine Phoenix Island would have already become a Holy Land! Even though these two cultivation methods have flaws, their formidable power already surpasses many core cultivation methods of fifth-grade sects. If one wishes to study these two sets of cultivation methods to the core boundary, one needs the bloodline of the Vermillion Bird or Blue Lian. Otherwise, the fifth-grade sects would have already long rampaged and plundered Divine Phoenix Island.

“It is said that with the complete secret texts of the ancient Phoenix race, if one cultivated their manuals to the highest realm, then one’s body could become like a Phoenix, rebirthing through nirvana in a sea of flames, immortal and indestructible…”

As Mu Qianyu spoke, Lin Ming was shocked.

One’s body could become like a Phoenix, rebirthing through nirvana in a sea of flames, immortal and indestructible?

If what Mu Qianyu said wasn’t an exaggeration, then the secret texts of this ancient Phoenix Clan were no worse than the top cultivation methods within the Realm of the Gods, and might also be tied with the Heretical God Force that was left behind by an archaic Evil God!

Of course, the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’ and the ‘Blue Luan Abstract Phantom Code’ were just a small part of the ancient Phoenix Clan’s secret texts, and most of it was missing, flawed.

Alas, these was how things were. Still, Lin Ming’s heart couldn’t help but stir and he asked, “Miss Mu said that in order to practice these cultivation methods to the core boundary, I will need the bloodline of a Vermillion Bird or Blue Luan. Does that mean that I cannot cultivate these methods?”

Mu Qianyu sighed. Even if Lin Ming had the bloodline of a Vermillion Bird, he was limited by his fire origin energy fusion compatibility; there was no way he would be able to cultivate it to the highest level.

Mu Qianyu said, “Divine Phoenix Island has a secret technique to transplant part of a Saint Beast’s bloodline into you. However, if the bloodline is too thin, it will be insufficient to study the most core section of the ‘Vermillion Bird Forbidden Divine Chronicle’. Only if…” As Mu Qianyu spoke, she suddenly fell silent, her face flashing with the color of embarrassment.